<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>G7 1200 Scania ModShop v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/g7-1200-scania-modshop-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-375480 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-cars">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    June 2, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="1080" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 1920w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-scania-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w" width="1920"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Cars" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      G7 1200 Scania ModShop v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     You’re specifying a very popular and high-quality bus mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2: the Marcopolo Paradiso G7 1200 with a Scania chassis, developed and sold by ModShop.
     <br/>
     This is a highly sought-after combination for several reasons:
     <br/>
     Marcopolo Paradiso G7 1200: As discussed, this is a staple of Brazilian intercity bus travel, known for its modern design and comfort. The “G7” refers to the seventh generation of Marcopolo’s Paradiso line, and “1200” is a specific model within that generation.
     <br/>
     Scania Chassis: Many Marcopolo buses, including the G7 1200, are built on Scania chassis (e.g., Scania K360, K400, K420IB). Scania engines are known for their power and distinct sound, which ModShop strives to replicate accurately in their mods. This combination provides a powerful and responsive driving experience.
     <br/>
     ModShop: As a premium mod developer, ModShop is known for creating highly detailed, realistic, and feature-rich bus mods. They often invest in recording real engine sounds and crafting intricate 3D models for both the interior and exterior.
     <br/>
     ETS2 (Euro Truck Simulator 2): This mod transforms ETS2 from a truck sim into a bus sim, allowing players to experience driving these iconic Brazilian buses across the virtual European (or modded Brazilian) landscapes.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      What to expect from a G7 1200 Scania ModShop ETS2 mod:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Authentic Scania Sounds: A major highlight will be the custom-recorded engine and transmission sounds, specifically designed to mimic the distinct audio characteristics of a real Scania bus engine (like the DC13 engine sound for Scania K series).
     <br/>
     Detailed Scania Dashboard and Controls: The interior will be meticulously modeled, often featuring the Scania dashboard layout, gauges, and potentially animated controls.
     <br/>
     Realistic Performance: The mod will aim to provide accurate engine power (e.g., 360hp, 400hp, 410hp options) and transmission behavior, reflecting the real-world Scania chassis specifications.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization: You’ll likely find options for:
     <br/>
     Different chassis configurations (e.g., 6×2)
     <br/>
     Interior variations (seat textures, curtain colors)
     <br/>
     Exterior accessories (lights, mirrors, spoilers)
     <br/>
     Customizable digital destination signs (letreiros), often through an “APP ModShop Edit” for advanced personalization.
     <br/>
     Compatibility with SCS Software’s cabin accessories DLC.
     <br/>
     High-Quality Visuals: The 3D model will be high-fidelity, with detailed textures for both the bus body and interior components, including realistic reflections and lighting.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    MODSHOP
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/40rrfb3klj7s/g7_1200_scania_modshop.rar.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bau norma pisc game 1.5x ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/bau-norma-pisc-game-1-5x-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-375482 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trailers">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    June 2, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/bau-norma-pisc-game-ets2-1.5x-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/bau-norma-pisc-game-ets2-1.5x-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/bau-norma-pisc-game-ets2-1.5x-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/bau-norma-pisc-game-ets2-1.5x-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/bau-norma-pisc-game-ets2-1.5x-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trailers" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Bau norma pisc game 1.5x ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     Okay, let’s break down “bau norma pisc game ETS2.”
     <br/>
     This phrase, especially with “pisc,” strongly suggests you’re looking for information about “bau” (cargo boxes/dry vans) with “norma” (standard/legal) specifications for transporting fish (pisc) in the context of Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2).
    </p>
    <p>
     Here’s a detailed explanation:
     <br/>
     Baú: In Portuguese, “baú” refers to a dry van trailer or a box truck body. It’s the most common type of enclosed trailer used for general cargo.
     <br/>
     Norma: This means “standard,” “norm,” or “regulation.” In the context of “baú norma,” it implies a standard, perhaps legally compliant or commonly accepted, type of dry van. However, the key part here is often linked with ANVISA regulations in Brazil, especially when talking about food transportation.
     <br/>
     Pisc (Peixe / Peixes): This is where it gets specific. “Pisc” is likely a shorthand for “peixe” (fish) or “pescado” (fished/seafood). Transporting fish, being a perishable food item, requires specific conditions, primarily refrigeration.
     <br/>
     Game ETS2: This refers to Euro Truck Simulator 2, the popular PC simulation game.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      What you’re likely looking for:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     You are probably searching for a refrigerated dry van trailer mod (baú frigorífico) for ETS2 that is designed to transport fish or seafood. The “norma” part might be emphasizing a desire for a realistic or regulation-compliant mod for this type of cargo, perhaps one that reflects Brazilian standards (like ANVISA) even though ETS2 is set in Europe.
    </p>
    <p>
     Why this is important in ETS2 (especially for Brazilian players):
     <br/>
     Realism and Immersion: Brazilian players often seek mods that reflect the reality of trucking in Brazil. This includes specific types of cargo, like fish, which require temperature-controlled trailers.
     <br/>
     Specialized Cargo: Transporting refrigerated cargo (frigorífico) is a common task in real-world trucking and adds variety to the types of jobs players can take in ETS2.
     <br/>
     Modding Community: The ETS2 modding community, particularly the Brazilian one, creates highly detailed and specialized trailers for various purposes.
    </p>
    <p>
     How to find a “Baú Norma Pisc” (Refrigerated Fish Trailer) Mod for ETS2:
     <br/>
     Since the base game doesn’t have specific “fish” trailers or Brazilian regulatory features built-in, you’ll need to look for mods.
    </p>
    <p>
     Search Terms: Use the following terms when searching for mods:
     <br/>
     “ETS2 baú frigorífico mod” (ETS2 refrigerated dry van mod)
     <br/>
     “ETS2 trailer de peixe mod” (ETS2 fish trailer mod)
     <br/>
     “ETS2 reefer trailer mod” (Reefer is the common English term for refrigerated trailer)
     <br/>
     “ETS2 baú frigorífico ANVISA” (if you want something specifically referencing Brazilian health regulations)
     <br/>
     You might combine these with truck brands like “Scania baú frigorífico ETS2” or “Volvo FH baú frigorífico ETS2” if you’re looking for a specific combo.
     <br/>
     .
     <br/>
     Check Mod Details:
     <br/>
     Game Version Compatibility: Always ensure the mod is compatible with your current ETS2 game version.
     <br/>
     Trailer Ownership DLC: Some advanced trailer mods might require the “Trailer Ownership” DLC to function correctly, allowing you to buy and customize your own refrigerated trailer.
     <br/>
     Cargo Compatibility: Verify that the mod specifically includes “fish” or “seafood” as an available cargo type, or if it’s just a generic refrigerated trailer.
     <br/>
     By using these terms and looking in the right places, you should be able to find the “baú norma pisc” (refrigerated fish trailer) mod you’re seeking for ETS2.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    PISC GAME
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/p8pl0z7a1p4o/bau_norma_pisc_game.rar.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 1200 Facelift ModShop ETS2 v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-375478 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-cars">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    June 2, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/g7-1200-facelift-modshop-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Cars" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      G7 1200 Facelift ModShop ETS2 v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     When you refer to “G7 1200 Facelift ModShop ETS2”, you’re talking about a highly popular bus mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2), specifically the Marcopolo Paradiso G7 1200 Facelift model, often developed and sold by a modding group known as ModShop.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Here’s a breakdown:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Marcopolo Paradiso G7 1200 Facelift: This is a modern, iconic long-distance bus model manufactured by Marcopolo, a Brazilian company. The “Facelift” indicates a refreshed version of the original G7 1200, often featuring updated front and rear designs, and interior improvements. These buses are a common sight on Brazilian roads for intercity travel.
     <br/>
     ModShop: This is a well-known Brazilian modding team or individual developer that creates high-quality, realistic bus mods for ETS2 (and sometimes American Truck Simulator). Their mods are often paid, meaning you purchase them directly from their website (like modshop.com.br). This allows them to invest more time and resources into developing detailed models, realistic sounds, and extensive customization options.
     <br/>
     ETS2 (Euro Truck Simulator 2): As you know, this is the popular truck simulation game by SCS Software. While the base game focuses on trucks, the vibrant modding community, particularly in Brazil, has extensively developed bus mods, transforming the game into a bus simulator for many players.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Key features and aspects of the G7 1200 Facelift ModShop for ETS2:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     High Realism: ModShop buses are renowned for their attention to detail. This includes:
     <br/>
     Accurate 3D models: Replicating the exterior and interior of the real bus faithfully.
     <br/>
     Realistic engine sounds: Often custom-recorded from actual buses (e.g., Mercedes-Benz O500RSD or Scania chassis sounds).
     <br/>
     Authentic physics: Aiming to simulate the feel of driving a bus, including suspension behavior.
     <br/>
     Detailed interiors: With working gauges, lights, and often animated elements.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization: These mods typically offer a wide range of options to personalize the bus:
     <br/>
     Chassis variations: Often available with different engine and transmission combinations (e.g., Scania 6×2, Mercedes-Benz O500RSD Euro 5).
     <br/>
     Interior options: Different seat fabrics, curtain colors, dashboard variations, and compatibility with SCS cabin accessories DLCs.
     <br/>
     Exterior accessories: Such as different mirrors, lights, spoilers, and unique paint jobs/skins (often sold separately or in packs).
     <br/>
     Animated features: Like digital destination boards (letreiros) that can be customized, animated windows, and sometimes even passengers inside the bus.
     <br/>
     ModShop App Compatibility: Some ModShop bus mods, including the G7 1200 Facelift, may be compatible with an “APP ModShop Edit” for customizing digital signs/letreiros, providing an extra layer of immersion.
     <br/>
     Paid Mod: Unlike many free mods, ModShop bus mods are typically paid. This often translates to better quality, more frequent updates, and dedicated support from the developers.
     <br/>
     Compatibility: They are generally kept up-to-date with the latest ETS2 versions (e.g., 1.54xx as mentioned in some product descriptions), but it’s always crucial to check the mod’s specific compatibility before purchasing or downloading.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    MODSHOP
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/2do0xfskieel/g7_1200_facelift_modshop.rar.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costellation Boiadeiro v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/costellation-boiadeiro-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-375486 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    June 2, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/costellation-boiadeiro-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/costellation-boiadeiro-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/costellation-boiadeiro-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/costellation-boiadeiro-v1.0-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/costellation-boiadeiro-v1.0-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Costellation Boiadeiro v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     When you mention “Constellation Boiadeiro ETS 2”, you are referring to a Volkswagen Constellation truck equipped with a livestock trailer (boiadeira) specifically within the game Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2).
     <br/>
     Here’s a breakdown of what that means in the context of ETS2:
     <br/>
     Volkswagen Constellation: This is a popular line of heavy-duty trucks from Volkswagen Caminhões e Ônibus (Volkswagen Trucks and Buses), widely used in Brazil. Players often seek to drive these trucks in ETS2 for a more authentic “Brazilian truck simulator” experience.
     <br/>
     Boiadeira: This refers to the specialized trailer used for transporting cattle. In ETS2, “boiadeira” mods allow players to haul livestock as cargo, adding a unique type of transport to the game.
     <br/>
     ETS2 (Euro Truck Simulator 2): This is a highly popular truck simulation game developed by SCS Software. While the base game focuses on European trucks and territories, a vibrant modding community exists that creates content from other regions, including Brazil.
    </p>
    <p>
     How to get a “Constellation Boiadeiro” in ETS2:
     <br/>
     Since the Volkswagen Constellation and “boiadeira” trailers are not part of the base ETS2 game, you’ll need to use mods. These are fan-made additions that introduce new trucks, trailers, maps, and other features to the game.
     <br/>
     To get a “Constellation Boiadeiro” in ETS2, you would typically:
    </p>
    <p>
     Volkswagen Constellation truck mod: This adds the truck itself to the game. Many versions exist, offering different chassis configurations, engine options, and customization possibilities.
     <br/>
     Boiadeira trailer mod: This adds the livestock trailer. Sometimes, truck mods come with integrated trailer options, or you might need a separate trailer pack.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    DINO
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/lqud0835grmv/costellationboiadeiro_dinomods.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOLVO FH16 2009 1.54 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/volvo-fh16-2009-1-54-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-375484 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    June 2, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/volvo-fh16-2009-1.54-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/volvo-fh16-2009-1.54-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/volvo-fh16-2009-1.54-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/volvo-fh16-2009-1.54-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/volvo-fh16-2009-1.54-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      VOLVO FH16 2009 1.54 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     You’ve provided some interesting information here related to a Volvo FH16 2009 mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2). Let’s break it down:
     <br/>
     VOLVO_FH16_2009_1.54-: This is almost certainly the file name of an ETS2 mod for the Volvo FH16 2009 truck.
     <br/>
     VOLVO_FH16_2009: Identifies the truck model. The FH16 2009 is a classic and very popular truck in ETS2, even with the newer FH models available.
     <br/>
     1.54-: This indicates the ETS2 game version the mod is designed for, or at least compatible with. The hyphen often suggests it works for version 1.54 and potentially newer versions up to a certain point.
     <br/>
     F.G: This could be an abbreviation for the mod author’s initials or a specific modding group/website. It’s common for modders to include their tags in file names.
     <br/>
     senha frc9k31: This is a password! When you download mods, especially from certain file-sharing sites or forums, they are often compressed into a .zip or .rar file that requires a password to extract. This “senha frc9k31” is the key to unlocking that specific mod file.
     <br/>
     In summary:
     <br/>
     You have found a Volvo FH16 2009 truck mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2, designed for game version 1.54 or later, and the password to extract it is frc9k31.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    FERNANDO GAME
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/lng0mfqe93pw/volvo_fh16_2009_1_54_f_g_senha_frc9k31.zip.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
