<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Iveco Hi-Way Jean Rittono 1.55 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-1-55-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-381151 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 28, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-ets2-1.55-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-ets2-1.55-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-ets2-1.55-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-ets2-1.55-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/iveco-hi-way-jean-rittono-ets2-1.55-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Iveco Hi-Way Jean Rittono 1.55 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     The Iveco Hi-Way Jean Rittono 1.55 ETS2 refers to a highly customized and popular mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2, specifically designed for game version 1.55. Jean Rittono is a well-known content creator in the ETS2 modding community, particularly popular among Brazilian players, and his mods often feature a high level of detail and a distinct style.
     <br/>
     This mod aims to deliver a more immersive and personalized Iveco Hi-Way experience, going beyond the base game’s offerings.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Key Features You Can Expect
     </strong>
     <br/>
     While the exact features can vary depending on the specific release by Jean Rittono, here’s what mods like this typically include:
    </p>
    <p>
     Version 1.55 Compatibility: Crucially, this mod is designed to work with ETS2 game version 1.55. This is important as game updates often break older mods. Version 1.55 itself brings significant changes like asynchronous loading, UI redesigns, and the new Driving Academy.
     <br/>
     Highly Detailed Model: Expect a meticulously crafted Iveco Hi-Way model, often with improved textures, realistic lighting, and intricate interior details.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization: This is where Jean Rittono’s mods often shine. You’ll likely find a wide array of options for:
     <br/>
     Chassis: Multiple configurations (e.g., 4×2, 6×2, 6×4) to suit different hauling needs.
     <br/>
     Engines & Transmissions: A broad selection of engines with varying power outputs and realistic gearbox options.
     <br/>
     External Accessories: Custom bumpers, side skirts, spoilers, light bars, mudflaps, and various paintable parts. Many mods by Brazilian creators include “corujinhas” (small decorative owls), specialized antennas, and other regional aesthetic elements.
     <br/>
     Interior Customization: Enhanced dashboard, custom seats, additional interior lights, and various personalizable items.
     <br/>
     Custom Sounds: High-quality mods often come with unique engine sounds, air brake sounds, and horn sounds that are recorded from real Iveco Hi-Way trucks, greatly enhancing immersion.
     <br/>
     Ownable: You will be able to purchase this customized Iveco Hi-Way from a mod truck dealer in the game, allowing you to fully personalize it and add it to your fleet.
     <br/>
     Potential for Tandem/Trailer Integration: Some truck mods are designed to work seamlessly with specific trailers or offer tandem chassis options, although it’s worth noting that some mod trailers (like certain bitrems) might have compatibility issues with invisible cargo.
    </p>
    <p>
     Download the Mod File: The mod will typically come as an .scs file (or sometimes a .zip archive containing one or more .scs files).
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Place in Mod Folder:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Navigate to your ETS2 documents folder: Documents/Euro Truck Simulator 2/mod.
     <br/>
     Copy the downloaded .scs file(s) into this mod folder.
     <br/>
     Activate in Game:
     <br/>
     Launch Euro Truck Simulator 2.
     <br/>
     From the profile selection screen, click on Mod Manager.
     <br/>
     Locate the “Iveco Hi-Way Jean Rittono” mod (or its specific name) in the left panel.
     <br/>
     Double-click it or use the arrow to move it to the Active Mods list on the right.
     <br/>
     Mod Order: Always check if the mod creator provides specific instructions for mod order. Sometimes, certain mods need to be placed higher or lower in the Mod Manager list to function correctly.
     <br/>
     Click Confirm Changes.
     <br/>
     Load your game profile.
     <br/>
     Purchase In-Game: Once your game loads, visit an in-game Truck Dealer (it might be listed as a “Mod Dealer” or simply the Iveco dealer, depending on how the mod is structured) to purchase and customize your new Iveco Hi-Way.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Important Considerations
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Mod Compatibility: While this mod is specifically for 1.55, running many mods together can sometimes lead to conflicts or crashes. If you experience issues, try disabling other mods to see if the problem persists.
     <br/>
     Performance: Highly detailed mods can sometimes impact game performance, especially on older or less powerful PCs.
     <br/>
     Updates: Game updates (e.g., from 1.55 to 1.56) often break mod compatibility. You’ll need to check if Jean Rittono releases an updated version for future game patches.
    </p>
    <p>
     Have you tried any of Jean Rittono’s mods before, or are you just getting started with ETS2 modding?
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    JR
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/yyqpeexas3zu/iveco_hi_way_jean_rittono_1_55_bq.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volvo VS1 ETS2 v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/volvo-vs1-ets2-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-381141 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 28, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="386" sizes="(max-width: 686px) 100vw, 686px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/volvo-vs1-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/volvo-vs1-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 686w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/volvo-vs1-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w" width="686"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Volvo VS1 ETS2 v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     When you refer to “Volvo VS1 ETS2,” you’re likely talking about a mod (modification) for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2) that adds a specific Volvo truck model or a highly customized version of an existing Volvo truck to the game.
     <br/>
     Unlike the official Volvo trucks already in ETS2, a “VS1” mod would be a community-created addition, often featuring unique details, more extensive customization options, or even representing a specific real-life Volvo model not officially present in the game.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      What to Expect from a Volvo VS1 ETS2 Mod
     </strong>
     <br/>
     While the exact features can vary depending on the mod’s creator and version, generally, you can anticipate:
     <br/>
     Unique Volvo Model or Customization: This mod would introduce a particular Volvo truck that stands out from the default in-game options. It might be an older generation, a specialized variant, or simply a highly detailed re-imagining.
     <br/>
     High-Quality Details: Modders often put a lot of effort into making their truck models as realistic as possible, including:
     <br/>
     Detailed Exterior: Accurate modeling of the truck’s body, lights, and various components.
     <br/>
     Realistic Interior: A well-crafted cabin with functional gauges, custom textures, and potentially new animations.
     <br/>
     Extensive Tuning Options: This is a hallmark of good truck mods. You’d typically find a wide range of choices for:
     <br/>
     Chassis: Different axle configurations (4×2, 6×2, 6×4, etc.).
     <br/>
     Engines: A selection of power outputs and torque curves.
     <br/>
     Transmissions: Various gearboxes to suit different driving preferences.
     <br/>
     Accessories: An abundance of external and internal accessories like lights, bumpers, side skirts, mirrors, interior decorations, and custom paint jobs.
     <br/>
     Custom Sounds: Many high-quality truck mods include unique engine sounds recorded from the real-life truck, enhancing the immersion.
     <br/>
     Ownable: Like most truck mods, the Volvo VS1 would likely be an “ownable” truck, meaning you can purchase it from a mod dealer in the game, customize it, and use it for your deliveries.
    </p>
    <p>
     Download the .scs File: Most ETS2 mods come as a .scs file (or sometimes a .zip archive containing one or more .scs files).
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Locate Your ETS2 Mod Folder:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Go to your “Documents” folder.
     <br/>
     Find the “Euro Truck Simulator 2” folder.
     <br/>
     Inside that, you’ll see a “mod” folder. If not, create one.
     <br/>
     The full path is usually: Documents/Euro Truck Simulator 2/mod.
     <br/>
     Copy the Mod File: Place the downloaded .scs file(s) into the mod folder.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Activate in Game:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Launch Euro Truck Simulator 2.
     <br/>
     On the profile selection screen, click “Mod Manager.”
     <br/>
     Find the “Volvo VS1” mod (or whatever its name appears as) in the list on the left.
     <br/>
     Double-click it or use the arrow button to move it to the “Active Mods” list on the right.
     <br/>
     Mod Order: Pay attention to the load order. Sometimes, specific mods need to be higher or lower in the list to work correctly or avoid conflicts with other mods. The mod’s download page usually provides instructions on load order if it’s crucial.
     <br/>
     Click “Confirm Changes.”
     <br/>
     Load your game profile.
     <br/>
     Purchase in Game: Once in the game, visit a truck dealer (often listed as a “Mod Dealer” or “Volvo Dealer” if the mod replaces it) to purchase your new Volvo VS1.
     <br/>
     Keep in mind that mods are community-made and may not always be compatible with the latest game versions or other mods you have installed. Always check the mod’s description for compatibility information.
     <br/>
     Are you looking for a specific version of the Volvo VS1 mod, or do you have any other questions about it?
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    VASCO
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/33uqep9jv0y7/volvo_vs1_terminado.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man TGX 2020 Beraldo v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/man-tgx-2020-beraldo-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-381143 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 28, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="386" sizes="(max-width: 686px) 100vw, 686px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/man-tgx-2020-beraldo-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/man-tgx-2020-beraldo-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 686w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/man-tgx-2020-beraldo-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w" width="686"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Man TGX 2020 Beraldo v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     The MAN TGX 2020 by Beraldo refers to a popular modification (mod) for the game Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2).
     <br/>
     This mod enhances the in-game experience by offering a detailed and customizable version of the MAN TGX 2020 truck. Key features of the
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Beraldo mod typically include:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Ownable: Players can purchase and customize the truck in the game.
     <br/>
     XXL Cabin: A larger, more spacious cabin option.
     <br/>
     Chassis options: Various configurations like 4×2, 6×2, and 6×4.
     <br/>
     Engine variety: A wide selection of engines to choose from.
     <br/>
     Detailed Interior: An enhanced and more realistic interior.
     <br/>
     Gearbox options: Numerous gearbox choices to suit different driving styles.
     <br/>
     Tuning and Accessories: Extensive customization options for both performance and aesthetics.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    BERALDO
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/pykml0a8pu0u/man_tgx_2020_beraldo.7z.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford Cargo 2006 Tractor AJ3D ETS2 v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/ford-cargo-2006-tractor-aj3d-ets2-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-381139 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 28, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="360" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/ford-cargo-2006-tractor-aj3d-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/ford-cargo-2006-tractor-aj3d-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 480w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/ford-cargo-2006-tractor-aj3d-ets2-v1.0-ets2-1-300x225.jpg 300w" width="480"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Ford Cargo 2006 Tractor AJ3D ETS2 v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     The Ford Cargo 2006 Tractor-AJ3D for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2) refers to a community-created mod that brings the classic Ford Cargo truck into the game as a drivable vehicle. These mods are very popular among ETS2 players who want to expand their truck fleet beyond the official in-game models and experience different truck aesthetics and driving dynamics.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      What to Expect from This Mod
     </strong>
     <br/>
     While specific features can vary slightly between different versions or updates of the mod by AJ3D, you can generally expect:
     <br/>
     Ownable Truck: You’ll be able to purchase this Ford Cargo model from a mod dealer in the game, allowing for full customization.
     <br/>
     Detailed Model: Mods like this typically feature a well-modeled exterior and interior, aiming for realism as much as possible, given the base game’s limitations.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Customization Options:
     </strong>
     This usually includes:
     <br/>
     Chassis Options: Various configurations (e.g., 4×2, 6×2, 6×4) to suit different hauling needs.
     <br/>
     Engine & Transmission Choices: A range of engine power options and gearbox configurations to customize performance.
     <br/>
     Paint Jobs & Accessories: Options for different colors, metallic paints, and various external accessories like lights, bull bars, spoilers, and more, as well as interior customizations.
     <br/>
     Custom Sounds: Many truck mods come with their own unique engine sounds to accurately reflect the real-life truck.
     <br/>
     Where to Find and Install It
     <br/>
     Since this is a mod, you won’t find it in the official ETS2 game. You’ll need to download it from third-party modding websites. Popular places to find
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Installation is generally straightforward for ETS2 mods:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Download the Mod File: The mod usually comes as a .scs file.
     <br/>
     Locate Your ETS2 Mod Folder: This is typically found in your Documents folder: Documents/Euro Truck Simulator 2/mod.
     <br/>
     Copy the .scs File: Paste the downloaded .scs file into the mod folder.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Activate in Game:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Launch Euro Truck Simulator 2.
     <br/>
     From the profile selection screen, click on “Mod Manager.”
     <br/>
     Find the “Ford Cargo 2006 Tractor-AJ3D” mod in the list.
     <br/>
     Double-click it (or use the arrow button) to move it to the “Active Mods” side.
     <br/>
     Make sure to place it above any other mods that might conflict (e.g., other truck mods).
     <br/>
     Click “Confirm Changes” and load your game profile.
     <br/>
     After activation, you should be able to find the Ford Cargo 2006 at an in-game truck dealer.
     <br/>
     Do you have any other specific questions about this mod, or are you looking for help with installing it?
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    AJD
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/2gitb0jnc9h5/ford_cargo_2006_tractor_aj3d.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO ICONS MOD 1.54-1.55.x ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/no-icons-mod-1-54-1-55-x-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-381134 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-other">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 28, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="1080" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1.jpg 1920w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w" width="1920"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Other" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
     <a data-rel="lightbox" href="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1.jpg">
      <img alt="" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" decoding="async" height="160" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-1-160x160.jpg" width="160"/>
     </a>
     <a data-rel="lightbox" href="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-2.jpg">
      <img alt="" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" decoding="async" height="160" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-2-160x160.jpg" width="160"/>
     </a>
     <a data-rel="lightbox" href="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-3.jpg">
      <img alt="" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" decoding="async" height="160" loading="lazy" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/no-icons-mod-ets2-1.54-1.55.x-ets2-3-160x160.jpg" width="160"/>
     </a>
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      NO ICONS MOD 1.54-1.55.x ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     <strong>
      v3.0
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Updated to 1.55.x by RussianGuy
     <br/>
     Changed load cones to flagpole with warning flag.
    </p>
    <p>
     (For people don’t know or wan’t edit game files or game console).
     <br/>
     No load icon (flagpole with warning flag).
     <br/>
     No unloading position (only cones).
     <br/>
     No dead end barriers (clear)
     <br/>
     No fuel service icon (sewer)
     <br/>
     No truck shop icon (sewer)
     <br/>
     No tolls icon (sewer)
     <br/>
     And more.
    </p>
    <p>
     From Russia with love.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    RussianGuy,Tomas Turbado
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/j01nu7volnq6/no_icons_mod_v3_0_1_55.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
