<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>CONSTELLATION 1.55 SHOP PISC v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/constellation-1-55-shop-pisc-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-379419 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 11, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-1.55-shop-pisc-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-1.55-shop-pisc-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-1.55-shop-pisc-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-1.55-shop-pisc-v1.0-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-1.55-shop-pisc-v1.0-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      CONSTELLATION 1.55 SHOP PISC v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     Constellation 1.55 Shop Pisc” refers to a mod for the Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2) game, specifically featuring a Volkswagen Constellation truck.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Here’s a breakdown of what that means:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Volkswagen Constellation: This is a real-world series of heavy-duty trucks manufactured by Volkswagen Caminhões e Ônibus (Volkswagen Trucks and Buses) in Brazil.
     <br/>
     1.55: This likely refers to the game version of Euro Truck Simulator 2 that the mod is compatible with. ETS2 regularly receives updates, and mods need to be updated to remain compatible.
     <br/>
     Shop Pisc: This is the creator or distributor of the mod. Shop Pisc appears to be a Brazilian website that sells various mods for ETS2.
     <br/>
     Mod (Modification): In gaming, a mod is a piece of software that alters a video game, in this case, adding a new truck (the VW Constellation) to ETS2 that isn’t originally in the game.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Key features and details of the Constellation 1.55 Shop Pisc mod, based on available information, typically include:
     </strong>
    </p>
    <p>
     Volkswagen Constellation 2024 Model: The mod aims to bring a detailed representation of the 2024 Volkswagen Constellation truck into the game.
     <br/>
     Customization Options: Mods like this often include various customization options, such as:
     <br/>
     Multiple cabins and chassis configurations.
     <br/>
     Different engine and transmission options (including various horsepower and torque choices, and both direct and original engine sounds).
     <br/>
     A wide array of accessories, like stickers for the windshield and back of the cabin, auxiliary lights, interior decorations (e.g., Bibles), antennas, and different exhaust styles.
     <br/>
     Various paintable parts and materials (plastic, black piano finishes).
     <br/>
     Digital dashboard.
     <br/>
     Compatibility: It’s designed to work with ETS2 version 1.55 and may receive periodic updates to maintain compatibility and add new features.
     <br/>
     Origin: The mod is created by Shop Pisc, a Brazilian entity.
    </p>
    <p>
     These mods are popular among ETS2 players who want to expand their game with vehicles not officially included or to add a personal touch to their trucking experience.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    pisc game
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/zjatgclkixsr/constellation_1_55_shop_pisc.zip.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constellation 30.330 JL Mods v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/constellation-30-330-jl-mods-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-379417 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 11, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="399" sizes="(max-width: 592px) 100vw, 592px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-30.330-jl-mods-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-30.330-jl-mods-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 592w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/constellation-30.330-jl-mods-v1.0-ets2-1-300x202.jpg 300w" width="592"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Constellation 30.330 JL Mods v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     Constellation 30.330 JL Mods” refers to modifications (mods) for the Volkswagen Constellation 30.330 truck within the game Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2).
     <br/>
     The “JL Mods” part likely points to a specific modder or group of modders, or it could be a general term for high-quality mods available through channels like “JL Diesel” (a real-world parts supplier for trucks, which might also be associated with modding in the gaming community, though the primary search results for “JL Diesel” point to actual truck parts).
     <br/>
     The Volkswagen Constellation 30.330 is a popular truck in Brazil, known for its robustness and versatility. Because of its prevalence in the real world, it’s a highly sought-after truck to be modded into ETS2, especially for players who enjoy driving on Brazilian map mods.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Common Features of Constellation 30.330 Mods for ETS2:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Mods for this truck typically aim for a high level of realism and customization, often including:
     <br/>
     Detailed 3D Model: Recreating the exterior and interior of the Constellation 30.330 as accurately as possible. This includes detailed textures, correct proportions, and often specific details like the dashboard, seats, and controls.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Multiple Chassis Configurations:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Bitruck (8×2): This is a very common configuration for the 30.330, often featuring two steerable axles and two drive axles at the rear.
     <br/>
     Other configurations like 6×2 or even 4×2 might also be available depending on the mod.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Various Cab Options:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Extended Cab (Cabine Estendida): A smaller cabin without a full sleeper.
     <br/>
     Low Roof Sleeper (Leito Teto Baixo): A sleeper cab with a lower roof.
     <br/>
     High Roof Sleeper (Leito Teto Alto): A more spacious sleeper cab for long-haul comfort.
     <br/>
     Engine and Transmission Options:
     <br/>
     Cummins ISL Engines: The real 30.330 often uses a Cummins ISL engine, and mods will feature various horsepower options (e.g., 330 HP, and often higher fictional ones for gameplay).
     <br/>
     V-Tronic Transmission: The real truck features an automated ZF V-Tronic transmission, and mods will often include realistic gear ratios and sounds for these.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization/Tuning Parts: This is where many truck mods shine. Players can often customize:
     <br/>
     Exterior Accessories: Spoilers, side skirts, bull bars, protective grills, sun visors, custom lights (foguinhos, LEDs), antennas, air horns, exhaust stacks.
     <br/>
     Interior Accessories: Various dashboard items (GPS, phones, drinks), curtains, seat options, custom steering wheels.
     <br/>
     Paint Jobs/Skins: Support for custom paint jobs and often includes a variety of pre-made Brazilian-style skins and company liveries.
     <br/>
     Wheel and Tire Options: Different rim designs, tire types, and hub covers.
     <br/>
     Realistic Sounds: Many high-quality mods come with custom engine sounds, horn sounds, and interior sounds that mimic the real truck.
     <br/>
     Compatibility: Mods are generally built for specific versions of ETS2 (e.g., 1.4x, 1.50, 1.55). It’s crucial to check the mod’s compatibility with your game version.
     <br/>
     Integration with Brazilian Maps: These mods are particularly popular when combined with Brazilian map mods (like EAA, Mapa Minas Gerais, Mapa RBR, etc.) for a truly immersive Brazilian trucking experience.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    ruan
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/6mt51azsrc2d/Constellation_30.330_JL_Mods.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MB1620 JL v1.0 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/mb1620-jl-v1-0-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-379415 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trucks">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 11, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="720" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/mb1620-jl-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/mb1620-jl-v1.0-ets2-1.jpg 1280w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/mb1620-jl-v1.0-ets2-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/mb1620-jl-v1.0-ets2-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/mb1620-jl-v1.0-ets2-1-768x432.jpg 768w" width="1280"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trucks" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      MB1620 JL v1.0 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     MB1620 JL Mods” refers to a mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2) that introduces the iconic Mercedes-Benz MB 1620 truck into the game, often created or distributed by “JL Mods” or a modder associated with that name.
    </p>
    <p>
     The Mercedes-Benz MB 1620 is a legendary truck in Brazil, widely known for its reliability and use across various applications, from hauling general cargo to agricultural produce. Its popularity in the real world makes it a highly sought-after vehicle for ETS2 players, especially those who enjoy playing on Brazilian map mods.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Key Features of MB1620 JL Mods for ETS2:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Mods like this one typically aim to provide an authentic and customizable experience. Here’s what you can generally expect:
    </p>
    <p>
     Detailed 3D Model: The mod will feature a highly detailed and realistic recreation of the MB 1620, both externally and internally. This includes accurate textures, proper scaling, and attention to details like the dashboard, steering wheel, and cabin layout.
     <br/>
     Multiple Chassis Configurations: The MB 1620 was known for its versatility. Mods often include:
     <br/>
     Bitruck (8×2): A popular configuration in Brazil, featuring two steerable axles and two drive axles at the rear, common for heavier loads.
     <br/>
     6×2 or 4×2: Other configurations might be available, offering different load capacities and driving dynamics.
     <br/>
     Engine and Transmission Options:
     <br/>
     Original Mercedes-Benz Engines: The real MB 1620 used Mercedes-Benz engines (often with a distinctive sound). Mods typically offer various horsepower options, some mimicking the real engine, others being more powerful for gameplay.
     <br/>
     Realistic Sounds: High-quality mods often come with custom engine sounds, horn sounds, and air brake sounds that are true to the real MB 1620. This is a big draw for immersion.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization Options: Players love to personalize their trucks, and MB 1620 mods usually provide a wealth of accessories, such as:
     <br/>
     Exterior: Different grille options, bumpers, sun visors, custom lights (like “foguinhos” or marker lights), exhaust stacks (including “boiadeiro” style), mudflaps (“lameiros”), and various paintable parts.
     <br/>
     Interior: Dashboard accessories (GPS, mobile phones, flags, Bibles), curtains, custom seats, and different steering wheel options.
     <br/>
     Wheels and Tires: A selection of rim designs and tire types.
     <br/>
     Multiple Body Options (for Rigid versions): Some MB 1620 mods come as “rigid” trucks, meaning they have a fixed body. These can include:
     <br/>
     Open Cargo Beds (Carroceria): For general loose cargo.
     <br/>
     Refrigerated Boxes (Câmera Fria): For transporting perishable goods.
     <br/>
     Dry Van Boxes (Baú): Standard enclosed boxes.
     <br/>
     “Boiadeira” (Cattle Transporter): A specific type of open trailer used for livestock.
     <br/>
     Compatibility: Mods are generally designed for specific versions of ETS2. It’s crucial to check that the mod is compatible with your current game version (e.g., 1.50, 1.52, 1.54, 1.55, etc.) to ensure it works correctly and doesn’t cause crashes.
     <br/>
     Integration with Brazilian Maps: The MB 1620 is a perfect fit for Brazilian map mods like EAA, Mapa Minas Gerais, Mapa RBR, or others, enhancing the realism and immersion of driving in a Brazilian setting.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    jl
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/p0qd8qiqyvij/20jl.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRANEL GUERRA SHOP PISC 1.55 ETS2</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/granel-guerra-shop-pisc-1-55-ets2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-379413 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ets2-trailers">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 11, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="722" sizes="(max-width: 752px) 100vw, 752px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/granel-guerra-shop-pisc-1.55-ets2-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/granel-guerra-shop-pisc-1.55-ets2-1.jpg 752w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/granel-guerra-shop-pisc-1.55-ets2-1-300x288.jpg 300w" width="752"/>
    <img alt="ETS2 Trailers" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ets3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      GRANEL GUERRA SHOP PISC 1.55 ETS2
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     “Granel Guerra 1.55 Shop Pisc” refers to a mod for Euro Truck Simulator 2 (ETS2) that introduces a Granel Guerra” trailer (or reboque, in Portuguese) with realistic cargo loading features.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Here’s a breakdown of what that means:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Granel Guerra: This translates to “Bulk War” or “Grain War,” and it refers to a specific type of bulk cargo trailer, often used for transporting grains, fertilizers, and other loose materials. These trailers are quite common in Brazil, and the mod aims to bring a realistic representation of them into ETS2.
     <br/>
     1.55: This indicates the version of Euro Truck Simulator 2 that the mod is compatible with. Game updates often require mods to be updated as well.
     <br/>
     Shop Pisc: This is the creator and distributor of the mod. Shop Pisc is a Brazilian website known for selling a variety of high-quality mods for ETS2 and American Truck Simulator (ATS), often focusing on Brazilian trucks and trailers.
     <br/>
     Mod (Modification): In gaming, a mod is custom content that adds to or alters a video game. In this case, it introduces a new type of trailer to the game.
    </p>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Key Features of the Granel Guerra 1.55 Shop Pisc Mod:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     This mod is highly regarded for its realism and customization options, often including:
     <br/>
     Realistic Cargo Loading: A major highlight is the “realistic loading system” or “dynamic cargo” feature. This means that when you pick up a bulk cargo, the visuals of the trailer fill up realistically, rather than just appearing as a static image.
     <br/>
     Multiple Configurations: The mod typically offers various configurations for the Granel Guerra trailer, such as:
     <br/>
     Different Axle Counts: Two-axle, three-axle, and sometimes even bitrem (double trailer) options.
     <br/>
     Various Side Wall Heights: Options for low or high side walls, influencing the types and quantities of cargo it can carry.
     <br/>
     Tarpaulin (Lona) Options: You can choose to have the trailer covered with a tarpaulin or uncovered, depending on the cargo. The mod often ensures that when a tarpaulin is on, it correctly hides the cargo.
     <br/>
     Extensive Customization: Players can personalize their Granel Guerra trailers with:
     <br/>
     Paintable Parts: Allowing for custom colors and liveries.
     <br/>
     Accessories: Such as reflective stripes, various mudflap designs (“lameiro Guerra”), different taillight models, “foguinhos” (small lights), and options for chassis height (e.g., normal or “arqueado” for a more lifted look).
     <br/>
     Detailed Models: The mod aims for a high level of detail in the trailer’s appearance.
     <br/>
     Compatibility: Designed for ETS2 version 1.55, it’s also often updated to ensure compatibility with newer game versions and typically works well with both standard and Brazilian-themed maps, including Promods.
     <br/>
     Diverse Cargoes: The mod usually includes a wide range of standard SCS (game’s original) cargoes, but also optimized custom cargoes that fit the “Granel Guerra” theme, such as rolls of cotton, asbestos tiles, and tractors.
     <br/>
     These mods are very popular with ETS2 players, especially those in Brazil, who enjoy a more authentic and immersive trucking experience with vehicles and trailers commonly seen on Brazilian roads.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    pisc
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/x0fw8tuka44i/granel_guerra_1_55_shop_pisc.zip.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover Ontario and Quebec V7-155 ATS</title>
      <link>https://www.ets2world.com/discover-ontario-and-quebec-v7-155-ats/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<article class="post-379410 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail hentry category-ats-maps">
 <div class="post-inner group">
  <p class="post-byline">
   <span class="vcard author">
    <span class="fn">
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/" title="Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       Euro Truck Simulator 2 Mods
      </span>
     </a>
     |
     <a href="https://www.ets2world.com/category/american-truck-simulator-mods/" title="American Truck Simulator Mods">
      <span style="color: #777;">
       American Truck Simulator Mods
      </span>
     </a>
    </span>
   </span>
   |
   <span class="published">
    July 11, 2025
   </span>
  </p>
  <center>
   <div class="thumbnail">
    <img alt="" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" height="360" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/discover-ontario-and-quebec-v7-155-ats-1.jpg" srcset="https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/discover-ontario-and-quebec-v7-155-ats-1.jpg 640w, https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/discover-ontario-and-quebec-v7-155-ats-1-300x169.jpg 300w" width="640"/>
    <img alt="ATS Maps" class="tinythumbicon" src="https://image-proxy-beta.vercel.app/proxy?url=https://www.ets2world.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ats3.png"/>
   </div>
  </center>
  <div class="clear">
  </div>
  <div class="entry themeform">
   <div class="entry-inner">
    <hr/>
    <center style="margin-top:15px;">
    </center>
    <center>
    </center>
    <p>
     <strong>
      Discover Ontario and Quebec V7-155 ATS
     </strong>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <p>
     Version V 7-155 for SCS 1.55
     <br/>
     Ontario-Quebec now all in one map, update for 1.55,
     <br/>
     You will need EMMN to connect.
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <strong>
     Credits:
    </strong>
    Attom
    <br/>
    <p style="margin-bottom:3px;">
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <hr>
    <strong>
     How to install ETS2 mods or ATS Mods
    </strong>
    <br/>
    In Euro Truck Simulator 2 it’s easy to install mods. You just need to download mod from here, copy/unzip files into: “My Documents\Euro Truck Simulator 2\mod” folder or if you play ATS please install mods to: “My Documents\American Truck Simulator\mod” folder. To unzip files you can use: WinRAR or 7zip. After that you need to activate the mods you want to use.
    <hr>
     <div>
      <span style="font-size:15px; color: #f42d36;">
       Report bugs in the comments and help modders improve this mod. Always check the comments, you can find a solution.
      </span>
     </div>
     <hr/>
     <center>
     </center>
     <p>
      <center>
       <div>
        <a class="dmod" href="https://modsfile.com/g84mjibruf3s/ontario_quebec_v_7_155.scs.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">
         <strong>
          DOWNLOAD MOD
         </strong>
        </a>
       </div>
      </center>
     </p>
     <center style="margin-top:35px;">
     </center>
     <nav class="pagination group">
     </nav>
    </hr>
   </div>
   <div class="clear">
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <hr/>
</article>
<br><br><br>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
