<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Trying to Interupt my Conversation! (Game Fails #448)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/stop-trying-to-interupt-my-conversation-game-fails-448/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A shuttle goes flying in Helldivers and more funny game fails.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 76: Every New Location Added in the Season 20 and Ghoul Within Update</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-76-every-new-location-ghoul-within-update-season-20/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Whether or not players plan on transforming their character into a Ghoul, the new questline available to all players in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 76
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s Ghoul Within update will take players to some new marked locations that were added in the recent update. Even beyond the locations that are featured in the quests, there are other new areas added in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  that players may want to know about, and where to find them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Overall,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s Ghoul Within update has added six new marked locations. While this update isn’t considered a new map expansion for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , the playable area still seems to have been expanded to introduce some of these new locations.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="new-locations-added-in-fallout-76-rsquo-s-ghoul-within-update">
  New Locations Added in Fallout 76’s Ghoul Within Update
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1925867692" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1925867692" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1925867692" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1925867692" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1925867692-img" id="article-gallery-1-1925867692">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1925867692" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1192642055">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Old Danielson Cabin
  </li>
  <li>
   Hillside Cavern
  </li>
  <li>
   Radiant Hills
  </li>
  <li>
   The Bullengrube
  </li>
  <li>
   Point Repose
  </li>
  <li>
   Susan's Cabin
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="old-danielson-cabin">
  Old Danielson Cabin
 </h3>
 <p>
  As players begin heading North in the Savage Divide, one of the first new locations they will discover is the Old Danielson Cabin. At first glance, there seemingly isn’t much to this new cabin, but keen players have discovered that this location is a reference to the
  <em>
   Evil Dead
  </em>
  films.
 </p>
 <h3 id="hillside-cavern">
  Hillside Cavern
 </h3>
 <p>
  This location is a nuclear missile silo facility that Ghouls have repurposed as a sanctuary. Humans will be able to enter the Hillside Cavern, but further exploration in this area will be off-limits to humans.
 </p>
 <h3 id="radiant-hills">
  Radiant Hills
 </h3>
 <p>
  Radiant Hills consists of an exterior and interior location, which are both home to the new Ghoul Renegade residents of Appalachia. Human players who can survive the radiation of the Radiant Hills' above-ground exterior can explore here, but the locals won’t be too kind to them, compared to Ghoul players. The interior of this location can be found deeper within the nuclear silo at the new Hillside Cavern location, and it is a free fast travel point, but it will only be accessible for players who transform their
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  character into a Ghoul.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players who transform into a Ghoul will need to visit Jaye Vo within the Radiant Hills interior to equip or remove a disguise needed to visit some of the factions in
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     who aren’t friendly to Ghouls, such as the Raiders, Settlers, and the Brotherhood of Steel.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="the-bullengrube">
  The Bullengrube
 </h3>
 <p>
  At the bottom of a series of waterfalls, players can find a small pond with a secret treasure known as the Bullengrube. While the body of water immediately located at the fast travel point here is a building-restricted area, players can still build in certain places around the nearby waterfalls and streams Northwest of the Bullengrube, making for several scenic CAMP locations in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="point-repose">
  Point Repose
 </h3>
 <p>
  Among the new locations in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , Point Pleasant is the farthest North location. Players can discover the sad story behind this location through the nearby notes left by the former residents.
 </p>
 <h3 id="susan-rsquo-s-cabin">
  Susan’s Cabin
 </h3>
 <p>
  A new meadow and cabin have mysteriously appeared on the Eastern outskirts of the Skyline Valley region, which will be used as the location for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s new Seasonal Public Event, the Big Bloom Event, which will run every Spring. When this Seasonal Event isn’t active, players can still visit this location to meet and chat with the meadow’s new resident, Black-Eyed Susan.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_19">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     According to
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     ’s Season 20 Community Calendar, this year’s Big Bloom event will run from April 29 – May 13.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="new-updated-unmarked-locations-in-the-ghoul-within-update">
  New/Updated Unmarked Locations in the Ghoul Within Update
 </h3>
 <p>
  Outside of the new marked locations added in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s Ghoul Within update, players may find that certain unmarked locations around the map have been updated with new scenery, potentially in anticipation of future updates for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  . One such location is a house located East of the Charleston Fire Department, which is now decorated with some of the same flowers that can be found at Susan’s Cabin.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intergalactic's Sword Isn't the Only Gameplay Detail Its Trailer Seemingly Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/intergalactic-heretic-prophet-sword-melee-gameplay-movement-parkour/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  As is the case with any high-profile game with little to no available footage,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Intergalactic: The Heretic Prophet
   </em>
  </strong>
  has had its reveal trailer relentlessly picked apart for clues. The high-adventure science-fiction epic is shaping up to be a significant departure for Naughty Dog, hopefully allowing the award-winning studio to spread its wings a bit and experiment with different narrative and gameplay ideas.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Among the most heavily dissected elements of the
  <em>
   Intergalactic
  </em>
  trailer is the protagonist's high-tech sword. Glimpsed only briefly near the end of the cinematic, the flashy armament exudes a sort of incomprehensible futuristic power, suggesting that it will somehow be more powerful and versatile than a traditional sword. The trailer's focus on this weapon and its unique appearance suggests that it will be among the player's most valuable tools, maybe even being their primary option for dispatching enemies. This would mark something of a shift for Naughty Dog since, while
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  does include melee options, ranged combat has always been the backbone of its modern games. It's interesting to speculate about how a gameplay loop designed around close-quarters combat will look, and
  <em>
   Intergalactic
  </em>
  's trailer may offer a less-discussed hint about this framework.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="intergalactic-the-heretic-prophet-may-have-mobile-acrobatic-gameplay">
  Intergalactic: The Heretic Prophet May Have Mobile, Acrobatic Gameplay
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1237683357" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1237683357" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1237683357" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1237683357" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1237683357-img" id="article-gallery-1-1237683357">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1237683357" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-382968953">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-intergalactic-trailer-indicates-a-nimble-protagonist">
  The Intergalactic Trailer Indicates a Nimble Protagonist
 </h3>
 <p>
  Near the end of the trailer, protagonist Jordan A. Mun brandishes her high-tech sword and charges at a hostile automaton, leaping off a small boulder to initiate a strong overhead strike. This may seem like a small detail, but it's an intentional choice on the part of the trailer's animators and directors: the footage could have depicted Mun parrying a strike, sliding into a low attack, or performing any number of other maneuvers, thereby hinting at what the game's actual combat would look like. The decision to incorporate this environmental traversal in the trailer could very well be sending a message about
  <em>
   Intergalactic
  </em>
  's interactive elements.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fact that Mun leaps off a stone as part of her attack animation in this scene may speak volumes, if one assumes that Naughty Dog was as intentional as possible when developing this trailer. It could suggest an emphasis on mobility and acrobatic movement in the gameplay itself, with the player perhaps wall-running, mantling, or climbing as part of their traversal and combat moveset. But one doesn't have to simply go off the content of the trailer to make such assumptions; there's evidence of this design philosophy in Naughty Dog's previous work as well.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Naughty Dog and Sony were almost certainly aware that anything and everything in the
     <em>
      Intergalactic
     </em>
     trailer would be picked apart by fans and analyzed for their potential gameplay or story implications. This lends credence to the idea that even small details, like the aforementioned rock-jumping, were incorporated with methodical intention.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="uncharted-4-and-the-last-of-us-part-2-feature-highly-mobile-combat">
  Uncharted 4 and The Last of Us Part 2 Feature Highly Mobile Combat
 </h3>
 <p>
  It would make quite a bit of sense for Naughty Dog to build off the combat systems of its two most recent games, which would likely involve some amount of heightened mobility. In
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  , both Abby and Ellie could mantle over obstacles, squeeze through cracks, and, perhaps most satisfyingly, leap off ledges to assault enemies from above. The realistic, weighty movement of these characters made this approach to combat considerably dynamic and hard-hitting.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Uncharted 4
  </em>
  was even more mobile thanks to the inclusion of a grapple hook, which turned Nathan Drake into something of a deadly cross between Indiana Jones and Spider-Man raining death from above. When
  <em>
   Intergalactic: The Heretic Prophet
  </em>
  rolls around, it could very well adapt these mechanics into an even more fleshed-out, melee-centric sandbox.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Fan Builds Incredible In-Game Tribute to Emily</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-tribute-emily/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A Stardew Valley player created a massive farm portrait of their in-game wife, Emily, impressing fellow gamers.
     </li>
     <li>
      Emily was added as a bachelorette in a post-release update, drawing attention for her personality and style.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans reacted positively to the tribute, showcasing the strong love players have for Stardew Valley characters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  player has created a massive and impressive tribute to their in-game NPC wife, Emily. The show of affection for the
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  character has impressed and surprised fellow gamers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Emily is one of the bachelorettes that
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players can meet, date, and marry, though the game didn't start out that way. Emily and Shane were added to the bachelorette and bachelor lists, respectively, in a post-release update to the game. As one of the more unusual personalities of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , Emily draws a lot of attention for her story quests and her overall character, plus Emily's player makeovers, which have left some fans less than impressed with her sense of style.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it's pretty clear that
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fan HaappyPotatoo is more than a little fond of the character. They shared an image on the game's subreddit of their tribute to their in-game wife, revealing a massive farm portrait of Emily. The portrait looks to be roughly three houses long, dwarfing a nearby lake and taking up nearly half the length of the farm. A closer look reveals that HaappyPotatoo created the portrait by carefully setting down storage chests in different colors, creating an artwork that remakes the Emily sprite very well. As an extra cute touch, a small farm plot surrounded by bee houses to create the shape of a heart is right near her head.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-fans-react-to-emily-artwork">
  Stardew Fans React to Emily Artwork
 </h2>
 <p>
  Other players of the game have been extremely receptive to the artwork, praising the player's efforts and admiring their commitment to their in-game wife. Some joked that they wanted to find someone who would show this level of appreciation to them in a relationship, while others mused about how the player's Grandpa would feel seeing what their grandchild had ultimately done with the farm bequeathed to them. Others suggested that this particular level of dedication would really set off Clint, who is known to have a crush on
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's Emily but never admits it directly to her face.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1914517005" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1914517005" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1914517005" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1914517005" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1914517005-img" id="article-gallery-1-1914517005">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1914517005" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-367597641">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players show a strong love for the game year after year. The characters that developer ConcernedApe has created have resonated with many fans, as they each have their flaws and character traits that make them endearing. Of course, not every player is as committed to one marriage candidate as HaappyPotatoo. Some have made waves by marrying every villager in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , even when mods are required to make it happen. However players choose to play
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , it's earned a spot in the hearts of many.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'll Let You Off With a Warning (Game Fails #445)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/ill-let-you-off-with-a-warning-game-fails-445/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player is surprised by a worm in No Man's Sky and more funny game fails.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
