<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Open-World Games For Challenging Exploration, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-open-world-games-for-challenging-exploration-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Forest presents survival challenges on a dangerous island where resource management is vital.
     </li>
     <li>
      Subnautica strands players on a dangerous aquatic planet filled with exploration risks and unseen dangers.
     </li>
     <li>
      Red Dead Redemption 2 offers vast exploration but lacks extremely challenging enemies, focusing more on the vast and detailed map.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As opposed to titles in other genres,
  <strong>
   open-world
  </strong>
  games allow players tremendous freedom regarding how they want to play, the path they want to create for themselves and their companions, and the challenges they want to face along the way.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some open-world titles opt for a more linear narrative, whereas others allow for a ton of exploration, which gives players the chance to interact with various NPCs, take on several side quests, and discover more of the virtual world around them. Exploration can be challenging enough by itself, so the decision to make it difficult on top of that is a big risk that often pays off, but not always. Here are some of the
  <strong>
   best open-world games with challenging exploration.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-forest">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   The Forest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-man-must-survive-on-a-dangerous-island">
  A Man Must Survive On A Dangerous Island
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-610644760" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-610644760" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-610644760" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-610644760" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-610644760-img" id="article-gallery-1-610644760">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-610644760" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1856048347">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Eric LeBlanc must find his lost son
  </li>
  <li>
   Resource management is key
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The concept of a man looking for his lost son on a distant island has been covered since the days of
  <em>
   Jurassic Park 3
  </em>
  , and even before then. However,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Forest
   </em>
  </strong>
  manages to present players with a very interesting premise of survival on an island full of cannibalistic monsters and various other threats.
 </p>
 <p>
  To survive, Eric LeBlanc will have to come up with ingenious ways to craft different items, find bases for shelter, and keep his eyes open at all times. Given how many dangers the island holds,
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  is an excellent open-world game with challenging exploration.
 </p>
 <h2 id="subnautica">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Subnautica
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="planet-4546b-is-dangerous-to-say-the-least">
  Planet 4546B Is Dangerous, To Say The Least
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-877052792" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-877052792" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-877052792" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-877052792" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-877052792-img" id="article-gallery-2-877052792">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-877052792" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2119102004">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Players are stranded on an inhospitable oceanic planet
  </li>
  <li>
   Survival is uncertain
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Every Sci-Fi fan has, at some point, thought about how scary it would be to find themselves on an inhospitable planet with no form of human contact and no way to get off the surface. This is exactly the premise that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Subnautica
   </em>
  </strong>
  presents to players, which is terrifying, to say the least.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will have to find different ways to survive on the dangerous aquatic planet while staying away from many of the dangers that are lurking on the ocean floor. Exploration is necessary, but also very risky.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost-of-tsushima">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost Of Tsushima
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="some-mongol-groups-are-very-challenging">
  Some Mongol Groups Are Very Challenging
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1205952681" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1205952681" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1205952681" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1205952681" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1205952681-img" id="article-gallery-3-1205952681">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1205952681" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-116454133">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   A combination of peaceful and challenging exploration
  </li>
  <li>
   Mongolian camps hold very dangerous enemies
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ghost of Tsushima
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one of those samurai-themed open-world games that delivers the best experience to players when set to the hardest difficulty. This game follows the story of Jin Sakai during the Mongolian invasion of his beloved homeland, the island of Tsushima.
 </p>
 <p>
  As players explore the vast world crafted for them, they will often encounter various Mongolian camps full of challenging enemies that will probably kill them more than once. Granted, exploration also makes for very peaceful moments where Jin is surrounded by large, open fields, but when players encounter a group of enemies, catlike reflexes and patience are key.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="mutants-giant-bugs-and-deathclaws-are-an-ongoing-threat">
  Mutants, Giant Bugs, And Deathclaws Are An Ongoing Threat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-77641175" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-77641175" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-77641175" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-77641175" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-77641175-img" id="article-gallery-4-77641175">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-77641175" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1156828504">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The Boston Commonwealth is very dangerous
  </li>
  <li>
   Deathclaws and super-mutants await at every turn
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When it comes to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 4
   </em>
  </strong>
  's premise, there's no deception or room for confusion. Within the first hour of the game, players will be well aware that they’re about to explore a wasteland caused by a nuclear holocaust, which, naturally, holds many dangers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Throughout the game, players will have to face super-mutants, giant bugs, and even lethal Deathclaws, which are not only very intimidating, but also extremely powerful and hard to kill unless players are wearing a Power Armor. And even then, some legendary enemies will still pose a challenge. All in all, exploring the Boston Commonwealth is never a walk in the park, but with the right perks, it can be made more manageable.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sometimes-exploration-can-lead-geralt-directly-to-death-39-s-door">
  Sometimes Exploration Can Lead Geralt Directly To Death's Door
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1843079521" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1843079521" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1843079521" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1843079521" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1843079521-img" id="article-gallery-5-1843079521">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1843079521" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-108616795">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Using decoctions can help make the game easier
  </li>
  <li>
   Players can choose to have their enemies level up with them
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Similarly to other titles in this genre,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Witcher 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  only poses a significant challenge during exploration when set to the highest difficulty, “Death March!”. This difficulty level not only makes enemies much stronger and more lethal, but also removes many of the perks that players would usually get from meditating throughout the day.
 </p>
 <p>
  Depending on how much of a challenge they want to face, players can choose to have their enemies level up with them or remain at their predetermined level. Although
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  can be very challenging, using the right weapons and the best decoctions can go a long way in making the experience a lot simpler.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Elden Ring
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sites-of-grace-are-the-only-breather-players-will-get">
  Sites Of Grace Are The Only Breather Players Will Get
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1273572287" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1273572287" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1273572287" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1273572287" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1273572287-img" id="article-gallery-6-1273572287">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1273572287" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1818489521">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Challenging from beginning to end
  </li>
  <li>
   Exploration is often justly rewarded
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Although the
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  franchise had already catapulted FromSoftware to stardom many years before
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring
   </em>
  </strong>
  was even an idea, this open-world title captivated many more players and introduced them to the challenging universe of Soulslikes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Anyone who's ever played a FromSoftware game knows that they’re challenging from beginning to end. This is something that some players love and others dislike, so it’s a matter of personal preference. With that being the case, there’s no denying that
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  offers challenging exploration that is often rewarded with thousands of Runes, and valuable items.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-legend-of-zelda-breath-of-the-wild">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   The Legend Of Zelda: Breath Of The Wild
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-kingdom-of-hyrule-is-enormous">
  The Kingdom Of Hyrule Is Enormous
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1086368026" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1086368026" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1086368026" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1086368026" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1086368026-img" id="article-gallery-7-1086368026">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1086368026" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1244793368">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Various recipes that can help Link in his journey
  </li>
  <li>
   There are many friends and foes on the map
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a Nintendo game, so by no means should players expect to find the same kind of grim atmosphere that they would encounter in games like
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . However, that is not a bad thing, as this title does its own thing and presents players with a vast open world that is full of life and challenges.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Breath of the Wild
  </em>
  , exploration is tough, but if players take their time and learn some of the best cooking recipes in the Kingdom of Hyrule, their chances of survival will be much greater.
 </p>
 <h2 id="red-dead-redemption-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-map-is-huge-making-exploration-fun-yet-challenging">
  The Map Is Huge, Making Exploration Fun, Yet Challenging
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-988297912" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-988297912" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-988297912" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-988297912" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-988297912-img" id="article-gallery-8-988297912">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-988297912" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1347966218">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The map is vast and hard to cover without fast travel
  </li>
  <li>
   Players can sometimes accidentally wander into towns where they're wanted
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Red Dead Redemption 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  has many things going for it. However, having extremely challenging exploration due to difficult enemies is not one of them. That said, exploration is still difficult due to how big the map of the United States is. At the beginning of the game, players will not have the option to fast travel, which means that they'll have to explore uncharted territory and various counties without knowing what they might find.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sure, O’Driscoll gang ambushes can be hard to manage sometimes, but the real challenge comes from riding on horseback for long periods, and sometimes even trusting strangers who aren’t really in danger, but simply want to rob Arthur instead. The level of detail present in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  is something very hard to come by these days, and that includes the different possible endings depending on Arthur's Honor level. This is why it deserves the top spot on the list.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Best Ways To Make Money In Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/disney-dreamlight-valley-best-ways-make-money/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Disney Dreamlight Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the hottest cozy games in recent years. It allows players of all ages to interact with their favorite animated Disney characters (from Mickey Mouse to Vanellope von Schweetz) while creating a dream world to fit their unique tastes. Fishing, gardening, mining, and cooking are just some ways players can spend time in a magical realm of childhood dreams and adventures.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One prime feature of the game is Scrooge McDuck’s shop, where players can find clothing, furniture, and themed decor. The savvy Scottish billionaire will also be there to upgrade buildings like Remy’s restaurant and the homes of new residents. Of course, Scrooge doesn’t give anything away for free, so players will need gold coins to invest in the Valley of their dreams. Here are some of the best ways to get some cold, hard cash.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated on December 29, 2024, by Gemma Johnson:
   </em>
  </strong>
  Making money is a big part of
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley.
  </em>
  Whether buying ingredients, upgrading stalls, or adding more homes to the Valley, knowing how to make money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  is essential. Of course, it takes time to make the big bucks, with Gold Star Coins being the primary currency that players may need to dip into frequently. Consequently, knowing the
  <strong>
   best ways to make money
  </strong>
  <strong>
   in
   <em>
    Disney Dreamlight Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  is invaluable, especially for players eager to make millions of Gold Star Coins fast. Making money is also helpful before each big update, so players can better prepare themselves for any potential new additions to the game and progress more quickly. Fortunately, there are numerous things players can do to ensure they have plenty of cash in their pockets. This update adds one new entry and updates the existing ones where relevant.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="farm-beginner-crops">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Farm Beginner Crops
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="low-cost-decent-profit">
  Low Cost, Decent Profit
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-276457920" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-276457920" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-276457920" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-276457920" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-276457920-img" id="article-gallery-1-276457920">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-276457920" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-200920783">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the best ways to make money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  is by
  <strong>
   growing early game crops
  </strong>
  . While players must progress to access the highest earners, some early-game crops like carrots can yield a decent profit. A bag of carrot seeds costs just 10 Gold Star Coins. Once grown, players can sell each carrot for 44 Gold Star Coins.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once players start to unlock other biomes, other crops worth farming to help make more money include tomato seeds from Dazzle Beach, costing just 8 Gold Star Coins a Bag and selling for 22 Gold Star Coins each. Players can also buy onion seeds from the Forest of Valor or okra seeds from the Glade of Trust, depending on which biome they decide to unlock first. Onions sell for 170 Gold Star Coins each and Okra for 114 Gold Star Coins.
 </p>
 <h2 id="level-up-friendships-with-villagers">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Level Up Friendships With Villagers
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="get-friendship-rewards-like-star-coins">
  Get Friendship Rewards Like Star Coins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-421020391" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-421020391" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-421020391" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-421020391" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-421020391-img" id="article-gallery-2-421020391">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-421020391" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-769672662">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One benefit of leveling up
  <strong>
   friendships
  </strong>
  with
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  villagers is not only completing their quests but receiving rewards per friendship level. In the character collection pages, players can scroll down and see their friendship with each character and unlockable rewards. While this could be a cosmetic item specific to that character, it could also be around 500 or 1,000 Gold Star Coins, which is a great way to top up funds.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, it's worth spending time hanging out with villagers when doing everyday activities like mining, digging, and fishing. If players take a character with that same specialty, they can also net more finds, like more gems, while mining. After players complete friendship quests, they often receive rewards in their mailbox to sell for extra cash.
  <strong>
  </strong>
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dig-up-and-sell-pearls">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Dig Up And Sell Pearls
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-quick-and-easy-way-for-players-to-pocket-extra-star-coins">
  A Quick And Easy Way For Players To Pocket Extra Star Coins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1052756222" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1052756222" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1052756222" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1052756222" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1052756222-img" id="article-gallery-3-1052756222">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1052756222" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1195398770">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another way to make money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  is
  <strong>
   by digging up and selling Pearls
  </strong>
  . While Pearls are an exclusive crafting item in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  's
  <em>
   A Rift in Time
  </em>
  expansion, they are also a quick and easy way to put extra Star Coins in players' pockets. Players need only start digging in the grassy areas of Ancient Landing on Eternity Isle for a chance to get one or more of these shiny delights. Indeed, players can scoop up around three Pearls at once in a single dig spot worth 10 Gold Star Coins each once sold.
 </p>
 <p>
  While this doesn't sound like a lot, it can soon add up, especially if players bring along a digging companion or some Miracle Shovel Varnish to net some more as an alternative to mining for gems.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tidy-up-the-valley">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Tidy Up The Valley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="make-space-and-extra-cash">
  Make Space And Extra Cash
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-671981653" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-671981653" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-671981653" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-671981653" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-671981653-img" id="article-gallery-4-671981653">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-671981653" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1473195908">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players can also make extra money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  by
  <strong>
   having a tidy-up around the Valley.
  </strong>
  Depending on how neat players like to keep their Valley as they go along, it's probably likely they will find all kinds of high-value items just lying around on the ground waiting to be collected, especially near rocks. Tidying up the Valley not only frees up more placement space but also gives players more things to sell at Goofy's stall.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's also worth players de-cluttering their storage to check for time-limited forageables worth selling, like buttons from the "Thrills and Frills" update. Some are worth around 50 Star Coins each, which soon adds up if sold in large batches.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="clear-away-night-thorns">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Clear Away Night Thorns
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="quickly-gain-star-coins-and-a-chance-of-gold-chests">
  Quickly Gain Star Coins And A Chance Of Gold Chests
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-578089999" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-578089999" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-578089999" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-578089999" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-578089999-img" id="article-gallery-5-578089999">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-578089999" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-945364306">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the start of
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  , the world is under a dark spell known as the Forgetting. One symptom is that the Valley is overrun by spiky
  <strong>
   Night Thorns
  </strong>
  , which can be the bane of the player's existence, as they can often get in the way. However, Night Thorns are also a potential cash cow. For every bundle players whisk away, they have the potential to earn at least 10 Gold Star Coins. It may not seem like much, but with Thorns cropping up almost constantly, that money soon adds up to buy things like
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  upgrades. Of course, players with access to
  <em>
   A Rift in Time
  </em>
  can also clear away Splinters of Fate for a chance of Star Coins spawning.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, clearing Night Thorns can spit out a bundle of sparkling Star Coins at least once a day. The music changes, indicating a countdown to collect them all for a golden chest reward containing more Star Coins before the time runs out. While the prize changes randomly, it can sometimes reward players with around 250 coins.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sell-shiny-gems">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Sell Shiny Gems
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="high-value-jewels-to-make-money-fast">
  High-Value Jewels To Make Money Fast
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-253526872" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-253526872" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-253526872" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-253526872" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-253526872-img" id="article-gallery-6-253526872">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-253526872" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1064909598">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Similar to the real world,
  <strong>
   gems
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  are very valuable. Unlike in the real world, they are super easy to find. Each area in the game has rocks to mine with specific gems found in certain biomes. Bringing along a friend with a mining specialty can also help, as they can mine extra gems while “hanging out” with the player.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shiny gems are rarer and typically earn more coins when players
  <strong>
   sell them at Goofy’s stall.
  </strong>
  Some of
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  's best gems are Shiny Diamonds, as players might expect, located in the Forgotten Lands. Each Shiny Diamond is worth a whopping 2,400k. The next most valuable is the Shiny Amethyst at 2,000k, which players can find in the Forgotten Lands and Frosted Heights. Shiny Rubies and Shiny Sapphires are also worth a pretty penny at 1,400k and are discoverable in the Vitalys Mines. Of course,
  <em>
   A Rift in Time
  </em>
  also has other valuable shiny gems for players to mine, like Shiny Blue Zircon worth 2,000 Coins.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sell-rare-fish">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Sell Rare Fish
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="valuable-fish-equal-more-star-coins">
  Valuable Fish Equal More Star Coins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1398035964" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1398035964" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1398035964" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1398035964" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1398035964-img" id="article-gallery-7-1398035964">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1398035964" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-564523594">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Like so many popular cozy games, fishing is a staple activity here, and there are many varieties of fish in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  for players to discover. Of course, the rarer the fish, the more money Goofy will pay at his stall. To make more money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  , players can
  <strong>
   find rare fish
  </strong>
  around the valley by aiming for gold-colored ripples fishing at certain times of the day.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some of the rarest fish in the game include Here and There Fish, which are introduced in Nala’s questline 'Here and There and Back Again.' This beautiful specimen is worth 2K gold coins and can be found anywhere in the Valley early morning or at night. The next best fish to sell in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  is the Anglerfish, worth 1.5K and found in the Forgotten Lands, followed by White Sturgeon for 1.2K (Frosted Heights) and Walleye for 1.1K (Sunlit Plateau).
 </p>
 <h2 id="moana-39-s-fishing-boat">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Moana's Fishing Boat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="cash-in-a-bunch-of-fish-for-little-to-no-effort">
  Cash In A Bunch Of Fish For Little To No Effort
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1432667259" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1432667259" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1432667259" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1432667259" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1432667259-img" id="article-gallery-8-1432667259">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1432667259" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-817784321">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players who earn a Level 2 friendship level with Moana can unlock her quest called 'Fixing the Boat', which involves fixing and restoring Moana's boat to its former glory. Once fixed, players can start raking in the benefits as Moana uses her boat to catch and brings back fish for players to do with what they like.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s also worthwhile upgrading Moana’s boat as much as possible, which can be expensive, but often worth it. Once fully upgraded, Moana brings back around 20 fish, with a good chunk of them often rare finds. Players can then choose the ones they want to keep for recipes and sell the rarer ones for big bucks.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="make-and-sell-meals">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Make And Sell Meals
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="make-5-star-recipes-with-a-big-price-tag">
  Make 5-Star Recipes With A Big Price Tag
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-467773917" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-467773917" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-467773917" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-467773917" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-467773917-img" id="article-gallery-9-467773917">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-467773917" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1997111781">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The best chefs know that the key to
  <strong>
   cooking
  </strong>
  is combining the right ingredients. With Remy’s help in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   players can earn serious Star Coins by cooking and selling top-tier meals.
  </strong>
  Five-star meals are the best bet, and the more variety of ingredients, the better. Indeed, some of the best meals to sell in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  include Pan-Fried Angler Fish worth 2,457 Star Coins and Poached Basil-Butter Sturgeon worth 2,010 Coins.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players with access to recipes from
  <em>
   A Rift in Time
  </em>
  can also make Shawarma for a whopping 3,782 Star Coins and Blend of the Bayou for 2,182 Coins. Making and selling such delectable delicacies is often fun and can be a great way to earn some extra money.
 </p>
 <h2 id="wall-e-39-s-garden">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Wall-E's Garden
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stock-up-on-veggies-for-free">
  Stock Up On Veggies For Free
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-222443114" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-222443114" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-222443114" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-222443114" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-222443114-img" id="article-gallery-10-222443114">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-222443114" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-305401691">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Like Moana’s Fishing Boat quest, players can help their favorite trash-collecting robot by making the perfect vegetable garden. Wall-E’s level 2 friendship quest, 'Village Project: The Garden', unlocks a treasure trove of crops to sell, and players don’t even have to lift a finger! Well, after they collect all the materials and craft all the needed tools, that is.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once the quest is complete,
  <strong>
   Wall-E’s garden
  </strong>
  is full of veggies to harvest. Of course, it helps to upgrade the garden as much as possible. The bigger the garden, the more crops will grow, and the more money players get for selling them. With a little time and investment, it’s easy money.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="grow-and-sell-pumpkins">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Grow And Sell Pumpkins
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sell-high-value-crops-like-pumpkins-to-fill-pockets">
  Sell High-Value Crops Like Pumpkins To Fill Pockets
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1845563808" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1845563808" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1845563808" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1845563808" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1845563808-img" id="article-gallery-11-1845563808">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1845563808" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-912023085">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Of course, why should Wall-E get to have all the gardening fun? For those who enjoy digging in the dirt and seeing the fruits and veggies of their labor, growing and harvesting high-value crops is one of the best ways to make money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  . While players must sometimes purchase costly seeds from Goofy’s stall to get started, the profit is worth it in the long run, especially once they know the best seeds to buy.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pumpkins
  </strong>
  remain some of the best crops to make money in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley,
  </em>
  despite their long growing time. Pumpkin seeds cost 275 Gold Stars Coins per bag but sell for 664 gold each, which is over twice the price of the seed itself. Leeks are also worth planting at only 120 Gold Star Coins per bag, and each leek harvested sells for 309 Coins. Players can buy both pumpkin and leek seeds at his stall in the Forgotten Lands, making them something for beginners to work towards unlocking.
 </p>
 <h2 id="craft-and-sell-miracle-potions">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Craft And Sell Miracle Potions
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="handy-potions-to-make-money-like-magic">
  Handy Potions To Make Money Like Magic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-323972341" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-323972341" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-323972341" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-323972341" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-323972341-img" id="article-gallery-12-323972341">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-323972341" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-504769767">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Crafting
  </strong>
  is an essential skill in
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  . Not only is it crucial for completing questlines, but helps to beautify and personalize the world’s aesthetic. Along their journey, players will receive recipes for crafting Miracle Elixirs. These potions greatly enhance tools, allowing them to mine, fish, and garden like a true pro.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the Miracle Potions are incredibly useful for collecting various treasures, they also have decent monetary value.
  <em>
   Disney Dreamlight Valley
  </em>
  's Miracle Pickaxe Polish, Miracle Growth Elixir, Miracle Fishing Bait, and Miracle Shovel Varnish are sellable for extra dough.
  <strong>
   Potions with the “Even More Miraculous” moniker are especially valuable.
  </strong>
  For example, crafting the Even More Miraculous Pickaxe Polish and selling it at Goofy’s stall will yield a very lucrative amount of 5,700 Coins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Open-World Games That Take The Longest To Beat</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/open-world-games-longest-beat/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Given their expansive nature,
  <strong>
   open-world
  </strong>
  projects
  <strong>
  </strong>
  tend to be some of the
  <strong>
   longest games
  </strong>
  in existence. It's possible to pour hundreds and thousands of hours into a single open-world game without exploring every nook and cranny. They are meant to keep someone engaged for weeks or months, and when done right, they can be absolutely spectacular. Now, longer does not always mean better, but when a project hits the mark, that can certainly be the case.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While there are short open-world games out there,
  <em>
   Shadow of the Colossus
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Mafia
  </em>
  immediately come to mind, most entries in the genre require a significant time investment. That's part of the reason these titles are so popular – they reward commitment with content and immersion. These titles are designed to be played for weeks or months on end, taking players on an epic journey across (usually) expansive worlds. Let's take a look at the
  <strong>
   longest open-world games
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated December 29, 2024 by Mark Sammut
   </strong>
   : Two more fairly recent open-world games have been added to this disucssion.
  </em>
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The listed times are taken from HowLongToBeat. The included range covers from the time required to finish a game's main story to a completionist playthrough. The former will be used as the primary metric, while the latter will be used in the case of a tie. Also,
     <strong>
      only one entry per franchise
     </strong>
     , although other games will be mentioned as notes. Finally, a game must have at least 4 input times to be considered.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="once-human">
  <span class="item-num">
   49
  </span>
  <span>
   Once Human
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="29-ndash-200-hours">
  29–200 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1757169317" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1757169317" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1757169317" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1757169317" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1757169317-img" id="article-gallery-1-1757169317">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1757169317" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-773396606">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Due to being something of a live service release,
  <em>
   Once Human
  </em>
  is a bit of an odd one since it never really feels 100% complete. That said, the game does have a story with an endpoint, so it is an option for players who just want to approach it like a single-player open-world rather than an online one.
 </p>
 <p>
  A survival game with looter shooter elements,
  <em>
   Once Human
  </em>
  brings to life a post-apocalyptic setting caused by a research organization that got its hands on alien material. Players are dropped into a fairly desolate world filled with both mutated creatures and factions who are at each other's throats. While decent enough as a single-player survival game,
  <em>
   Once Human
  </em>
  is at its best when played with a few friends and without focusing too much on the story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="subnautica">
  <span class="item-num">
   48
  </span>
  <span>
   Subnautica
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="30-ndash-53-hours">
  30–53 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2125900135" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2125900135" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2125900135" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2125900135" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2125900135-img" id="article-gallery-2-2125900135">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2125900135" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1616472103">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Very few open-world games specifically revolve around underwater exploration, and
  <em>
   Subnautica
  </em>
  represents this type of experience at its best. Unknown Worlds' 2018 epic is impressively well-rounded, delivering intense encounters, polished survival mechanics, a respectable selection of modes, and a decent enough story that has a strong sense of mystery. Also, the game can get pretty scary at times, even if these moments are not quite consistent enough to warrant a horror label.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, depending on the mode chosen,
  <em>
   Subnautica
  </em>
  can be quite a different experience; however, survival will likely be most people's first experience. As suggested by the name, this mode emphasizes character management by monitoring things like hunger and oxygen. Exploration drives
  <em>
   Subnautica
  </em>
  , and it is constantly fantastic.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_18">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Subnautica: Below Zero
     </em>
     lasts about 20 hours.
     <em>
      Subnautica 2
     </em>
     has also been announced.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-planet-crafter">
  <span class="item-num">
   47
  </span>
  <span>
   The Planet Crafter
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="31-ndash-48-hours">
  31–48 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1558300266" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1558300266" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1558300266" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1558300266" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1558300266-img" id="article-gallery-3-1558300266">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1558300266" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-201057180">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Planet Crafter
  </em>
  is a surprisingly cozy and relaxing survival game. The premise is quite straightforward: Players are tasked with terraforming an alien planet. They land in a mostly deserted world and have to spend their first few hours just meeting their basic needs, which is not easy when oxygen is limited. However, as time passes, they gradually earn the required resources to craft more impressive equipment, machines, and buildings, permitting them to turn this planet into something resembling a home.
 </p>
 <p>
  While crafting takes center stage, the game emphasizes exploration as well, and the world has quite a range of unique biomes that provide a change of scenery and challenge. More importantly,
  <em>
   The Planet Crafter
  </em>
  has a genuine endpoint (multiple, actually), so players will be working towards a conclusion rather than just endlessly engaging in a challenge of survival.
 </p>
 <h2 id="no-man-39-s-sky">
  <span class="item-num">
   46
  </span>
  <span>
   No Man's Sky
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="31-ndash-144-hours">
  31–144 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1052687536" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1052687536" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1052687536" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1052687536" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1052687536-img" id="article-gallery-4-1052687536">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1052687536" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-172821517">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   No Man's Sky
  </em>
  had an incredibly rough launch. When it was first released back in 2016, it was met with ire by much of the community. Players cited the lack of content and a failure to deliver on promises made by the developer as the biggest issues, with a general feeling that the game was unfinished. Thankfully, developers listened to the community and stuck with the project, pouring extra work into creating the game that they envisioned from the start.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nowadays,
  <em>
   No Man's Sky
  </em>
  is much improved and has seen a couple of DLC releases to help pad out its content even further. In fact, there is not so much to do in the sci-fi exploration and action release that deviating from the main story and doing all the side content will take over 100 hours. There is replayability here too.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dysmantle">
  <span class="item-num">
   45
  </span>
  <span>
   Dysmantle
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="32-ndash-75-hours">
  32–75 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-245340914" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-245340914" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-245340914" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-245340914" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-245340914-img" id="article-gallery-5-245340914">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-245340914" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-123466662">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  An indie open-world survival game,
  <em>
   Dysmantle
  </em>
  establishes a gameplay loop that is irresistibly addictive. Set in a post-apocalyptic world featuring zombies, this title's bare-bones sound rather unspectacular, but everything comes together quite seamlessly for one main reason: progression is constant and highly enjoyable.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players spend the majority of their time in
  <em>
   Dysmantle
  </em>
  destroying everything around them, and each action grants XP points that can then be used to forge better tools to cause even more devastation. It is a cycle that works brilliantly and ensures that grinding never feels pointless. The world is reasonably large too, even if the isometric camera angle makes the map seem smaller than it is.
 </p>
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   44
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="32-ndash-84-hours">
  32–84 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1196957170" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1196957170" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1196957170" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1196957170" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1196957170-img" id="article-gallery-6-1196957170">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1196957170" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-786966109">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rockstar's latest adventure was so well-received by the community that it continues to see updates and re-releases on consoles.
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  is one of the largest and most ambitious releases in Rockstar's franchise, with a main campaign that spans three separate playable characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although the main story is engrossing enough, there are tons of sidequests and stranger-style missions to complete. It'll take players quite a bit of time and effort to see all there is to see in Los Santos and all the surrounding areas. From there, players can also hop into
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto Online
  </em>
  , for even more stories and side-content to tackle.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_44">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Obviously,
     <em>
      GTA Online
     </em>
     is almost endless.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="divine-divinity">
  <span class="item-num">
   43
  </span>
  <span>
   Divine Divinity
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="32-ndash-70-hours">
  32–70 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-504796984" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-504796984" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-504796984" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-504796984" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-504796984-img" id="article-gallery-7-504796984">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-504796984" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-471902061">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Thanks to
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , Larian is well-established as one of the best modern RPG developers. While both of those games provide room for exploration and free roam, they are not open-world in the traditional sense but rather feature open areas. However, 2002's
  <em>
   Divine Divinity
  </em>
  is a more standard representative of the concept, even if it is fairly dated in a lot of ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  Blending
  <em>
   Diablo
  </em>
  -style combat with classic PC RPG elements,
  <em>
   Divine Divinity
  </em>
  does a pretty good job balancing out the two subgenres, delivering a fairly accessible hack and slash system alongside stat-fueled progression and builds. Players are free to explore the world as they see fit, tackling side quests at their leisure. While a bit rough around the edges, this title still has plenty of charm.
 </p>
 <h2 id="space-rangers-hd-a-war-apart">
  <span class="item-num">
   42
  </span>
  <span>
   Space Rangers HD: A War Apart
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="32-ndash-173-hours">
  32–173 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1458183674" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1458183674" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1458183674" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1458183674" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1458183674-img" id="article-gallery-8-1458183674">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1458183674" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-183469423">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although it certainly shows its age nowadays,
  <em>
   Space Rangers 2: Dominators
  </em>
  was an impressive sci-fi title when it debuted in 2004. The Russian game blends a surprising number of genres, from trade simulators to shoot 'em ups and RTS. The base game launched with hardly a shortage of content, but 2013's
  <em>
   Space Rangers HD: A War Apart
  </em>
  adds even more material to it, expanding this title to enormous lengths.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Space Rangers HD
  </em>
  takes place in a universe where evil robots called Dominators are trying to take over everything. The player steps into one of the game's various civilizations and must set out to complete faction missions, take a few trips to hyperspace, and make enemies and friends along the way. Not everything about
  <em>
   Space Rangers HD: A War Apart
  </em>
  has aged gracefully, but the game's open-ended nature is admirable and greatly enhances its replayability, making it one of the
  <strong>
   longest open-world games
  </strong>
  ever.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="skull-and-bones">
  <span class="item-num">
   41
  </span>
  <span>
   Skull And Bones
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="33-ndash-40-hours">
  33–40 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1356093065" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1356093065" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1356093065" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1356093065" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1356093065-img" id="article-gallery-9-1356093065">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1356093065" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1148787798">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ubisoft created one of the definitive pirate games in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed 4: Black Flag
  </em>
  , a project that was so successful that a spiritual successor removed from that franchise seemed inevitable.
  <em>
   Skull and Bones
  </em>
  took a very long time to materialize, and it went through a rather notoriously development cycle; by the time of its 2024 debut, the game had lost most of its momentum following an array of underwhelming reports and previews. While not without positives,
  <em>
   Skull and Bones
  </em>
  was undeniably a disappointment, particularly its limited gameplay, which felt more restrictive and one-note than the much older
  <em>
   Black Flag
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite technically containing a main story, this title follows a live-service structure that is meant to encourage indefinite sessions, sort of similar to something like
  <em>
   Sea of Thieves
  </em>
  . Even if it is not the focus, the campaign is fairly lengthy, and it mostly revolves around targeting specific pirates (who have very little personality). It took
  <em>
   Skull and Bones
  </em>
  roughly three months to poll just four main story times on HowLongToBeat, which is ridiculous for such a major release.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fade-to-silence">
  <span class="item-num">
   40
  </span>
  <span>
   Fade To Silence
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="34-ndash-40-hours">
  34–40 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1506011533" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1506011533" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1506011533" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1506011533" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1506011533-img" id="article-gallery-10-1506011533">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1506011533" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1694599958">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A survival open-world game that came and went in 2019,
  <em>
   Fade to Silence
  </em>
  is not a highlight of either genre it represents; however, it offers enough positives in each area to warrant an unenthusiastic recommendation to people looking for a bit of both. Dropped into a winter wasteland, players are cast as Ash, a guy who will be spending all of his time exploring, collecting resources, and expanding their base. The game tells a story as well, but it is not too important and does not distract from the gameplay loop.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fade to Silence
  </em>
  can be frustrating, particularly during scenarios that require engaging in combat. Nevertheless, players looking for a meaty survival game might enjoy what they find here, as long as they can deal with a few rough edges.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="outward">
  <span class="item-num">
   39
  </span>
  <span>
   Outward
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="33-ndash-98-hours">
  33–98 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-2134587424" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-2134587424" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-2134587424" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-2134587424" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-2134587424-img" id="article-gallery-11-2134587424">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-2134587424" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1652404730">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Usually, fantasy RPGs cast players as prominent figures, heroes summoned by the stars to change the course of history.
  <em>
   Outward
  </em>
  opts for a different take as its protagonist starts off as a common adventurer who is merely trying to pay off a debut, and it takes a while for them to become involved in a more important narrative.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Outward
  </em>
  has plenty of issues such as unsatisfying combat, the game nails its open-world. Players are allowed to explore the map to their hearts' content, and the game opens up very quickly. Sure, some routes lead to death, but that is to be expected in this sort of fantasy world.
 </p>
 <h2 id="pokemon-scarlet-and-violet">
  <span class="item-num">
   38
  </span>
  <span>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="34-ndash-87-hours">
  34–87 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1257558103" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1257558103" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1257558103" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1257558103" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1257558103-img" id="article-gallery-12-1257558103">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1257558103" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1731007847">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Arceus
  </em>
  ' footsteps,
  <em>
   Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  were the first main entry projects in Game Freak's franchise to go down the open-world route, a decision that attracted excitement and trepidation in equal measure. The ninth-generation games got a decisively mixed response, particularly due to pretty bad performance and bugs. Visually,
  <em>
   Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  also leave quite a bit to be desired and are fairly rough around the edges.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, they are
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  games that, for the most part, manage to preserve the traditional loop that has proven popular for the best part of three decades. Sure, the story might be reluctant to provide any significant challenge or try anything all that new, but neither of those things are game killers for
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  . The simple excitement of catching and training monsters will seemingly never grow out of fashion.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="s-t-a-l-k-e-r-2-heart-of-chornobyl">
  <span class="item-num">
   37
  </span>
  <span>
   S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="35-ndash-104-hours">
  35–104 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1698617734" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1698617734" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1698617734" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1698617734" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1698617734-img" id="article-gallery-13-1698617734">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1698617734" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-957275784">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Surviving a difficult production cycle,
  <em>
   S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl
  </em>
  launched to a generally positive reception, with most of the criticisms focusing on its technical state. Yes, the game had and still has its share of bugs and glitches, but the actual content is pretty darn great and arguably marks a new high point for the franchise (which is not a statement made lightly). Once again, players find themselves in The Zone, an area filled with radiation, mutants, and people trying to get ahead (and they are willing to kill for it).
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2
  </em>
  is massive, offering a way bigger world than any of its predecessors. Although not devoid of empty areas, which makes sense considering the setting, the map is fairly stacked with content. Beyond that,
  <em>
   S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2
  </em>
  strikes a pretty great balance between survival, horror, and gunplay.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-new-vegas-ndash-ultimate-edition">
  <span class="item-num">
   36
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout: New Vegas – Ultimate Edition
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="35-ndash-145-hours">
  35–145 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1107258620" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1107258620" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1107258620" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1107258620" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1107258620-img" id="article-gallery-14-1107258620">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1107258620" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-1561810496">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When it comes to main stories,
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  is the longest entry in Bethesda's franchise, although most of the 3D games are similar in length. Obsidian's spin-off is generally hailed as the best post-
  <em>
   Fallout 2
  </em>
  entry, particularly due to its implementation of actions and consequences that make the player's decisions seem important.
 </p>
 <p>
  As with most Bethesda games,
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  ' content and longevity go well beyond the base content, at least on PC. These titles are kept alive for years through active modding communities that add a plethora of fresh material, including stuff like quests.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_95">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Fallout 4 – Game Of The Year Edition
     </em>
     has a very similar length to
     <em>
      New Vegas
     </em>
     , with its story being roughly 34 hours. However, completionist runs are longer at 224 hours.
     <em>
      F
     </em>
     <em>
      allout 76
     </em>
     is similar at 35 hours, with 340 hours for everything.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="don-39-t-starve-together">
  <span class="item-num">
   35
  </span>
  <span>
   Don't Starve Together
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="35-ndash-254-hours">
  35–254 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-825724293" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-825724293" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-825724293" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-825724293" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-825724293-img" id="article-gallery-15-825724293">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-825724293" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-851522160">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Don't Starve
  </em>
  is a popular open-world survival game with a permadeath mechanic; meanwhile,
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  frames many of the same ideas around multiplayer, acting both as a sequel and a standalone experience. As both titles have their positives and are worth owning in their own right, players will need to decide which title is better suited to meet their needs. If someone is specifically looking to play with friends,
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  is their only choice.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  is the longer of the two projects, although the time required to complete playthroughs will vary greatly since this is one of those games that plays it fast and loose with its story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="starpoint-gemini-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   34
  </span>
  <span>
   Starpoint Gemini 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="36-ndash-52-hours">
  36–52 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-567739554" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-567739554" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-567739554" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-567739554" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-567739554-img" id="article-gallery-16-567739554">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-567739554" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1215228048">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Humanity seemed destined to always gaze at the stars, dreaming of a future when they may fly freely through space's endless expanse. While that reality is still far off, games present a way to experience a slightly similar thrill, all from the comfort of a gaming chair. While not lacking a story,
  <em>
   Starpoint Gemini 2
  </em>
  's main appeal is the freedom it grants players, allowing them to jump into their spaceship and explore to their hearts' content.
 </p>
 <p>
  A true sandbox experience, the game shines in its ability to reward aimlessness, crafting unique scenarios that can only be found if somebody is willing to just go where few have gone before. While not always smooth sailing and occasionally succumbing to repetition,
  <em>
   Starpoint Gemini 2
  </em>
  is generally an impressive outing, especially for a relatively small release that is more than a decade old by this point.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="days-gone">
  <span class="item-num">
   33
  </span>
  <span>
   Days Gone
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="37-ndash-65-hours">
  37–65 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-851741095" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-851741095" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-851741095" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-851741095" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-851741095-img" id="article-gallery-17-851741095">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-851741095" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-1436259666">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Days Gone
  </em>
  got lost in the PS4 exclusive shuffle and garnered a polarizing reception at launch. The zombie open-world game centers around Deacon St. John, a biker who goes on a journey to track down his supposedly deceased wife. A surprisingly character-driven piece,
  <em>
   Days Gone
  </em>
  's lengthy campaign does have some pacing issues and a slow start, but things do pick up after a couple of hours.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if the narrative fails to hit the spot with someone, they can at least look forward to driving their bike across a beautiful world while they try to avoid the undead hordes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elex-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   32
  </span>
  <span>
   Elex 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="37-ndash-78-hours">
  37–78 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-339952003" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-339952003" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-339952003" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-339952003" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-339952003-img" id="article-gallery-18-339952003">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-339952003" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-422325920">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Piranha Bytes specializes in open-world games, an endeavor that goes all the way back to 2001's
  <em>
   Gothic
  </em>
  . Although typically known for their Eurojank, Piranha's projects are endearing and ambitious for the company's size.
  <em>
   Gothic 2
  </em>
  is probably the developer's most famous title, but the
  <em>
   Risen
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Elex
  </em>
  series also have their fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  Debuting roughly a week after
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elex 2
  </em>
  was utterly overshadowed by FromSoftware's masterpiece. Now that the Lands Between has been fully explored, RPG fans might want to consider visiting Magalan for a fantasy sci-fi adventure.
  <em>
   Elex 2
  </em>
  wastes little time in cutting players loose so that they can explore its world, and the game even hands out a jetpack.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_121">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Elex
     </em>
     clocks in at 27 hours, along with a completionist time of 91 hours.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-39-s-dogma">
  <span class="item-num">
   31
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon's Dogma
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="37-ndash-102-hours">
  37–102 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1543728626" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1543728626" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1543728626" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1543728626" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1543728626-img" id="article-gallery-19-1543728626">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1543728626" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-1462067139">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  2012's
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma
  </em>
  is a great action RPG, and
  <em>
   Dark Arisen
  </em>
  adds roughly 10 hours of awesome content to the base game; however, according to HowLongToBeat, the vanilla version is actually the longer of the two games, at least when it comes to completing the main story. In reality,
  <em>
   Dark Arisen
  </em>
  might have been a revisit for quite a few players, so they got through the standard quests quicker since they were already familiar with the gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom drops players in Gransys, a gorgeous open-world densely populated with monsters. While not colossal, the map is expertly crafted to maximize gameplay and combat, the latter of which is fantastic.
  <em>
   Dark Arisen
  </em>
  introduces Bitterblack Isle, a post-campaign area that significantly ramps up the difficulty and dread.
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma
  </em>
  does not have much in the way of memorable characters or writing, and the game's storytelling is unlikely to leave much of a lasting impression. However, almost everything else is well above average, and the simple act of exploration is satisfying.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_128">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Dragon's Dogma 2
     </em>
     's main story comes in at 30 hours, while a completionist run requires about 95 hours.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="enshrouded">
  <span class="item-num">
   30
  </span>
  <span>
   Enshrouded
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="38-ndash-60-hours">
  38–60 Hours
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-1740088500" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-1740088500" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-1740088500" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-1740088500" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-1740088500-img" id="article-gallery-20-1740088500">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-1740088500" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-1137109129">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Similar to a few other very
  <strong>
   long open-world games
  </strong>
  ,
  <em>
   Enshrouded
  </em>
  is still in early access, so its overall length will likely fluctuate greatly over the coming months or maybe even years. Beyond that, Keen Games has created a survival RPG that focuses way more on gameplay than storytelling, and it even supports multiplayer and co-op (although solo builds are very viable in
  <em>
   Enshrouded
  </em>
  ). As such, the goal is to simply exist within this world while gradually expanding the Shroud, so there is not much narrative driving things forward.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Enshrouded
  </em>
  is still a long way off completion and does not include much of an endgame at this point. Consequently, the current time is very much a loose estimate that will be very different once the game properly launches.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Fans Unhappy With Hatch Day Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-unhappy-hatch-day-event-magby-elekid/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Magby and Elekid Hatch Day event disappointed Pokemon GO players due to short duration and lack of Community Day moves.
     </li>
     <li>
      The event only ran for 3 hours, and players could only obtain 2km eggs with Magby or Elekid during that time.
     </li>
     <li>
      Absence of Community Day moves, Stardust bonuses behind a paid ticket, and technical issues left players wanting changes for future events.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon GO
   </strong>
  </em>
  players are unhappy with the recently concluded Magby and Elekid Hatch Day event due to an array of reasons, ranging from the duration of the event to the absence of Community Day moves. While the Hatch Day event brought back a couple of Pokemon that
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players were eager to add to their collection, it seems like certain aspects of the event have tarnished the hype around it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  had an exciting year filled with tons of new content, but the community has been disappointed with the past few events. In particular, the highly anticipated
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Holiday event frustrated fans a lot due to the absence of good spawns. As fans await what content the developers will add in the new year, it seems like some aren't happy about the Elekid and Magby Hatch Day event.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a new post on the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  subreddit, user Foulmouth232 expresses their frustration over the recently concluded Hatch Day event. The Charged Embers Hatch Day event in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , which was held on December 29, brought back two fan-favorite baby Pokemon, Elekid and Magby. Ideally, players would be eager to catch those Pokemon, but it seems that the event lasting for only three hours has disappointed a lot of fans. Not to forget, the absence of Community Day moves and such a small event having a paid ticket are some of the other aspects fans aren't happy about.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="penultimate-pokemon-go-event-of-the-year-disappoints-fans">
  Penultimate Pokemon GO Event of the Year Disappoints Fans
 </h2>
 <p>
  The Charged Embers Hatch Day event had a few bonuses that players could take advantage of for three days, but the actual event itself ran only between 2 pm to 5 pm local time on December 29. This means that players would only be able to get 2km
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  eggs with Magby or Elekid during this period. It should be noted that eggs obtained before the event did not count, even if they were hatched during the event.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-378752043" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-378752043" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-378752043" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-378752043" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-378752043-img" id="article-gallery-1-378752043">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-378752043" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1027698585">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On the other hand, things like Stardust bonuses in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  were locked behind a ticket, which made things even worse. Many stated that Magby was the only Pokemon missing in their Johto collection, and it being available for such a short duration prevented them from getting the egg. In fact, some noted that they weren't able to catch either of the Pokemon despite getting an egg during the event. Additionally, there were some other technical issues surrounding the event as well, with players seeing the wrong price of the ticket in certain regions. Fans are hoping that the developers will take note of their feedback and accordingly implement changes in such events going forward.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duke Dennis' Car Broken Into</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/duke-dennis-car-broken-into-theft/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      YouTube and Twitch star Duke Dennis had his Lamborghini Urus broken into, leading to the theft of his bag from inside.
     </li>
     <li>
      The incident sparked various reactions online, with some criticizing his security measures and others praising his composure.
     </li>
     <li>
      Duke Dennis' response to the theft, where he shared photos smiling beside the damaged car, has divided opinions on social media.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Popular
  <strong>
   YouTube
  </strong>
  and Twitch streamer Duke Dennis recently took to social media to share the unfortunate news that his custom Lamborghini Urus was broken into. According to YouTube personality Dennis, the incident involved someone smashing the luxury vehicle's window and stealing a bag from inside.
 </p>
 <p>
  On Twitch, content creator Duke Dennis is well-known for his Just Chatting streams and gaming broadcasts, where he frequently plays popular titles like
  <em>
   NBA 2K19
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   NBA 2K21
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  , earning him over 2.5 million followers on the platform. His influence is even more pronounced on YouTube, where his main channel has over 3 million subscribers, featuring a variety of gaming content, personal vlogs, and engaging commentary. Additionally, Duke Dennis often collaborates with top Twitch streamers, most notably Kai Cenat, appearing in his streams and contributing to his vibrant, high-energy broadcasts.
 </p>
 <p>
  Recently, Duke Dennis revealed that his Lamborghini Urus SUV had been broken into while he was out on a date. Upon returning to the vehicle, he discovered the front passenger-side window shattered and his bag stolen from inside. Adding to the growing list of incidents involving content creators and their vehicles, Duke addressed the situation in a video, expressing disbelief at how the thieves "got one over" on him. Despite the unfortunate circumstances, he maintained his composure and even shared photos on Twitter of himself smiling beside the damaged car. The post quickly went viral, amassing over 2.8 million views and sparking widespread discussion.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="duke-dennis-poses-beside-smashed-lamborghini-window">
  Duke Dennis Poses Beside Smashed Lamborghini Window
 </h2>
 <p>
  The incident sparked a wide range of reactions online. Some criticized his decision to leave valuables in the car, emphasizing security concerns, while others sympathized with him, condemning the audacity and jealousy behind the act. Many, however, focused on Duke’s composure, pointing out the luxury of being so wealthy that even having a Lamborghini broken into and losing valuables doesn’t seem to faze him. For some, his response served as inspiration, with one user commenting on their motivation to "grind harder" to achieve a similar level of success. The incident also recalls other alarming cases involving streamers, such as in 2023, when Twitch streamer Justfoxii revealed that a viewer had set her car on fire.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-383756443" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-383756443" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-383756443" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-383756443" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-383756443-img" id="article-gallery-1-383756443">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-383756443" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-899854305">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Similarly, in July, Twitch streamer Fanum encountered police during the Dominican Day parade in NYC, resulting in his Lamborghini being seized. Fanum alleged that officers appeared more interested in joyriding the luxury car than addressing any legitimate concern and also announced his intentions to sue the NYPD following the incident, which involved guns being drawn during his live stream.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
