<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tales of Graces f Remastered - Official Pascal Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/tales-of-graces-f-remastered-official-pascal-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Check out this official trailer for a look at the Tales of Graces f Remastered character Pascal. Tales of Graces f Remastered is set to release on January 17th, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Reveals a Free Skin, but There’s a Catch</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-free-thor-skin-season-1-midnight-features/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Marvel Rivals Season 1 offers fans a free Thor skin through the Midnight Features event.
     </li>
     <li>
      New content includes the Doom Match mode, Midtown and Sanctum Sanctorum maps, and a battle pass with 10 original skins.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can also earn a free Iron Man skin and purchase new bundles for Mister Fantastic and Invisible Woman in the shop.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has surprised fans by giving them a chance to earn a free skin for Thor during Season 1's event, Midnight Features. When Dracula traps Doctor Strange and launches an attack on New York City, The Fantastic Four spring into action to protect their world. This is the plot of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' new season. Gamers have been able to jump into the action since January 10, and the season will end on April 11.
 </p>
 <p>
  Season 1 of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  has launched with a wide variety of new content for fans to enjoy. The new mode, Doom Match, gives 8–12 players the chance to face off against one another in a free-for-all, with the top 50% of players claiming victory when the game ends. Fans also have the ability to explore the new Midtown and Sanctum Sanctorum maps in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  <em>
   .
  </em>
  In addition, NetEase Games has launched a brand-new battle pass with 10 original skins and a plethora of other cosmetics for people to collect. Mister Fantastic and Invisible Woman have also been added to the game's ever-expanding roster, with Human Torch and The Thing expected to arrive in a large mid-season update.
 </p>
 <p>
  With the newest season of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  now live, players have the opportunity to earn a new skin for Thor by completing the Midnight Features event. The new "Reborn from Ragnarok" cosmetic features one of the hero's classic winged helmet looks from the comics. Thor's navy chestpiece is punctuated by silver discs and a crimson cape as tight chainmail hugs his arms and legs. NetEase Games is also giving all players a chance to claim a free Iron Man skin in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  by redeeming a code found on the game's social media accounts.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-can-earn-a-free-thor-skin">
  Marvel Rivals Can Earn a Free Thor Skin
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-337476305" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-337476305" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-337476305" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-337476305" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-337476305-img" id="article-gallery-1-337476305">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-337476305" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-874736166">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gamers can earn Thor's skin by completing challenges associated with the Midnight Features event. As of writing, only the first chapter of quests is available, with the rest unlocking over the course of a week. Gamers should have access to all the quests and the new skin by January 17. With the launch of Season 1, players will also have the opportunity to earn a free Hela skin in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  through Twitch Drops.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition to free cosmetics, NetEase Games has added new skins for Mister Fantastic and Invisible Woman in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' shop. Each bundle can be purchased for 1,600 Units, which players can acquire by completing quests and achievements or by trading in Lattice, the game's premium currency. Players who purchase the battle pass will have the opportunity to earn 600 Units and 600 Lattice as they complete all of the pages. With so much new content to enjoy, many players are enthusiastic about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 28 Is Going to Be a Big Day for Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Fans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-warzone-season-2-release-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Treyarch confirms Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 and Warzone Season 2 begins on Tuesday, January 28.
     </li>
     <li>
      Season 1 will have lasted for 75 days by the time Season 2 is released, making it one of the longest seasons in Call of Duty history.
     </li>
     <li>
      Details on new content for Season 2 are still unknown, but Treyarch has previously teased more classic map remasters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </strong>
  </em>
  developer Treyarch Studios has confirmed that the game's second season will be released on Tuesday, January 28, which will also bring a plethora of new content to the free-to-play Battle Royale title,
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  . Season 1 of
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  kicked off on November 14 and will have lasted for a total of 75 days by the time Season 2 rolls around, making it one of the longest seasons in
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  history.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  was a massive success for developer Treyarch Studios and publisher Activision, bringing in the highest number of players in the first 30 days and making it the biggest
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  game to date, the shooter has taken a sharp decline in recent weeks. The sudden drop in players is speculated to be due to the ongoing cheating issue in the game's Ranked Play mode, as well as continued server problems. But with Season 2 now on the horizon, fans are hopeful that new content and plenty of improvements could bring
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  back to what it was at launch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="call-of-duty-black-ops-6-and-warzone-season-2-release-date-confirmed">
  Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 and Warzone Season 2 Release Date Confirmed
 </h2>
 <p>
  In the most recent update for
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , Treyarch Studios confirmed that Season 2 will be released on Tuesday, January 28. When addressing an issue with Zombies in the January 9 patch notes, Treyarch discussed some fixes that could not be implemented but would be released with the game's next season. The studio then confirmed that Season 2 launches on January 28. While details on what the new season will bring are still under wraps, a new blog post with a full reveal is expected to be released in the build-up to Season 2.
 </p>
 <p>
  Season 1 of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  brought with it a plethora of new multiplayer maps, modes, weapons, events, and much more. The massive content update also marked the beginning of a new era for
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  players, as the Battle Royale's integration with
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  meant there was a brand-new movement system, a plethora of new weapons, massive gameplay updates, and even a new Resurgence map known as Area-99.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-974591921" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-974591921" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-974591921" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-974591921" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-974591921-img" id="article-gallery-1-974591921">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-974591921" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-276073649">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  's first season also saw the return of some fan-favorite multiplayer maps, including Nuketown and Hacienda from
  <em>
   Black Ops 4
  </em>
  . While details on the game's next season are still unconfirmed, Treyarch has previously teased more classic map remasters for
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  . During an interview back in December, Treyarch's Associate Creative Director Miles Leslie said that no
  <em>
   Black Ops
  </em>
  map is off the table when it comes to remasters, but did note that the studio prioritizes original maps over remasters.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jujutsu Infinite: How To Enable Innate Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/jujutsu-infinite-how-to-enable-innate-abilities/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Unlock Innate Techniques In Jujutsu Infinite
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Enable Innate Techniques In Jujutsu Infinite
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Innate techniques
  </strong>
  are abilities that players can use to defeat enemies in Roblox’s
  <strong>
   <em>
    Jujutsu Infinite
   </em>
  </strong>
  . These techniques are powered by cursed energy and are categorized into Common, Uncommon, Rare, Legendary, and Special Grade rarities.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  You can choose only two innate techniques at any time. However, if you have the Premium Game Pass, you can unlock two additional slots, making for a total of four technique slots accessible during gameplay. For beginners, it can be challenging to figure out how to enable these abilities.
  <strong>
   This guide will show you how to use Innate Techniques in
   <em>
    Jujutsu Infinite
   </em>
   .
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Unlock Innate Techniques In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to unlock innate techniques in jujutsu infinite" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  First things first, you’ll need to unlock the innate abilities to use them. To do this, go to the
  <strong>
   Customize section
  </strong>
  and click on the Spin icon under the Innates tab. The game will randomly assign one of the 19 techniques to you. Then, repeat the process for the second slot as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  Just to quickly mention, players can change their innate techniques if they’re not happy with their equipped ones by spinning again until they get a higher-tier technique. However, you’ll need enough spins to test your luck, which you can get by daily missions, redeeming codes, AFK farming, and many more.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once your techniques are selected, you need to
  <strong>
   unlock their nodes
  </strong>
  in the game. Start by heading to the Stats icon at the top of your screen (or at the bottom left if you're on PC). From there, navigate to the Innates button in the bottom bar and click on the Mastery 1 icon next to the first technique. A mini note will appear with the description of the ability and an Unlock Node button. Simply click on it to access the ability. Then, do the same process for the second technique.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-enable-innate-techniques-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Enable Innate Techniques In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to enable innate techniques jujutsu infinite " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-unlock-innate-techniques-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After your innate techniques are unlocked, you can enable them in
  <em>
   Jujutsu Infinite
  </em>
  . Here's
  <strong>
   how to trigger your cursed abilities
  </strong>
  in the game:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Tap on the fist-like icon (also named Skills) near the Stats icon.
  </li>
  <li>
   Go to the Innates section, where you’ll see all available techniques in a pop-up window.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select one of the abilities and assign it to any empty box from the eight available slots (you can do this by simply tapping on any visible box).
  </li>
  <li>
   Then, repeat the process for the other techniques.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When everything is set, your innate techniques are ready to activate in-game. To use your innate techniques in
  <em>
   Jujutsu Infinite
  </em>
  , click on the shining blue light ball icon located at the middle and bottom of the screen. This will display the abilities. Simply select any one of them to apply in the game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight: What Every Junji Ito Survivor Skin is Based On</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/dead-by-daylight-every-junji-ito-survivor-skin-explained-tomie-terumi/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Horror has been a core part of Japanese folklore forever, and it's always had a strong influence on the world of Japanese entertainment. In the 1950s, horror became a particularly prominent genre in the manga space, and it only grew more popular in the following decades, leading to a boom in the 1980s that saw the origins of some of the most renowned manga artists and writers of the modern age. Junji Ito is one such manga artist and writer, and his work has just appeared in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dead by Daylight
   </strong>
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Writing primarily for the
  <em>
   Monthly Halloween
  </em>
  magazine, Junji Ito quickly made a name for himself, using his unique artistic talents to deliver some truly terrifying body and cosmic horror imagery. Junji Ito also produced an array of memorable horror protagonists along the way, a few of which can now be found in
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  as paid Survivor skins.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="every-dead-by-daylight-junji-ito-survivor-skin-explained">
  Every Dead by Daylight Junji Ito Survivor Skin Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-903390670" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-903390670" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-903390670" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-903390670" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-903390670-img" id="article-gallery-1-903390670">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-903390670" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-500486887">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="yui-kimura---tsukiko-rsquo-s-uniform-from-tomie-39-s-photos">
  Yui Kimura - Tsukiko’s Uniform from Tomie's Photos
 </h3>
 <p>
  The first of three Junji Ito-inspired Survivor skins now in
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  , Yui Kimura receives an alternate outfit based on Tsukiko Izumisawa, the primary protagonist of a handful of
  <em>
   Tomie
  </em>
  stories. By far Junji Ito's most renowned creation,
  <em>
   Tomie
  </em>
  is a three-part manga series that lasted over a decade that follows the titular young woman as she enchants men with her supernatural powers. Tomie is also able to create clones of herself and 'infect' other people, using her blood and organs to convert them into clones as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  Tsukiko Izumisawa first encounters Tomie Kawakami at school, taking a picture of her for a classmate. She deduces that there's more to Tomie than meets the eye and tries to shed more light on the mysterious, rich new student. Izumisawa manages to survive two nearly fatal encounters with Tomie.
 </p>
 <h3 id="yun-jin-lee---terumi-rsquo-s-fame-from-the-hanging-balloons">
  Yun-Jin Lee - Terumi’s Fame from The Hanging Balloons
 </h3>
 <p>
  The 6th chapter of volume 4 of the
  <em>
   Horror World of Junji Ito
  </em>
  collection,
  <em>
   The Hanging Balloons
  </em>
  sees a woman being haunted by a giant balloon that resembles the face of her celebrity friend who has just committed suicide. Soon, balloons start appearing throughout the town, each one resembling a citizen's face. Coming into contact with a balloon results in the person hanging to death from a metal noose.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  's Yun-Jin Lee Survivor gets a skin based on
  <em>
   The Hanging Balloons
  </em>
  , turning her into the passed celebrity, Terumi Fujino.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Junji Ito was originally attached to work alongside Hideo Kojima and Guillermo del Toro for the long-since-canceled
     <em>
      Silent Hills
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="kate-denson---puppet-rsquo-s-troubled-ballet-from-marionette-mansion">
  Kate Denson - Puppet’s Troubled Ballet from Marionette Mansion
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Marionette Mansion
  </em>
  (also known as
  <em>
   House of the Marionettes
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   House of Puppets
  </em>
  ) is the 7th chapter of the 10th volume of the
  <em>
   Horror World of Junji Ito
  </em>
  collection. This short story sees a family of puppeteers being manipulated by the very puppets they thought they were in control of, leading to some violent deaths.
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  's Kate Denson receives a
  <em>
   Marionette Mansion
  </em>
  -inspired costume in this latest collaboration, turning her into one of the story's life-sized ballet dancer puppets.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  x Junji Ito collection also adds five Killer outfits to the game, including one based on the aforementioned Tomie.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
