<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: How to Open the Vault in Nightshift Forest</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-how-open-vault-nightshift-forest-bushranger-npc/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Open the Vault in Nightshift Forest
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What Do You Give the Bushranger NPC?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  maps tend to have their fair share of secrets, so each season gamers have a reason to explore every nook and cranny of the island. When Chapter 6 Season 1 started, fans got an entirely different
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  map as per usual. While there are no boss vaults in Chapter 6 Season 1, there is a vault that gamers can open if they know exactly what to do.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This guide will show players how to open the Vault in Nightshift Forest. This is one of the best vaults to be on the
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  island to date, as it an impressive amount of loot, making it totally worth the effort of breaking in.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-open-the-vault-in-nightshift-forest">
  How to Open the Vault in Nightshift Forest
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-608140006" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-608140006" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-608140006" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-608140006" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-608140006-img" id="article-gallery-1-608140006">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-608140006" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-336053611">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There is a vault in Nightshift Forest. While in previous seasons players would've normally had to beat a boss to acquire a medallion and open its door, that is not the case in Chapter 6 Season 1.
  <strong>
   To open the secret vault in
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
   's Nightshift Forest, players must acquire the Solunar Key from the Bushranger NPC
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="solunar key item fortnite" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-key-item-fortnite.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   The Bushranger NPC can be found on the northwestern part of the Nightshift Forest
  </strong>
  , so thankfully, gamers won't have to go far to retrieve the vault key. When players talk to Bushranger in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , they have the option to "Show Item". If players show them the right item, they will give them the Solunar Key item, which gives them access to the vault room.
 </p>
 <h2 id="what-do-you-give-the-bushranger-npc">
  What Do You Give the Bushranger NPC?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-717191978" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-717191978" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-717191978" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-717191978" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-717191978-img" id="article-gallery-2-717191978">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-717191978" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1882973549">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bushranger doesn't clarify what type of item they want the player to show them. So, even if gamers show them the best items they have in their loadout, nothing will happen.
  <strong>
   To get the vault key from Bushranger in
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
   , players have to show them a Sprite
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Any Sprite will work for this quest, so as soon as players spot a Sprite nearby, they must approach it, select "Pick Up" and bring it back to Bushranger. Then, they will drop the Solunar Key as a reward for their efforts.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="solunar vault fortnite" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/solunar-vault-fortnite.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once players have the Solunar Key, they must put it in their inventory and run back to the center of the Nightshift Forest POI. Here, they will find the
  <strong>
   vault door west of the main temple's entrance
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Inside the Nightshift Forest vault, gamers will find at least four Rare Chests, two Elemental Chests, a Safe, and a Typhoon Blade Stand. On top of this, they will also find several ammo boxes, rare ammo boxes, Slurp Barrels, which ensures they will leave fully shielded as well as with tons of boons and high-rarity weapons.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Ancient Relic Grind is Not for the Faint of Heart</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/indiana-jones-great-circle-ancient-relic-collectibles-hard-grind-reward/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  If players want it to be,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
   </em>
  </strong>
  can quickly become far more about slow-burn exploration and collectible-hunting between Fieldwork, Discoveries, and Mysteries than a flurry of haymakers in a cinematic thrill ride. There’s a sumptuousness to
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  ’s side content that is easy to sink teeth into, and having such beautifully rendered and real-world settings to explore simultaneously roots it to
  <em>
   Indiana Jones
  </em>
  ’ indelible historical richness. That said, anyone seeking out every last collectible for a completion percentage should be made aware of what lies in store for them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  features Adventure Books, notes, artifacts, radio frequencies, steles, medicine bottles, and ancient relics to collect, and that’s all while players come across new Fieldwork, Discoveries, and Mysteries, sometimes by merely picking up whatever’s interactable in the environment. Relics in particular can be a nuisance to locate whether players have purchased brochures to reveal where they are on each map or not, and how worthwhile it is to painstakingly search for them all is debatable.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-rsquo-s-side-quests-contribute-to-the-bulk-of-story-content">
  Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Side Quests Contribute to the Bulk of Story Content
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-703097965" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-703097965" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-703097965" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-703097965" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-703097965-img" id="article-gallery-1-703097965">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-703097965" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-304876539">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Role-playing as Indiana Jones, MachineGames puts clever side quests in players’ paths and makes side content incentivizing based purely on how enticing it can be to explore each map. Players can easily get swept up in Fieldwork, Discoveries, and Mysteries that are more long-winded or elaborate than they may have presumed, with some even leading to significant cutscenes, character development, and story beats players wouldn’t experience otherwise.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Because players can purchase pamphlets revealing where every point of interest or collectible is on any map,
     <em>
      Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
     </em>
     guides players with a gentle hand and never nudges them forcefully, which is commendable as it allows players to explore if and when they wish to.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Players can also revisit previous locations whenever they’d like to, and that’s a huge boon as it doesn’t stress a time constraint on players who may wish to come back, perhaps once they’ve found more Adventure Books or ascertained each story-related item that players will need on their journey, such as the camera, lighter, and rebreather. However, players digging themselves into a rabbit hole for numbered collectibles is when exploration and backtracking can become tiresome, especially considering what’s waiting for them when they finally obtain every ancient relic in
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-rsquo-s-ancient-relics-are-for-true-completionists">
  Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Ancient Relics are for True Completionists
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1370398000" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1370398000" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1370398000" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1370398000" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1370398000-img" id="article-gallery-2-1370398000">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1370398000" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1085862790">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ancient relics are a nuisance as they’re undoubtedly the most bothersome collectibles to pursue in
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  . Not only are relics difficult to find even when Indy’s nose is buried in his waypoint-littered journal maps but they’re also spread out on maps in such a way that players should ideally be mindful of where one might be as they progress through the story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Indeed, story progression will lead to many relics and, unless players already purchased the required brochures and meticulously checked their map to see if one was nearby, players must return to these deep, labyrinthine tombs to reclaim them later on. Players can come across ancient relic puzzle doors in
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  that have them slot their acquired relics into holes and have adjacent pegs jut out, with all pegs jutting out unsealing the door and offering a single relic as an odd and seemingly disproportionate reward.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Similarly,
     <em>
      Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
     </em>
     ’s ‘The Serpent’s Chest’ Mystery has players search high and low between ancient ruins in the Vatican, Gizeh, and Shanghai, and when all three unique keys are collected and inserted into a snake-crested lockbox they are rewarded with one lowly relic.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  A seconds-long secret ending cutscene is locked behind this collectible hunt and a massive door with four slabs that players need to once more slot relics into to have each peg jut out. Of course, any and all extracurricular archaeology work players accomplish as Indy is fully of their own volition. That said, the reward for such determination in clearing maps of all associable collectibles is largely the inherent satisfaction players may earn for doing so, rather than any massively substantial or celebratory display for their efforts on
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  ’s part.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Prologue and Himalayas Make the Best Case for a Han Solo Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/indiana-jones-great-circle-prologue-himalayas-possible-han-solo-game/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  So long as players are steeped in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s hearty helping of exploration and collectible-hunting, the Vatican and Gizeh can slow to a crawl. Because these two regions have huge maps and are received back-to-back, it can be quite some time before
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  has another profoundly cinematic action sequence while players are busy with their noses in their maps as they attempt to hunt down relics, notes, medicine bottles, and Adventure Books. It isn’t until players are prepared to depart from Gizeh that the game truly takes a hard pivot and becomes a high-octane adrenaline rush.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_1">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     The Himalayas are perhaps as stark of a locale segue that the game could have taken after visiting Egypt, and it’s also a relief as it boasts a much smaller map to maneuver.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Here, players can simply bask in how superb
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  ’s graphical fidelity and performance are, especially with excellent snow tracking tech. Seeing Harrison Ford’s likeness as Indiana Jones wearing a parka and a fur-lined hat while trekking through mountainous snow in a brutal blizzard recalls the same imagery of Han Solo on Hoth in
  <em>
   The Empire Strikes Back
  </em>
  and, in tandem with the game’s
  <em>
   Raiders of the Lost Ark
  </em>
  prologue, no other stretch of gameplay makes a more compelling argument for a standalone Han Solo
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="a-han-solo-game-should-take-notes-from-indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-rsquo-s-prologue-and-himalayas">
  A Han Solo Game Should Take Notes from Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Prologue and Himalayas
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-403347350" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-403347350" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-403347350" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-403347350" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-403347350-img" id="article-gallery-1-403347350">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-403347350" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-98861915">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  was technically not the only game released in 2024 to wield Harrison Ford’s likeness as a carbonite-frozen Han Solo appears in
  <em>
   Star Wars Outlaws
  </em>
  . Still, while a standalone Han Solo game has always been somewhat of a no-brainer given how it could rely on a safety net of nostalgia and iconography, MachineGames’ reverence for
  <em>
   Indiana Jones
  </em>
  ’ source material and its depiction of Dr. Henry Jones Jr. demonstrates that the studio fully understands the character and has written him phenomenally for a game that can easily span upwards of 40–50 hours.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Moreover,
     <em>
      Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
     </em>
     boldly chooses to depict the opening of
     <em>
      Raiders of the Lost Ark
     </em>
     as a playable prologue that elevates the source material in MachineGames’ signature first-person perspective.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Much later in the game, Indy visits the Himalayas with Gina Lombardi and players who adore
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  will likely be reminded of when Han Solo searches Hoth’s gelid landscape for Luke Skywalker. It would be incredible to see a Han Solo game rendered with the same striking fidelity as
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  if one was ever in the works, and being able to experience
  <em>
   The Empire Strikes Back
  </em>
  ’s Hoth sequence in a playable prologue would be exceedingly nostalgic with players igniting Luke’s lightsaber in first-person and being prompted to slice open the belly of a tauntaun.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-a-han-solo-star-wars-game-could-adapt-indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-rsquo-s-disguises">
  How a Han Solo Star Wars Game Could Adapt Indiana Jones and the Great Circle’s Disguises
 </h3>
 <p>
  On paper, Indiana Jones is not an exhilarating character. He’s not an athlete or a gymnast, and yet he manages to scrape by in some bewilderingly daring circumstances via his fists and luck. If this was what MachineGames relied on wholly,
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  would’ve been a slog with slow climbing animations being the icing on a bland cake.
 </p>
 <p>
  That’s why
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  ’s disguise feature is remarkable—new disguises in each setting allow for greater immersion as Indy adapts to severe weather conditions while also allowing him to blend in with the environment and its fascist or Nazi occupations. A Han Solo game could have the tremendous advantage of piloting the Millennium Falcon in space-faring dogfights and pursuits, but otherwise it would rely on the same principles of gunplay (swapping Indy's revolver for Han's DL-44), melee combat, and simple traversal as Han Solo isn’t known for superhuman exploits either.
 </p>
 <p>
  A disguise system could work similarly brilliantly for Han Solo, where he could immersively don disguises such as a stormtrooper suit with an equipped E-11 blaster rifle. Likewise, it would be neat to see Han wear appropriate outfits for certain locales like the forest moon of Endor. The sky would be the limit with which planets and disguises Han might wear, not unlike
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46 Best Steam Deck Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/steam-deck-best-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Debuting in February 2022, Valve's
  <strong>
   Steam Deck
  </strong>
  has been around for a couple of years by this point. While hitting a few bumps along the road, the handheld system has generally been a resounding success and helped usher in a new era of portable PCs. Despite some competitors offering legitimate alternatives, the Steam Deck is still the most popular and definitive option for any PC gamer who wants to access their libraries on the go. Not every title is compatible with the platform, but the
  <strong>
   best games on Steam Deck
  </strong>
  are also some of the greatest projects of the last few years.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Currently, Valve is selling multiple tiers of the Steam Deck. There are three main models: 256GB LCD, 512GB OLED, and 1TB OLED. However, the 64GB and 512GB LCD versions can be purchased while their stocks last. Valve has even started selling refurbished Decks, although they are frequently out of stock. After picking up a console, players might wish to read a breakdown of the
  <strong>
   best Steam Deck Verified games
  </strong>
  . The selection is updated monthly.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_2">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Steam Decks can be purchased via Valve's store. Also, make sure to double-check a game's Steam profile to see if it is Verified for the Deck. Protondb is also a great resource for checking a game's Steam Deck performance.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on December 25, 2024, by Mark Sammut:
   </strong>
   Valve is constantly verifying games for the Steam Deck. While not every major release manages to get checkmarked, the device can run more than its fair share of big titles, with even Dragon Age: The Veilguard making the grade recently. Two more Steam Deck verified games have been added. Click below to jump to these new entries.
  </em>
 </p>
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Dragon Quest 3 HD-2D Remake
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Legacy of Kain Soul Reaver 1 + 2 Remastered
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="left-4-dead-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-539657145" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-539657145" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-539657145" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-539657145" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-539657145-img" id="article-gallery-1-539657145">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-539657145" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-294626116">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  OK,
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  is just a placeholder for every Deck Verified Valve game. There is a reason these titles continue to rank among Steam's most active titles; they are timeless. Outside purely multiplayer games like
  <em>
   Team Fortress 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Counter-Strike
  </em>
  , which are not Deck Verified,
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  is arguably Valve's most replayable game since there is never a bad time for a group of friends to get together and blast a few hundred zombies in the face. Many projects have tried to replicate the
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead
  </em>
  formula, but none have come close to matching the excellence of Valve's second entry in the series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Elden Ring
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-92">
  Steam User Rating: 92%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-357380886" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-357380886" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-357380886" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-357380886" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-357380886-img" id="article-gallery-2-357380886">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-357380886" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1538574875">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Released very close to the Steam Deck's debut,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  was something of a test of the portable system's potential. Could Valve's platform handle a massive open-world game? Thankfully, the answer was yes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Among the best games of 2022,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  implements the
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  formula into a sandbox environment that generally allows players to go wherever they please. The Lands Between is stuffed with content, both compulsory and optional, and the base game can readily keep a player engaged for 100+ hours. Build variety, epic boss fights, PvP, and lore depth are just a couple of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  's strengths, and they are just the tip of the iceberg.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_18">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Shadow of the Erdtree
     </em>
     is now available.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1049438392" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1049438392" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1049438392" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1049438392" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1049438392-img" id="article-gallery-3-1049438392">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1049438392" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1063528643">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Considering
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3's
  </em>
  full debut attracted a peak Steam player count of more than 800,000 users, it is safe to say that the game's stint in early access paid off. Due to the success of its
  <em>
   Divinity
  </em>
  series, Larian Studios is nowadays well-established as perhaps the greatest modern developer specializing in the tactical RPG genre, making the company the perfect pick to revisit one of the most decorated IPs in gaming history. Putting aside the spin-offs,
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate's
  </em>
  main projects are synonymous with excellence, so any new entry would be automatically compared to some of the best RPGs of all time. In the future, games in the genre will be compared to
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , which has set the bar so high that it might be the standard-bearer for decades.
 </p>
 <p>
  Larian has crafted a dense RPG filled with humor, drama, and player-driven choices. Right out of the gate, the game hits a home run with its character creator, which not only offers impressive depth but also influences the gameplay and world. The party-based combat system is fairly slow-paced since it focuses on planning and strategy over action or reflexes, and battles can get brutal quickly. Anyone familiar with grid-based tactical RPGs should feel at home, but newcomers to the genre might need a few hours to adapt to its rhythm.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fields-of-mistria">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Fields Of Mistria
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1501302367" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1501302367" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1501302367" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1501302367" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1501302367-img" id="article-gallery-4-1501302367">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1501302367" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1671728768">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Farming sims are so common nowadays that they tend to blend into each other, forming a blob of similar mechanics and aesthetics. In most ways,
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  is a fairly traditional entry that mostly delivers what is expected of these types of projects; however, it adds just enough unique elements to feel like a fresh revamp rather than just a competent retread. While it probably will not hit the mark with people who historically have not been able to get into the genre, the game is a must-play for anyone who is remotely a fan of these releases, particularly if they are fond of retro visuals from the GBA era.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite being in early access,
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  is surprisingly polished in its current state, to the point that it can be recommended as a robust option despite not currently being complete. Although not shallow, the game mostly opts for streamlined mechanics, creating a relaxing experience that requires constant thought but should rarely inspire frustration. As far as cozy farming sims are concerned,
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  is a new top contender on Steam.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_31">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     While not a massive part of the package,
     <em>
      Fields of Mistria
     </em>
     's mines contain combat.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hades">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Hades
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1686531698" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1686531698" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1686531698" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1686531698" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1686531698-img" id="article-gallery-5-1686531698">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1686531698" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1063957037">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Roguelikes and roguelites have exploded in popularity over the last decade, developing into one of the most popular genres in gaming, particularly the indie scene. While far from the first of its type,
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  is undeniably among the most successful roguelites of all time, primarily thanks to its addictive combat and clever blend of story and gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  Dying and starting from scratch is central to roguelites, but
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  shakes things up by justifying this mechanic through its narrative (which involves the son of Hades repeatedly trying to escape hell). Regardless of whether someone is a roguelike/lite veteran or new to the genre, they should check out Supergiant's 2020 masterpiece.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_38">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Hades 2
     </em>
     is also Verified for the Steam Deck, but it is still in early access.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="shin-megami-tensei-5-vengeance">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Shin Megami Tensei 5: Vengeance
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-95">
  Steam User Rating: 95%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1508683312" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1508683312" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1508683312" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1508683312" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1508683312-img" id="article-gallery-6-1508683312">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1508683312" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1612571072">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Initially a Switch exclusive,
  <em>
   Shin Megami Tensei 5
  </em>
  is now available on all platforms, including the Steam Deck.
  <em>
   Vengeance
  </em>
  is, essentially, the definitive version of
  <em>
   SMT5
  </em>
  , delivering the original campaign alongside a brand-new alternative route that changes the story's back half considerably, which was one of the original iteration's main criticisms.
  <em>
   Vengeance
  </em>
  elevates what was already a fantastic and long JRPG, arguably delivering an even more complete upgrade than
  <em>
   Persona 5 Royal
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  As the series is not exactly known for PC releases,
  <em>
   SMT 5: Vengeance
  </em>
  might be a lot of people's first foray into Atlus' mainline series. While the battle system is somewhat similar to
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   SMT
  </em>
  is far harder and way more prominent. In fact, combat and the mechanics surrounding it are the main focus of the game, with the story and characters taking a backseat.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kingdom-hearts--hd-1-5-2-5-remix">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Kingdom Hearts -HD 1.5+2.5 ReMIX-
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-70">
  Steam User Rating: 70%
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Donald and Goofy greet Sora as he returns to Destiny Islands in Kingdom Hearts 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/donald-and-goofy-greet-sora-as-he-returns-to-destiny-islands.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Steam users had to wait an absurdly long time to get their hands on Square Enix's
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  , but the franchise is finally available in its entirety on the platform. Newcomers looking to get into the series should pick up
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts -HD 1.5+2.5 ReMIX-
  </em>
  , a bang-for-your-buck compilation that features four full games along with two cutscene movies.
 </p>
 <p>
  That is a lot of content, especially since each
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  campaign will take comfortably 20+ hours to complete. And, except for
  <em>
   Re:Chain of Memories
  </em>
  , the games hold up great. The original
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  is both the simplest and hardest entry in the series, and it tells a straightforward story that is very charming.
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts 2
  </em>
  is generally regarded as the franchise's peak due to its brilliant combat, great selection of Disney worlds, and lore expansion.
  <em>
   Birth by Sleep
  </em>
  has the best gameplay, and that includes
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_52">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Kingdom Hearts -HD 1.5+2.5 ReMIX-
     </em>
     has a mixed reputation on Steam due to the game crashing on certain AMD graphic cards. This might be fixed in the future, but this comment is based on the launch version. It works fine on Steam Deck, but this point is still worth mentioning since some people might be planning to buy the package on multiple devices.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="dave-the-diver">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Dave The Diver
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-158390281" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-158390281" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-158390281" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-158390281" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-158390281-img" id="article-gallery-7-158390281">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-158390281" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1591547122">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Great sushi requires a lot of hard work.
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  is a sim about running a restaurant. Also,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  is an exploration game revolving around an ever-changing underwater paradise that is home to quite a few majestic and massive creatures. Basically,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  wears a lot of hats, and they nearly all fit like a glove.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mintrocket's project strikes a fun balance between open-ended dives into known but uncharted waters and a satisfying management game. Although they do not share all that much in common, these mechanics are complementary, with one side directly feeding into the other.
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  combines great gameplay with gorgeous visuals, a charming sense of humor, and a story that has more depth than meets the eye.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-planet-crafter">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   The Planet Crafter
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1922951358" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1922951358" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1922951358" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1922951358" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1922951358-img" id="article-gallery-8-1922951358">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1922951358" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1616613048">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In 2021, Miju Games released a free prologue for
  <em>
   The Planet Crafter
  </em>
  , granting players interested in the survival genre an opportunity to test out the upcoming project. While it took more than a year to materialize, the full game launched in April 2024, landing to a generally positive reception. Even though they are gradually becoming more commonplace, survival open-world games are still niche, and
  <em>
   The Planet Crafter
  </em>
  is a fairly small release in the grand scheme of things. However, Migu built a game that knows exactly what it wants to be and shows enough ambition without pushing itself too far.
 </p>
 <p>
  Dropped onto an inhospitable planet and tasked with terraforming it into a potential home for humans,
  <em>
   The Planet Crafter
  </em>
  delivers an addictive sense of progression as players gradually transform a deserted wasteland into a lively and vibrant paradise. Even during the early hours when the focus is primarily on meeting the protagonist's physical needs and building a basic base, players should still feel like they are constantly working towards a tangible goal, creating a satisfying loop.
 </p>
 <h2 id="like-a-dragon-infinite-wealth">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Like A Dragon: Infinite Wealth
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-91">
  Steam User Rating: 91%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-427372050" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-427372050" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-427372050" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-427372050" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-427372050-img" id="article-gallery-9-427372050">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-427372050" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1192369803">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sega's
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  /
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  franchise is widely compatible with the Steam Deck, with most of the entries being verified. The license's commitment to Valve's handheld was once again made evident when
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  ran well on the Deck at launch. By far the biggest (and longest) entry in the series, the 8th mainline entry is a tour-de-force that delivers quantity and quality. While the project garnered some criticism due to its DLC practices, there is no denying that the actual content is top-notch. Once again, Ichiban takes center stage as the protagonist, although this time he is accompanied by the returning Kazuma; more importantly, the story leaves Japan and heads to Hawaii, a change that makes the whole experience feel incredibly fresh.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if someone focuses solely on the game's main campaign, they are looking at about 50+ hours of gameplay, and that scenario is unlikely to transpire due to
  <em>
   Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  's fantastic substories and mini-games. The turn-based combat is not too far removed from
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  's system, but it is fine-tuned to create a more enjoyable and satisfying package. The same can be said for the Jobs systems, which adds plenty of build variety and customization options.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="balatro">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Balatro
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-958276774" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-958276774" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-958276774" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-958276774" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-958276774-img" id="article-gallery-10-958276774">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-958276774" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-443203814">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Roguelikes are a dime-a-dozen, and deck-builders are not rare either. Consequently, a project that falls into both categories needs to be something special if it wants to stand out from a crowd that has produced plenty of great releases over the decades.
  <em>
   Balatro
  </em>
  deserves to sit alongside the likes of
  <em>
   Slay the Spire
  </em>
  as an example of a roguelike deck-builder done to absolute perfection. Inspired by
  <em>
   Poker
  </em>
  , LocalThunk's game presents a fantastic and accessible twist on the casino classic, delivering an experience that is immediately satisfying while also offering a gratifying sense of progression.
 </p>
 <p>
  Split into Blinds and Antes, players must put together a round-winning hand, which generally means achieving one of
  <em>
   Poker
  </em>
  's standard lineups. The core gameplay is straightforward, but it is complemented by a plethora of special cards that enhance a player's hand. Whether talking about Jokers or Tarots, these cards significantly open up the possibilities, allowing for a massive array of potential loadouts. They transform would could have been a fun but short-lived game into something that is very replayable.
 </p>
 <h2 id="animal-well">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Animal Well
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1668793257" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1668793257" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1668793257" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1668793257" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1668793257-img" id="article-gallery-11-1668793257">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1668793257" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1950135793">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Steam Deck's key selling point is that it allows AAA games like
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  to be played on the go. That is something that classic handheld consoles were never able to offer, and even the Switch is fairly limited in what projects it can run. However, as exciting as holding
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  in your hands is, the Steam Deck is arguably even better as a platform for playing smaller-scale indie adventures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Garnering near-universal praise,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  is a Metroidvania with an eye-catching presentation and brain-teasing puzzles that generally fall on the side of difficult but satisfying rather than just frustrating. Focusing on platforming rather than combat, Shared Memory's project builds an incredible atmosphere through its surreal pixel art, lending an otherworldly tone to the campaign. Be it during boss fights or just in standard rooms, the puzzles make frequent clever use of enemies, switches, and items.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hi-fi-rush">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1715769086" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1715769086" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1715769086" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1715769086" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1715769086-img" id="article-gallery-12-1715769086">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1715769086" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1986273435">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  came out of nowhere. Tango Gameworks' game was announced and released on the same day, and it is even available on Xbox Game Pass. As an added bonus, the hack and slash title is already Steam Deck verified, so owners of the handheld system can immediately jump into this project.
 </p>
 <p>
  Boasting striking visual design and a stellar soundtrack,
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  is a feast for the senses. Ultimately, high production value does not mean that much if the gameplay is not up-to-snuff, which is something that Tango clearly understands.
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  rewards players who sync their movement to the beat, and this goes beyond providing a power boost in combat. Even exploration benefits from this synergy.
 </p>
 <h2 id="persona-3-reload">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1794163619" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1794163619" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1794163619" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1794163619" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1794163619-img" id="article-gallery-13-1794163619">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1794163619" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-631516333">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the same cannot be said for every spin-off, all mainline
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  games on Steam are Deck Verified. Consequently, JRPG fans can pick from
  <em>
   Persona 3 Portable
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Persona 4 Golden
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Persona 5 Royal
  </em>
  , and the recently released
  <em>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </em>
  , all of which are brilliant projects in their own right. Now, everyone is likely to have a personal favorite, and many are likely to argue that
  <em>
   P5R
  </em>
  is the franchise's peak; however,
  <em>
   P3R
  </em>
  rejuvenates arguably the strongest story in Atlus' series by giving it a makeover reminiscent of its successors.
 </p>
 <p>
  Telling a dark and mature story,
  <em>
   Persona 3
  </em>
  was groundbreaking in 2006 since it introduced the social sim elements that would come to define the license moving forward. Although still enjoyable, the original title and its PSP version show their ages, and they needed and deserved an ambitious remake that caters to a modern audience.
  <em>
   P3R
  </em>
  is that game, and it is nothing short of a masterpiece.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cuphead">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Cuphead
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1029343839" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1029343839" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1029343839" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1029343839" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1029343839-img" id="article-gallery-14-1029343839">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1029343839" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-363110802">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Inspired by classic cartoons,
  <em>
   Cuphead
  </em>
  has gorgeous visuals, tight controls, and many brilliantly designed bosses who yearn to make players suffer. The
  <strong>
   best Steam Deck games
  </strong>
  might be the ones that cater to shorter play sessions, and
  <em>
   Cuphead
  </em>
  is one such title.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, while the levels themselves are not extremely long, their high difficulty greatly expands their completion time, so they do require commitment. Also, try to resist the urge to fling the Steam Deck out of a window out of sheer frustration.
 </p>
 <h2 id="neon-white">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Neon White
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-2104080207" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-2104080207" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-2104080207" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-2104080207" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-2104080207-img" id="article-gallery-15-2104080207">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-2104080207" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-940694217">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A pleasant surprise,
  <em>
   Neon White
  </em>
  is specifically designed for speedrunning. The goal is to repeat stages in search of progressively quicker times, and while that might seem like a niche structure, the game's strong fundamentals give it wide appeal.
  <em>
   Neon White
  </em>
  builds its platforming and combat on a card-based system that forces the player to think on their feet, and executing a perfect run after memorizing the stage's layout is incredibly satisfying.
 </p>
 <p>
  As stages do not last more than a few minutes, this is the perfect Steam Deck game for short bus rides or quick breaks. Admittedly,
  <em>
   Neon White
  </em>
  's addictive nature makes it difficult to put down once someone finds their rhythm, which might lead to some missed meetings.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-7-remake-intergrade">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Intergrade
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-89">
  Steam User Rating: 89%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1294216205" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1294216205" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1294216205" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1294216205" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1294216205-img" id="article-gallery-16-1294216205">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1294216205" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-368839038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  is currently a PS5 exclusive, PC players will have to settle for its predecessor.
  <em>
   FF7 Remake
  </em>
  got the ball rolling in Square Enix's modern revamp of its most iconic story, telling the first chapter in a trilogy that looks set to recontextualize, expand, and honor its 1997 ancestor. The
  <em>
   Intergrade
  </em>
  version contains the base game and the Intermission DLC that shines a spotlight on Yuffie, a beloved character who is a strong addition to the core cast.
 </p>
 <p>
  Along with a major graphical upgrade,
  <em>
   FF7 Remake
  </em>
  utilizes a real-time combat system that also implements turn-based elements, finding a middle ground that works surprisingly well. With great action, beautiful visuals, and a strong story, this action JRPG is comfortably among the franchise's best efforts in a long time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-wild-hunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-266681013" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-266681013" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-266681013" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-266681013" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-266681013-img" id="article-gallery-17-266681013">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-266681013" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-1430796637">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Valve worked with CD Projekt Red to optimize
  <em>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  for the Steam Deck, ensuring that owners can take these ambitious RPGs on the go and have a blast in the process.
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  set a benchmark for gaming in general, particularly when it comes to storytelling in side content.
 </p>
 <p>
  Set in a beautifully crafted world that builds upon the lore of previous franchise releases while still delivering an accessible package for newcomers,
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  is gripping, deep, and addictive. The combat system takes a bit of getting used to, but things do start to come together once the player grows familiar with Geralt's signs and tools.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="stardew-valley">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Stardew Valley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1199052087" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1199052087" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1199052087" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1199052087" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1199052087-img" id="article-gallery-18-1199052087">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1199052087" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-650903674">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Steam's library is flushed with indie games that exploded in popularity, growing into cultural phenomenons along the way. Even among this elite group of success stories,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  exists in its own tier.
 </p>
 <p>
  A farming sim with RPG elements, Concerned Ape's game frees players to manage their land, all the while providing them with plenty of other activities they can interact with. The campaign is not directionless either and tries to ensure there is always something on the horizon that players can look forward to. Charming, ambitious, and addictive,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  is reaching the point when it can be called timeless.
 </p>
 <h2 id="against-the-storm">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Against The Storm
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-95">
  Steam User Rating: 95%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1457124654" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1457124654" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1457124654" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1457124654" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1457124654-img" id="article-gallery-19-1457124654">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1457124654" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-318034939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After spending more than a year in early access,
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  made its full debut in December 2023, earning a spot among Steam's best modern city builders. While popular, the genre has a reputation for being time-consuming and inaccessible to newcomers, especially for its classic releases. Although not sacrificing depth,
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  strives to remove a lot of the grind associated with the genre, prioritizing self-contained efforts rather than an endless campaign that can potentially stretch to hundreds of hours. Players are tasked by the queen to establish a settlement, with the goal being to simply satisfy the needs of the populace while keeping the ruler happy. Both elements are easier said than done, and if the queen's patience runs out, the playthrough is over. Conversely, if the settlement is a success, then players triumph.
 </p>
 <p>
  This simple concept lends itself well to bite-sized sessions that can run through a beginning, middle, and end in the span of a few hours. Progression comes in the form of permanent upgrades that are maintained from settlement to settlement, adding an almost roguelite element to the gameplay.
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  focuses on randomization quite a bit, and while this might sound frustrating on paper, it results in a highly replayable package that rewards flexibility and creative thinking. City builders are known to have dense UIs that are not necessarily great fits for a portable system like a Steam Deck, but this 2023 release works fine on the hardware (although players might need to tweak a few settings).
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Leak Reveals Human Torch’s Ability Kit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-human-torch-ability-kit-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Human Torch's ability kit reveals ranged attacks and fiery walls, as well as a possible team-up with Storm.
     </li>
     <li>
      Leaks hint at upcoming characters like The Thing, Mister Fantastic, and fresh cosmetics.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  leaker has revealed the ability kit for Human Torch, a new Duelist hero possibly coming to the game. NetEase Games recently shared that 20 million fans have played
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  since its launch, which is a big milestone for the newly released hero shooter. The Twitter account for
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  also announced that the game's Discord has reached two million users.
 </p>
 <p>
  NetEase Games has debuted its first major event, Winter Celebration, by giving all
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  players a free skin bundle for Jeff the Land Shark. In order to claim the bundle, fans will need to earn Gold Frost and Silver Frost by completing challenges in the festive game mode. As players finish tasks, they will be rewarded with items from the bundle one by one, with the final cosmetic being Jeff's Cuddly Fuzzlefin skin.
 </p>
 <p>
  RivalsLeaks posted the ability kit for Human Torch on Twitter, giving fans their first glimpse at the hero's potential move set within the game. It appears as if the character will be a ranged Duelist, with his primary ability allowing players to shoot fireballs at enemies. Gamers will also be able to create flame fields on the map, which can later be connected to form fiery walls or triggered to ignite fire tornadoes. It also seems as if Human Torch will have a team-up with Storm, allowing the duo to imbue one another's abilities with fiery tornadoes and hurricanes. RivalsLeaks also posted the ability kit for Ultron within
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , suggesting the villain will be a Strategist.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="human-torch-may-be-a-duelist-in-marvel-rivals">
  Human Torch May Be a Duelist in Marvel Rivals
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2038987324" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2038987324" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2038987324" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2038987324" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2038987324-img" id="article-gallery-1-2038987324">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2038987324" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2002626248">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Recent leaks have also suggested popular characters like The Thing, Mister Fantastic, Captain Marvel, and Blade could be coming to the game in the near future. According to leakers, The Thing will be a Vanguard within
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , making him a very valuable addition to the roster of heroes and villains. Many players have been clamoring for more Vanguards and Strategists, as the game currently has more Duelists than any other role.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition to new characters, some leakers have been busy digging through the game's files for fresh cosmetics, showing off new
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  skins for Venom, Squirrel Girl, Moon Knight, Doctor Strange, and more. The Venom skin appears to be inspired by the character Agent Venom in the comics, which was a version of the symbiote hero that featured Flash Thompson as the host. While many fans were happy about the style of the new skin, some were upset that Agent Venom might not be a fully fledged Duelist within the game. While many players have taken the skin as a sign Agent Venom will only appear as a cosmetic, there's no telling what the future may hold for the hero shooter.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
