<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man FAIL Compilation!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/spider-man-fail-compilation/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A special episode of Spider-Man clips are featured.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic: The Gathering's Yoni Skolnik Discusses Connection Between Aetherdrift and Thunder Junction</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/magic-the-gathering-aetherdrift-outlaws-thunder-junction-saddle-mounts/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Aetherdrift and Outlaws of Thunder Junction are connected, with the former influencing mechanics like Saddle and Mounts.
     </li>
     <li>
      Aetherdrift's focus on vehicles applies thematically to specific factions, but not the Alacrian Quickbeasts.
     </li>
     <li>
      Aetherdrift's Saddle and Mount mechanics were created before Outlaws of Thunder Junction.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are four other Standard-legal sets coming out in 2025, but
  <strong>
   <em>
    Magic: The Gathering
   </em>
  </strong>
  kicked the year off on a high note thanks to Innistrad Remastered in January and Aetherdrift one month ago. While Aetherdrift is a major shift from the typical aesthetics and themes of most
  <em>
   MTG
  </em>
  sets, it does nail the multiplanar death race fantasy on its head with its collection of cards, including the various racing teams and their vehicles. Aetherdrift's vehicles in
  <em>
   MTG
  </em>
  faced a few challenges due to the card type not being quite successful among fans in the past, but not all fans may know that the first Standard-legal set of the year is in a way a "predecessor" to Outlaws of Thunder Junction.
 </p>
 <p>
  During an interview with Wizards of the Coast Principal Designer and Aetherdrift's Lead Designer Yoni Skolnik, Game Rant learned that despite Outlaws of Thunder Junction's release being in April of 2024, it actually owes one of its main mechanics to Aetherdrift.
  <em>
   Magic: The Gathering
  </em>
  's Western-themed set had several interesting mechanics when it came out, including Plot, Commit Crimes, the Bounties Commander minigame, and then the combination of Saddle and Mounts, making for a very appropriate addition. However, Saddle and Mounts were first designed and ideated for Aetherdrift, rather than Outlaws of Thunder Junction.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="magic-the-gathering-39-s-mounts-and-saddle-didn-39-t-truly-come-with-outlaws-of-thunder-junction">
  Magic: The Gathering's Mounts and Saddle Didn't Truly Come With Outlaws of Thunder Junction
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2037001615" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2037001615" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2037001615" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2037001615" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2037001615-img" id="article-gallery-1-2037001615">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2037001615" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1782572016">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's not too rare for tabletop games, TCGs, and video games alike to release an update or new expansion that includes mechanics that were originally conceived when developing a later piece of content for that game. In the case of
  <em>
   Magic: The Gathering
  </em>
  's Aetherdrift set, Skolnik confirmed that they had already prepared the Saddle and Mount combination for the death race expansion ahead of time, which made it possible for Outlaws of Thunder Junction to "steal" it despite its release being 10 months prior to that of Aetherdrift.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is an interesting piece of knowledge, as Aetherdrift's focus on vehicles can only apply to factions (teams, in this case) for which it makes sense thematically and from a setting and lore point of view. That's why Mounts were a perfect fit for the Alacrian Quickbeasts, a Selesnya - Green and White - team that uses the titular Quickbeasts to move quickly on the tracks of the Ghirapur Grand Prix. The leader of the Alacrian Quickbeasts is Caradora, who rides a mighty Quickbeast called Lagorin, exemplifying the use of Saddle and Mount Creatures in terms of
  <em>
   Magic: The Gathering
  </em>
  mechanics.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-mounts-and-saddle-compare-to-vehicles-and-crew-in-mtg">
  How Mounts and Saddle Compare to Vehicles and Crew in MTG
 </h3>
 <p>
  With 13 Mount Creatures, of which four are Green, six are White, two are Red, and one is Green and White, Aetherdrift has fewer than Outlaws of Thunder Junction, which instead features a total of 17. This makes sense considering the themes of both sets, particularly when considering Aetherdrift has the highest number of vehicles in
  <em>
   Magic: The Gathering
  </em>
  expansions to date. Skolnik mentioned that vehicles like Aetherdrift's Hulldrifter in
  <em>
   MTG
  </em>
  were meant to make the card type more interesting and varied, and in a way, Mounts can be considered vehicles - just living ones, hence why they are not Artifacts.
 </p>
 <p>
  Furthermore, Saddle and Crew have similar rules when it comes to Mounts and vehicles. Saddle can be activated by tapping Creatures one controls with power equal to or greater than the Saddle value on a given Mount, activating the corresponding effect on the card. On the other hand, vehicles require players to Crew them for a given amount of power or greater to turn them into Creatures. As such, it's interesting to see Outlaws of Thunder Junction's Western world become enriched in terms of mechanics by a multiplanar death race set like Aetherdrift.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPO: How To Fix Client Timeout</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/repo-client-timeout-issue-how-fix-troubleshoot/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       REPO Client Timeout Error Explained
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Fix Client Timeout In REPO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one of the representatives of the cooperative survival horror genre in the
  <em>
   Lethal Company
  </em>
  style. And, like other similar games, it has some bugs on release, especially considering that it is in early access.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Many players have reported a bug that prevents them from starting a game with teammates. Instead of booting into the game, they get a Client Timeout error, which, fortunately, can be fixed in several ways. This guide will detail a number of fixes for the Client Timeout issue in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="repo-client-timeout-error-explained">
  REPO Client Timeout Error Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO character" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It is not surprising that a game in early access has bugs and errors, but the Client Timeout error is critical because it completely deprives you of the gaming experience. Often, it is caused by errors in the app, a
  <strong>
   poor network connection
  </strong>
  , damaged game files, or outdated graphics drivers. So, to fix the Client Timeout error in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  , you need to check each of these options.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-fix-client-timeout-in-repo">
  How To Fix Client Timeout In REPO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO character" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fix-client-timeout-repo-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   First of all, you should
   <strong>
    check your network connection
   </strong>
   since
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   strongly recommends creating a lobby only for those players who have the best internet. To do this, you can use third-party apps or simply launch other online games.
  </li>
  <li>
   Your next step is a good old
   <strong>
    restart of your device
   </strong>
   . In many cases, this step fixes the Client Timeout error in
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   .
  </li>
  <li>
   After that, you should check the
   <strong>
    integrity of the game files
   </strong>
   . To do this, just open Steam and find
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   there. Next, right-click and select Properties. Then, go to the Downloaded Files tab. There, you can check the integrity of the game files and reinstall them if some are corrupted.
  </li>
  <li>
   If none of this helped to fix the Client Timeout error in
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   , then you should
   <strong>
    check your graphics drivers
   </strong>
   . It's always best to use the official apps of your graphics card manufacturers for this.
  </li>
  <li>
   And last but not least, try to
   <strong>
    launch
    <em>
     REPO
    </em>
    as an administrator
   </strong>
   . To do this, you must find the REPO.exe file. By default, it is located in the drive\steam\steamapps\common\REPO directory. Then, right-click on the file and select Run as administrator.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     If launching
     <em>
      REPO
     </em>
     as administrator helps you fix the Client Timeout error in
     <em>
      REPO
     </em>
     , then you can set this option permanently. All you need to do is right-click on the launcher and go to Properties. Then, in the
     <strong>
      Compatibility tab
     </strong>
     , select the option to always run the program as an administrator.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Fans Suggest Change to Wood Storage</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-wood-storage-house-lumber-pile/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players propose using the decorative wood pile by the front door as actual storage, finding it more practical.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans like the idea, particularly for wood storage next to the front door, making it easier to access and store ingredients.
     </li>
     <li>
      Possible drawbacks include accessibility issues in multiplayer mode, but some players are eager for potential changes despite concerns.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  players are discussing the way that storing wood in the game works, and have made a suggestion as to how it could be changed. The idea would make a fair amount of sense, and would utilize something that already exists in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , storage and item management can quickly become a big deal. Players start out with very limited storage space, and even after upgrading a backpack in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , there may not be enough to work with. Adding storage chests to the farm is one way to keep more supplies, but players are now suggesting an idea on how storing wood could be improved.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user BroVival has pointed out that it would be a nice addition if the wood a player needed to store could be kept in the wood pile by the front door of their house. The wood pile in its current state is decorative, with only one particular item being picked up from it, and only after players have finished a series of quests for Mr. Qi. BroVival thinks that using the pile as an actual wood inventory would be helpful, and a number of players have agreed with them. They also recommended that the pile could change appearance based upon what kind of wood is stored there.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-fans-like-wood-storage-idea">
  Stardew Valley Fans Like Wood Storage Idea
 </h2>
 <p>
  Players have said that they like the idea of being able to access their wood stores next to their front door. Considering the amount of wood needed in the game for certain crafts or upgrading buildings, it could be helpful to have dedicated storage just for those ingredients. Some have also added on to BroVival's original idea, suggesting that having dedicated storage for stones and wood would be nice, especially if Robin could directly access it when a
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  player requests a building upgrade or new construction. In its current state, players have to grab the supplies and bring them to her when making the request. Some have lamented that it's easy to forget to bring the materials, and by the time they return with them, she's often left for the day.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1824598779" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1824598779" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1824598779" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1824598779" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1824598779-img" id="article-gallery-1-1824598779">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1824598779" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-722394006">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On the other hand, there could be some potential pitfalls to this idea. The player's porch is only accessible from the stairs. Having wood stored there when playing in multiplayer mode could make matters frustrating if a player is blocked from accessing the wood or leaving the porch, depending on a second farmer's position. In theory, the developer could make the wood pile accessible from the side of the house as well, which would potentially prevent this problem. However, it remains to be seen if any real changes are made to the wood pile. Some players in the comments are eager for ConcernedApe to be able to move on to his next game,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  , rather than continuing to make small changes to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Announces Fuzzy Buddy Research Day</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-fuzzy-buddy-research-day-featured-pokemon/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO Research Day on March 29 features Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful with shiny chances.
     </li>
     <li>
      Thye event includes themed Field Research tasks with wild spawns of other critters, plus a $2 Paid Timed Research option.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fuzzy Buddy Research Day also aligns with Pokemon GO City Safari in select cities.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has announced a Research Day featuring Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful. The event will take place on March 29 and will be a chance for
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players to add to their collections the adorable quartet of bear Pokemon and other critters available through wild spawns.
 </p>
 <p>
  Research Day is one of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  's recurring events that usually features exclusive Field Research tasks for players to complete, increasing their chances of finding these shiny variant critters. The first
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Research Day took place in 2019 and featured Feebas. Since then, it has happened another 20 times, most recently in December last year, featuring Trapinch, Horsea, Swablu, and Skrelp. This time, the augmented reality game is preparing for its first Research Day in 2025, highlighting several adorable companions.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  has announced Fuzzy Buddy Research Day for March 29, starting at 2 pm and ending at 5 pm local time. During this period, players will receive themed Field Research tasks that will reward them with encounters of Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful, which can be shiny. The Pokemon GO City Safari will take place on March 29 and 30 in Milan, Mumbai, Santiago, and Singapore, and trainers who attend the event in any of the cities will also be able to join the Fuzzy Buddy Research Day.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-announces-first-research-day-of-2025">
  Pokemon GO Announces First Research Day of 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1964555982" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1964555982" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1964555982" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1964555982" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1964555982-img" id="article-gallery-1-1964555982">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1964555982" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-204262328">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Date: Saturday, March, 29, 2025, from 2 pm to 5 pm local time
  </li>
  <li>
   Featured Pokemon: Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful (all have shiny chance)
  </li>
  <li>
   Incresead wild spawns: Sentret, Slakoth, Bidoof, Minccino, and Bunnelby (all have shiny chance)
  </li>
  <li>
   A $2 Paid Timed Research will be available, rewarding with encounters of Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Fuzzy Buddy Research Day will increase the spawns in the wild of Sentret, Slakoth, Bidoof, Minccino, and Bunnelby, and just like the pocket monsters featured in the Field Research tasks,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players will be able to find shiny variants of these critters. A $2 Paid Timed Research will be launched during the event, giving trainers a second chance to find Teddiursa, Cubchoo, Pancham, and Stufful. As seen in other
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  events, the Fuzzy Buddy Research Day Paid Timed Research must be completed and have the rewards claimed by March 29, 5 pm local time.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a lot of activities going on in March to keep
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players engaged, such as the Max Battle Weekend featuring Dynamax Raikou taking place on March 15 and 16.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  trainers will be able to encounter the Fossil Pokemon Archen in a new edition of the Catch Mastery event, which will take place on March 16. Other highlights of the month include Mega Absol Raid Day on March 23, and the debut of Sizzlipede in the Bug Out event, which will take place from March 26 to 30.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
