<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki Teases the Return of Popular Character</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-character-return-tease-giovanni/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  After contacting the support team for
  <em>
   <strong>
    Infinity Nikki
   </strong>
  </em>
  , excited fans received an answer that Giovanni will feature in an upcoming storyline in the near future. While players have had mixed thoughts about the story in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  , they have praised the way NPCs were handled over the course of the narrative. Characters such as Giovanni, Raggy, Aderinna, and the Banshee have all left an impression on the community, and most recently, Marques Jr. had a major role to play during the Carnival of Fireworks.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While Momo in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  exists in a tier of his own, the broody and morally complex Giovanni has captured the heart of many a fan. Born as Griffith Cicchetto, Giovanni is a Stylist from Stoneville who was captured by the Faewish Sprite Paladins and spent the next fifteen years in captivity, separated from his sick grandfather. He is directly responsible for pulling Nikki into the world of Miraland by using the Aureum Vase to wish for a power to defeat Chigda, the corrupt lord of the Faewish Sprites who personifies the seven deadly sins.
 </p>
 <p>
  An
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  player named Present_Bend_3994 contacted support about the disappearance of Giovanni from the game world, as other NPCs in the game can still be found in their designated areas. Following the completion of Chapter 8, Giovanni should have left for Cicchetto Manor, which remains mysteriously empty. However, the support team answered his absence was intended, and that Giovanni would return for a new storyline in a future
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  update.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="infinity-nikki-when-is-giovanni-coming-back">
  Infinity Nikki: When is Giovanni Coming Back?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-967451662" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-967451662" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-967451662" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-967451662" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-967451662-img" id="article-gallery-1-967451662">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-967451662" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-417547658">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The earliest possible return for Giovanni is Update 1.3, which may be adding housing to
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  as well. As a Wishfield character, the developers will likely want to feature the next chapter of Giovanni's tale before moving on to a new region. If he isn't featured in Update 1.3, then the most plausible outcome would be for Giovanni to make an appearance sometime before Summer 2025, given the rapid release schedule of
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  With Update 1.3 still a few weeks away, players can take their time to enjoy the fireworks in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  , as the latest update added a brand-new zone connected to Florawish. Much like the base game's open world, players can explore, solve puzzles, and gather collectibles, such as Dews of Firework and Whim Balloons on the Firework Isles. Update 1.2 for
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  is expected to last until late February 2025, and will also receive a new set of 4-Star banners in the second half of the patch.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Society is Shutting Down</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/midnight-society-shutting-down-deadrop-canceled/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Midnight Society is shutting down, ending work on Deadrop.
     </li>
     <li>
      Dr. Disrespect was previously removed from the studio.
     </li>
     <li>
      The studio is looking for employment opportunities for its developers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Midnight Society, the studio co-founded by
  <strong>
   YouTube
  </strong>
  streamer Dr Disrespect, announced that it made the difficult decision to shut down. The developer was working on a first-person extraction shooter called
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  , which faced backlash for its use of NFTs. Although it also dealt with controversies involving Dr. Disrespect, Midnight Society had previously reassured fans that it was moving on without the YouTube streamer.
 </p>
 <p>
  Last year, a former Twitch staff member claimed that Dr Disrespect was banned because he was caught "sexting a minor" using the platform's Whisper function. The streamer didn't outright deny the accusation and did admit to sending inappropriate jokes to a minor on Twitch Whisper. This controversy led to Dr Disrespect losing several brand partnerships, getting demonetized on YouTube, and being removed from Midnight Society's board.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite Dr Disrespect's removal, Midnight Society promised that it was still working on
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  , and many fans expected the full version to come out sometime this year. Dr Disrespect previously claimed that
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  might launch in 2024, but it never came out. Unfortunately, Midnight Society announced on social media that it's shutting its doors and canceling
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  after three years. In a statement, it expressed its gratitude to the developers who worked on
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  and the community that supported the effort. It is also actively seeking other game studios that would offer employment opportunities to its 55 developers.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="midnight-society-39-s-closure-has-an-interesting-coincidence">
  Midnight Society's Closure Has an Interesting Coincidence
 </h2>
 <p>
  In the replies, many gamers hoped that Midnight Society would issue a refund to the people who paid to support
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  . A good number also asked the developer to release the dev build and let the community finish the game instead. Meanwhile, some people pointed out that Midnight Society's closure happened on the same day Dr Disrespect reportedly got remonetized on YouTube. Dr Disrespect had been working on reversing his YouTube demonetization and was refused a number of times, but he seems to have finally succeeded this time.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's no proof that Midnight Society closed down because of Dr Disrespect's remonetization, but people couldn't help but notice that the studio's announcement came less than an hour after Jake Lucky's report on Twitter. Dr Disrespect also confirmed his remonetization in a tweet shortly after. Nonetheless, it's still unfortunate that some developers lost their jobs following Midnight Society's closure, and many people are hoping that they will continue pursuing game development in different companies.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1806433561" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1806433561" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1806433561" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1806433561" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1806433561-img" id="article-gallery-1-1806433561">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1806433561" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1217873200">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Meanwhile, Dr Disrespect has been streaming regularly on YouTube again to thousands of viewers, and even ranked as one of the top YouTube streamers last October. He has yet to comment on Midnight Society's closure and
  <em>
   Deadrop
  </em>
  's cancelation, but some people online are expecting that he might not say anything good.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Eyes On Target!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-eyes-on-target/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player scores an impressive multi-elimination and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Big Street Fighter 6 Update Detailed</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/street-fighter-6-february-update-new-ranks-mai-debut/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Street Fighter 6 update on February 5 brings three new ranks, Mai Shiranui, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players at Master rank will see changes affecting matchmaking.
     </li>
     <li>
      Quality-of-life improvements like Match Restore and replays will also be added.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  has revealed new details about the next big update, which will drop on February 5, adding three new ranks, Mai Shiranui, and more.
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  was released in June 2023, and since then, Capcom has been supporting the game through periodic updates with gameplay adjustments, character balancing, and new names for the roster.
 </p>
 <p>
  Among the biggest additions was Akuma's return in
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  in May 2023, bringing players an even more intimidating version of the iconic villain. September of the same year saw the debut of Terry Bogard, the poster boy for the SNK franchise, who became part of the game as the second DLC character of Year 2. Now, another
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  patch is coming, and players know what to expect.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom gave more details of
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  's next big update, which arrives on February 5, and one of the main new features is the addition of the ranks High Master, Grand Master, and Ultimate Master. Players on Master will see this change when their Master Rate (MR) reaches a certain number, although it hasn't been revealed which ones. Two new systems targeting
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  players at this rank will be added; the first will determine the MR of the start of a new Phase based on the MR of the previous one, aiming to improve matchmaking. The second will give gamers points for playing matches, which they can use in exchange for rewards, such as alternative character colors.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="mai-debuts-in-street-fighter-6-with-big-ranked-update">
  Mai Debuts in Street Fighter 6 With Big Ranked Update
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1710935078" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1710935078" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1710935078" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1710935078" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1710935078-img" id="article-gallery-1-1710935078">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1710935078" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-629375013">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the adjustments to ranked matches are a highlight of the update, it will also have quality-of-life improvements, such as introducing the Match Restore option. With this, players can resume custom matches interrupted by disconnection, a feature that promises to be helpful, especially for online tournament matches. Players will have the option to see replays of previous matches, whether ranked or casual.
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  's World Tour mode will also receive improvements, making it easier to track down and train with the Masters.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition to the revelation of these new features, the next big update will be Mai Shiranui's debut in
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  . With moves that mix nostalgia and some new maneuvers, Mai is the third DLC character from Year 2. In addition to Terry Bogard, Year 2 released M. Bison in June last year, and will bring Elena from
  <em>
   Street Fighter 3
  </em>
  in the Spring of this year on a date yet to be confirmed.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Are Capcom's Top 10 Best-Selling Video Game Series</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/capcom-best-selling-video-game-series/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Resident Evil tops Capcom's list with 167 million sales, followed by Monster Hunter at 108 million.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ace Attorney and Devil May Cry fans express desire for new installments.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some Capcom series made the list despite not receiving new entries in years.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   Capcom
  </strong>
  has revealed its top ten best-selling video game series over the course of its existence, with some interesting reveals. While most fans would expect Capcom hard-hitters like
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Street Fighter
  </em>
  to be on the list, there are a few games that made the top ten despite not having received new entries in some time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom got its start way back in 1979, though it wouldn't release its first arcade game until 1983. The company then introduced
  <em>
   Ghosts n' Goblins
  </em>
  and home console games for the first time in 1985. The company has since produced a number of memorable game series, including some that are still alive and well to this day. Many of these made the list.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom's top ten games have been revealed via a recent financial report from the company.
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  takes the crown, followed by
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  , with
  <em>
   Street Fighter
  </em>
  closing out the top three. However, the distance between the three games is significant.
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  has sold over 167 million units in its lifetime, while
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  has sold 108 million, and
  <em>
   Street Fighter
  </em>
  56 million. Following these three are
  <em>
   Mega Man
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dead Rising
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Marvel vs. Capcom
  </em>
  , and finally,
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-991666674" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-991666674" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-991666674" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-991666674" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-991666674-img" id="article-gallery-1-991666674">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-991666674" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1521664148">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="capcom-top-ten-sellers-reveal-interesting-insights">
  Capcom Top Ten Sellers Reveal Interesting Insights
 </h2>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Resident Evil - 167 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Monster Hunter - 108 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Street Fighter - 56 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Mega Man - 42 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Devil May Cry - 33 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Dead Rising - 18 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Dragon's Dogma - 13 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Ace Attorney - 13 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Marvel vs. Capcom - 12 million units
  </li>
  <li>
   Onimusha - 8.7 million units
  </li>
 </ol>
 <p>
  There are some interesting games that have made this list. While it's hard to argue their popularity, a number of the included series haven't seen new entries for a while. For example,
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  , the #10 spot, has only sold 8.7 million copies, but it's also been largely stagnant since the 2018 remaster of
  <em>
   Onimusha: Warlords
  </em>
  . While the
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  series is getting a new entry soon, it's only released a VR demo since 2018, yet still managed to maintain its spot. In a similar vein,
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  has sold 13 million units, but hasn't seen a new installment (outside of ports and compilations) since 2017. Meanwhile,
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma
  </em>
  has achieved the same number of sales as
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  with only two mainline games and one Japan-only MMORPG.
 </p>
 <p>
  Many long-time fans of some of Capcom's series have seen this list and are wondering why so many of the top ten games have gone stagnant. Players in the comments called for a new
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  , while others shared their expectations and eagerness for the new
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  game,
  <em>
   Onimusha: Way of the Sword
  </em>
  . Others shared frustrations at games that didn't make the top 10 and have been largely forgotten, like
  <em>
   Dino Crisis
  </em>
  , using the news as an opportunity to ask Capcom for sequels or remakes.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
