<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Reveals Tour Pass for Upcoming Unova Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-tour-pass-unova-event-details/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A new Tour Pass for Pokemon GO's Unova event will be available from February 24 to March 9, offering rewards and milestones.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can level up the Tour Pass by earning Tour Points through tasks like catching Pokemon and completing raids.
     </li>
     <li>
      A free and deluxe version of the Tour Pass will be available.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has announced that a new Tour Pass will be available for all players on February 24. The pass is another addition to the Pokemon GO Tour, the popular
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  event that this year focuses on Unova, bringing Gen 5-themed wild encounters, raids, and egg spawns.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Pokemon GO Tour is an annual event that takes place around Pokemon Day and celebrates a specific region. The first edition took place in 2021 and celebrated the beginning of everything in Kanto, adding nine previously unavailable shiny pocket monsters, including Mew and Ditto. The most recent edition of the GO Tour was last year and focused on Sinnoh, adding some Pikachu variants with special accessories and Dialga Origin Forme and Palkia Origin Forme.
 </p>
 <p>
  In anticipation of Pokemon GO Tour 2025, Niantic has announced a new Tour Pass that will be available from February 24 at 10 am until March 2 at 6 pm local time. All players will get a pass for free, and to level it up, they must earn Tour Points by completing daily tasks, catching Pokemon, completing raids, and hatching eggs. As they progress through the tour pass, trainers will hit Minor and Major milestones, receiving items like candy and stickers. Those who reach the final milestone will be rewarded with an encounter with a Zorua who has a special background. It's important to note that all rewards expire on March 9 at 6 pm, so players should claim their items before they disappear forever.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-announces-new-pass-in-anticipation-of-unova-39-s-go-tour">
  Pokemon GO Announces New Pass in Anticipation of Unova's GO Tour
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-76937489" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-76937489" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-76937489" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-76937489" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-76937489-img" id="article-gallery-1-76937489">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-76937489" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1761027038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the regular Tour Pass will be free, a deluxe version will be available for $14.99 on the Pokemon GO Webstore from February 24 at 10 am until March 2 at 6 pm. This version will give trainers all the rewards from the free and paid tracks, an encounter with the Mythical Pokemon Victini, and the new Lucky Trinket item. This single-use item turns a friend from the player's list into a Lucky Friend, turning the next trade into a Lucky Pokemon, and resetting the Lucky Friend status after that. A variant of the deluxe pass with 10 unlocked ranks will be sold for $19.99. Like the free version, the deluxe pass rewards and the Lucky Trinket will be available until March 9 at 6 pm.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Tour Pass for Unova's GO Tour comes to keep players even more excited. After all, the event promises to be a great time, with Kyurem Black and White making their
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  debuts via fusion, similar to Necrozma on last year's GO Tour. Another highlight will be the debut of shiny Meloetta, available via ticketed Masterwork Research.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynasty Warriors: Origins - What To Do With Old Coins</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/dynasty-warriors-origins-what-do-with-old-coins/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What To Use Old Coins For In Dynasty Warriors: Origins
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Get Old Coins In Dynasty Warriors: Origins
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Exploring the overworld in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dynasty Warriors: Origins
   </strong>
  </em>
  can reward you in a few ways that will help you in future battles. While farming Pyroxene can be used to make gems, you'll also often find Old Coins, which won't have a clear use early on in the game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are a few ways to get Old Coins, and you'll quickly get a good few with there being hundreds in the game. Here's what you use Old Coins for along with the various methods on how to get them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-to-use-old-coins-for-in-dynasty-warriors-origins">
  What To Use Old Coins For In Dynasty Warriors: Origins
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-755999551" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-755999551" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-755999551" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-755999551" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-755999551-img" id="article-gallery-1-755999551">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-755999551" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1425884617">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  You won't be able to use Old Coins during the first chapter of the game, so at first just ignore them and
  <strong>
   progress the main story
  </strong>
  . After beginning Chapter 2, complete the following main story battles:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Suppression of You Province
  </li>
  <li>
   Suppression of Jing Province
  </li>
  <li>
   Suppression of Liang Province
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  After completing these three main battles you'll return to the city of Ji and meet a man named Sima Hui. After finishing up the conversation and going to get incense for the Innkeeper, the
  <strong>
   Shui Jing Retreat will now be in the overworld right next to the city of Ji
  </strong>
  . Here you can talk to Sima Hui, and use your Old Coins. While you can also check your bonds and rewatch old Interactions, you can also turn in Old Coins for rewards.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Rewards are given out by hitting specific milestones with Old Coins, so always turn them in when passing by.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col" style="text-align:center;">
      <p>
       Required Old Coins
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col" style="text-align:center;">
      <p>
       Reward
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        5
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       1000 Gold
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        10
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Ravenous Spirit Amulet
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        20
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       10 Pyroxene
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        40
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       10,000 Gold
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        70
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       20 Pyroxene
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        100
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Amulet of Fortune
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        140
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       30,000 Gold
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        180
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Amulet of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        230
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       50 Pyroxene
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        280
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Amulet of Means
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        350
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       100 Pyroxene
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        400
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Musou Bond
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        450
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       Panacea
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       <strong>
        500
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td style="text-align:center">
      <p>
       War God's Sash
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-old-coins-in-dynasty-warriors-origins">
  How To Get Old Coins In Dynasty Warriors: Origins
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-914171475" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-914171475" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-914171475" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-914171475" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-914171475-img" id="article-gallery-2-914171475">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-914171475" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2066305056">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With 500 Old Coins to find in the game, it's best not to try and farm them early on, as you'll slowly unlock more ways to farm them. The various methods are:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Finding them in the overworld.
  </li>
  <li>
   Get them from
   <strong>
    Bond Interactions
   </strong>
   with your companions and officers.
  </li>
  <li>
   Getting them from
   <strong>
    letters in the Inn
   </strong>
   after story moments.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Regional Peace
   </strong>
   rewards collected at Waypoints.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When looking for Old Coins in the overworld, the icon that represents them is
  <strong>
   very small and only appears once you get close
  </strong>
  , unlike Pyroxene. The rewards for Old Coins range in usefulness, and overall you should focus on playing the game and they will come naturally.
  <br type="_moz"/>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Directed Mode Has Been Huge for Zombies</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-directed-mode-zombies-success-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Activision has confirmed that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  Directed mode has almost doubled the number of players participating in the main quest. While many
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Zombies players focus on survival, Directed mode has played a role in how many focus on the story.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Since the release of the first
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  Zombies mode in
  <em>
   World at War
  </em>
  , the spinoff game mode has featured a story. This story has exponentially expanded over the years as more Zombies experiences have been added, something that remains true with
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  . Although the
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  player base has declined since the game was released, the Zombies mode continues to have a large community of recurring players. Zombies features a wave-based system of progressively more difficult enemies pushing in on up to four players. This leaves many of the participants more interested in upgrading their firepower and defenses than completing the story.
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  introduced Zombies Directed mode in the Season 1 update, and it's already a hit with the community.
 </p>
 <p>
  A recent
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  blog post has confirmed that Directed mode has increased the
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Zombies main quest completion rate from 4% to 8.23%. This data has been calculated based on 480 million hours of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Zombies gameplay, with a small fraction occurring since the November 14 release of Directed mode. As Treyarch intended for Directed mode to increase the number of Zombies players participating in the main quest, the change is being considered a success due to the doubling of completions. Given that Treyarch confirmed that this means just over 90% of players still don't complete the main quest, they are still working on ways to increase this number.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="call-of-duty-black-ops-6-39-s-directed-mode-made-major-improvements-in-one-key-area">
  Call of Duty: Black Ops 6's Directed Mode Made Major Improvements in One Key Area
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-343613677" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-343613677" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-343613677" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-343613677" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-343613677-img" id="article-gallery-1-343613677">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-343613677" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1509961428">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Zombies' Directed mode was part of
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  's Season 1 update which included three new maps, two game modes, and more. Although Zombies Directed mode features guardrails for players to progress between, it helps the community experience the latest installment in the Zombies storyline. Over the years, the Zombies storyline has featured interdimensional portals, zero-point energy, time travel, and teleportation, making it somewhat difficult for newcomers to grasp. While Directed mode helps
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  players follow the story, earlier installments have mostly left players to their own devices.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Directed mode in place, more Zombies fans may be able to complete a main quest than ever before. As Treyarch continues to update
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , future adjustments to Zombies and Directed mode may further improve the main quest stats.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Fan Shows Off Arlecchino Cosplay</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-arlecchino-cosplay/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Arlecchino became playable in Genshin Impact in Version 4.3 as a popular 5-star Pyro unit with unique mechanics.
     </li>
     <li>
      A fan paid homage to Arlecchino through a cosplay, capturing the design of the character in real life.
     </li>
     <li>
      The next featured characters in Genshin Impact's banners after Mavuika will be Arlecchino and Clorinde.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Genshin Impact
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has shared their impressive cosplay of Arlecchino with the community, complete with the character's signature weapon. The
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  fanbase is a large one, and players often pay homage to their favorite characters through cosplay, fan art, and more.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arlecchino was first revealed in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's "Winter's Night Lazzo" animated short back in 2022. However, she did not appear in-game until the Fontaine Archon Quest. Arlecchino finally became playable in Version 4.3 in April 2024 as a 5-star Pyro unit. She quickly became one of the most popular DPS characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  next to Neuvilette, Navia, and other powerful 5-stars. Fans have also praised Arlecchino's design due to the uniqueness of her outfit and signature weapon. Because of her popularity, fans tend to portray Arlecchino in fan creations, as one particular cosplayer did.
 </p>
 <p>
  Faira Star, a popular Russia-based cosplayer, shared their incredibly detailed cosplay of Arlecchino with a life-size replica of her scythe. They also used contact lenses to mimic Arlecchino's distinct cross-shaped pupils. According to the
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  fan, they wore this cosplay to the Genshin Festival, a large official event held in Shanghai. In the post, users applauded their rendition of the fourth Fatui Harbinger. Faira Star has previously cosplayed other HoYoverse characters, like Feixiao from
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  and Astra Yao from
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  . Arlecchino's popularity might resurface among fans soon as well, as she will be featured in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's upcoming banners.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-fan-shares-incredible-arlecchino-cosplay">
  Genshin Impact Fan Shares Incredible Arlecchino Cosplay
 </h2>
 <p>
  Since her release, fans have expressed that Arlecchino's gameplay isolates itself from other characters, particularly because of her Bond of Life mechanic. Earlier leaks indicated that
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  would change Arlecchino's animations in Version 5.4, though the reason behind this decision remains unclear. Arlecchino is the latest Fatui Harbinger to join the playable roster, and while players hoped that Capitano would be next in line, the outcome of the Natlan Archon Quest suggested it won't happen in upcoming updates. Now fans are wondering who will be the next playable Fatui, with Columbina being a popular option.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-254852427" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-254852427" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-254852427" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-254852427" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-254852427-img" id="article-gallery-1-254852427">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-254852427" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1289996902">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  Version 5.3 debuted the highly-anticipated Mavuika, and the Pyro Archon has proved to be a strong character both as a DPS and Sub-DPS. Her banner is scheduled to end on January 21, after which Arlecchino and Clorinde will have their respective reruns.
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  plans on debuting more characters throughout the 5.0 cycle, so players can expect more news from developers starting from Version 5.4.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Feel The Rainbow!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-feel-the-rainbow/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players score eliminations with C4 and other accidental wins are featured in Rainbow Six Siege.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
