<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals’ Competitive Rank Distribution Has One Obvious Influence</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-competitive-rank-distribution-gold-peak-why-moon-knight/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Marvel Rivals
   </strong>
  </em>
  ' inaugural season, "Doom's Rise," has undoubtedly been a massive success. Though not all players have tried Competitive, it was recently revealed that
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  surpassed 20 million players within two weeks of launching. As a massive hit on platforms like Steam and Epic Games, the hype surrounding the superhero shooter shows no signs of slowing down.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  According to Rivals Tracker, nearly 520,000 PC players have participated in Competitive. With eight tiers to climb in Competitive, most of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' player base is found in Bronze 3 and Gold 3. Interestingly, based on the available data, clear factors influence the distribution of the ranked ladder.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="in-game-rewards-influence-marvel-rivals-39-competitive-scene">
  In-Game Rewards influence Marvel Rivals' Competitive Scene
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-525523454" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-525523454" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-525523454" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-525523454" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-525523454-img" id="article-gallery-1-525523454">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-525523454" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-214958914">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="marvel-rivals-39-free-competitive-rewards-motivate-players-but-only-up-to-a-point">
  Marvel Rivals' Free Competitive Rewards Motivate Players, But Only Up to a Point
 </h3>
 <p>
  When referencing the graph, people may notice that nearly 100,000 players are ranked Bronze 3. With
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  being a relatively new game and its popularity attracting fans from various gaming niches to the hero-shooter genre, it makes sense that most of the playerbase is conglomerating in Bronze. After all, players here are often familiarizing themselves with the heroes, maps, and positioning. Moreover, several of these players may have jumped into
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' ranked mode a few times before deciding they preferred Quickplay, leaving them indefinitely in Bronze 3.
 </p>
 <p>
  The next highest player count is Gold 3, at almost 47,000 players. While data from similar games like
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  suggest that this rank aligns with the average for most players on the ranked ladder, the free Moon Knight skin in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  has likely been a defining factor. Because the Golden Moonlight costume can be obtained by reaching any division in Gold, whether Gold 3, Gold 2, or Gold 1, it makes sense that players grinding for the free cosmetic would stop at the lowest tier.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Ranked rewards are distributed at the end of the season, so players must achieve Gold rank or higher to earn the Golden Moonlight costume.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  With the potential to drop out of Gold if they continue playing, some players opt to hit Gold 3 and stop participating in Competitive entirely to ensure they get the skin at the end of the season. This strategy guarantees their eligibility for the reward. As such, it's very clear that, whether intentional or not,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Competitive Moon Knight comes with a price and directly impacts the number of players hovering in Gold 3.
 </p>
 <h3 id="marvel-rivals-offers-multiple-competitive-rewards-for-higher-ranks">
  Marvel Rivals Offers Multiple Competitive Rewards For Higher Ranks
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Marvel Rivals Season 0 Top 600 Leaderboard" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/marvel-rivals-season-0-top-600-leaderboard.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's worth noting that many people are clustered in both Platinum 3 and Diamond 3. For the latter, it makes sense, considering that if all players in the lobby are Diamond 3 or above, hero bans are implemented. Therefore, players used to insta-locking hard meta characters in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  Season 0, such as Doctor Strange, Hela, Luna, and Mantis, may climb slower if that hero is banned.
 </p>
 <p>
  Significantly,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  also rewards those who achieve Grandmaster rank and Top 500. For Grand Master, players must climb to Grandmaster 3 to receive the Silver Crest of Honor, whereas the Top 500 will earn a Gold Crest of Honor. The Top 500 will vary based on how many people play the game and their skill rating, but as of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  Season 0, all 500 players have placed One Above All. Crests of Honor will be displayed on player's name cards as a mark of distinction when the season ends, which may also explain why various people are camping in Grandmaster 3.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helldivers 2's Lance and Baton Suggest a Sad Truth About Future Melee Weapons</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/helldivers-2-lance-baton-melee-weapons-meta-stun-good-bad-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The surprise release of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Helldivers 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s latest update at The Game Awards 2024 was a sweet treat that delivered several of the community’s most highly requested features. Not only did this update introduce a new enemy faction to fight against in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  ’s ongoing Galactic War, but among several other noteworthy additions, players can now use proper melee weapons in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While the two new melee weapons introduced in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  ’s Omens of Tyranny update may only be the first of many more melee weapons to come, the future of this weapon type doesn’t seem too bright so far. Compared to other secondary weapons, the existing melee weapons in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  are quite powerful, but beyond this though, melee weapons will likely never be able to compete with the constantly evolving meta for primary and support weapons.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-melee-weapons-will-likely-never-compete-with-helldivers-2-rsquo-s-meta">
  Why Melee Weapons Will Likely Never Compete with Helldivers 2’s Meta
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-472936591" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-472936591" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-472936591" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-472936591" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-472936591-img" id="article-gallery-1-472936591">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-472936591" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1552664166">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-stun-baton-and-stun-lance-in-helldivers-2-rely-too-heavily-on-their-stun-capabilities">
  The Stun Baton and Stun Lance in Helldivers 2 Rely Too Heavily on Their Stun Capabilities
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of the biggest strengths of the new CqC-19 Stun Lance and the CQC-30
  <strong>
  </strong>
  Stun Baton in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  is that they can stun enemies and leave them vulnerable to a practically endless combo of follow-up attacks. However, if not for the stun capabilities allowing players to repeatedly attack enemies, these two melee weapons would be much less viable since it often takes multiple attacks to kill some of the weakest enemy units from each faction in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The Stun Lance is available in
     <em>
      Helldivers 2
     </em>
     ’s Urban Legends premium Warbond, and the Stun Baton is periodically available in the Super Store.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Ultimately, if future updates for
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  introduce more melee weapons, they might not be worthwhile alternatives to the Stun Lance and the Stun Baton if they don’t have stun capabilities. Otherwise, intentionally getting within proper range to use melee weapons would be an even bigger risk than it already is, one that could cost players a couple of Stims at best, or a reinforcement at worst, which is quite a costly investment either way.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The Stun Baton and the Stun Lance can be paired with the
     <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="640220" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/helldivers-2-sh-20-ballistic-shield-backpack-2.png"/>
      SH-20 Ballistic Shield Backpack
     </span>
     , the
     <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="640217" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/helldivers-2-sh-32-shield-generator-pack-2.png"/>
      SH-32 Shield Generator Pack
     </span>
     , or the new Directional Shield to make engaging in close-quarters combat less risky.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="anti-armor-weapons-and-stratagems-are-a-must-for-helldivers-2-rsquo-s-higher-difficulties">
  Anti-Armor Weapons and Stratagems Are a Must for Helldivers 2’s Higher Difficulties
 </h3>
 <p>
  Compared to some of the best secondary weapons available in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  , the Stun Lance and the Stun Baton are both relatively powerful weapons. Admittedly though, this is quite a low bar to clear since secondary weapons are categorically some of the weakest weapons in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the main reasons why secondary weapons are at the bottom of
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  ’s current meta is that they generally have little to no armor penetration. This isn’t as much of a problem when playing on
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  ’s lower-difficulty settings where heavily armored enemies are few and far between, but anti-armor weapons and Stratagems essentially become must-haves when playing on higher difficulties. So, unless future melee weapons come with innate armor penetration or a complimentary buildcrafting tool that provides this buff, like a body armor perk or a booster, melee weapons will likely never be able to compete with some of the best primaries and support weapons in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  For the time being, it remains to be seen if future updates for
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  will continue to add more proper melee weapons to the game beyond the Stun Lance and the Stun Baton. However, unless they have a stun utility and/or heavy armor penetration capabilities, future melee weapons in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  may be doomed to remain more of a gimmick than a viable alternative to the latest metas.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Switch 2 Leak Reveals Possible Joy-Con Images</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-joy-con-images-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Nintendo could be close to revealing its successor for the Nintendo Switch.
     </li>
     <li>
      A recent leak shows potential new images of the Joy-Con for Switch 2
     </li>
     <li>
      The images give a look at the colors and magnetic connection for the controller.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Some new images have leaked online, seemingly confirming what the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch
  </strong>
  successor console's Joy-Con controllers will look like. While the Nintendo Switch still has games releasing in 2025, the console could be nearing the end of its rope. The announcement of a successor to the hybrid console is coming relatively soon, as Nintendo has confirmed it will be making an announcement about it by the end of the 2024 fiscal year. With its impending reveal on the horizon, rumors about the Nintendo Switch 2 have been more prominent than ever.
 </p>
 <p>
  With the Nintendo Switch 2's launch rumored for March 2025, there have been a lot of leaks going around that are attempting to nail down its specifications and features. A lot of hardware rumors have also been circulating, mainly due to third-party developers and insiders who supposedly have "fairly accurate" photos of the console itself. Other details like how the Switch 2 will retain its use of the Joy-Cons were also revealed, including what colors they'd be. A new set of images has leaked online that seemingly confirm what the Switch 2's Joy-Cons will look like.
 </p>
 <p>
  The photos were posted on the r/NintendoSwitch2 subreddit by SwordfishAgile3472, claiming they got these new Joy-Con images from a Chinese SNS. These are the clearest photos of the Joy-Cons gamers have seemingly gotten yet, showing the back and side of the left controller. The photos were then shared on social media as well, confirming the Switch 2's new magnetic Joy-Cons, a consistent rumor about the controllers themselves. Instead of a rail-based connection, it uses magnetic fields as opposed to physical contact.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="switch-2-joy-con-leak-explained">
  Switch 2 Joy-Con Leak Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-543931032" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-543931032" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-543931032" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-543931032" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-543931032-img" id="article-gallery-1-543931032">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-543931032" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-37171570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The colors of the Switch 2 Joy-Con were also shown off, with this being primarily blue and black, just like the original. Unlike the Switch's Blue Joy-Con, the controller itself is primarily black, with the rail being blue, though this can only be discerned due to the images only showing the side and back of the Joy-Con. Gamers also get a brief glimpse of the new button layout of the Switch 2's Joy-Con, where there are decently sized "SL" and "SR" buttons, along with a third button on the back.
 </p>
 <p>
  The third button is speculated to detach the Joy-Cons from the Switch 2, likely to release the magnets. The photos of the Joy-Con seem to match up with various other leaks that show off the console and various mockups of the Switch 2 that have circulated recently. Fans won't know for sure until an official look at the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  is given.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring Nightreign Removing an Iconic Feature is a Necessary Evil</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elden-ring-nightreign-messages-removed-necessary-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  FromSoftware didn't announce a sequel to
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  during The Game Awards 2024, but it did announce a spin-off called
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring Nightreign
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The reveal of
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  came as a surprise to many FromSoftware fans for a multitude of reasons. Some gamers didn't think FromSoftware would return to the world of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  so soon, especially since it had just released the critically-acclaimed
  <em>
   Shadow of the Erdtree
  </em>
  expansion. Others, meanwhile, weren't really expecting a spin-off of any kind, considering FromSoftware typically wasn't known for releasing side games in its flagship franchises. Nonetheless,
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  's announcement became one of the biggest highlights of The Game Awards in the eyes of many fans.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Although
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  looks similar to
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  from a distance, it is actually quite different from the acclaimed 2022 RPG in a lot of ways. Unlike its predecessor, the game is focused primarily on co-operative multiplayer, and it features significantly more fluid, fast-paced combat.
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  takes place in a procedurally-generated version of Limgrave and, as such, is more of a roguelike rather than a traditional Soulslike. Interestingly,
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  is also not going to include a major feature that was present in
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  and many of FromSoftware's other Soulslikes: the ability to leave comments on the ground for other players to see. The removal of this iconic gameplay mechanic is disappointing, but understandable, especially considering what type of game
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  is.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="elden-ring-nightreign-ditching-the-messaging-mechanic-from-elden-ring-makes-sense">
  Elden Ring Nightreign Ditching the Messaging Mechanic from Elden Ring Makes Sense
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-65916011" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-65916011" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-65916011" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-65916011" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-65916011-img" id="article-gallery-1-65916011">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-65916011" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-369320898">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="most-of-fromsoftware-39-s-soulslikes-allow-players-to-leave-messages-for-others-to-see-in-game">
  Most of FromSoftware's Soulslikes Allow Players to Leave Messages for Others to See In-Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  Since the release of 2009's
  <em>
   Demon's Souls
  </em>
  , FromSoftware has incorporated a unique communication mechanic into almost all of its Soulslikes (excluding the singleplayer-only
  <em>
   Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice
  </em>
  ). Instead of a traditional direct message or chat system like in most other multiplayer games, many of FromSoftware's recent titles allow players to interact with others by leaving messages in certain areas within a game. These messages are sometimes used by players to warn fellow gamers of nearby dangers and to provide tips to beginners. In many instances, though, they are used simply to leave joke comments or to mislead people to get them killed in-game.
 </p>
 <h3 id="elden-ring-nightreign-won-39-t-give-players-the-ability-to-leave-messages-for-a-few-reasons">
  Elden Ring Nightreign Won't Give Players the Ability to Leave Messages For a Few Reasons
 </h3>
 <p>
  During a recent interview with IGN Japan,
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  director Junya Ishizaki stated that the upcoming RPG would limit the amount of asynchronous multiplayer mechanics that were present in the original
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . Although he noted that players would still be able to see the ghosts of other players, he confirmed that the game would not include the "ability to leave messages." Considering
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  's multiplayer slant, players will probably be able to send messages to one another in other ways, but they won't be able to interact as easily with others as they could in
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Some may be concerned about what the removal of this feature in
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  could mean for future FromSoftware games, but there shouldn't be much to worry about. There are, after all, some good reasons for its omission in the upcoming RPG. As Ishizaki himself stated, the gameplay loop of
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  is far more condensed compared to its
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  counterparts. The game is meant to be played in short, 40-minute rounds, and because of this, players won't have the time to go around reading messages that others left on the ground.
 </p>
 <p>
  One other aspect of
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  that's important to keep in mind when discussing this topic is its procedurally-generated environments. Since no two levels in the RPG will ever be the same, leaving messages in these areas would kind of be pointless. In a game with no consistent level designs, the communication method in
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  wouldn't really work as intended, considering how context-specific the messages that players leave usually are. Therefore, it's not surprising that FromSoftware decided to get rid of this beloved mechanic in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring Nightreign
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honkai: Star Rail Leak Reveals Tribbie's Signature Light Cone</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/honkai-star-rail-leak-tribbie-signature-light-cone/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Recent Honkai: Star Rail leaks are detailing the unique ability of new character Tribbie's signature Light Cone, coming during Version 3.1.
     </li>
     <li>
      Tribbie's Light Cone will feature a stacking mechanic that provides bonuses to her allies' Crit DMG and Energy after using their Ultimate.
     </li>
     <li>
      Amphoreus is set to debut a wide variety of content to Honkai: Star Rail, ranging from new places to explore and new characters to a brand-new playable Path.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Honkai: Star Rail
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak is detailing the special, unique effects of new character Tribbie's signature Light Cone, set to debut during Version 3.1. Light Cones serve as one of the most influential options when building a character in the sci-fi RPG, with lots of different aspects to consider when optimizing their build. Light Cones each feature different substats, improving everything from ATK and Crit DMG to more rare stats like Break Effect, while also coming with a unique ability catered towards a specific playstyle. New leaks are now showing off one of Version 3.1's featured Light Cones.
 </p>
 <p>
  The release of
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's fourth playable world, Amphoreus, is set to bring plenty of new content to the beloved RPG. Amphoreus will host the next chapter of the game's main story, with the Astral Express traveling to the world as a means to acquire more fuel for the interstellar train. Early teasers about Amphoreus have shown heavy inspiration from the Greek and Roman empires within its world design, also showing off several new characters coming to the roster. Now, one of the newest characters, Tribbie, has seen her signature Light Cone leaked.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="honkai-star-rail-leaks-tribbie-39-s-light-cone">
  Honkai: Star Rail Leaks Tribbie's Light Cone
 </h2>
 <p>
  A leak shared by prominent HoYoverse leaker Shiroha is showing off the details for the unique ability of Tribbie's signature Light Cone. Tribbie's signature Light Cone will feature a stacking mechanic, adding stacks each time one of the user's allies attacks an enemy. The stacks will then be depleted when the wearer uses their Ultimate, granting bonus Crit DMG and restoring Energy to their allies based on the number of stacks consumed. Tribbie and her signature Light Cone will both debut during
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's Version 3.1 update, launching on February 25.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-311869691" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-311869691" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-311869691" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-311869691" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-311869691-img" id="article-gallery-1-311869691">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-311869691" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1205853137">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Tribbie's signature Light Cone will look to be a powerful bonus for a wide variety of Harmony characters, with Ultimates often being essential for Harmony characters. Tribbie herself is expected to be heavily reliant on her Ultimate as her main source of damage, with the Version 3.1 Harmony character rumored to provide greater damage than typical supports. Many other characters, like Ruan Mei and Sparkle, will likely look to benefit from the Light Cone as well, with both characters' Ultimates providing powerful team-wide buffs.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's fourth playable world looks to have plenty of exciting content on the way, between its cast and new gameplay additions. The Version 3.0 update will finally introduce Remembrance as a playable Path, both featuring a new S-Rank character in Aglaea and the next variant of the Trailblazer. Version 3.0 will also introduce another highly-anticipated character to the game's roster, with Herta's true form finally being released as The Herta. Harmony characters look to be getting a powerful new tool with Tribbie's Light Cone during Version 3.1.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
