<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Landing On My Feet!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-landing-on-my-feet/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players take some tumbles in GTA and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation Has the Perfect Excuse to Revive One Dormant IP in the Near Future</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/playstation-gravity-rush-live-action-movie-adaptation-revive-ip/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   PlayStation
  </strong>
  has become increasingly reliant on first-party IP over the last decade or so. While Sony obviously still has a good relationship with third-party publishers like Capcom and Konami, it's first-party franchises like
  <em>
   Marvel's Spider-Man
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  that are being used to really showcase PlayStation's latest hardware and get new adopters on board. But PlayStation's first-party IP isn't being used just to shift consoles.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Over the last few years, PlayStation has been slowly wading its way into the wider world of entertainment, and its arsenal of first-party IP is once again leading the charge. Live-action movies like
  <em>
   Uncharted
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Gran Turismo
  </em>
  , and shows like HBO's
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  are just the tip of the iceberg for PlayStation's plans, and there's one upcoming live-action project that should bring about the return of a long-dormant franchise.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="gravity-rush-could-be-on-the-verge-of-a-comeback">
  Gravity Rush Could Be On The Verge of a Comeback
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-759532208" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-759532208" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-759532208" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-759532208" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-759532208-img" id="article-gallery-1-759532208">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-759532208" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1569868297">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="a-gravity-rush-movie-is-in-the-works">
  A Gravity Rush Movie Is In The Works
 </h3>
 <p>
  Back in August 2022, Deadline's Matt Grobar reported that a
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  movie was in the works at PlayStation Productions, working alongside Scott Free Productions. At the time, it was reported that Emily Jerome would write the script for the movie, while Anna Mastro would direct. Sony didn't confirm the project officially until January 2024, when a few brief clips of the live-action
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  movie were shown during a CES sizzle reel.
 </p>
 <p>
  The extremely brief footage came and went with little to no fanfare from Sony itself, and no official details have been given about the
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  movie in the year since CES 2024. But as far as fans are currently aware, there is still a
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  live-action adaptation in the works, and they could see it within the next year or two, so long as there are no major issues behind the scenes that fans don't know about.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-gravity-rush-movie-could-start-a-chain-reaction">
  The Gravity Rush Movie Could Start a Chain Reaction
 </h3>
 <p>
  Debuting in 2012,
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  is a short-lived series created by Sony's Japan Studio, a developer best known for working on series like
  <em>
   Ape Escape
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   LocoRoco
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Patapon
  </em>
  , and the early
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  entries. Originally released as a PS Vita-exclusive,
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  is an action-adventure game that sees players take control of Kat, a girl with the ability to manipulate the gravitational fields around her.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  received a PS4 remaster (courtesy of Bluepoint) in 2016, and got a sequel just a year later, the
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  series never became one of PlayStation's heavy-hitters, even despite receiving a good critical reception overall. Because of this, and a major part of the series' appeal being the player getting to actively manipulate gravity themselves, a
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  live-action movie seems like a bit of an odd project for Sony to tackle, especially when compared to its recently announced slate of live-action projects that includes
  <em>
   Helldivers
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Horizon Zero Dawn
  </em>
  movies.
 </p>
 <p>
  But anything can be good if it has enough care, attention, and talent behind it. And if the
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  live-action adaptation ends up being a hit, a revival of the game series would be a no-brainer for PlayStation. A revival of
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  would also fit in nicely with Sony's rumored strategy regarding dormant IPs, with VGC's Andy Robinson claiming recently that PlayStation is in the process of bringing back some "deep-cut old IP" to potentially supplement the publisher's larger first-party releases.
  <em>
   Gravity Rush
  </em>
  would be an ideal pick for a smaller first-party title that could come in between major franchise entries like Naughty Dog's
  <em>
   Intergalactic: The Heretic Prophet
  </em>
  or the next
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Find Out Current Path of Exile 2 Currency Exchange Rates</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/path-of-exile-2-current-currency-exchange-rate-currencies-poe-2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Currency Exchange is one of the most important features of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Path of Exile 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , capable of converting up your Currencies to higher-tier Currencies for trade with other players (or for use as Crafting materials). But despite its important in maintaining a healthy collection of Currencies, it's somewhat difficult to figure out the current Currency Exchange rates.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Because the
  <em>
   PoE 2
  </em>
  Currency Exchange rates constantly fluctuate, updating according to the market, the only way to reliably tell what the current Currency Exchange rates are for each Currency combination is to check the price in-game.
 </p>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-check-currency-exchange-rates-in-poe-2">
  How To Check Currency Exchange Rates In PoE 2
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="asking for distilled fear in the currency exchange in path of exile 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/asking-for-distilled-fear-in-the-currency-exchange-in-path-of-exile-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Talk to the gambling vendor in any Act after reaching Cruel Difficulty to access the Currency Exchange. In the Currency Exchange menu you will see two boxes for Currencies.
 </p>
 <p>
  Click the left box, and select the Currency you are seeking – or the Currency you want to exchange your owned Currencies for. For example, to check the current Divine Orb price, click the left item tab and select the Divine Orb from the list.
 </p>
 <p>
  Click the right item tab on the Currency Exchange menu to see a list of your available Currencies across your Inventory and Stashes. To continue the example, to check the price of a Divine Orb in Exalted Orbs, you should select Exalted Orb from the list of available Currencies in your Stash.
 </p>
 <p>
  The conversion ratio of your selected Currencies is displayed in between the item selection boxes. So, to get a Divine Orb with Exalted Orbs, you would have to pay the number of Exalted Orbs listed on the right-hand side of the ratio.
 </p>
 <p>
  This works the other way around, too. If you have a Divine Orb and want to convert it to Exalted Orbs, request Exalted Orb from the "Want" list, and select your Divine Orb in the "Have" list.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Currency Exchange rate updates constantly, so the conversion of one to another may drastically change from one hour to the next. Check back regularly while playing to see if you can get a good deal on a powerful Currency item.
 </p>
 <p>
  If a Currency combination is not available (such as Divine Orb for Scrolls of Wisdom), a ratio will not appear and the exchange won't be valid.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Players Want Tiny Change That Would Be Huge QOL Improvement</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-change-qol-improvement-warp-totem-confirm/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley players are asking for a "yes or no" prompt before using warp totems to prevent accidental waste.
     </li>
     <li>
      Accidental use of warp totems can ruin in-game progress, but a simple prompt addition could solve this issue.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans hope developer ConcernedApe will consider implementing this change to improve the gameplay experience.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  players are calling for a simple change to be made to the game that would add a simple prompt asking if players are sure before they utilize a warp totem. The
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  adjustment seems like it wouldn't take much to implement in a future patch, and players are commiserating over the problems that have arisen in the feature's absence.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Stardew Valley,
  </em>
  warp totems are one of the fastest ways to get around, whether players want to quickly move to another location around Pelican Town or even go to a distant island. While
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's obelisks provide endless teleports, warp totems are a single-use item. Unfortunately, some players end up using them when they don't mean to, leading to the call for this change.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user stover158 shared their thoughts about the
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  warp totems, asking for a very simple feature: a yes or no prompt that triggers when a player uses the totem. The player points out that when a player tries to eat something in their inventory, the game asks for them to confirm before going through with it. However, no such prompt exists for warp totems. As the comments indicate, numerous players have unfortunately used their warp totems when they didn't mean to, by accidentally highlighting it and hitting the use button.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="does-stardew-valley-need-a-warp-totem-confirmation">
  Does Stardew Valley Need a Warp Totem Confirmation?
 </h2>
 <p>
  Accidentally triggering a warp totem not only wastes it, but depending on what the player was doing when they used it, it may also ruin their day.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players only have so much time per day, so if someone were, for example, making their way through the Skull Cavern only to trigger the totem by accident, they'd lose all of their progress and likely not have enough time remaining in the day to try again.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-117613484" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-117613484" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-117613484" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-117613484" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-117613484-img" id="article-gallery-1-117613484">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-117613484" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1974214371">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Luckily for fans,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  developer ConcernedApe seems to be constantly looking for ways to improve upon the game, so this could potentially be added to the title someday. Fans have pointed out that in addition to food, the game also prompts players before they do things like trade an item to another player in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's multiplayer mode. However, there are other moments that are also missing a prompt, leading to things like accidentally gifting valuable items to villagers who don't appreciate them. Thankfully,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players can always restart the day and regain any lost items, but a simple prompt addition would likely save a lot of time and prevent headaches.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Event Adding Long-Requested Feature for a Limited Time</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-remote-raid-passes-shadow-raids-limited-time/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO players can use remote raid passes in Shadow Raids during Fashion Week: Taken Over.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players have the chance to capture Pokemon with higher IV stats during Shadow Raids.
     </li>
     <li>
      Remote raid passes will only be available in Shadow Raids for a limited time.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Niantic has announced that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  players can use remote raid passes for Shadow Raids for the first time during the upcoming Fashion Week: Taken Over event. Shadow Raids were introduced to
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  in 2023 and have been a popular way of catching strong Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  As 2025 gets underway, Niantic has already announced a host of updates for the popular augmented reality game. In January alone,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players see the return of Ralts for the second
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Community Day of the month. With a new event about to commence, the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  developers have surprised fans by bringing a long-awaited feature to the mobile game.
 </p>
 <p>
  During the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Fashion Week: Taken Over event, trainers can use remote raid passes for Shadow Raids for the first time. The event runs from Wednesday, January 15, at 12:00 a.m. to Sunday, January 19, 2025, at 8:00 p.m. local time, during which players can participate in any one-star, three-star, and five-star Shadow Raids in person or remotely. Any players who take part in Shadow Raids will have the chance to capture Pokemon with higher IV stats.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-temporarily-introducing-remote-raid-passes-for-shadow-raids">
  Pokemon GO Temporarily Introducing Remote Raid Passes for Shadow Raids
 </h2>
 <p>
  Even though the feature will be limited to the Fashion Week: Taken Over event, players can remotely battle in the Shadow Ho-Oh Raid day on January 19 between 2:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m. local time. On the raid day, trainers will have a boosted chance to catch an elusive shiny shadow Ho-Oh, along with the ability to teach it the charged attack Sacred Fire. Players can also use a Charged TM on Shadow Pokemon to forget the move Frustration.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1280438839" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1280438839" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1280438839" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1280438839" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1280438839-img" id="article-gallery-1-1280438839">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1280438839" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1279306737">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gamers will undoubtedly be excited to use their remote raid passes in Shadow Raids, as it remains one of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  ’s most requested features since they were first added to the game in 2023. It is worth noting that after the Fashion Week: Taken Over event concludes, players can no longer use any remote raid passes in Shadow Raids.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is hard to say if Niantic will allow players to use remote raid passes for shadow raids going forward or if this is a one-off experience. The developers of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  have faced criticism over Dynamax and Gigantamax battles due to the number of trainers required to gather in person to take on the tougher monsters, so it would make sense for many fans if this feature became permanent.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
