<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals' Invisible Woman Is Breaking Bot Matches</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-bots-matches-invisible-woman-trick/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Sue Storm's uncanny superpowers are now being used as a tool to thwart
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  ' bot lobby problem, something players have been pushing back against. One player, in particular, has discovered a way to uncover bots during matches by using Sue Storm's invisible abilities. The new character is just one part of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' recent update, though her bot-seeking powers are likely not an intended part of her kit.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' unique blend of team-based objectives and satisfying third-person shooter mechanics hit the mark for many players, with the game cultivating a massive fan base since its initial release. The continued success of the game is due in large part to consistent and significant updates from its developer NetEase, with
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  recently entering its new Season 1 update cycle. This new season brought with it new modes and maps, as well as a new battle pass, though the most notable addition has been the introduction of both Mister Fantastic and Sue Storm, the latter of which may actually help players figure out if they are in one of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' dreaded bot lobbies.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user barky616 shared their rather clever method of identifying potential bots during matches, though the strategy hinges on Sue Storm's invisible ability. Players will find a staircase on one of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Asgard maps, and while it is primarily used by most to quickly get back into the action, the player discovered that it may also help reveal if there are bots in-game. While invisible as Sue Storm, the player stood in front of the staircase, causing the enemy team to get stuck.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="player-uses-sue-storm-to-find-bots-in-marvel-rivals">
  Player Uses Sue Storm to Find Bots in Marvel Rivals
 </h2>
 <p>
  One would think real opponents would simply move or attack, but Hulk, Adam Warlock, and Winter Soldier all stand perfectly still, possibly confirming that there are bots in certain
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  matches. Players started pushing back against potential bots in online matches last month. While NetEase has not made any official statement regarding its use of bots, the practice isn't unprecedented, with fellow live-service game
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  utilizing bots in a variety of ways.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-83206963" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-83206963" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-83206963" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-83206963" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-83206963-img" id="article-gallery-1-83206963">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-83206963" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-514823548">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  Season 1 cycle is in full effect, and as previously mentioned, the new update has brought a plethora of upgrades and changes for players other than enjoy. Aside from
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' two new characters, players can now play several new game modes, including the game's new Doom Match, which essentially acts as a free-for-all deathmatch among 12 people. Season 1 of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  is expected to run for roughly three months, winding down sometime in April, meaning players have a hefty amount of time to enjoy the current crop of new additions as well as upcoming mid-season updates.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Pokedex Entries Were Literal (Volume 67)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/if-pokedex-entries-were-literal-volume-67/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The world of Pokemon really makes very little sense.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect From Witcher, Cyberpunk Developer CD Projekt Red in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cd-project-red-2025-news-updates-cyberpunk-witcher-4-multiplayer-mods/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  CD Projekt Red is one of the most fascinating AAA developers in the gaming scene right now. After building up years of good will with the
  <em>
   Witcher
  </em>
  franchise, the company's reputation threatened to tank with the disastrous release of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  . Now, after years of updates and the terrific
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  DLC, CD Projekt Red is once again viewed as a creatively rich, impressive force in the industry. Hopefully, the coming years see this upward trajectory continue.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  And 2025 will certainly be an interesting and potentially pivotal year for the studio, despite there being no major releases on the schedule. Indeed, CD Projekt Red is juggling a number of promising projects right now, including new mainline entries in both the
  <em>
   Witcher
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  franchises and a number of spin-offs. The prestigious developer has certainly been putting its nose to the grindstone, and while the fruits of much of this labor won't materialize this year, audiences could definitely obtain more information about them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="don-39-t-expect-the-witcher-4-or-cyberpunk-2-in-2025">
  Don't Expect The Witcher 4 or Cyberpunk 2 in 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1385688115" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1385688115" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1385688115" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1385688115" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1385688115-img" id="article-gallery-1-1385688115">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1385688115" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1139362648">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before looking at what 2025 has in store for CD Projekt Red, it may be worth setting realistic, albeit disappointing, expectations for the current calendar year.
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  fans have been riding high off
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  's cinematic reveal at this past Game Awards, and some have even speculated that the game will land sometime in 2025. The only evidence that would support such a claim is a statement made by CDPR CEO Adam Kicinski in 2022, where he said that
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  was at least three years away from launch. Considering that the game was only just revealed, and through a pre-rendered movie rather than gameplay, it's safe to say that CDPR isn't on the low end of that estimate.
 </p>
 <p>
  On a similar note, 2025 probably won't be the year that CD Projekt Red draws back the curtain on the
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  sequel, codenamed
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  only just entered its research and development stage last year, so while CDPR no doubt has big plans for this next chapter in the series, these plans are very unlikely to be illuminated within the next twelve months.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-39-s-modding-scene-could-explode-in-2025">
  The Witcher 3's Modding Scene Could Explode in 2025
 </h2>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  has always had a rich modding scene, but 2025 could see it enter a new era of greatness. This is thanks to CD Projekt Red's proprietary mod editor that was introduced to the game last June, which should make modding easier and more accessible than ever. With the arrival of these new tools, the game that many consider to be CDPR's magnum opus is likely to expand with both ambitious and small-scale mods, so players with an interest in this side of the game's community and legacy should definitely keep an eye out in these next few months.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cd-projekt-red-may-issue-a-statement-about-the-witcher-multiplayer-game-this-year">
  CD Projekt Red May Issue a Statement About the Witcher Multiplayer Game This Year
 </h2>
 <p>
  One of CD Projekt Red's many in-development projects is a
  <em>
   Witcher
  </em>
  multiplayer spin-off, referred to simply as
  <em>
   Project Sirius.
  </em>
  <em>
   Project Sirius
  </em>
  reportedly restarted development at the start of 2023, though, which indicates that it could be shifting gears. With
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  out of the way, and with
  <em>
   Project Sirius
  </em>
  being positioned as the next cab off the rank in CDPR's 2022 strategy update, there's a strong chance that the company will loop audiences in regarding its status in 2025. At the very least, some light could be shed on whether the project has been truly restarted, and whether the outlook for it has changed.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: One of 2024's Best Games Could Be Coming to the Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-games-leaks-metaphor-refantazio/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Metaphor: ReFantazio is rumored for the Nintendo Switch 2 launch window.
     </li>
     <li>
      Multiple leakers have claimed that Metaphor is coming to the new console.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fellow Atlus game Persona 3 Reload is also rumored for the Switch 2.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  According to a new rumor, 2024's critically-acclaimed
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  could be coming to the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  in the console's launch window. Nintendo has not officially revealed the Nintendo Switch 2 just yet, but there have been no shortage of leaks about the highly-anticipated next-generation system.
 </p>
 <p>
  If the leaks are to be believed, the Switch 2 is going to essentially be a more powerful Switch with various quality of life upgrades. The latest rumors suggest that the Switch 2 reveal will happen in a matter of days, with the console expected to launch in May or June of this year. Whether there's any truth to those claims remains to be seen, but the supposed leaks aren't slowing down in the meantime.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the latest Switch 2 leaks suggests that
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  is in the works for the Switch 2. Well-known leaker PH Brazil has suggested that while
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  may not be a Switch 2 launch title, the beloved JRPG will potentially release within the system's "launch window." If past Nintendo consoles are any indication, the Switch 2 "launch window" constitutes the time from its release date to the end of the year.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="metaphor-refantazio-rumored-for-switch-2">
  Metaphor: ReFantazio Rumored for Switch 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1031607494" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1031607494" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1031607494" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1031607494" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1031607494-img" id="article-gallery-1-1031607494">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1031607494" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1729706372">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For those unfamiliar with the game,
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  earned a great deal of acclaim and was in fact one of the highest-rated new releases of 2024.
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  was nominated for multiple awards at The Game Awards 2024, including Game of the Year, and won the awards for Best Narrative and Best Art Direction. Considering the close working relationship between Nintendo and
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  publisher Sega, it is a no-brainer to bring the game to the Switch 2.
 </p>
 <p>
  This isn't even the first time that we've heard about
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  potentially coming to the Switch 2. Last year, a separate leak said that not only is
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  coming to the Switch 2, but
  <em>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </em>
  is in the works for the console as well. Again, none of this would be surprising, but it's great to hear that Nintendo is seemingly already getting a great deal of third-party support for its next-generation console.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the meantime,
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  isn't the only game rumored for the Switch 2 launch window. Ubisoft reportedly has over half a dozen games in development for the Switch 2, while companies like Konami and even Microsoft are rumored to be preparing releases for the device as well. Multiple rumors have said that the next
  <em>
   Mario Kart
  </em>
  will be a launch title, while a new 3D
  <em>
   Super Mario
  </em>
  game will be released within the launch window, but fans will have to wait and see if there's any truth to these claims.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch 2's Rumored C Button May Have a Weird Function</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-c-button-purpose-function-campus-chat-rooms-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Nintendo Switch 2's rumored C button may be used for chat functionality.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some recent datamining efforts suggest the Switch 2 will support a group and voice chat feature code-named Campus.
     </li>
     <li>
      The next Nintendo console will reportedly be officially revealed on January 16.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The C button that the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  is rumored to feature may be used for chat-related functionality, according to a newly surfaced report. Taken at face value, this claim could shed some much-needed light on one of the biggest remaining mysteries regarding the hardware of Nintendo's next console.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Switch 2 has leaked on numerous occasions since late 2024. The current consensus among industry watchers is that this influx of leaks is a result of the console entering mass production around that time. All of these unofficial looks at the upcoming device indicated that the console will have one extra button compared to its predecessor. Marked with a dark gray "C," the mysterious key was repeatedly depicted as positioned on the right Joy-Con, immediately below its home button. However, none of the sources who leaked the Switch 2 in recent weeks knew anything about the purported button's purpose.
 </p>
 <p>
  One theory about the rumored C button has now emerged as a result of some datamining efforts centered on the latest version of the Switch OS. According to a report originating from a fast-growing Discord server dedicated to the Switch 2, Nintendo's newest firmware contains references to a feature code-named "Campus." This is supposedly related to some kind of group and voice chat support for Nintendo Switch Online subscribers.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="nintendo-switch-2-will-reportedly-support-screen-sharing">
  Nintendo Switch 2 Will Reportedly Support Screen Sharing
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Nintendo Switch 2 Discord server C button chat rooms datamine report GR screenshot" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/01/nintendo-switch-2-discord-server-c-button-chat-rooms-datamine-report-gr-screenshot.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The same source suggests that Campus will allow screen sharing, whereas its chat groups will be able to accommodate up to 12 users. While its codename starts with a "C," if this rumored feature has anything to do with the new button said to be present on Nintendo's next console, then the letter on that key is much more likely to stand for "chat" rather than "Campus." These findings represent a blow to the popular fan theory that the C button might be used for casting the contents of the Nintendo Switch 2 screen to another device.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1487457586" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1487457586" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1487457586" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1487457586" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1487457586-img" id="article-gallery-1-1487457586">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1487457586" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1953889554">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="chat-support-isn-39-t-exactly-in-line-with-the-switch-39-s-kid-friendly-design">
  Chat Support Isn't Exactly in Line With the Switch's Kid-Friendly Design
 </h3>
 <p>
  Since group and voice chats require internet connectivity, it's likely if the Switch 2 were to feature them, it would only offer them to NSO subscribers. But that's still a big "if," especially seeing how the Switch marked Nintendo's conscious attempt to move away from such functionality. By not allowing users to chat with others, the Switch is inherently more kid-friendly, and reintroducing a feature like the Miiverse text chat could open up a can of worms that Nintendo would rather keep closed.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether the much-anticipated console truly has a C button—and what its purpose is—may become clear before long. According to multiple sources, the Switch 2 will at last be officially announced this Thursday, January 16.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
