<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals' Quit Penalty is a Necessary Evil</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-quit-penalty-good-bad-important-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  It’s not hard to see where
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has taken inspiration from
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  . From the simple concept of a 6v6 ability-focused multiplayer game to certain characters like Hawkeye and Black Panther being very similar to Hanzo and Genji, it’s clear that NetEase was at the very least inspired by Blizzard’s
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  concepts. But NetEase has nearly a decade of hindsight. It can look back at what
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  did well, yes, but also what it could’ve improved on and what the game was lacking when it first launched.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One such feature was a quit penalty. Though
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  has always had leaver penalties for ranked play,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  takes this a step further and penalizes players for disconnecting too frequently during their unranked Quick Play matches. Though some may find this excessive given the pick-up and play nature of the more casual game mode, its inclusion in the game is one of the main reasons
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is currently in a healthier spot than the competition from which it borrowed so many ideas.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-marvel-rivals-needs-its-quit-penalty">
  Why Marvel Rivals Needs Its Quit Penalty
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-199661874" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-199661874" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-199661874" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-199661874" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-199661874-img" id="article-gallery-1-199661874">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-199661874" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1290917196">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="discouraging-leaving-improves-the-marvel-rivals-experience-for-everyone">
  Discouraging Leaving Improves the Marvel Rivals Experience for Everyone
 </h3>
 <p>
  Obviously, a leaver penalty is going to be critical to have in competitive game modes. If someone rage quits, it becomes egregiously unfair to the other five players on that team, as they’re basically stuck fighting an impossible battle only to eat the ranked loss. The leaver penalty is in place to discourage this type of behavior in the more serious side of the game, where players are actively trying their best to win and improve their skills. Losing ranked games due to rage quitting leavers (or people who otherwise get interrupted while playing) would be the most titling thing
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  players could experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Leaver penalties in the ranked modes are only logical, but what some players might scratch their heads about is why the penalty is also applied to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' casual matches. The pickup and play nature of Quick Play is seemingly meant to encourage people to come and go as they please.
 </p>
 <p>
  But in a game as focused on teamwork as
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , that was never going to cut it. Players leaving on a whim negatively impacts the flow of the game, be it in ranked or casual play. Teammates can’t access game-winning ultimates, team comps are constantly changing at unsustainable speeds, and that’s in the event the game mode allows for backfill. In games like
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  , leavers make for a miserable match for the other players on their team, even in casual modes, and NetEase has done right in trying to discourage and minimize that behavior where at all possible.
 </p>
 <h3 id="marvel-rivals-39-leaver-penalty-isn-rsquo-t-even-that-aggressive">
  Marvel Rivals' Leaver Penalty Isn’t Even That Aggressive
 </h3>
 <p>
  When it’s all said and done,
  <em>
   Rivals
  </em>
  ’ leaver penalty isn’t game-breaking in the least. The biggest argument against leaver penalties is that they unfairly penalize those with unreliable internet connections. And while it’s true that lagging out of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  matches or dropping connections can incur a penalty,
  <em>
   Rivals
  </em>
  gives players a short grace window to rejoin a match before the demerit falls on their account. This gives players who legitimately suffered an internet hiccup a chance to rejoin their original game and avoid being labeled as a quitter.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if someone is having a heated gaming moment and willingly disconnects from a casual game, the game allows one or two incidents like these before instilling a very forgiving five-minute matchmaking ban as a simple reminder for them to take some time and cool off before returning to the fun. Ranked bans are a little more severe, but
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  players actively and intentionally sandbagging their teammates in the more serious game modes are easily more deserving of a few extra minutes in the time-out corner.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Playtime Chapter 4: How to Find Limon Easter Egg</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/poppy-playtime-chapter-4-how-to-find-limon-easter-egg/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  During
  <em>
   <strong>
    Poppy Playtime: Chapter 4
   </strong>
  </em>
  , players must navigate the horrific prison beneath the Playtime Co. Factory. Dealing with the machinations of "The Doctor" a cruel former employee who was responsible for many of Playtime Co's terrifying experiments, players will have to enter the prison and navigate their way through countless traps and puzzles created by the Doctor for his own amusement. Fortunately, there are still a few moments of levity, such as Limon.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-a74842fca297545d" id="emaki-video-player-a74842fca297545d">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Poppy Playtime: Chapter 4
  </em>
  , players can once again find Limon. This lemony Easter Egg has been in every chapter of Poppy Playtime so far, serving as a nod to the game's Discord Community. First added in the QOL Updates to Chapter 1, Limon has been found throughout the game's four chapters so far and its most recent appearance is the subject of this guide.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-find-limon-in-poppy-playtime-chapter-4">
  How to Find Limon in Poppy Playtime: Chapter 4
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-96529432" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-96529432" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-96529432" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-96529432" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-96529432-img" id="article-gallery-1-96529432">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-96529432" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1070322006">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Limon can be found surprisingly early in Poppy Playtime: Chapter 4, appearing shortly after you enter the prison proper. After completing the train puzzle, riding the train, and arriving in the Prison, you're finally in the right place to find Limon. Proceed through the prison and find a hole in the floor of one of the cells, allowing you to drop to the other floor. From here, you'll need to find a cell with a hole in its back wall, covered by a wooden board. (It's the cell circled in image 2, above.)
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-518755027" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-518755027" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-518755027" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-518755027" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-518755027-img" id="article-gallery-2-518755027">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-518755027" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1000720939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Use the Grab Pack to pull the board off the hole in the wall and crouch through it to get into a corridor behind the cell. From here, you'll want to walk to the far end of this hallway (where there's another hole you can crouch through) and then turn and look back the way you came. Limon is on one of the girders above where you entered, so you can grab it with the Grab Pack. Once you've pulled Limon down, you can drop it to hear it say its name, or just bring it along on your adventure for a while.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki: How to Get Whiskerfish</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-how-get-find-whiskerfish/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There are countless outfits to discover and collect in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Infinity Nikki
   </strong>
  </em>
  , and plenty of adorable creatures and other resources to find across Miraland. Many of those resources are integral to crafting Nikki's best fashion ensembles, a core feature of the game that has kept its player community thoroughly engaged since its spectacular launch in December 2024.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One particular creature in Infinity Nikki that can be surprisingly tricky to find is the Whiskerfish. If you need some for your crafting endeavors, then you'll need to know exactly how and where to find them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-whiskerfish-in-infinity-nikki">
  How to Get Whiskerfish in Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-596696447" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-596696447" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-596696447" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-596696447" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-596696447-img" id="article-gallery-1-596696447">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-596696447" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1893441349">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Whiskerfish
  </strong>
  is one of the many aquatic critters found in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  and, thankfully, you don't need to progress very far into the game to find them. After reaching Florawish and neighboring Breezy Meadow in the first two chapters of the main story questline, and unlocking Nikki's fishing ability, you can start exploring the areas around Silken Lake for various types of fish, including the Whiskerfish.
 </p>
 <p>
  To find Whiskerfish you'll need to venture out to Breezy Meadow, specifically to the
  <strong>
   Leisurely Anglers Florawish Branch
  </strong>
  along the lakeside. There are a handful of fishing nodes scattered around the area, each filled with up to 3 randomized fish for you to gather. Approach one of these nodes and equip your Rippling Serenity fishing outfit (or any fashionable alternative such as Shark Mirage). Cast your line and try your luck until a Whiskerfish manages to bite.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whiskerfish are relatively sparse compared to other fish in the game, so it can take a good bit of exploration to find up to a handful of them a day. Aside from Leisurely Anglers, their other main spawn location is much further south in the
  <strong>
   Abandoned Fanatic Wisher Camp area
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-779835842" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-779835842" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-779835842" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-779835842" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-779835842-img" id="article-gallery-2-779835842">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-779835842" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-550953801">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you've caught at least one Whiskerfish in the game, you can start tracking them via your Map's incredibly convenient
  <strong>
   Collections tracker feature
  </strong>
  . Pull up your map and select the book icon in the bottom left corner of your screen, which will pull up the Collections menu. Click the fish icon on the far right and scroll until you find the Whiskerfish. Select it and then press the yellow 'Track' button beneath its description.
 </p>
 <p>
  From there, your map will automatically locate the next available fishing node that contains Whiskerfish, indicated by a yellow circle. If you manage to catch at least 100kg of Whiskerfish, you can unlock Precise Tracking to further pinpoint their exact locations. However, since fish are always caught in group nodes regardless of region, Precise Tracking isn't necessarily as important as it may be for other animals and items.
 </p>
 <p>
  Alternatively, another reliable method to collect Whiskerfish is by using the
  <strong>
   Dig, Pear-Pal
  </strong>
  feature on your Peal-Pal. It allows you to passively "dig" for up to five different resources at a time by exchanging a small amount of Bling for each one. If you aim to collect the maximum allowance Whiskerfish, the process takes 24 hours from the moment you press 'Dig', so you can collect your resources the following day.
 </p>
 <p>
  One other method of obtaining Whiskerfish is via the 'Resonance' tab in the in-game store. You can exchange your Tranquility Droplets for up to 10.0kg of Whiskerfish (8 x Tranquility Droplets per 1.0kg) every 30 days. This is another convenient way of collecting more of a rare resource (such as Crown Fluff) that otherwise takes significant time to acquire.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon TCG Pocket Leak Teases Upcoming Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-pocket-leak-distribution-event-genetic-apex-expansion/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A Pokemon TCG Pocket leak reveals a potential upcoming distribution event for rare cards from Feb 27 to April 30.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can obtain rare cards like Pikachu, Charizard, and Mewtwo through the Genetic Apex Expansion event.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak has revealed an upcoming distribution event that will give rare cards to players. Like physical cards,
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  players can get a selection of rare cards to add to their collections. To do this, they open booster packs, counting themselves lucky to pull these coveted cards or gather enough pack points to craft them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  cards are divided by rarity, the lowest being one-diamond and the highest being the crown cards. While diamond cards have a 100% chance of appearing from the first to the third slot of a booster pack, crown cards only have a 0.040% chance of dropping in the fourth slot and a 0.16% chance of appearing in the fifth slot. Obtaining the rarest cards in the game requires a good dose of luck and patience, but a new leak brings promising news for players.
 </p>
 <p>
  According to a leak shared by Pokemon Zone,
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  will have a distribution event giving away cards of rarity four-diamond upwards. The information says that the event will start on February 27, and three packs from the Genetic Apex expansion will be given away; one of Pikachu, Charizard, and Mewtwo. While this will be a great chance for players to pull coveted cards, there is a twist: only the fifth card in each pack will be rare, with the others being regular. The leak also informs that players will have until April 30 to claim the packs in their Gift Box.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-tcg-pocket-leaked-genetic-apex-expansion-distribution-event-details">
  Pokemon TCG Pocket Leaked Genetic Apex Expansion Distribution Event Details
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2099880581" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2099880581" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2099880581" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2099880581" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2099880581-img" id="article-gallery-1-2099880581">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2099880581" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1519629543">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Event date: February 27 to April 30
  </li>
  <li>
   Rewards: a Pikachu, Charizard, and Mewtwo booster pack (guaranteed rare card in the fifth slot)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The four-diamond rarity cards in the Genetic Apex set are the regular ex, which includes popular names like Mewtwo, Blastoise, and Exeggutor. The one-star rarity are the full art rare cards, the two-star rarity are the full art ex and trainer cards, and the three-star rarity are the immersive
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  cards. The crown rarity cards are the most difficult to see in the game and are the ex with golden backgrounds featuring Pikachu, Charizard, and Mewtwo.
 </p>
 <p>
  As with other leaks, players should take this information with a grain of salt as there has been no official confirmation from the developers. In the meantime, other events are officially available. One of them is giving players new
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  promo cards, including Cresselia ex. Like the Lapras event, this is the only way to get the ex variant of the Gen 4 Legendary. The other is the PvP event, which is giving away themed badges from the new Space-Time Smackdown expansion.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Soulslike Games More Like Sekiro Than Dark Souls</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/soulslike-games-more-like-sekiro-than-dark-souls/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice stands out as a gem among 2019 games for its punishing swordplay and stealth emphasis.
     </li>
     <li>
      NIOH offers a challenging action rollercoaster with historical references, innovative combat stances, and a unique parry system.
     </li>
     <li>
      Wo Long, Thymesia, and Lies of P all provide varying degrees of Sekiro-inspired combat systems and challenging gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Depending on who is asked, 2019 was either a lackluster year for games or a downright terrible one. However, there is unanimity in the fact that there was one gem from the selections for 2019 in the form of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice
   </strong>
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The game, developed by the legendary FromSoftware, was a beauty to behold, and even years later, players are still replaying the game and consider it one of the best FromSoftware offerings. Among other things,
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  made a name for itself with its punishingly difficult swordplay and parry system, along with its emphasis on stealth. Thankfully, many other Soulslike titles can scratch the
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  itch if players want to take a break from the
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated February 4, 2025, by Famutimi Oluwafemi:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   The term 'soulslike' has become a staple in the gaming industry, and there are always new titles and even old that fall into this category. That said, with how revolutionary Sekiro: Shadows Die Twice was, there is a growing demand for games that are closer to the Japanese action adventure than to the more brooding Lovecraftian surroundings of Dark Souls. Here are some of the best of such games.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="nioh">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   NIOH
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-great-soulslike-with-a-dash-of-history-just-like-sekiro">
  A Great Soulslike With A Dash Of History Just Like Sekiro
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2059459601" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2059459601" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2059459601" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2059459601" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2059459601-img" id="article-gallery-1-2059459601">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2059459601" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-9959133">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Team Ninja’s
  <em>
   <strong>
    NIOH
   </strong>
  </em>
  is an action rollercoaster that features real historical references, which might be fascinating for anyone with a passing interest in history. The player controls William, a character based on William Adams, an Englishman who is considered one of the only Western samurai.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   NIOH
  </em>
  might not be as hard as
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , but it is certainly challenging. It also makes use of a parry system, and the player can choose between stances, which makes combat more innovative and engaging.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kristala">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Kristala
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="if-cats-were-warriors">
  If Cats Were Warriors
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-340092138" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-340092138" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-340092138" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-340092138" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-340092138-img" id="article-gallery-2-340092138">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-340092138" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-928239760">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Platform
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Microsoft Windows, Playstation 5, Xbox Series X and Series S
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Developer
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Astral Clocktower Studios
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Genres
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Action game, Indie game
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Publisher
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Astral Clocktower Studios
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Released
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       June 2024
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kristala
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a game from developers Astral Clocktower Studios, where the player takes control of their own anthropomorphic character (in this case, cats) and sets off on an epic adventure. It was released in 2024 and is a mix between a soulslike and
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  . The oppressive surroundings are certainly more akin to the Souls games.
 </p>
 <p>
  But the combat is where it takes more inspiration from
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , as players have to parry when fighting enemies. Not only that, but there is a lot of rolling and dodging involved, too. Furthermore, the traversal skills are also more akin to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , as the player moves like a cat, jumping from building to building with great agility, and the absence of fall damage (the player is a cat afterall) just adds to the realism.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hollow-knight">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Hollow Knight
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-indie-darling-in-every-sense-of-the-word">
  An Indie Darling In Every Sense Of The Word
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-158275321" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-158275321" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-158275321" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-158275321" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-158275321-img" id="article-gallery-3-158275321">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-158275321" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2066282654">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hollow Knight
   </em>
  </strong>
  is the indie version of a
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  game. It features a deep and interesting story, gloomy backgrounds and areas, and satisfying boss battles.
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  incorporates beautiful animation and very innovative gameplay, which means that each victory feels earned, something that should feel familiar to fans of Soulslikes.
 </p>
 <p>
  It has a lot in common with a game like
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , but it also differs, with players having to think of the platforming aspect of the game, which can also be difficult to grasp. A lot of
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  ’s
  <em>
  </em>
  difficulty is found in the DLC content, where boss rush battles can be maddeningly challenging. So, anyone looking to pick this game up should be ready for a tough time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="wo-long-fallen-dynasty">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="get-ready-to-parry">
  Get Ready To Parry
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-226080987" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-226080987" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-226080987" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-226080987" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-226080987-img" id="article-gallery-4-226080987">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-226080987" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-109028122">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Released in 2023,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty
   </em>
  </strong>
  is sometimes called the Chinese
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , mostly because of its feudal Chinese setting. Where
  <em>
   Wo Long
  </em>
  misses in terms of an engaging story, it more than makes up for with its combat system.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Wo Long
  </em>
  , the player has access to a bevy of weapons, which makes combat varied. The parry mechanic is also reminiscent of
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , but unlike the latter, where fans can’t parry and counter certain enemies,
  <em>
   Wo Long
  </em>
  integrates the parry system in every encounter. It has good replay value and is certainly a great "
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  -like" for those looking for something similar.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="thymesia">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Thymesia
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-combat-leans-more-toward-sekiro">
  The Combat Leans More Toward Sekiro
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1850324526" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1850324526" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1850324526" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1850324526" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1850324526-img" id="article-gallery-5-1850324526">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1850324526" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1404195738">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Set in a plague-ridden world,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Thymesia
   </em>
  </strong>
  requires the player to figure out what is causing the plague and bring an end to it. The story itself is vague and not the most compelling, but the bright spot is the very fun combat system.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the atmosphere, story beats, and characters make this feel more like a soulsborne game, the combat leans more towards
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  in the fighting style, which allows the player to dodge attacks or deflect them, and enemies need to have both their white life bar and green "wounds" bar depleted to die. While not the most challenging game, it still offers a good time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="steelrising">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Steelrising
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-french-revolution-but-with-robots">
  The French Revolution But With Robots
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-255340234" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-255340234" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-255340234" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-255340234" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-255340234-img" id="article-gallery-6-255340234">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-255340234" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1891247197">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Steelrising
   </strong>
  </em>
  was developed by Spiders, a France-based outfit, and fittingly, the game is set during the French Revolution. The story is a lot more straightforward than a lot of these kinds of games, and while the atmosphere and gameplay feature a lot of soulslike elements, it does differentiate itself in a number of ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  For one, the protagonist, Aegis, is wonderfully designed and is definitive, which isn't always the case with other souls-like games that feature indecipherable protagonists. Also, traversal borrows some things from
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , as the character has something of a grappling hook and is also equipped with an air dash. The bosses are fun to fight, the weapon variety is impressive, and the world is likely to delight history fans.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="code-vein">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Code Vein
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="features-a-detailed-combat-system-for-players-to-master">
  Features A Detailed Combat System For Players To Master
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1371458477" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1371458477" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1371458477" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1371458477" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1371458477-img" id="article-gallery-7-1371458477">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1371458477" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-353875859">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Code Vein
   </em>
  </strong>
  was developed by Bandai Namco, who is also the publisher of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , one of FromSoftware's more recent games.
  <em>
   Code Vein
  </em>
  is unabashedly a soulslike, boasting a lot of the mechanics linking it to the classic FromSoftware title.
 </p>
 <p>
  Its similarity to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  lies largely in its deliberate combat system, which revolves a lot around recognizing enemy patterns and responding appropriately, whether it's to dodge, block, or attack. The game isn’t too challenging, and while the enemy variety is lacking, it does feature some awesome boss battles and enables the player to customize their character to their heart’s content.
 </p>
 <h2 id="nine-sols">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Nine Sols
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="nine-sols-features-all-the-awesome-sekiro-gameplay-coupled-with-beautiful-hand-drawn-animation">
  Nine Sols Features All The Awesome Sekiro Gameplay Coupled With Beautiful Hand-Drawn Animation
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-351921309" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-351921309" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-351921309" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-351921309" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-351921309-img" id="article-gallery-8-351921309">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-351921309" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1127650493">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Nine Sols
   </strong>
  </em>
  is an underrated gem from 2024 from RedCandleGames, where players take control of the vengeful Yi who is after the Nine Sols of the Tiandao Council. The game immediately stands out with stunning 2D visuals that are similar to
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  - just with a lot more color.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Nine Sols
  </em>
  has surprisingly deep lore that the player can learn all about as they progress in the story. There is a fair bit of platforming, and the combat is incredible, featuring smooth animations and a parry mechanic that can make taking down enemies feel extremely satisfying. Enemy variety is top-notch, too, and taking control of a badass like Yi is just great.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="lords-of-the-fallen-2023">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Lords Of The Fallen (2023)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="features-a-resurrection-system-similar-to-sekiro">
  Features A Resurrection System Similar To Sekiro
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-629582942" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-629582942" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-629582942" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-629582942" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-629582942-img" id="article-gallery-9-629582942">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-629582942" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1491998424">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Lords Of The Fallen
   </strong>
  </em>
  is the reboot of an earlier game simply called
  <em>
   Lords of The Fallen
  </em>
  , which was released in 2014.
  <em>
   The Lords Of The Fallen
  </em>
  is a different kettle of fish in that it gets the soulslike trope really well with a few innovations.
 </p>
 <p>
  It compares to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  in how it utilizes the world of the dead, which is an alternate realm that the player can access by way of a lantern. If the character dies, he can be revived, similar to how Sekiro can be revived by Kuro's Dragon Heritage.
 </p>
 <h2 id="star-wars-jedi-survivor">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Star Wars Jedi: Survivor
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-soulslike-with-a-little-more-jank">
  A Soulslike With A Little More Jank
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1839645678" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1839645678" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1839645678" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1839645678" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1839645678-img" id="article-gallery-10-1839645678">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1839645678" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-492607654">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Star Wars Jedi: Survivor
   </strong>
  </em>
  is the sequel to the highly successful
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order
  </em>
  . The game takes place quite a while after the first game, and though it would be a good idea to check out the first game before playing this one, doing so is not mandatory.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Survivor
  </em>
  has the player hop planets while fighting different enemie. While some might bristle at its comparison to
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  , it is totally a soulslike. The difficulty is right up there, especially when playing on the Grandmaster difficulty, and it leans into the style of
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  with some of the parry mechanics and the intricate fighting style. The game also includes stances that help to vary the fighting style quite a bit and keep things interesting for the player.
  <em>
   Survivor
  </em>
  is an amazing sequel to a game that took many by surprise, and it’s a great game to try out for fans of
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost-of-tsushima">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost Of Tsushima
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-vibrant-world-set-in-13th-century-japan">
  A Vibrant World Set In 13th Century Japan
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-645596554" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-645596554" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-645596554" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-645596554" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-645596554-img" id="article-gallery-11-645596554">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-645596554" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1231676089">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Ghost Of Tsushima
   </strong>
  </em>
  is an adventure game that brings the Japan of 1274 to life with stunning vibrancy. The exploration and story elements of the game are genius, and players can easily sink hours and hours into it without feeling tired. The combat feels authentic, and it is reminiscent of
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  in that it revolves around parrying enemy attacks and fighting back.
 </p>
 <p>
  While not nearly as difficult as
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  or any of the other souls games, it is a great example of a title that can usher newer players into the harsh world of challenging games. For gamers looking for a challenge, the game also features a 'lethal mode,' in which both enemies and players die within a couple of hits. This really freshens the game up and offers the player an element of satisfaction as they mow down enemies in the most realistic fashion.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kannagi-usagi">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Kannagi Usagi
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sekiro-but-with-bunny-inspired-anime-girls">
  Sekiro But With Bunny-Inspired Anime Girls
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1060505060" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1060505060" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1060505060" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1060505060" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1060505060-img" id="article-gallery-12-1060505060">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1060505060" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-772496334">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Platform
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Microsoft Windows
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Developer
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tonoji
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Genres
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Action game, Indie game
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Publisher
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tonoji
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Released
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       November 2023
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kannagi Usagi
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a strange game. Released late in 2023, the developer, Tonoji, is relatively unknown, and this is the only game they have made. The game is free and available on Steam, and anyone who has played it says the same thing: It is exactly like
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The game is short and can be completed in under 30 minutes. It solely features boss fights where the player will need to parry attacks while looking for an opening against the opponent to strike back and try to attain victory.
 </p>
 <p>
  There is no real story to speak of, neither is there anything like exploration, as the game lives and dies by its combat. Its remarkably similar fighting style to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  makes it a perfect primer for those who haven’t played
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  and need something to give them a feel of what to expect from the FromSoftware game’s combat. The difficulty is not as punishing as
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  , but it is enough to prove a challenge for the average gamer.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="lies-of-p">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Lies Of P
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="where-understanding-the-flow-of-battle-is-paramount">
  Where Understanding The Flow Of Battle Is Paramount
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1673005799" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1673005799" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1673005799" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1673005799" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1673005799-img" id="article-gallery-13-1673005799">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1673005799" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1332011636">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This 2023 soulslike was unabashed in showing off where it got its inspiration from, and if one were to simply compare it by atmosphere, this game is more like
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  . But what makes it much closer to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  is the importance of parrying attacks. In
  <em>
   <strong>
    Lies Of P
   </strong>
  </em>
  , the player will be left helpless if they don't try to understand the flow of battle and know when to parry.
 </p>
 <p>
  In terms of difficulty,
  <em>
   Lies of P
  </em>
  does not disappoint, as it was so challenging that dissident voices forced the developers to patch the game to make it a tad less difficult.
 </p>
 <h3 id="honorable-mention-ndash-tenchu-stealth-assassins">
  Honorable Mention – Tenchu: Stealth Assassins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1309337532" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1309337532" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1309337532" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1309337532" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1309337532-img" id="article-gallery-14-1309337532">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1309337532" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-681195769">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Tenchu
   </strong>
  </em>
  was a game released in 1998 that tasked the player with carrying out missions using stealth. Thus, it predates the use of the "soulslike" term and doesn't neatly fit the definition. However,
  <em>
   Tenchu
  </em>
  's influence on
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  is unmistakable. A lot of the battle mechanics and difficulty will remind any
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  player of the game, so it's worth mentioning.
 </p>
 <p>
  FromSoftware was heavily involved in the production of
  <em>
   Tenchu 3
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   4
  </em>
  , which is something that also links the two games with
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Tenchu
  </em>
  might sport some dated visuals now, but it is still a very good game to help one get into the groove for
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
