<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Best Games Of The Decade So Far (2020-)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-games-decade-2020s/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Even though the 2020s still have a ways to go, the decade has already produced several fantastic games. As the years fly by and studios become more familiar with the limits of the PS5 and Xbox Series X/S, the industry will test what Sony and Microsoft's systems can do. In the meantime, the Nintendo Switch will enter the last stretch of its existence, and the console could go out with a bang.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There is still plenty of gaming to be done this decade, and it could very well be that the
  <strong>
   best games of the 2020s
  </strong>
  are still many years away. That being said, things have gotten off to an exciting start. What are the greatest titles to come out in the decade so far?
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_2">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Only games that debuted in the 2020s will be considered, so re-releases or expanded editions will be omitted. Games are also listed in reverse chronological order. Furthermore, no early access titles (
     <em>
      Palworld,
     </em>
     <em>
      Hades 2
     </em>
     , or
     <em>
      Path of Exile 2
     </em>
     ) since those are still works in progress.
    </p>
   </div>
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Also, games are listed by release date, not quality.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated on January 4, 2025 by Mark Sammut:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   The new year is here, and 2025 will hopefully produce some all-timers that will be remembered for decades to come. Also, 2024 ended its run on a high note, with December including two particularly stellar games.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle">
  Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-ambitious-adventure-that-captures-the-magic-of-the-original-movie-trilogy">
  An Ambitious Adventure That Captures The Magic Of The Original Movie Trilogy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1918017388" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1918017388" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1918017388" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1918017388" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1918017388-img" id="article-gallery-1-1918017388">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1918017388" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1029958257">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  led a weird pre-release life. Despite having a pretty great track record for crafting memorable first-person games set in a similar era, MachineGames' teasers and trailers for its Indy project garnered a surprisingly muted response. Fortunately, that reaction did not foreshadow the game's launch reception, which ended up being all-around positive.
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  is simply outstanding, delivering a globe-trotting epic that captures the original movies' wit, style of action, and brain-teasers.
 </p>
 <p>
  While not devoid of action, the game emphasizes puzzles and stealth, which makes sense since Indy is a professor with a taste for adventure and not
  <em>
   Wolfenstein
  </em>
  's Blazkowicz. The story moves at a good pace and features a top-notch presentation for both the gameplay and cutscenes, with the latter doing an impressive job of replicating Harrison Ford's look and voice. Even more so than the modern movies,
  <em>
   The Great Circle
  </em>
  comes the closest to delivering a new Indy masterpiece that can stand alongside
  <em>
   Raiders of the Lost Ark
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="infinity-nikki">
  Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-relaxing-trip-through-an-open-world-with-an-impeccable-fashion-sense">
  A Relaxing Trip Through An Open-World With An Impeccable Fashion Sense
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1762617712" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1762617712" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1762617712" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1762617712" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1762617712-img" id="article-gallery-2-1762617712">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1762617712" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1881968681">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For some odd reason, December 2024's first week was defined by free-to-play games.
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  launched to widespread success, quickly finding an audience in the process. Anybody craving a hero shooter alternative to
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  has probably already checked out NetEase's release.
  <em>
   Delta Force
  </em>
  did not enjoy the same level of exposure, but it is an easy recommendation for FPS fans who want to try something new. Even
  <em>
   UFL
  </em>
  has its positives.
 </p>
 <p>
  Finally, there was
  <em>
   Infinity Nikk
  </em>
  <em>
   i
  </em>
  , an open-world gacha game that focuses on exploration, NPC interaction, and wardrobe building over combat. The IP previously enjoyed success on mobile devices, but the 2024 entry marked its biggest push to find an international audience. For the most part, it worked, with
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  delivering stunning visuals, an endearing vibe, and an addictive outfit system. While free-to-play games can be hard to sell since the business model has a negative reputation,
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  is too impressive to ignore.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="batman-arkham-shadow">
  Batman: Arkham Shadow
 </h2>
 <h3 id="worthy-of-carrying-the-arkham-name">
  Worthy Of Carrying The Arkham Name
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-62887087" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-62887087" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-62887087" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-62887087" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-62887087-img" id="article-gallery-3-62887087">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-62887087" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-302834881">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After the disappointing
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  , the last thing
  <em>
   Arkham
  </em>
  fans expected or wanted to hear was that the next entry would be a Meta Quest 3 exclusive. While its reveal garnered widespread criticism,
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Shadow
  </em>
  ended up proving most of its doubters wrong, delivering not only one of The Dark Knight's better gaming adventures but also just one of the best VR projects on the market. Even with all the necessary changes implemented to adapt to virtual reality, Camouflaj succeeded in crafting a game that 100% fits into Rocksteady's legendary franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Arkham Shadow
  </em>
  is a prequel set after
  <em>
   Origins
  </em>
  that finds Batman investigating a new criminal organization built around the Rat King. Avoiding spoilers, let's just say that the story goes in a fresh and exciting direction that emphasizes VR's immersive abilities. The combat system retains
  <em>
   Arkham
  </em>
  's traditional loop of combos, blocks, crowd control, and gadgets.
  <em>
   Arkham Shadow
  </em>
  might not be quite as expansive as, say,
  <em>
   Arkham City
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Arkham Knight
  </em>
  , but it drops players into a fully realized universe that still feels larger than life.
 </p>
 <h2 id="metaphor-refantazio">
  Metaphor: ReFantazio
 </h2>
 <h3 id="another-atlus-masterpiece">
  Another Atlus Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2066729969" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2066729969" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2066729969" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2066729969" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2066729969-img" id="article-gallery-4-2066729969">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2066729969" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-216548438">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At this point, Atlus producing a JRPG that is one of the best games of the year is hardly surprising. An argument could be made that the publisher has two 2024 games that qualify, with
  <em>
   Shin Megami Tensei 5: Vengeance
  </em>
  being amazing in its own right. Still,
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  is extra special and stands out among the publisher's illustrious releases, especially due to its fantasy rather than an urban setting.
 </p>
 <p>
  The premise, lore, and story are too complicated to adequately summarize, but they involve political upheaval, a race for the throne, and ideological battles. While most of its themes are presented through on-the-nose dialogue, the writing is generally mature. Beyond that,
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  's turn-based combat shows Atlus (and Studio Zero)'s expertise with the gameplay style, and the same can be said for the well-implemented archetype system and social elements. This October 2024 release is Atlus at its peak.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="silent-hill-2-remake">
  Silent Hill 2 Remake
 </h2>
 <h3 id="respectfully-reviving-a-horror-classic">
  Respectfully Reviving A Horror Classic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-672928689" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-672928689" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-672928689" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-672928689" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-672928689-img" id="article-gallery-5-672928689">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-672928689" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1584249608">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To say the reveal of Bloober Team's
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  remake garnered a poor reception would be an understatement. The project was mocked years before its debut, and many seemed ready to write it off as a cash grab that would have very little in the way of redeeming factors. However, as its release approached and more footage came out,
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  started to look kind of good. Then, the game debuted and the unthinkable happened:
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  was great. More than that, it was one of the best horror games of the last few years.
 </p>
 <p>
  As Konami's 2001 masterpiece cannot be surpassed in terms of influence, the remake respectfully modernizes the same core ideas and themes, allowing it to sit comfortably alongside the original.
  <em>
   SH2
  </em>
  is genuinely intense and horrifying, so much so that a single playthrough will likely be enough for most people. Silent Hill, the town, has never looked better and, arguably, scarier.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-legend-of-zelda-echoes-of-wisdom">
  The Legend Of Zelda: Echoes Of Wisdom
 </h2>
 <h3 id="zelda-39-s-grand-adventure-is-a-throwback-to-the-past-with-an-appreciation-for-the-present">
  Zelda's Grand Adventure Is A Throwback To The Past With An Appreciation For The Present
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1396951558" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1396951558" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1396951558" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1396951558" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1396951558-img" id="article-gallery-6-1396951558">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1396951558" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-433994976">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Of course, a new mainline
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  game is brilliant. After
  <em>
   Tears of the Kingdom
  </em>
  , Nintendo wisely opted to return to the franchise's classic isometric formula to provide a more streamlined but still ambitious adventure. Excitingly, Princess Zelda takes center stage in
  <em>
   Echoes of Wisdom
  </em>
  , going on her first solo adventure in decades; more importantly, this is by far her best playable role, and she is not a carbon copy of Link.
 </p>
 <p>
  Armed with the Tri Rod and a helpful sidekick, Zelda has to clear her name and save Hyrule from more than just Ganon. The story is decent enough for
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  , but
  <em>
   Echoes of Wisdom
  </em>
  is primarily about its gameplay and exploration. While not as open-ended as
  <em>
   BOTW
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   TOTK
  </em>
  , the 2024 release still has a sandbox feel that encourages players to get creative and go beyond the beaten path. The main gameplay hook revolves around Zelda's ability to create copies of enemies and items, the former of which are used for battles while the latter are crucial for world traversal.
 </p>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="satisfactory">
  Satisfactory
 </h2>
 <h3 id="early-access-pays-off">
  Early Access Pays Off
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1355642772" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1355642772" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1355642772" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1355642772" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1355642772-img" id="article-gallery-7-1355642772">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1355642772" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1775459535">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This almost feels like a cheat since
  <em>
   Satisfactory
  </em>
  launched in early access in 2019, but the full version did not debut until September 2024. More importantly, Coffee Stain constantly evolved its original vision to actualize this final form, crafting what might just be the best factory-building game of all time. Also, this is one of 2024's best open-world games.
  <em>
   Satisfactory
  </em>
  is really extraordinary, especially since – on paper – it does not sound particularly fun or accessible.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players need to mine a planet's resources so they can complete building tasks demanded by their employer. Initially, this means scouring for resources and putting together fairly simple factory lines to produce basic tools. Gradually but surely, the company's demands grow more ridiculous, requiring the construction of factories that are enterprising in scope and execution. Each request is (essentially) a series of puzzles, and
  <em>
   Satisfactory
  </em>
  manages to provide enough guidance so players do not feel lost while still mostly leaving them to their own devices.
 </p>
 <h2 id="paper-mario-the-thousand-year-door">
  Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door
 </h2>
 <h3 id="once-a-masterpiece-always-a-masterpiece">
  Once A Masterpiece, Always A Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-537871005" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-537871005" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-537871005" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-537871005" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-537871005-img" id="article-gallery-8-537871005">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-537871005" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-357836764">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door
  </em>
  is one of the greatest GameCube games of all time, and it has aged pretty well despite some frustrating elements like an emphasis on backtracking. Now, the
  <em>
   TTYD
  </em>
  remake is also one of the greatest Switch games of all time, and it even improves some of the original version's more divisive elements. Boasting upgraded visuals that compare favorably to pretty much any game on Nintendo's console, the game is not only gorgeous but also overflowing with personality, which extends to the impeccable (and often hilarious) writing.
 </p>
 <p>
  While long-time fans can look forward to revisiting the best Mario RPG with some additional content, newcomers can pick up the 2024 release if they have yet to engage in the franchise's role-playing spin-offs.
  <em>
   Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door
  </em>
  is overall a far better game than
  <em>
   Super Mario RPG
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="mullet-madjack">
  Mullet Madjack
 </h2>
 <h3 id="frantic-roguelike-fps">
  Frantic Roguelike FPS
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1474387320" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1474387320" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1474387320" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1474387320" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1474387320-img" id="article-gallery-9-1474387320">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1474387320" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-503803682">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The 2020s is shaping up to be a brilliant decade for indie first-person shooters, and
  <em>
   Mullet Madjack
  </em>
  sits comfortably alongside the likes of
  <em>
   Ultrakill
  </em>
  as a kinetic shooter masterpiece. Drenched in cheesy (but awesome) '80s imagery and featuring a plot device that should be well-known to the Nintendo faithful,
  <em>
   Mullet Madjack
  </em>
  is built on a simple premise: players have 10 seconds to live. The main way to extend that time is to kill robots, and slowing down is not an option. Therefore, Jack must shoot, kick, finish, and slide through levels as fast as possible, leaving behind a wake of blood-soaked cybernetic monstrosities that were foolish enough to stand in his way.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mullet Madjack
  </em>
  is a roguelite, with each chapter consisting of randomly generated floors that reward completion with a temporary upgrade (which can be weapons, speed boosts, or even HP reductions to the chapter's boss). Dying on a floor resets that chapter, forcing players to start from scratch; however, once a chapter is completed, players can move on and even unlock a permanent upgrade. While the reset might sound unappealing to people who are not fans of roguelikes, the floors are extremely short, usually lasting less than a minute. As a chapter can easily be completed within about 5–10 minutes, it rarely feels like too much progress is lost following a defeat. More importantly, the gameplay is so fun that it does not matter.
 </p>
 <h2 id="animal-well">
  Animal Well
 </h2>
 <h3 id="atmospheric-metroidvania-with-no-combat">
  Atmospheric Metroidvania With No Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1224247006" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1224247006" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1224247006" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1224247006" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1224247006-img" id="article-gallery-10-1224247006">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1224247006" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-395018957">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Indie Metroidvanias are a dime-a-dozen, with most months seemingly producing at least a couple of worthwhile projects that fit the genre. Therefore,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  had to be particularly remarkable to leave a notable mark on the industry. Due to debuting directly on PS Plus Extra, Shared Memory's puzzle game was immediately exposed to a wider audience than might be the norm for these types of smaller releases, and it took full advantage of this opportunity. Right from the first screen,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  instantly showcases its beautiful but also creepy visual style, which is further enhanced by a haunting but not overbearing soundtrack.
 </p>
 <p>
  The title nails its presentation, but that would mean nothing if the gameplay was not also top-notch. With combat largely a non-factor,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  revolves entirely around platforming, exploration, and puzzles, all of which are handled well. That said, the latter component is the highlight, with most rooms containing clever brain-teasers that challenge players to rethink ways they can utilize their assortment of tools and items.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="unicorn-overlord">
  Unicorn Overlord
 </h2>
 <h3 id="tactical-rpg-with-depth-in-every-area">
  Tactical RPG With Depth In Every Area
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1143889390" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1143889390" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1143889390" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1143889390" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1143889390-img" id="article-gallery-11-1143889390">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1143889390" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-712103804">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A Vanillaware release is always a cause for celebration, and
  <em>
   Unicorn Overlord
  </em>
  continues the developer's hot streak of brilliant RPGs that throw in the occasional genre blend. While not as experimental and hard to define as
  <em>
   13 Sentinels: Aegis Rim
  </em>
  , the 2024 title is nevertheless innovative, even if it is framed as a slightly more traditional tactical RPG.
 </p>
 <p>
  Telling a fairly typical rebellion story that, eventually, goes to unique places,
  <em>
   Unicorn Overlord
  </em>
  's combat is the main element that is likely to keep players hooked, at least during the campaign's opening hours. The system delivers large-scale tactical warfare by focusing on squad-based armies, with players guiding their units along fairly expansive maps. When a group of soldiers encounters an enemy, a quick automatic battle will take place, its result determined by the decisions and orders given before the encounter. The combat has a lot of depth and can take a while to get used to.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-7-rebirth">
  Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-ambitious-amp-large-scale-jrpg">
  An Ambitious &amp; Large-Scale JRPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-705956745" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-705956745" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-705956745" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-705956745" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-705956745-img" id="article-gallery-12-705956745">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-705956745" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-599060115">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The second chapter in Square Enix's remake trilogy,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  expands beautifully on its predecessor, delivering a campaign that feels bigger in more ways than one. The major selling point is that, finally, the story heads away from Midgar, allowing players to experience more of this reimagined universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  While not far removed from its predecessor, the combat is also fine-tuned and polished, arguably representing Square Enix's peak in the real-time action sphere. Gorgeous and engaging,
  <em>
   Rebirth
  </em>
  takes an all-time classic and revamps it for a modern age, crafting an experience that can entertain both long-time fans who grew up with
  <em>
   FF7
  </em>
  and newcomers who are just familiar with the remake era.
 </p>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="helldivers-2">
  Helldivers 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="endless-fun">
  Endless Fun
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-2043154161" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-2043154161" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-2043154161" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-2043154161" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-2043154161-img" id="article-gallery-13-2043154161">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-2043154161" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1932900634">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  's brilliance did not come as a massive surprise since Arrowhead has historically created quality projects, but its commercial success was unexpected, catching even the developers off-guard. Despite debuting in between two major releases (
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Skull &amp; Bones
  </em>
  ),
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  wound up being the bigger game, garnering widespread praise for its addictive combat, engaging loadout system, and community-driven campaign. Except for a period of technical difficulties due to the server being overloaded,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  has been nothing short of a massive triumph.
 </p>
 <p>
  Casts as Super Earth's soldiers, players are tasked with liberating planets, a process that involves shooting down thousands of Terminids and Automatons. Depending on the community's actions, Arrowhead has been gradually developing a story, a process that has made it very easy to become invested in this universe. More than anything,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  is just fun, and most missions do not overstay their welcome either.
 </p>
 <h2 id="like-a-dragon-infinite-wealth">
  Like A Dragon: Infinite Wealth
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fantastic-chapter-in-a-franchise-that-rarely-misses-the-mark">
  A Fantastic Chapter In A Franchise That Rarely Misses The Mark
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-760038690" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-760038690" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-760038690" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-760038690" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-760038690-img" id="article-gallery-14-760038690">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-760038690" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-603848243">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sega's
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  is nothing if not consistent, with even the spin-offs being generally top-notch.
  <em>
   Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  amplifies everything wonderful about the series: storytelling, optional content, and world-building. Building on its predecessor's turn-based foundations, the 2024 release has a more confident combat system that is overflowing with personality, all the while still paying plenty of homage to masterpieces of yesteryear.
 </p>
 <p>
  As always,
  <em>
   Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  lives and dies on the strength of its main story, and it ranks among the franchise's best efforts. In a fresh twist, the majority of the campaign is set in Hawaii's Honolulu City, a metropolis dense with content and entertainment. The mini-games and side stories are a blast, as tends to be the case with this IP's releases.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="alan-wake-2">
  Alan Wake 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="rich-story-lore-amp-characters">
  Rich Story, Lore, &amp; Characters
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-818690437" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-818690437" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-818690437" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-818690437" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-818690437-img" id="article-gallery-15-818690437">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-818690437" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1697717497">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It took a while to materialize, but
  <em>
   Alan Wake 2
  </em>
  was well worth the wait. Remedy returned to its survival horror license with an ambitious sequel that easily surpassed its 2010 predecessor, a game that is pretty good in its own right. The campaign is told from two perspectives that are connected but still feel different from each other. One half focuses on an FBI agent named Saga Anderson as she investigates a murder in Bright Falls, and these chapters expand beautifully on the ideas of the original
  <em>
   Alan Wake
  </em>
  . The other half switches over to the eponymous writer, and Alan has been stuck in the Dark Place for more than a decade.
 </p>
 <p>
  With a captivating storyline that takes quite a few unexpected turns,
  <em>
   Alan Wake 2
  </em>
  is worth playing just for its stellar writing and characters. Fortunately, the game also has solid gameplay, immersive sound design, and impeccable visuals.
 </p>
 <h2 id="marvel-39-s-spider-man-2">
  Marvel's Spider-Man 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="gorgeous-open-world-game-with-brilliant-movement-amp-combat">
  Gorgeous Open-World Game With Brilliant Movement &amp; Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1001727185" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1001727185" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1001727185" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1001727185" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1001727185-img" id="article-gallery-16-1001727185">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1001727185" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-654728516">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Building on two fantastic games,
  <em>
   Marvel's Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  comes very close to perfecting the superhero formula. Insomniac has a well-earned reputation for crafting gorgeous games with fast-paced and satisfying gameplay along with fun narratives, and the 2023 release highlights the studio at its peak powers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Featuring two protagonists, Peter Parker and Miles Morales,
  <em>
   Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  's central storyline is among its strongest features, and it does a superb job of highlighting both leads, even if Peter is prioritized slightly more than Miles. The combat system is not that different from its predecessors, but it does have a couple of tweaks and additions that take things up to the next level. While the optional content is still not brilliant, the open-world is generally a joy to explore thanks to the smooth controls.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  Baldur's Gate 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ultimate-rpg">
  The Ultimate RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1213657774" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1213657774" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1213657774" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1213657774" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1213657774-img" id="article-gallery-17-1213657774">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1213657774" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-803307156">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As it launched into early access in 2020, Larian Studios’
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  was a known quantity long before its full debut, so the game’s brilliance hardly came as a surprise. Similar to the developer’s
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </em>
  , the 2023 RPG uses a turn-based battle system that demands strategic planning and holistic thinking. Complex and challenging with a degree of unpredictability due to its
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  origins,
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  ’s combat can take some getting used to if someone is not familiar with tactical RPGs, but it is well worth the effort of mastering.
 </p>
 <p>
  Larian’s game has a lot more to offer than just fantastic combat; in fact, that is really just the tip of the iceberg.
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  comes with a deep customization system that not only allows players to create unique characters but also rewards their choices with different in-game experiences. Along with a lengthy main story, the RPG is also overflowing with optional content.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dave-the-diver">
  Dave The Diver
 </h2>
 <h3 id="clever-blend-of-genres">
  Clever Blend Of Genres
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-2039955077" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-2039955077" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-2039955077" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-2039955077" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-2039955077-img" id="article-gallery-18-2039955077">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-2039955077" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-2099350165">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  2023 proved to be a wonderful year for fishing-themed indie games, and
  <em>
   Dredge
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  are also wildly different experiences. The former’s Lovecraftian take on fishing sims is inspired, while the latter opts for a more vibrant aesthetic and lighthearted tone. The eponymous Dave is running a sushi restaurant with a few friends, and if that was not already hard enough, he is also placed in charge of farming the fish they plan to sell.
 </p>
 <p>
  During the night, players run a restaurant; during the day, they dive into the blue unknown in search of fish. It is a simple loop that works brilliantly, especially since the underwater area regularly changes to ensure exploration never grows stale.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="street-fighter-6">
  Street Fighter 6
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-start-of-a-new-era-for-capcom-39-s-iconic-fighting-franchise">
  The Start Of A New Era For Capcom's Iconic Fighting Franchise
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-168478766" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-168478766" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-168478766" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-168478766" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-168478766-img" id="article-gallery-19-168478766">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-168478766" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-1365163483">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While Capcom has been on a remarkable run in recent years, the stink of
  <em>
   Street Fighter 5
  </em>
  ’s launch continued to linger. The franchise needed to nail its next entry if it wanted to regain its place as one of the fighting genre’s definitive casual options, and it is safe to say that Capcom managed to do just that. In some ways,
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  seems like an apology for its predecessor, particularly its inclusion of the single-player-focused World Tour. Lasting for over a dozen hours, this story mode is overflowing with content and fanservice, and it even includes open areas that players can freely explore. The narrative itself is nothing special, but World Tour’s character creator and progression system are rewarding.
 </p>
 <p>
  A robust single-player mode is all well and good, but a modern fighting game’s longevity is determined by its online options.
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  has this covered with the Battle Hub, which not only serves as a place for players to engage in PvP encounters but also as a celebration of the franchise as a whole.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-legend-of-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom">
  The Legend Of Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom
 </h2>
 <h3 id="breath-of-the-wild-but-grander">
  Breath Of The Wild, But Grander
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-721934929" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-721934929" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-721934929" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-721934929" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-721934929-img" id="article-gallery-20-721934929">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-721934929" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-587294346">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Breath of the Wild
  </em>
  was one of the best games of the 2010s, and the sequel managed to repeat this feat for the follow-up decade.
  <em>
   Tears of the Kingdom
  </em>
  builds heavily on its predecessor's impeccable foundation, crafting an adventure that successfully retains
  <em>
   BOTW
  </em>
  's many positives while introducing a few welcome twists. An underground investigation leaves Zelda missing and Hyrule in chaos, prompting Link to go on another long and epic journey filled with discovery, action, and creative crafting.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if the minute-by-minute routine is very similar to
  <em>
   BOTW
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   TOTK
  </em>
  's new additions and mechanics result in a rather different overall experience. This time around, Link earns the ability to fuse items together, and this concept plays a part in nearly every facade of the campaign. Despite landing on a dated and limited console,
  <em>
   TOTK
  </em>
  still succeeds in being modern, expansive, and creative.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="resident-evil-4-remake">
  Resident Evil 4 Remake
 </h2>
 <h3 id="revitalizing-an-all-time-masterpiece">
  Revitalizing An All-Time Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-21-386129929" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-21-386129929" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-21-386129929" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-21-386129929" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-21-386129929-img" id="article-gallery-21-386129929">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-21-386129929" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-21">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-21-slides-container-730419673">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  2023 produced two high-profile horror remakes:
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  . While perhaps not surpassing their predecessors, both projects live up to their legacies, which is no easy feat. Out of these releases,
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  just about edges out
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  , although big sci-fi fans will likely prefer the latter.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom's remake finds Leon, once again, traversing a creepy European village and castle in search of Ashley Graham, the US president's daughter. Familiar but still fresh, this trip offers way more than just a nostalgic blast with modern visuals.
  <em>
   RE4
  </em>
  tweaks the campaign in both obvious and subtle ways, crafting a remake that can comfortably exist alongside the original version.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hi-fi-rush">
  Hi-Fi Rush
 </h2>
 <h3 id="awesome-gameplay-music-amp-visuals">
  Awesome Gameplay, Music, &amp; Visuals
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-22-574100086" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-22-574100086" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-22-574100086" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-22-574100086" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-22-574100086-img" id="article-gallery-22-574100086">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-22-574100086" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-22">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-22-slides-container-617014724">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Roughly a month into 2023, Tango Gameworks and Microsoft surprised Xbox Game Pass subscribers with not only a new game but also one that proved to be among the year's best when everything was said and done.
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  is an action-platformer with a taste for music; basically, players can enhance their movesets by syncing their button inputs to the soundtrack. In combat scenarios, this translates to higher damage output and the option to execute finishers. When not fighting robots, players can also improve their platforming performance by adhering to the beat.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  matches an awesome central gimmick with (potentially) timeless cel-shaded visuals and an endearing roster of characters. The story is fairly by the numbers, but it is executed well by Tango. Furthermore,
  <em>
   Hi-Fi Rush
  </em>
  has some genuinely funny and witty writing.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chained-echoes">
  Chained Echoes
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rpg-throwback-done-to-perfection">
  A RPG Throwback Done To Perfection
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-23-696094539" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-23-696094539" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-23-696094539" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-23-696094539" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-23-696094539-img" id="article-gallery-23-696094539">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-23-696094539" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-23">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-23-slides-container-591899858">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Chained Echoes
  </em>
  ' inspirations are not too difficult to figure out as the game feels ripped right out of the '90s JRPG scene, in a good way. Along with beautiful 16-bit graphics, the RPG utilizes a turn-based combat system that will seem immediately familiar to anyone who grew up with titles from that decade; however,
  <em>
   Chained Echoes
  </em>
  is not happy to merely rethread worn-out ground. During battles, players need to keep an eye on a risk &amp; reward meter, adding an element of strategy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Another thing that sets
  <em>
   Chained Echoes
  </em>
  apart is its skill-based progression system. Rather than leveling up, characters grow more proficient as they reuse skills, which allows players to mold their party to fit specific roles. Narratively, the RPG hits the mark as well.
 </p>
 <h2 id="god-of-war-ragnarok">
  God Of War Ragnarok
 </h2>
 <h3 id="kratos-39-nordic-era-comes-to-an-end-in-spectacular-fashion">
  Kratos' Nordic Era Comes To An End In Spectacular Fashion
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-24-2102439569" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-24-2102439569" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-24-2102439569" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-24-2102439569" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-24-2102439569-img" id="article-gallery-24-2102439569">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-24-2102439569" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-24">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-24-slides-container-1398062731">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  reinvigorated Santa Monica's franchise following 2013's disappointing
  <em>
   Ascension
  </em>
  , launching a new era in Kratos' story.
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  builds beautifully on the work of its predecessor. On the surface, the sequel offers more of the same, but
  <em>
   God of War: Ragnarok
  </em>
  expands or fine-tunes enough elements to distinguish itself from what came before.
 </p>
 <p>
  As implied by its title,
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  revolves around an event in Norse mythology that signals the end of a number of key figures. The story is epic and unpredictable, expertly blending grandiose set pieces with character nuance and growth. The combat system is satisfying and intense, being a notable improvement over the 2018 entry.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_158">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The free
     <em>
      Valhalla
     </em>
     expansion only served to further cement
     <em>
      God of War: Ragnarok
     </em>
     as one of the
     <strong>
      2020s' best games
     </strong>
     . Also, on September 19, 2024, the game will be ported to PC.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="immortality">
  Immortality
 </h2>
 <h3 id="great-amp-intelligent-storytelling">
  Great &amp; Intelligent Storytelling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-25-1676304209" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-25-1676304209" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-25-1676304209" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-25-1676304209" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-25-1676304209-img" id="article-gallery-25-1676304209">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-25-1676304209" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-25">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-25-slides-container-801145877">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Immortality
  </em>
  is not for everyone, and some might even suggest this project does not qualify as a game. Marissa Marcel, an actress, has gone missing, and the only way to solve the case is to piece together clues by watching clips from three of her movies. Each scene can be paused and interacted with, allowing players to explore the people or items that appear in the flick.
 </p>
 <p>
  Essentially,
  <em>
   Immortality
  </em>
  is a puzzle-detective game with a unique presentation, very good acting, and a strong sense of mystery. An interactive film lives and dies by its story, and this release knocks it out of the park in that department.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cult-of-the-lamb">
  Cult Of The Lamb
 </h2>
 <h3 id="wicked-sense-of-humor-brilliant-gameplay">
  Wicked Sense Of Humor, Brilliant Gameplay
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-26-1064585944" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-26-1064585944" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-26-1064585944" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-26-1064585944" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-26-1064585944-img" id="article-gallery-26-1064585944">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-26-1064585944" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-26">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-26-slides-container-1191296676">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Time to start a cult.
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  has a quirky sense of humor, a gorgeous art style, and addictive fast-paced combat. Massive Monster's rogue-like puts players in the body of a lamb that decides to form a cult in honor of its god, a process that requires traveling to five regions to recruit animals. Once at the village, these followers can be assigned unique roles.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  is fun, and that is often enough the only thing a game needs to be. However, this title has more to offer than just a solid battle system. The story's dark tone and the action's tendency to inspire gore juxtaposition amusingly with the cute character models and charming visuals.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xenoblade-chronicles-3">
  Xenoblade Chronicles 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="pushing-the-switch-to-its-limit">
  Pushing The Switch To Its Limit
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-27-1475389021" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-27-1475389021" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-27-1475389021" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-27-1475389021" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-27-1475389021-img" id="article-gallery-27-1475389021">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-27-1475389021" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-27">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-27-slides-container-1056305070">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Monolith's
  <em>
   Xenoblade
  </em>
  series has been knocking it out of the park for more than a decade, and the third numbered entry might be the franchise's peak.
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles 3
  </em>
  is an action JRPG set in a sci-fi world. Despite being on a relatively underpowered console, the game's open-world is massive and packed to the brim with secondary content. This RPG can keep somebody busy for longer than 100 hours.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles
  </em>
  is known for throwing dozens of mechanics upon each other to the point of exhaustion. While by no means dumbed-down,
  <em>
   XC3
  </em>
  does a much better job than its predecessor of introducing its concepts to players in a timely manner, allowing the deep battle system to flourish more quickly.
 </p>
 <h2 id="neon-white">
  Neon White
 </h2>
 <h3 id="card-based-gameplay-is-executed-perfectly">
  Card-Based Gameplay Is Executed Perfectly
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-28-791154090" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-28-791154090" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-28-791154090" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-28-791154090" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-28-791154090-img" id="article-gallery-28-791154090">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-28-791154090" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-28">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-28-slides-container-1088111460">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Neon White
  </em>
  is all about speed. Split into short missions, players are tasked with killing everyone en route to an endpoint. While this might sound simple, the twist is that cards are needed to execute actions, and each one can either be used as a weapon or a move. With finite options, players must carefully decide when, where, and how to use a card in order to shave a few seconds from their completion time.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Neon White
  </em>
  is one of those titles that can be hard to put down as the core gameplay loop is nearly flawless. Although the story is polarizing, the visuals are pretty stunning.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-shredder-39-s-revenge">
  Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Shredder's Revenge
 </h2>
 <h3 id="accessible-beat-39-em-up-that-is-a-blast-solo-or-with-friends">
  Accessible Beat 'Em Up That Is A Blast Solo Or With Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-29-122538277" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-29-122538277" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-29-122538277" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-29-122538277" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-29-122538277-img" id="article-gallery-29-122538277">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-29-122538277" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-29">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-29-slides-container-1335514205">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A blast from the past,
  <em>
   Shredder's Revenge
  </em>
  is a love letter to the
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  , particularly the franchise's arcade gaming run during the '90s. This modern beat 'em up pays homage to a classic like
  <em>
   Turtles in Time
  </em>
  while adding more than enough elements to set itself apart from everything that came before it. This is a great game on its own and not because it reminds people of fond memories from their childhood.
 </p>
 <p>
  This 2022 release features gorgeous pixel art graphics, seven playable characters (including April O'Neil), and a wide plethora of legendary
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  villains overflowing with personality. All of these elements serve as the icing on the cake that is
  <em>
   Shredder's Revenge
  </em>
  's incredibly fun and challenging gameplay.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rogue-legacy-2">
  Rogue Legacy 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-roguelike-masterpiece">
  A Roguelike Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-30-740037087" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-30-740037087" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-30-740037087" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-30-740037087" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-30-740037087-img" id="article-gallery-30-740037087">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-30-740037087" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-30">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-30-slides-container-251316758">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After more than 18 months in early access,
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy 2 was
  </em>
  officially released on April 28, 2022, and the game was well worth the wait. Considering 2013's
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy
  </em>
  was such a resounding success, the sequel needed to knock it out of the park to not feel like a disappointment. While
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy 2
  </em>
  changes a number of things from its predecessor, including the class and weapon systems, it is still fundamentally the same core experience – and that is not a criticism.
 </p>
 <p>
  In this roguelike platformer, players take charge of multiple generations of warriors as they venture into dungeons. As experience is gained, new classes, weapons, and traits are unlocked, significantly impacting the gameplay.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kirby-and-the-forgotten-land">
  Kirby And The Forgotten Land
 </h2>
 <h3 id="kirby-goes-3d-amp-produces-gold">
  Kirby Goes 3D &amp; Produces Gold
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-31-925015151" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-31-925015151" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-31-925015151" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-31-925015151" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-31-925015151-img" id="article-gallery-31-925015151">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-31-925015151" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-31">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-31-slides-container-948548043">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It took a while but the pink puff finally received a proper 3D adventure in 2022, and it was well worth the wait.
  <em>
   Kirby and the Forgotten Land
  </em>
  translates the franchise's standard template into a wider landscape, providing all the copy abilities and charm synonymous with this pretty consistent license.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although not without its flaws,
  <em>
   Kirby and the Forgotten Land
  </em>
  is beautiful and fun, the latter of which is arguably the most important thing a game can be. Hopefully, the series continues down this route as this is a stellar first attempt at a full-scale 3D campaign.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tunic">
  Tunic
 </h2>
 <h3 id="blend-of-zelda-amp-soulslikes">
  Blend Of Zelda &amp; Soulslikes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-32-1532872986" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-32-1532872986" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-32-1532872986" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-32-1532872986" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-32-1532872986-img" id="article-gallery-32-1532872986">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-32-1532872986" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-32">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-32-slides-container-1466359507">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of 2022's most pleasant surprises,
  <em>
   Tunic
  </em>
  is a delightful (and challenging) throwback to classic
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda
  </em>
  games. Even though it takes a fair few ideas from Nintendo's iconic franchise, this indie game still succeeds in carving out its own identity, mainly through its robust combat system.
 </p>
 <p>
  A confident adventure that expertly blends exploration, puzzle-solving, and battles,
  <em>
   Tunic
  </em>
  is a rewarding experience from start to end. The game resists the urge to hand-hold players, largely leaving them to their own devices; consequently, the early hours can be slightly frustrating, but things come together quite nicely after that point.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  Elden Ring
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fromsoftware-39-s-biggest-souls-style-game-to-date">
  FromSoftware's Biggest Souls-Style Game To Date
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-33-2051750632" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-33-2051750632" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-33-2051750632" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-33-2051750632" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-33-2051750632-img" id="article-gallery-33-2051750632">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-33-2051750632" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-33">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-33-slides-container-1571058478">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  FromSoftware's latest masterpiece pushes the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  formula to the next level.
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  drops players in The Lands Between, a massive open-world divided into six regions filled with lore, items, enemies, bosses, and secrets. Unlike
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  is very much an RPG that permits players to approach encounters in a style that matches their preferences, be it melee combat, magic, or even stealth. Character-building is an integral part of the
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  experience, and the game's commitment to player freedom enhances its replayability and flexibility.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  is a no-brainer for any fan of FromSoftware's previous releases. For those who tend to be put off by the studio's penchant for difficult games, the 2022 title is slightly more accessible while still offering a significant challenge.
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  is a leading contender for the
  <strong>
   best game of the 2020s
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_217">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Shadow of the Erdtree
     </em>
     is just as good as the base game.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="horizon-forbidden-west">
  Horizon Forbidden West
 </h2>
 <h3 id="expands-on-horizon-zero-dawn-well">
  Expands On Horizon Zero Dawn Well
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-34-838085758" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-34-838085758" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-34-838085758" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-34-838085758" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-34-838085758-img" id="article-gallery-34-838085758">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-34-838085758" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-34">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-34-slides-container-1543312790">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Guerrilla Games' highly anticipated sequel to 2017's
  <em>
   Horizon Zero Dawn
  </em>
  builds upon its predecessor's foundations beautifully, offering a bigger and better package that opts to fine-tune rather than re-invent the wheel.
  <em>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </em>
  continues Aloy's story while dedicating a significant amount of time to building the rest of the world without relying too heavily on long passages of exposition. The main quest is better-paced than the first game's story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Filled with unforgettable sites of both natural and human-made origins,
  <em>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </em>
  's map is huge, gorgeous, and dense. The combat system is also a blast, giving Aloy access to a wide selection of tools to make battles more dynamic.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="forza-horizon-5">
  Forza Horizon 5
 </h2>
 <h3 id="open-world-racing-game-packed-with-top-tier-content">
  Open-World Racing Game Packed With Top-Tier Content
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-35-1099980677" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-35-1099980677" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-35-1099980677" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-35-1099980677" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-35-1099980677-img" id="article-gallery-35-1099980677">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-35-1099980677" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-35">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-35-slides-container-781205874">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  By this point, it has become a tradition for Playground Games to release the
  <strong>
   best arcade racer
  </strong>
  on the market whenever they drop a new
  <em>
   Forza Horizon
  </em>
  . This time around, Mexico serves as the Horizon crew's sandbox, and the country has proven to be the ideal choice due to its diversity in locations.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  's huge map comes packed with all sorts of challenges, ranging from standard races to death-defying jumps and the gloriously over-the-top showcase events. With a huge collection of cars to unlock and an active ecosystem,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  will probably be the definitive arcade racer until its sequel releases.
 </p>
 <h2 id="metroid-dread">
  Metroid Dread
 </h2>
 <h3 id="samus-39-long-anticipated-return">
  Samus' Long-Anticipated Return
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-36-125099049" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-36-125099049" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-36-125099049" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-36-125099049" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-36-125099049-img" id="article-gallery-36-125099049">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-36-125099049" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-36">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-36-slides-container-212481184">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following a forgettable 2010s,
  <em>
   Metroid
  </em>
  wasted little time in getting the ball rolling for the next decade.
  <em>
   Metroid Dread
  </em>
  is a welcome return to the influential franchise's 2D roots, and it barely sets a foot wrong. At its core, this is a "classic" Metroidvania, one that expertly blends exploration, combat, and flashes of storytelling to craft a constantly excellent campaign.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Metroid Prime 4
  </em>
  in the pipeline, the 2020s could be Samus Aran's decade, something that has been a long time coming.
  <em>
   Metroid Dread
  </em>
  might feel a touch smaller scale than Nintendo's other first-party releases, but it serves as a top-tier example of how to execute a 2D Metroidvania that fits neatly into the genre's conventional depiction while still feeling fresh.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="psychonauts-2">
  Psychonauts 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="overflowing-with-creativity">
  Overflowing With Creativity
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-37-34896659" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-37-34896659" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-37-34896659" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-37-34896659" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-37-34896659-img" id="article-gallery-37-34896659">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-37-34896659" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-37">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-37-slides-container-1728854922">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fans had to wait a long time for a sequel to 2005's
  <em>
   Psychonauts
  </em>
  but few will argue that Double Fine failed to meet expectations. Raz is welcomed into the Psychonauts as an intern, a role that gives him free access to explore Motherlobe, the sequel's impressive hub area. With the identity of the mastermind behind Truman's abduction still unknown, Raz sets out to piece together the Psychonauts' history.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Psychonauts 2
  </em>
  is a rare example of a platformer with a prominent and effective storyline. The gameplay is not ground-breaking, but Raz's Psi-Powers allow for some freedom on how areas are approached. The levels themselves are expansive, creative, and visually mind-blowing.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ratchet-amp-clank-rift-apart">
  Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
 </h2>
 <h3 id="unbeatable-gunplay-amp-fun-multiverse-story">
  Unbeatable Gunplay &amp; Fun Multiverse Story
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-38-200744799" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-38-200744799" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-38-200744799" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-38-200744799" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-38-200744799-img" id="article-gallery-38-200744799">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-38-200744799" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-38">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-38-slides-container-303163765">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Insomniac's
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
  </em>
  was arguably the first PS5 game to truly come across as a next-generation project, even if
  <em>
   Demon's Souls
  </em>
  also did a pretty darn good job as a launch day title. Gorgeously animated and making good use of the DualSense controller's features,
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  is a blockbuster of an action-platformer that delivers thrilling gunplay, precise movement, and lovable characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fans of Sony's long-running series will get a kick out of this new entry, while those entering the
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  universe through
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  will almost definitely feel tempted to go back and play the previous games. As it might be a while before the series produces another entry,
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  at least got things off to a great start by being one of the
  <strong>
   best games of the 2020s
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="returnal">
  Returnal
 </h2>
 <h3 id="challenging-amp-unforgettable-roguelike">
  Challenging &amp; Unforgettable Roguelike
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-39-590955667" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-39-590955667" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-39-590955667" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-39-590955667" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-39-590955667-img" id="article-gallery-39-590955667">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-39-590955667" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-39">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-39-slides-container-1859257502">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A tough-as-nails roguelike with a captivating and character-driven story,
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  will not hit the mark with everyone. Housemarque crafted an addictive but unforgiving third-person shooter that follows Selene, an astronaut who finds herself on a strange planet while stuck in a time loop. To break from this hell, which seems to morph to reflect the protagonist's trauma, Selene needs to clear six biomes, which is easier said than done when death results in a (mostly) fresh start.
 </p>
 <p>
  If it clicks with someone,
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  can be very difficult to put down, largely thanks to its fast-paced gunplay, impressive and challenging boss fights, and constant sense of growth during each cycle. While having to restart with a basic gun and from the first biome is frustrating, players should still be making enough progress to not feel like they accomplished nothing.
 </p>
 <h2 id="it-takes-two">
  It Takes Two
 </h2>
 <h3 id="co-op-perfection">
  Co-Op Perfection
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-40-907909009" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-40-907909009" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-40-907909009" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-40-907909009" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-40-907909009-img" id="article-gallery-40-907909009">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-40-907909009" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-40">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-40-slides-container-2048081462">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Specifically designed with co-op in mind,
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  is a platformer that constantly shakes things up throughout its 10-hour campaign. Taking control of two parents who are trapped in dolls, players have to guide Cody and May through a wild journey that seeks to test and heal their fractured relationship.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  's story is satisfying on an emotional level, while the gameplay is precise and evolves throughout the campaign as new abilities are unlocked in each chapter. At the moment,
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  is the
  <strong>
   best 2020s co-op game
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hades">
  Hades
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-definitive-roguelite">
  The Definitive Roguelite
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-41-2026339736" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-41-2026339736" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-41-2026339736" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-41-2026339736" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-41-2026339736-img" id="article-gallery-41-2026339736">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-41-2026339736" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-41">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-41-slides-container-71894703">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Supergiant Games'
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  is a roguelike that utilizes the subgenre's conventions to enhance its story. The game finds Hades' son, Zagreus, trying to make the trip from the Underworld to Mount Olympus, a journey that entails taking on a number of the Greek Pantheon's powerful warriors.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  ' combat is frantic, smooth, and flexible; each weapon frees up a world of possibilities and playstyles, magnifying the game's replayability. While roguelikes are not generally known for their narratives,
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  ' story and characters develop beautifully as Zagreus repeatedly tries to leave behind the Underworld. All of these things combine to make
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  one of the
  <strong>
   best games of the 2020s
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="microsoft-flight-simulator">
  Microsoft Flight Simulator
 </h2>
 <h3 id="travel-the-world-from-the-comfort-of-a-gaming-chair">
  Travel The World From The Comfort Of A Gaming Chair
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-42-1836995532" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-42-1836995532" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-42-1836995532" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-42-1836995532" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-42-1836995532-img" id="article-gallery-42-1836995532">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-42-1836995532" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-42">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-42-slides-container-1396658623">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Microsoft Flight Simulator
  </em>
  is not for everyone. However, if someone is searching for a flight sim that offers the entire planet as its map, then they can't possibly find anything better than
  <em>
   Microsoft Flight Simulator
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This title is jaw-dropping in its scale; while the sim does come with ready-made flight plans that players can take on, pilots are also free to plot their own course and travel the globe. Visually stunning and mechanically complex,
  <em>
   Microsoft Flight Simulator
  </em>
  is a reason to own an Xbox Series X or a high-end PC.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-last-of-us-2">
  The Last Of Us 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="polarizing-greatness">
  Polarizing Greatness
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-43-1561213341" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-43-1561213341" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-43-1561213341" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-43-1561213341" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-43-1561213341-img" id="article-gallery-43-1561213341">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-43-1561213341" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-43">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-43-slides-container-1866636667">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Perhaps the most highly anticipated sequel of recent years,
  <em>
   The Last of Us 2
  </em>
  is a challenging experience in terms of gameplay and narrative. Lasting well over 20 hours and featuring multiple protagonists,
  <em>
   The Last of Us 2
  </em>
  moves away from the core relationship that defined its beloved predecessor, opting to focus on a story dealing with revenge, grief, and self-destruction.
 </p>
 <p>
  The gameplay is visceral and, at times, discomforting, two traits that complement this universe's grounded and unforgiving nature.
 </p>
 <h2 id="doom-eternal">
  Doom Eternal
 </h2>
 <h3 id="evolution-of-doom-2016-that-mostly-works">
  Evolution Of Doom 2016 That Mostly Works
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-44-1666612660" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-44-1666612660" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-44-1666612660" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-44-1666612660" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-44-1666612660-img" id="article-gallery-44-1666612660">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-44-1666612660" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-44">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-44-slides-container-1041935810">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Id Software's sequel to 2016's
  <em>
   Doom
  </em>
  didn't have to do anything but deliver more of the same; however,
  <em>
   Doom Eternal
  </em>
  went the extra mile. While the gunplay remains largely unchanged since there is no way to improve on perfection,
  <em>
   Doom Eternal
  </em>
  expands Doomguy's movement options, including a dash and the introduction of the Meat Hook.
 </p>
 <p>
  An aggressive FPS that manages to make the player feel extremely powerful and simultaneously vulnerable,
  <em>
   Doom Eternal
  </em>
  is a cathartic masterpiece with few peers in its genre. While an argument could be made that not every change from
  <em>
   Doom
  </em>
  2016 was for the better, the sequel highlights the franchise's willingness to adapt and grew rather than just repeat past successes.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="half-life-alyx">
  Half-Life: Alyx
 </h2>
 <h3 id="not-half-life-3-but-arguably-the-best-vr-game-of-all-time">
  Not Half-Life 3, But Arguably The Best VR Game Of All Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-45-1573997845" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-45-1573997845" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-45-1573997845" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-45-1573997845" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-45-1573997845-img" id="article-gallery-45-1573997845">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-45-1573997845" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-45">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-45-slides-container-1232528458">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It might not have been the
  <em>
   Half-Life
  </em>
  release people have been anticipating since 2007, but
  <em>
   Alyx
  </em>
  is comfortably among the
  <strong>
   best VR games of all time
  </strong>
  . Set prior to the events of the second game and featuring Alyx Vance as the protagonist,
  <em>
   Half-Life: Alyx
  </em>
  is a fully realized entry in the iconic first-person shooter franchise. The game makes expert use of virtual reality to completely immerse players in City 17, and the controls are precise and easy to master.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Half-Life: Alyx
  </em>
  is the type of game that justifies the hype surrounding virtual reality. Hopefully, the 2020s will be filled with VR games that match Valve's success.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaphor: ReFantazio - Chimenza Weakness Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/metaphor-refantazio-chimenza-weakness-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Chimenza Weakess &amp; Affinities In Metaphor: ReFantazio
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Beat Chimenzas In Metaphor: ReFantazio
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The trick to beating any monster or boss in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Metaphor: ReFantazio
   </em>
  </strong>
  is knowing exactly what you're up against. Knowing the attacks of an enemy will help you bring skills or items to counter any additional attacks while knowing a weakness will help you deal additional damage and earn more Press Turn icons.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Chimenzas are powerful Chimera-like enemies that you'll see in multiple dungeons throughout
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  and all of them will have the same weakness. Here's what that weakness is and how to beat Chimenzas.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="chimenza-weakess-amp-affinities-in-metaphor-refantazio">
  Chimenza Weakess &amp; Affinities In Metaphor: ReFantazio
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A Chimenza In The Analysis Menu " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/metaphor_-refantazio_20250102204842.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Weakness
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Resistance
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Block
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Wind
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Fire
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Electric
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Common Drop - Spirit Dew
  </li>
  <li>
   Rare Drop - Beast Fang Katana
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <br type="_moz"/>
 </p>
 <p>
  In terms of attacks, Chimenzas have multi-target and single-target fire and electric skills, along with a slash and strike physical attack.
  <strong>
   Skull Crusher has a chance to inflict Forget
  </strong>
  on a party member, while both of the fire-based skills have a chance of leaving the target burned. The wider range of elemental attacks makes this enemy especially difficult, as it will usually favor the party-wide attacks and will hit your weakness.
 </p>
 <p>
  Chimenzas also have Dekunda, so trying to debuff them will usually be a waste of time. On hard mode,
  <strong>
   these enemies alone will have three Press Turn icons
  </strong>
  . On top of their wide range of offensive capabilities, Chimenzas also have a decent amount of health and will be mid to high-level monsters in a dungeon, but bringing the right team can make fighting them much easier.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-beat-chimenzas-in-metaphor-refantazio">
  How To Beat Chimenzas In Metaphor: ReFantazio
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-252328845" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-252328845" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-252328845" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-252328845" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-252328845-img" id="article-gallery-1-252328845">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-252328845" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1930991139">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Obviously, you'll first want to target their weakness to wind, which is easily done using the Seeker Archetype earlier in the game and later using the Summoner after progressing. Seeker lineage Archetypes do have a weakness to fire, so it's best to transfer those wind skills over to
  <strong>
   another Archetype such as the Warrior,
  </strong>
  since it has a resistance to fire.
 </p>
 <p>
  You'll also want a healer or
  <strong>
   at least Patra or Ren Patra from a healer
  </strong>
  as Chimenzas will have a chance of inflicting Forget or burning party members, both of which can quickly turn the tide in battle or have you waste precious Press Turn icons. Instead of debuffing the enemy, focus on buffing yourself using Archetypes from the General lineage as they offer party-wide buffs that will be safe from the enemy's Dekunda skill. You'll also want party-wide healing, as these enemies tend to favor their party-wide attacks over single-target attacks unless they know they are hitting a weakness.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost of Tsushima's Cut Content Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ghost-of-tsushima-cut-content-jin-backstory-ryuzo-location/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Jin's backstory had major cuts, altering a key plot point.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ryuzo's backstory was also impacted by cut content.
     </li>
     <li>
      A location called the "Otsuna Grasslands" was scrapped pre-release.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ghost of Tsushima
   </em>
  </strong>
  launched in 2020, it didn't take long for it to become one of the most memorable titles released in gaming's modern era. However, in spite of its most notable features — like its breathtaking landscapes and compelling narrative — not every idea conceived during
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  's development made it into the final release.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  is literally named after its protagonist, Jin Sakai, the game's story naturally revolves around the character. That's what makes a major cut to his backstory so significant, as it changes one of the story's biggest plot points. This, in addition to even more cut backstory for Ryuzo and a scrapped location, comprises the biggest portions of
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  that never made it beyond the cutting room floor.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="everything-cut-from-ghost-of-tsushima">
  Everything Cut From Ghost of Tsushima
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1877171839" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1877171839" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1877171839" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1877171839" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1877171839-img" id="article-gallery-1-1877171839">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1877171839" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1583664116">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="a-major-part-of-jin-39-s-backstory-was-cut-from-the-game">
  A Major Part of Jin's Backstory Was Cut From the Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  Jin Sakai,
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  's protagonist, is a compelling character for a number of reasons, but many of those reasons revolve around his backstory and motivations. Jin was born into the Sakai Clan, a prestigious samurai family on Tsushima Island, with his father, Kazumasa Sakai, serving as the clan leader. When Jin was a child, his father was killed right in front of him, leaving him deeply scarred and laden with guilt throughout his life, as he believes he should have been able to protect his father. After his father's death, Jin was raised by his uncle, Lord Shimura, the governor of Tsushima Island. Lord Shimura then trained Jin in the ways of the samurai, emphasizing honor and discipline, which ultimately plays a major role in Jin's transformation into the Ghost of Tsushima.
 </p>
 <p>
  Apparently, as if Jin's backstory wasn't already dark and tragic enough, more of the beloved protagonist's story was cut ahead of
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  's release. In some recovered dialogue audio for
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  , Jin can be heard telling morbid stories about his father to Yuna, who comments on Jin's scars. Jin then explains where the scars came from, and the story behind them actually arguably lessens the tragedy of his father's death, which the game heavily relied on for its storytelling. In his conversation with Yuna, Jin explains:
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "When that would happen to me, I would grab a bokken, and hide in the forest, slash at the bamboo, and pretend it was my father. When I was a child, I once spied on my father dressing for battle. I watched him put this mask on, and I ran in terror because my father disappeared. In his place was the one who killed men on the battlefield — the one who hurt me at home."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  In more cut dialogue, Yuriko explains to Jin that she understands the pain that his father put him through and that he "knew how to train warriors, but he never learned how to raise a son." She explains to Jin that since his father was a "hero to many people," the truth about his treatment of Jin could not be revealed to the public, lest it ruin any hope the people had once placed in Kazumasa. Even more cut dialogue between Jin and Yuriko has Jin explaining his desire to be free of his father and how his scars are "proof" of his father's love. Yuriko then tells Jin that his father was happy the day Jin was born, and that she hoped Jin's birth would change Kazumasa.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     More cut
     <em>
      Ghost of Tsushima
     </em>
     dialogue features a conversation between Ryuzo and Jin, where Ryuzo comments on Jin's aggression, to which Jin replies, "It wasn't about you. I was fighting someone else."
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="some-of-ryuzo-39-s-backstory-was-cut-from-the-game-as-well">
  Some of Ryuzo's Backstory Was Cut From the Game as Well
 </h3>
 <p>
  Jin's backstory in
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  wasn't the only one impacted by cuts, as more scrapped audio divulges a layer of Ryuzo's backstory as well. In the cut dialogue, Jin asks Ryuzo if he has ever wondered what became of his family. Ryuzo replies, "I was just a kid. There's no answer in the world that would make sense." Then, when Jin asks if Ryuzo wants to know why his family left him, he replies, "Those people aren't my family. I'm riding with mine!" Jin then attempts to comfort Ryuzo by telling him that he will be a samurai one day, be able to fill a home with a family, and "get old, lazy, and fat."
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-location-was-scrapped-ahead-of-release">
  A Location Was Scrapped Ahead of Release
 </h3>
 <p>
  A final piece of
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  cut content involves a location named the "Otsuna Grasslands," although it could very well be that the location was simply renamed or repurposed, rather than removed altogether. The Otsuna Grasslands were originally featured in the E3 2018 gameplay reveal for
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  as a location on Tsushima Island. In the game, Otsuna is a prefecture within the Toyotama region, between Izuhara and Kamiagata, so the Otsuna Grasslands would have been found somewhere around there. However, the location was ultimately cut ahead of the game's release, though it's possible that the Kushi Grasslands replaced it.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Games To Play If You Like Mass Effect</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/games-like-mass-effect/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  When one talks about some of the greatest role-playing games ever made, it goes without saying that the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mass Effect
   </em>
  </strong>
  series would be a major part of this conversation. While the series might've ended on a frustratingly low note, there's no denying the fact that BioWare had created a rich, deep, and intricate sci-fi world that had enraptured fans from all over the globe.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Be it through the original versions or the
  <em>
   Legendary Edition
  </em>
  remasters, Commander Shepard's story is always worth revisiting. Even
  <em>
   Andromeda
  </em>
  has plenty of positives. However, the wait for the franchise to produce something new could be very long, so here are some
  <strong>
   games like
   <em>
    Mass Effect
   </em>
  </strong>
  that fans can choose to play instead before this sci-fi epic finally makes its much-awaited return to the modern gaming market.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated January 4, 2025 by Mark Sammut:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   It will probably be a long while until a new Mass Effect materializes, assuming another entry does eventually find its way to store shelves. In the meantime, fans might want to look elsewhere to try and get their fill of third-person shooter goodness. Honestly, there are not all that many
   <strong>
    games similar to Mass Effect
   </strong>
   , so two fairly different titles have been added that warrant a mention. Click below to jump directly to these new additions.
  </em>
 </p>
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       The Order: 1886
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Returnal
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="warhammer-40-000-space-marine-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   31
  </span>
  <span>
   Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-all-out-war-against-an-overwhelming-threat">
  An All-Out War Against An Overwhelming Threat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-829519459" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-829519459" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-829519459" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-829519459" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-829519459-img" id="article-gallery-1-829519459">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-829519459" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2110228934">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  is pretty awesome and worth a recommendation for anyone craving a planet-hopping epic; that said, its strengths lie in different areas than the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  trilogy. BioWare's franchise shines the brightest in its universe-building, character-writing, and player choice. Conversely,
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  's crowning achievements are its crunchy combat and co-op implementation. That's not to say that Saber Interactive put together a terrible story, just that it is not the priority. The campaign tells a respectable tale over the span of about 10 hours, even finding the time to give its protagonist an arc; however, ultimately, it is just there to usher players from set piece to set piece, allowing them to demolish armies and armies of enemies along the way.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still,
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  is a blast that shares just enough elements with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  to warrant a mention. Both games feature team-based combat, with players being sidelined by two NPCs. Fortunately, the 2024 release supports co-op, allowing other users to take control instead of AI. Although only featuring three planets,
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  still has quite a bit of variety, all the while demonstrating an impressive sense of scale through its environments. The campaign nails the fact that players are engaged in an overwhelming war against a threat of cosmic proportions.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     While it can be intimidating to jump into an IP like
     <em>
      Warhammer 40K
     </em>
     ,
     <em>
      Space Marine 2
     </em>
     takes steps to welcome new players.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="warframe">
  <span class="item-num">
   30
  </span>
  <span>
   Warframe
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="free-to-play-mmo-sci-fi-epic">
  Free-To-Play MMO Sci-Fi Epic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-671909756" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-671909756" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-671909756" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-671909756" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-671909756-img" id="article-gallery-2-671909756">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-671909756" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-115111987">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Warframe
  </em>
  has managed to remain relevant for nearly a decade, an impressive feat considering the game had a relatively rough launch. Digital Extremes' sci-fi action RPG started life as a fun but repetitive shooter consisting of linear missions. Over the years, the free-to-play title has greatly expanded its scope, even introducing open areas that emphasize exploration. Nowadays, the game also offers far more options when it comes to builds.
 </p>
 <p>
  Naturally, this sort of project tends to be a grind, and
  <em>
   Warframe
  </em>
  is no exception. While money can be spent to speed up progression, players who stick to the free version will not feel too restricted by their decision. More importantly, they can look forward to hundreds of hours of tight gameplay, slow but good storytelling, and a fair amount of customization options.
  <em>
   Warframe
  </em>
  even expands into open areas after its initial hours.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-expanse-a-telltale-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   29
  </span>
  <span>
   The Expanse: A Telltale Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-decent-gateway-into-a-great-sci-fi-universe">
  A Decent Gateway Into A Great Sci-Fi Universe
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1652068230" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1652068230" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1652068230" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1652068230" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1652068230-img" id="article-gallery-3-1652068230">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1652068230" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2120397880">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Admittedly, this recommendation is mostly driven by a desire to promote
  <em>
   The Expanse
  </em>
  as a whole rather than specifically the 2023 prequel game, which is largely a middle-of-the-road Telltale-style experience. That said, the latter is a respectable addition to the show (or books) that also serves as a serviceable introduction to this universe, requiring no prior knowledge to appreciate or consume. Now, as the title implies,
  <em>
   The Expanse: A Telltale Series
  </em>
  is primarily a graphic novel with light gameplay, player-driven choices, and episodic content. Compared to other Telltale outings, this effort is a touch more interactive, granting players some freedom to explore their immediate surroundings. While welcome, these changes are fairly minimal and do not result in a particularly different experience than
  <em>
   A Wolf Among Us
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   The Walking Dead
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  For people already familiar with
  <em>
   The Expanse
  </em>
  , this prequel follows Camina Drummer as she leads the Artemis crew on scavenger runs. The inciting incident involves them finding a valuable item, and the rest of the story focuses on that fallout. Drummer is, by far, the best part of the game, and her writing is consistent with the version that shows up in the Amazon Prime Video series. The Artemis' crew is a bit underwhelming as they are not given enough screen time to shine, and the campaign is a bit too short. Still, the game touches upon Drummer's relationship with her crewmates, along with the general politics that define this universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  Honestly, if nothing else, just watch
  <em>
   The Expanse
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="sword-art-online-fatal-bullet">
  <span class="item-num">
   28
  </span>
  <span>
   Sword Art Online: Fatal Bullet
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-anime-third-person-shooter">
  An Anime Third-Person Shooter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1329434552" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1329434552" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1329434552" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1329434552" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1329434552-img" id="article-gallery-4-1329434552">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1329434552" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1928980915">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  OK, this recommendation comes with a big disclaimer that
  <em>
   Fatal Bullet
  </em>
  should only be considered if someone is a relatively big fan of the source material,
  <em>
   Sword Art Online
  </em>
  . There are plenty of games based on anime that can be enjoyed without familiarity with the series;
  <em>
   SAO
  </em>
  's adaptations are not usually among them since they expect players to have some connection to the characters already.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, if someone likes the franchise and wants an anime third-person shooter that also emphasizes team building, they are likely to have a good time with this 2018 release. Overall,
  <em>
   Fatal Bullet
  </em>
  is one of the better
  <em>
   SAO
  </em>
  games on the market, and its gameplay shares some similarities with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  . For one, players put together a 4-member party when they go on quests, each one filling conventional RPG roles. The combat blends gunplay and skills, both of which are executed reasonably well. Finally, the game dedicates a lot of time to socializing with the secondary characters, encouraging players to build their relationships with them.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-order-1886">
  <span class="item-num">
   27
  </span>
  <span>
   The Order: 1886
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="awesome-setting-great-visuals-ok-gameplay">
  Awesome Setting, Great Visuals, OK Gameplay
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-70169020" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-70169020" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-70169020" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-70169020" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-70169020-img" id="article-gallery-5-70169020">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-70169020" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1327606809">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Garnering quite a bit of criticism at launch,
  <em>
   The Order: 1886
  </em>
  was a fairly big flop on the PS4, at least in terms of reviews. While a hard sell as a full-price title, Ready at Dawn's project is frequently on sale for under $10 nowadays, making it far easier to recommend as a decent third-person shooter that can keep someone entertained for a weekend. Most people will probably not get much more than 5 hours out of the campaign, but they should at least be enjoyable, if not spectacular.
 </p>
 <p>
  Besides its visuals, which still look good roughly a decade later,
  <em>
   The Order: 1886
  </em>
  's best feature is its setting, which takes place in a steampunk version of London during the 19th century. Players step into the shoes of knights who are monster hunters, which is a fantastic premise that really should have amounted to way more than just a single short game. Still, for what it is,
  <em>
   The Order: 1886
  </em>
  is fine.
 </p>
 <h2 id="returnal">
  <span class="item-num">
   26
  </span>
  <span>
   Returnal
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-addictive-sci-fi-third-person-shooter">
  An Addictive Sci-Fi Third-Person Shooter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1677988735" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1677988735" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1677988735" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1677988735" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1677988735-img" id="article-gallery-6-1677988735">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1677988735" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-634411709">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  is phenomenal. Housemarque's jump to full 3D proved to be a massive success, producing one of the best PS5 games that is an easy recommendation for anyone craving a third-person shooter or a roguelike. The 2021 release does not share all that much in common with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , so this is primarily for those who want another sci-fi epic that is ambitious in scope and execution. Selene is an astronaut who becomes trapped in a time loop on an alien planet, and she must complete six biomes to escape. As is typical for roguelikes, death means going back to the start, although the story progresses through defeat and there is a checkpoint about halfway through the campaign.
 </p>
 <p>
  During each run, Selene can pick up or buy items and new weapons, so she is always getting stronger during a run. Initially,
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  is extremely difficult, and most players are likely to spend a good 10 hours in the first three biomes. However, the game arguably becomes easier as it goes along, especially since it is easy to become overpowered during the second half of the campaign.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="helldivers-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   25
  </span>
  <span>
   Helldivers 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="spreading-democracy-through-the-cosmos-one-bullet-at-a-time">
  Spreading Democracy Through The Cosmos, One Bullet At A Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1100068678" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1100068678" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1100068678" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1100068678" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1100068678-img" id="article-gallery-7-1100068678">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1100068678" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-920007838">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  is a very different beast than
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , but the two games overlap in a few key areas. For one, they are both third-person shooters with campaigns that revolve around visiting different planets. As part of a 4-member squad, players will find themselves shooting down a plethora of enemies using an assortment of weapons, and co-op is a big part of
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  's core appeal (unlike
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  ).
 </p>
 <p>
  Narratively, the games share almost nothing in common, except for generally strong writing. While BioWare's franchise focuses on character development and telling an overarching plot with long-reaching consequences, Arrowhead's game is a hilarious satire drenched in propaganda. Even though it does not prioritize its storytelling,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  has great world-building.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately, this 2024 release is for PS5 and PC owners who want an addictive co-op shooter with a lot of replay value. Gameplay-wise,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  is a blast, offering both enjoyable minute-to-minute action along with a plethora of exciting unlockables.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-bureau-xcom-declassified">
  <span class="item-num">
   24
  </span>
  <span>
   The Bureau: XCOM Declassified
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="very-similar-combat-system">
  Very Similar Combat System
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-2023977018" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-2023977018" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-2023977018" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-2023977018" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-2023977018-img" id="article-gallery-8-2023977018">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-2023977018" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1878720530">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Few situations exist that allow for
  <em>
   The Bureau: XCOM Declassified
  </em>
  to be promoted ahead of the franchise's mainline entries, but this is one of those rare scenarios. A spin-off to Firaxis' turn-based tactical series,
  <em>
   XCOM Declassified
  </em>
  is a fairly typical third-person shooter, albeit one with a cool setting and some tactical elements. Set during the 1960s, the story finds America under siege by aliens, which naturally forces the eponymous Bureau to step up to take care of business.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Bureau: XCOM Declassified
  </em>
  shares quite a few things in common with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , including squad-based combat that forces players to constantly command two partners during shootouts. While most of the campaign consists of linear levels, these sequences are spaced apart by interludes set within the Bureau's headquarters, which acts as a hub area. Here, players can mingle with other characters, and there are even dialogue trees.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_57">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Just to temper expectations,
     <em>
      The Bureau: XCOM Declassified
     </em>
     does not handle these elements as well as
     <em>
      Mass Effect Andromeda
     </em>
     , let alone the original trilogy. Nevertheless, the game is fine.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077">
  <span class="item-num">
   23
  </span>
  <span>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stellar-storytelling-amp-world-building">
  Stellar Storytelling &amp; World-Building
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-949461527" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-949461527" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-949461527" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-949461527" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-949461527-img" id="article-gallery-9-949461527">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-949461527" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-241118119">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's launch was a bit of a disaster, hurting the game's reputation. CD Projekt Red's title had plenty of problems on the PS4 and Xbox One, but it fared better on PC or current-gen hardware. The game has also come far since its debut, and it is now far better. A first-person shooter set in the detailed Night City, a futuristic urban hub dominated by corporations and overrun with violence, this RPG has a lot of positives, despite its technical issues.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's story and world-building are its crowning achievements. Night City is packed with fascinating and well-written characters, memorable side content, and environmental storytelling. This is a universe that people can get lost in, immersed in the world's vibrancy, sociopolitical undertones, and strangeness.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lost-planet-extreme-condition">
  <span class="item-num">
   22
  </span>
  <span>
   Lost Planet: Extreme Condition
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="impressive-boss-battles">
  Impressive Boss Battles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1445702231" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1445702231" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1445702231" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1445702231" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1445702231-img" id="article-gallery-10-1445702231">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1445702231" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-285469999">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Lost Planet
  </em>
  got off to such a promising start, only to fizzle out in the span of one console generation. While
  <em>
   Lost Planet 2
  </em>
  is an enjoyable multiplayer-focused experience, anyone looking for a single-player package should check out the original game in the series. The third-person shooter takes place on a hostile, frozen planet overflowing with bug aliens that can reach sizes that allow them to tower over buildings.
 </p>
 <p>
  While not lacking a story,
  <em>
   Lost Planet
  </em>
  is first and foremost about its gameplay, which does set it apart from BioWare's trilogy. Thankfully, Capcom knows a thing or two about crafting addictive combat, and
  <em>
   Lost Planet
  </em>
  is far from an exception. The game contains a satisfying assortment of weapons and gadgets (along with a mech suit) that combine to create a varied and flexible battle system that offers a surprising amount of depth. The casual enemies are good fun, but
  <em>
   Lost Planet
  </em>
  comes alive during its boss battles.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="outriders">
  <span class="item-num">
   21
  </span>
  <span>
   Outriders
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fun-co-op-third-person-shooter">
  Fun Co-Op Third-Person Shooter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1823816178" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1823816178" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1823816178" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1823816178" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1823816178-img" id="article-gallery-11-1823816178">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1823816178" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1564682435">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  People Can Fly's
  <em>
   Outriders
  </em>
  is a live-service game and a good mid-tier option. The third-person shooter launched in a somewhat rough state, but
  <em>
   Outriders
  </em>
  ' gameplay was generally well-received, and it has only improved since the title's launch. The shooter allows players to create a custom character in one of four classes: Devastator, Pyromancer, Technomancer, and Trickster. Along with skills to unlock, each of these classes has three sub-classes, freeing players to explore a wide range of builds.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Outriders
  </em>
  ' narrative doesn't come close to replicating
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's magic, as it struggles to maintain momentum for extensive periods. However, the games' customization and combat should feel right at home for fans of BioWare's RPG classic.
 </p>
 <h2 id="vampire-the-masquerade-bloodlines">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Vampire: The Masquerade Bloodlines
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="choices-matter">
  Choices Matter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-157562370" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-157562370" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-157562370" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-157562370" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-157562370-img" id="article-gallery-12-157562370">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-157562370" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-371031178">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It might be starting to show its age a little now, but
  <em>
   Vampire: The Masquerade Bloodlines
  </em>
  still has more than enough about it to keep players engaged and entertained. It's an exceedingly well-scripted game with an interesting cast who each have their own distinct personalities and motivations. Like the game's visuals, the combat leaves a little to be desired when compared to modern titles, but those who can look past these minor blemishes will find a lot to love here.
 </p>
 <p>
  When it comes to games with meaningful choices, few projects offer as many as this one. Most of these choices fall squarely into that morally gray wasteland that lies between good and evil and so, as a result, the game lacks a traditional morality system. That doesn't make decisions any less important though and there's nothing stopping players from making up their own minds about whether their choices are right or wrong.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="red-dead-redemption-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="character-driven-masterpiece">
  Character-Driven Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-589185951" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-589185951" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-589185951" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-589185951" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-589185951-img" id="article-gallery-13-589185951">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-589185951" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-732703318">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  OK, this is a weird one.
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  has almost nothing in common with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  ; in fact, their settings are polar opposites. While both titles are third-person shooters, their systems only share some basic elements. Rockstar's project is also a proper open-world, and it moves at a slower pace than any of the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite all these differences,
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  still seems like it's cut from the same rare cloth as
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  . They both tell gripping character-driven stories that focus on themes dealing with family, death, and responsibility. They both completely immerse players in their familiar but alien universes, taking them on lengthy journeys that linger in the mind long after the credits roll.
 </p>
 <h2 id="binary-domain">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Binary Domain
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="squad-based-sci-fi-action">
  Squad-Based Sci-Fi Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1855411664" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1855411664" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1855411664" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1855411664" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1855411664-img" id="article-gallery-14-1855411664">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1855411664" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-1318300035">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio might be primarily known for the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  franchise, but the developer has quite a few other projects to its name.
  <em>
   Binary Domain
  </em>
  is a third-person shooter set in a world ravished by global warming that relies heavily on advanced robotics. The campaign follows a special task force created to support a law designed to keep humans and robots separate.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Binary Domain
  </em>
  emphasizes teamwork as players will need to give orders to their AI partners. The player's actions and performance determine the rest of the squad's behavior toward them, which creates an interesting dynamic that influences the gameplay.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="anachronox">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Anachronox
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dated-but-impressive">
  Dated But Impressive
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1172254204" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1172254204" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1172254204" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1172254204" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1172254204-img" id="article-gallery-15-1172254204">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1172254204" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1863780910">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Admittedly, the combat mechanics found in
  <em>
   Anachronox
  </em>
  are a lot closer to a JRPG than an action RPG like
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , but the game still deserves a mention on account of its brilliant storytelling and fascinating characters. It's smart, it's funny, and – best of all – it's wonderfully unique. It's certainly not a masterpiece by any stretch of the imagination, but what it does, it tends to do exceedingly well.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game does have its shortcomings, however, particularly when it comes to locations and general exploration. Much of the story unfolds in dull and desolate environments which can at times distract from the amazing writing, although this is but a minor annoyance in the grand scheme of things. It's hard not to like what
  <em>
   Anachronox
  </em>
  has to offer even despite its flaws and now-dated visuals.
 </p>
 <h2 id="jade-empire">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Jade Empire
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bioware-39-s-passion-project">
  BioWare's Passion Project
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-396195204" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-396195204" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-396195204" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-396195204" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-396195204-img" id="article-gallery-16-396195204">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-396195204" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1610470745">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Much of the systems and mechanics found in the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  games can actually be traced back to one of BioWare's earlier titles.
  <em>
   Jade Empire
  </em>
  was the studio's first original role-playing IP and built upon much of the excellent work done developing the
  <em>
   Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game features a fully fleshed-out morality system based on the one used in
  <em>
   KOTOR
  </em>
  and dialogue choices that are tied to the character's moral alignment. It still looks okay, has a fantastic combat system, and features one of the best RPG storylines of its era. It perhaps falls a little short of those Mass Effect levels of excellence that the studio would later go on to achieve, but it isn't too far behind.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="alpha-protocol">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Alpha Protocol
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="rough-but-worthwhile">
  Rough But Worthwhile
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-36469543" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-36469543" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-36469543" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-36469543" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-36469543-img" id="article-gallery-17-36469543">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-36469543" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-1662271187">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although BioWare did a fantastic job of making it feel as though every choice mattered throughout the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  trilogy, the team could learn a thing or two from the studio behind
  <em>
   Alpha Protocol
  </em>
  . Pretty much everything that the player does prompts some kind of reaction and although they might not all be life and death, they're noticeable enough to make players think twice about every choice that they make.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game certainly had its fair share of flaws at the time of its release and time hasn't done it any favors in this respect. The graphics are still below par, many of the characters are still weak, and the overall story is nothing to write home about. Nonetheless, the nearly endless amount of minor choices that the player can make throughout the game quickly add up to make a major difference when it comes to both their sense of agency and their enjoyment. Those who like
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  should love what
  <em>
   Alpha Protocol
  </em>
  has to offer.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-outer-worlds">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   The Outer Worlds
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="planet-hopping-rpg-with-clever-writing">
  Planet-Hopping RPG With Clever Writing
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-642033360" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-642033360" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-642033360" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-642033360" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-642033360-img" id="article-gallery-18-642033360">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-642033360" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-282728916">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Obsidian's 2019 sci-fi shooter is traditionally compared to
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  , but
  <em>
   The Outer Worlds
  </em>
  is also an easy recommendation for
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans. Smartly written and witty, this RPG grants players a fair few creation choices that influence the protagonist's personality and, consequently, how NPCs react to them. Combat-wise,
  <em>
   The Outer Worlds
  </em>
  is a relatively by-the-numbers first-person shooter, albeit one that emphasizes teamwork through its companions.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Outer World
  </em>
  's story is not quite as epic as
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , but it is nevertheless a fantastic first effort. In fact, the 2019 game is not all that dissimilar from 2007's
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , and Obsidian has a rock-solid foundation to use for the sequel.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="vanquish">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Vanquish
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="intense-third-person-shooter-action">
  Intense Third-Person Shooter Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-2050334382" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-2050334382" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-2050334382" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-2050334382" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-2050334382-img" id="article-gallery-19-2050334382">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-2050334382" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-705156389">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While its gunplay is fine,
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's brilliance lies in its characters, world-building, relationships, and story; Conversely,
  <em>
   Vanquish
  </em>
  is all about gameplay. PlatinumGames took a break from hack and slash to craft a frantically-paced third-person shooter that demands players are always moving. The sci-fi game has a much steeper difficulty curve than BioWare's franchise, and it is more than fantastic enough to justify the effort.
 </p>
 <p>
  Rather than a
  <strong>
   game like
   <em>
    Mass Effect
   </em>
  </strong>
  ,
  <em>
   Vanquish
  </em>
  should be treated as a companion piece that highlights a completely different side of the shooter genre. It is also relatively short, so players can blast through the campaign in between longer RPGs. Just be prepared for a punishingly difficult final boss.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dead-space-remake">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Dead Space Remake
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="horror-in-space">
  Horror In Space
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-835882484" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-835882484" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-835882484" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-835882484" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-835882484-img" id="article-gallery-20-835882484">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-835882484" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-1195988674">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not scary,
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  touches upon a few horror concepts; in fact, Reapers are a pretty great example of Lovecraftian monsters. Still, the games themselves are action RPGs and rarely try to terrify players. If someone wants that, they will need to turn to EA's
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  . Visceral Games' trilogy introduced the world to Necromorphs, terrifying cosmic terrors that are like a mix of zombies and
  <em>
   Alien
  </em>
  's Xenomorphs. In terms of gameplay and tone,
  <em>
   Dead Space 2
  </em>
  and particularly
  <em>
   3
  </em>
  are closer to
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  since they lean into action territory, and they are both fun (especially the second one).
 </p>
 <p>
  Conversely,
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  is unquestionably a survival horror experience. Set predominantly in an abandoned spaceship, the story follows Isaac Clarke, a guy forced into a life-and-death situation that goes well beyond his area of expertise. 2023's
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  remake retains the original's vicious combat and nightmare-inducing atmosphere, all the while tweaking a few things to provide a fresh experience to franchise veterans.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 5 Has the Perfect Villain Inspiration Sitting Right Under its Nose</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-5-tv-show-villain-inspiration-ghoul-good-why-how/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Official news on Fallout 5 is slow due to Bethesda currently focusing on other projects.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Fallout TV show's The Ghoul could inspire Fallout 5's antagonist, breaking from traditional villains.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fallout 76 adding playable Ghouls may lead to similar important roles for Ghouls in Fallout 5.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Official news about the next
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout
   </em>
  </strong>
  title
  <strong>
   <em>
   </em>
  </strong>
  may not be forthcoming in the immediate future, as, although it's certain that Bethesda's massively popular post-apocalyptic series will eventually see another entry, the developer is focusing on other projects. Most recently, the studio has turned its attention more to supporting
  <em>
   Starfield
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , with the fifth mainline
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  title likely still far down the pipeline at this point. Players have thus had plenty of time to speculate on and discuss what Bethesda's plans and direction for
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  might be once it does decide to reveal more.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the meantime, fans received Amazon's live-action
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  TV series that debuted in the Spring of 2024. The show was highly acclaimed, and helped maintain some of the hype and excitement for the next title. It brought the world to life with new characters and storylines in the trademark setting, capturing
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's distinct look and tone, especially the combination of absurd, tragic humor and stylized violence. Perhaps no other element in the adaptation was a better representation of these than the character of The Ghoul. While the wait for
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  is likely to stretch on, given The Ghoul's popularity and role in the show, Bethesda could already have a great core concept for the next game's villain.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-fallout-tv-show-39-s-ghoul-provides-the-perfect-template-for-fallout-5-39-s-antagonist">
  The Fallout TV Show's Ghoul Provides the Perfect Template For Fallout 5's Antagonist
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-255381397" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-255381397" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-255381397" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-255381397" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-255381397-img" id="article-gallery-1-255381397">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-255381397" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2088828621">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="fallout-has-often-featured-the-same-type-of-villains">
  Fallout Has Often Featured the Same Type of Villains
 </h3>
 <p>
  The franchise has pitted players against some iconic villains throughout its course. Figures like The Master and Frank Horrigan were imposing and effective foes, presenting an ideological and physical challenge to the scrappy Vault Dwellers. In the latter's case, having close ties to the nefarious Enclave– the group composed of the remnants and descendants of the pre-War military and governmental elite– marked a trend that would accelerate and continue throughout the series. The Enclave often became the go-to villain in later entries, with
  <em>
   Fallout 3
  </em>
  being the most notable example.
 </p>
 <p>
  There were also other threats, like
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  ' Ceasar's Legion and Mr. House. Although fans could ally with either side in that entry, they were both presented as the more evil-leaning choice. In other cases, and in keeping with
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's general themes, fans battled against mad or fanatical scientists, as with
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  's Institute, with the Enclave still being present in the background or as a secondary threat.
 </p>
 <p>
  The point is that the series has covered this ground well, and the angles are ones that fans have encountered multiple times.
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  presents an opportunity to attempt to incorporate and build on the differences in these elements from the show by potentially considering a lone outlaw-type character for its villain that relentlessly pursues the player, just like The Ghoul.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     will be adding playable Ghoul characters in March, which may be indicative of what Bethesda has in store for
     <em>
      Fallout 5
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="how-the-fallout-show-39-s-the-ghoul-could-be-the-basis-for-fallout-5-39-s-main-villain">
  How The Fallout Show's The Ghoul Could Be the Basis for Fallout 5's Main Villain
 </h3>
 <p>
  Walton Goggins' portrayal as The Ghoul in the TV series was a highlight for many. The Ghoul's skills and practical professionalism combined with a world-weary sense of cynicism made him an excellent foil to the naive and innocent Lucy MacLean. This dynamic and approach could easily fit into
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , and would also have some shades of the Courier's tale from
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  , which, as mentioned, broke from some of the previous conventions for its antagonists.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  could take The Ghoul's character conceit as a jumping-off point, and have its villain be an accomplished hunter who is tracking the protagonist down for their own mysterious motivations. This would be in stark contrast to bringing back the Enclave or another Institute-like group. Rather than returning to one of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's traditional factions that have previously acted as the villain, looking to The Ghoul for its antagonist's traits could provide a fresh and interesting direction for
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's next major baddie.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
