<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Judas Director Wants Fans To Check Out This Other BioShock-Inspired Action Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/judas-director-bioshock-inspired-game-recommendation/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Judas director Ken Levine suggests fans try Twisted Tower, with a demo now available on Steam.
     </li>
     <li>
      The title takes place in a demented version of a children's theme park and features gameplay similar to BioShock.
     </li>
     <li>
      Twisted Tower does not yet have a concrete release date.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Judas
  </em>
  director Ken Levine has suggested that fans of his work check out
  <strong>
   <em>
    Twisted Tower
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which is available now as a demo as part of the February 2025 Steam Next Fest. With FPS action gameplay heavily inspired by
  <em>
   BioShock
  </em>
  and a setting that puts an uncanny twist on theme parks like Walt Disney World, fans of games like Levine's releases may want to take a closer look at
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  First teased back in 2023, an early preview of
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  introduced audiences to the abandoned fairy-tale amusement tower where players will utilize a full arsenal of weapons to battle their way to the top and claim their prize. The game comes highly recommended by one of the video game industry's most renowned creatives and interested players can now jump into the world of
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  with a free demo on Steam.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ken Levine, the creative mind behind the original
  <em>
   BioShock
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   BioShock Infinite
  </em>
  , has praised the brand-new FPS action title
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  and encouraged players to check out what the game has to offer.
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  takes place in a demented version of a children's theme park, and players are tasked with fighting their way to the top of the tower while facing off against deadly mascots. Each level contains unique theming, such as a clown casino and carnival forest, along with corrupted fairy-tale characters. Players can choose from a variety of unique paths in each playthrough while collecting bizarre toys and upgrading comical weapons. The developer of
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  took inspiration from real old-school toys and classic carnival experiences to create a perfect blend between a deranged Disney-esque atmosphere with the punchy gameplay of
  <em>
   BioShock
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="twisted-tower-is-like-bioshock-meets-demented-disney">
  Twisted Tower Is Like BioShock Meets Demented Disney
 </h2>
 <p>
  With branching pathways,
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  looks to offer a high level of replayability and greater player agency than its more linear spiritual successor
  <em>
   BioShock
  </em>
  . The game also hopes to keep players invested by offering a unique Adventure Plus Mode in
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  . While not available in the current demo, this Adventure Plus Mode will serve as a sort of New Game Plus, giving fans even more to explore with new unlockable paths. Hauntingly beautiful levels, satisfyingly bloody gunplay, and an uncannily intriguing story await in
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  , available now as a free demo on Steam.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-513212705" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-513212705" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-513212705" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-513212705" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-513212705-img" id="article-gallery-1-513212705">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-513212705" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1440278569">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the time of this writing, there is no set release date for
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  , but the demo may be one of the best games to play while waiting for
  <em>
   Judas
  </em>
  or any future
  <em>
   BioShock
  </em>
  releases. Interested players will want to stay tuned for any updates on when they can expect to see the full launch of
  <em>
   Twisted Tower
  </em>
  on PC.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monopoly GO: What Happens To Extra Tokens Once Roll Treasures Ends</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monopoly-go-what-happens-extra-tokens-links-once-roll-treasures-ends/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What Happens to Leftover Hammers After Roll Treasures Ends in Monopoly GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Roll Treasures Rewards In Monopoly GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Roll Treasures event is currently active in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monopoly GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  . It started on Feb 24 and is set to run for
  <strong>
   two days.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Usually, Treasure Digging events last for four to five days, but this one is much shorter. Because of that, it only has 12 levels to complete. That means you might finish the event early or end up with extra tokens when it ends. So what happens to your leftover tokens after the Roll Treasures event ends? Do they disappear? Do you get something in return? Keep reading to find out.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-happens-to-leftover-hammers-after-roll-treasures-ends-in-monopoly-go">
  What Happens to Leftover Hammers After Roll Treasures Ends in Monopoly GO
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-8914f562bb9cd844" id="emaki-video-player-8914f562bb9cd844">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hammer Tokens are an important currency in the Roll Treasures event. Players will be using them to smash blocks and dig for treasures on the grid. Every single tile you smash costs one Hammer, so if you’re aiming to complete the event, you’re gonna need a lot of them.
 </p>
 <p>
  The good news is that your extra Hammer Tokens won’t go to waste.
  <strong>
   Once the Roll Treasures event ends, any unused Hammers will be automatically converted into dice rolls. For every 1 Hammer,
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monopoly GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   fans will get 3 dice rolls.
  </strong>
  So if you have 15 Hammers left, you’ll receive 45 dice in return.
 </p>
 <p>
  More dice mean more chances to move around the board, earn points in solo events and tournaments, and, of course, grab even more rewards. And it’s nice to know that all the effort you put into collecting Hammer Tokens doesn’t go to waste.
 </p>
 <p>
  That being said, it’s always best to use your Hammer Tokens while the event is still running. The rewards you get from the Roll Treasures event are better than just converting them into dice. So before the event ends, make sure to spend every last token you have. That way, tycoons will maximize their rewards and get the most out of the event.
 </p>
 <h2 id="roll-treasures-rewards-in-monopoly-go">
  Roll Treasures Rewards In Monopoly GO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Milburn Pennybags holding a mobile phone in front of the Monopoly GO! logo" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/monopoly-go-cover.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Levels
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Grid Size
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Roll Treasures Rewards
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4x4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5x5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       200 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50-100 Free Dice Rolls, Roll Treasure Tokens, Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       180-500 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5x5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Two-Star Sticker Pack, Roll Treasure Tokens, Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       7
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50-150 Free Dice Rolls, Roll Treasure Tokens, Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       8
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7x5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       400-1,000 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       9
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7x4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Three-Star Sticker Pack, Roll Treasure Tokens, Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       10
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       11
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6x6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Roll Match Booster
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       12
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7x7
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,000-2,000 Free Dice Rolls, Lucky Chance Booster
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Overwatch 2 Reaper Perks Feels Like The Rework Fans Have Been Waiting For</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/overwatch-2-reaper-perks-scrapped-rework-buffs-gameplay-good-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Perks have officially arrived in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Overwatch 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  Season 15, "Honor &amp; Glory." First revealed during
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  's Spotlight Event, Perks are the latest addition to Blizzard's hero-shooter, offering new unlockable passives across Minor and Major stages. With this new system in place, Team 4 has delivered on its promise of introducing "groundbreaking PvP gameplay changes" in 2025.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With 42 heroes currently on
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  's roster, players now have 168 Perks to analyze and study. The Minor Perks, Death's Shadow and Soul Reaving, and the Major Perks called Dire Triggers and Ravenous Wraith should be interesting for Reaper players. In particular, Dire Triggers is turning out to be a miniature rework for the Shadow Stepping damage hero.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="overwatch-2-abandoned-its-reaper-overhaul-but-it-really-didn-39-t">
  Overwatch 2 Abandoned Its Reaper Overhaul, But It Really Didn't
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1345267983" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1345267983" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1345267983" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1345267983" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1345267983-img" id="article-gallery-1-1345267983">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1345267983" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2032918324">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="reaper-39-s-perks-may-be-similar-to-his-scrapped-rework">
  Reaper's Perks May Be Similar To His Scrapped Rework
 </h3>
 <p>
  The February Spotlight event saw many of Team 4 sit down with popular streamers and content creators to detail what to expect from
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  in 2025. During a conversation with
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  streamer Emongg, Blizzard Systems Designer Gavin Winters mentioned that Moira and Reaper are no longer being considered for reworks. For some, this was disappointing news, considering Reaper has been targeted for an overhaul since late 2023.
 </p>
 <p>
  Leader Hero Designer Alec Dawson mentioned in a February 2024 interview with streamer mL7 that Blizzard was attempting to modernize "some of his other abilities like Shadow Step." This would have also included a fresh secondary ability. Though this concept never came to fruition, some believe that Reaper's Dire Triggers Perk was born from these experiments.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     It has not been officially confirmed whether Dire Triggers is the same ability or a similar one that was eventually scrapped.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Dire Triggers is one of two selections upon reaching level 3 in the Perks progression system. For PC players, pressing right click will "fire a volley with long range accuracy from both Hellfire Shotguns." While this alt-fire ability costs two ammo, its short three-second cooldown helps Reaper finish off players escaping his typical damage radius. Interestingly, this Perk closely aligns with what fans speculated Reaper’s 2023 rework would be.
 </p>
 <h3 id="reaper-39-s-perks-allow-for-varying-playstyles">
  Reaper's Perks Allow For Varying Playstyles
 </h3>
 <p>
  Notably, the alternate pick for Reaper's Major Perks is Ravenous Wraith. This ability grants 40% additional lifesteal for three seconds when exiting Wraith Form. Paired with Soul Reaving from his Minor Perks, which allows him to collect Soul Globes from dead enemies for 50 health, this build doesn't stray too far from Reaper's usual abilities in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  . Of course, Death's Shadow, another Minor Perk selectable at level 2, also has potential. According to the ability breakdown, when using Shadow Step, this passive "reloads Hellfire Shotguns and has 25% increased range." Coupled with Dire Triggers, Reaper can become a hero even distant squishy targets may respect.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though there have been some criticisms regarding Reaper's Perks not being impactful enough, it's undeniable that the variation in the Perks gives players some creative freedom in whether they'd like to lean into the brawl or assassination archetype more. As a damage hero that is typically picked to burn tanks, Dire Triggers delivers on Team 4's vision of giving Reaper a few "non-tank buster buffs." It also aligns with information from Blizzard's teaser in 2024 about Reaper’s changes, which were originally planned for Season 11 or later. Now that Season 15 of
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  is underway, it seems appropriate that Reaper has finally received a rework of sorts, though it's still possible that Team 4 will adjust his passives as they analyze the Perks system.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avowed's Kai and Mass Effect's Garrus Share More Than Just a Voice</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/avowed-kai-mass-effect-garrus-voice-actor-personality-backstory/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Kai in Avowed is voiced by Brandon Keener, the same voice actor who brought Garrus Vakarian to life in Mass Effect.
     </li>
     <li>
      Both Kai and Garrus have similar personalities, including a dry sense of humor and being haunted by past choices.
     </li>
     <li>
      The emotional depth and shared characteristics between Avowed's Kai and Mass Effect's Garrus make Kai a familiar and fresh presence for fans.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  By now, most
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans who have either seen footage of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Avowed
   </em>
  </strong>
  's Kai or heard him chattering in the background as they explore the Living Lands of Eora recognize his voice as belonging to their favorite turian companion. That's because
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's Kai is voiced by Brandon Keener, the very same voice that gave life to Garrus Vakarian throughout the original
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  trilogy. Immediately,
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans are likely to feel at home with
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's Kai, as they remember the time they spent with Garrus at their side through three of the best RPGs ever made.
 </p>
 <p>
  While simply hearing Garrus' voice in Kai as they play
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  is likely to stir something in
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans, it turns out that the two companions actually have a lot more in common than just their voices. As such, there's a chance that
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans may even forget that the charming voice they hear in the background as they explore the Living Lands isn't Garrus himself, especially as Kai's story in
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  unfolds over time. Specifically,
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's Kai and
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's Garrus not only have similar personalities, but they are also both haunted by their past.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="avowed-39-s-kai-and-mass-effect-39-s-garrus-are-strikingly-similar">
  Avowed's Kai and Mass Effect's Garrus Are Strikingly Similar
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-341405356" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-341405356" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-341405356" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-341405356" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-341405356-img" id="article-gallery-1-341405356">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-341405356" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1613919897">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="avowed-39-s-kai-and-mass-effect-39-s-garrus-have-similar-personalities">
  Avowed's Kai and Mass Effect's Garrus Have Similar Personalities
 </h3>
 <p>
  More than likely, Brandon Keener was intentionally chosen for the role of Kai in
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  due to the personality that Kai shares with
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's Garrus. Keener's vocal tone and delivery were large contributors to Garrus' personality, after all, so it's understandable that the personality the voice actor gave Garrus would apply to Kai as well. At the very least, this particular similarity the two companions share has likely been a unique way for
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans to not only connect with Kai in
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  but also the world itself.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both Garrus and Kai have a thoroughly dry sense of humor, to the point that some of Kai's jokes are simultaneously funny and eye-roll-inducing. While the same can't necessarily be said of Garrus in
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , he has been known to lighten the mood when the team is faced with difficult circumstances, which is a major part of his charm. Kai is very much the same way, though he is arguably more tender and sweet-natured than Garrus, and is therefore more sensitive in serious moments and a bit better at reading the room.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     There's even a subtle nod to Garrus in
     <em>
      Avowed
     </em>
     when Kai says, "I've got reach." In
     <em>
      Mass Effect 2
     </em>
     , Garrus says the same thing during his romantic subplot.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="avowed-39-s-kai-and-mass-effect-39-s-garrus-are-both-haunted-by-their-past">
  Avowed's Kai and Mass Effect's Garrus Are Both Haunted by Their Past
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's Kai and
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's Garrus are more alike than in their personalities, however, as they share similar themes in their backstories, both of which are revealed during their companion quests. More specifically, Garrus and Kai are two companions who are both haunted by the choices they've made in their past. Garrus feels responsible for the deaths of his vigilante group after Sidonis, one of its members, betrayed the team, leading to their massacre.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kai, on the other hand, deserted the Rauataian Navy during the Rauataian campaign in the Deadfire Archipelago. His desertion led him and several other soldiers to seek refuge in Thirdborn in the Living Lands. While they were stationed there, during a patrol near Sailor's Rest, east of Thirdborn, their unit was ambushed, leading to the fatal injury of Kai's friend Tama. As a result, Kai has harbored guilt for deserting the Rauataian Navy in the first place, as he believes it was the catalyst event that led to Tama's death.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     More than likely, Brandon Keener was intentionally chosen for the role of Kai in
     <em>
      Avowed
     </em>
     due to the personality that Kai shares with
     <em>
      Mass Effect
     </em>
     's Garrus.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <em>
   Avowed's
  </em>
  Kai serves as both a fresh and familiar presence for
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  fans, embodying the same kind of emotional depth that made
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's Garrus such a beloved companion. While the shared voice actor may be the most obvious link between them, it's the dry humor, unwavering loyalty, and the burden of past regrets that truly bridge the gap. Kai may not be Garrus, but for those who spent years traveling the galaxy with their favorite turian by their side, his presence in
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  feels like a homecoming in an entirely new world.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones: Kingsroad Shows Wildling Battles Beyond the Wall</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/game-of-thrones-kingsroad-demo/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A new trailer for Game of Thrones: Kingsroad has been released, along with a Steam demo.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players will be able to choose between Knight, Sellsword, and Assassin classes in the upcoming open-world RPG set in Westeros.
     </li>
     <li>
      Game of Thrones: Kingsroad will only be available for PC and mobile devices.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
   </em>
  </strong>
  has recently unveiled a new trailer and a Steam demo, showing a bit more combat across Westeros, including some amazing battles beyond the Wall. This will be the first chance gamers will have to explore
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  , a promising open-world adventure set in the popular universe created by George R. R. Martin.
 </p>
 <p>
  Originally announced in November 2024,
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  was featured during The Game Awards 2024, with the eagerly-awaited project set in the world of the popular
  <em>
   Game of Thrones
  </em>
  TV show. Created by the South Korean developer Netmarble,
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  promises to immerse players in Westeros, offer unique combat, and feature a mixture of both new and returning characters from the franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  Netmarble has now unveiled a new trailer and Steam demo for
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  . The short trailer focuses on combat, showing the main character fighting enemies both beyond the Wall and across regions of Westeros. It also showcases some well-known characters such as Cersei and Jaime Lannister, as well as Jon Snow. The game will be set after the first season of the popular fantasy TV show, and gamers will play a noble from House Tyre. By playing the demo of
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  , which was recently released as part of Steam Next Fest, gamers will be able to explore a bit and get a feel for the title's combat.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="new-game-of-thrones-kingsroad-trailer-shows-action-packed-gameplay">
  New Game of Thrones: Kingsroad Trailer Shows Action-Packed Gameplay
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-79e3519eb404b720" id="emaki-video-player-79e3519eb404b720">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gamers will be able to pick between three classes in
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  : the Knight, the Sellsword, and the Assassin. The Sellsword is a powerful fighter that can dish out a lot of damage but is quite slow on his feet, while the Assassin will focus on hit-and-run tactics to survive. The Knight will be a more balanced class, and some of the developers have claimed that it’s the ideal pick for beginners. Another highlight of
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  is that the RPG will feature an expansive open world, allowing gamers to explore Westeros as they see fit.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2147129562" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2147129562" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2147129562" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2147129562" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2147129562-img" id="article-gallery-1-2147129562">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2147129562" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1148276344">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  is likely the most exciting game set in Westeros to be announced in recent years, the upcoming title has one major limitation.
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  will only be available for PC and mobile devices, disappointing console owners. While the title may eventually receive a console port if it’s successful, there does not seem to be a plan for it at the moment.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
