<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch Had Plans For Virtual Console According to Leak</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-virtual-console-plans-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Leaked documents revealed Nintendo Switch was to include Virtual Console, which was eventually replaced by Nintendo Switch Online.
     </li>
     <li>
      Nintendo aimed to streamline its game release process and long-term maintenance by opting for Switch Online over Virtual Console.
     </li>
     <li>
      Developers wanted to avoid forcing consumers to repurchase games on new systems, a common issue with Virtual Console.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Leaked documents from developer iQue reveal that the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch
  </strong>
  was originally planned to feature the classic Virtual Console emulator. Nintendo fans often mention missing Virtual Console when discussing the Switch's offerings, but the company hasn't seemed to budge on the idea since canceling the service and any support for it. The developer iQue worked with Nintendo on creating its Virtual Console emulators, and the company was completely bought by Nintendo in 2013. Leaks from 2023 suggest that iQue developed the Nintendo 64 emulator used within Nintendo Switch Online.
 </p>
 <p>
  Virtual Console is a sorely missed aspect of Nintendo platforms from previous generations. The service was present on the Wii, Wii U, and Nintendo 3DS systems, allowing users to play through a rich selection of Nintendo's retro library via emulation. Eventually, Virtual Console was discontinued in 2019 for the Wii and in 2023 for the Wii U and 3DS. Since then, retro games offered on the Switch have abandoned the Virtual Console branding.
 </p>
 <p>
  A gaming preservation and emulation hobbyist known online as LuigiBlood shares findings from leaked iQue emails that there were plans in store for a Nintendo Switch Virtual Console. Through reviewing the company's documents, LuigiBlood has ascertained that a Switch Virtual Console that was codenamed "Clipper" was in development, beginning in 2015 as a possible collaboration between iQue and M2, another developer popular for emulation. Instead of Clipper, gamers were given a project that Nintendo codenamed "L-Classics" and eventually revealed as Nintendo Switch Online. The Nintendo Switch Virtual Console aimed to expand what was previously possible, with features like Netplay for up to four that could shuffle the controller to a different person every 30 seconds, shareable emojis, and premade messages like "thx, sry, plz," and "cya." Additionally, there was a thoroughly detailed CRT TV mode that included aspects like the buzzing of the retro television.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="virtual-console-was-the-switch-39-s-retro-gaming-plan">
  Virtual Console Was The Switch's Retro Gaming Plan
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-109061035" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-109061035" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-109061035" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-109061035" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-109061035-img" id="article-gallery-1-109061035">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-109061035" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1128222212">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It appears that the key reason that factored into using Nintendo Switch Online in place of a Switch Virtual Console was that the company wanted to target goals to ship various titles on a short schedule, ensure long-term maintenance for the Nintendo Switch emulation library, and be able to do this smoothly between hardware platforms moving forward. This was not possible previously, since developers needed to test extensively for each retro system emulator (NES, SNES, Nintendo 64) on each platform Virtual Console released on.
 </p>
 <p>
  LuigiBlood shared that in addition to avoiding a situation that could use too much time and resources for each release, developers expressed that they wanted to avoid a common customer frustration about having to purchase the same virtual console release on new systems. It appears that Nintendo Switch Online was able to avoid the pitfalls of Virtual Console, but there are still plenty of gamers who miss the older Nintendo platform.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals’ Invisible Woman Is Already a Big Hit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-invisible-woman-most-popular-strategist/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Invisible Woman in Marvel Rivals offers healing and support abilities bolstered by her invisibility.
     </li>
     <li>
      Many players are eager to try the new hero in lobbies, causing frustration for Strategist mains.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans find both Invisible Woman and Mister Fantastic to be powerful additions and are looking forward to more Fantastic Four characters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans have taken to social media to express excitement about Invisible Woman and her abilities. The new hero launched at the start of Season 1, which features Dracula as the game's main antagonist. Gamers have been flocking to experience the newest season of the popular hero shooter as
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  broke its concurrent player record on Steam with over 640,000 active users.
 </p>
 <p>
  Invisible Woman is a new Strategist in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , which means she has abilities that provide both healing and support for her teammates. The hero's primary ability penetrates characters in a straight line, healing teammates while dishing out damage to foes. Meanwhile, her secondary ability places a healing shield in front of allies that also blocks damage. Her ultimate ability creates a powerful healing zone that also makes all allies invisible to enemies outside the zone.
 </p>
 <p>
  A recent post by Reddit user jayvancealot shows an image of four players trying to select
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Invisible Woman at the same time. Many gamers said they've experienced the same thing in their lobbies, as most of the community seems eager to try out the new hero. Some people who typically only play Strategists said they finally had a chance to try out Duelist and Vanguard characters, as their team already had enough support heroes. While many people were excited to see so many fans clamoring to play a healer, other Strategist players were frustrated by the inability to try the new hero in their favorite role.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-lobbies-are-full-of-fans-eager-to-play-as-invisible-woman">
  Marvel Rivals Lobbies Are Full of Fans Eager to Play as Invisible Woman
 </h2>
 <p>
  Another post on Reddit by user BigPaleontologist520 asked players how they're feeling about the new Strategist. Many gamers expressed that
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' version of Invisible Woman feels powerful without being unbalanced. Some noted that they appreciate the ability to shove away dive tanks like Thor and Hulk, giving the healer more ways to avoid danger during a match. Of course, many noted that the character's passive ability to turn invisible makes her a huge asset, allowing her to maneuver around the battlefield unseen.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-338931946" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-338931946" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-338931946" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-338931946" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-338931946-img" id="article-gallery-1-338931946">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-338931946" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-194365595">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Mister Fantastic was added to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  alongside Invisible Woman and has also proven to be a powerful addition to the game's ever-expanding roster. While the hero is labeled as a Duelist, he also has a lot of ways to mitigate incoming damage and boost his health. Many fans seem to feel the character could have been labeled a Vanguard, as his abilities would also feel appropriate for a tank. With two more
  <em>
   Fantastic Four
  </em>
  characters on the way in Season 1, many fans are understandably excited about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Could Run Wild With One of Fortnite's Best Tricks</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-fortnite-skin-styles-similar-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has managed to make an absolutely massive impact in a short amount of time. Not only has
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  maintained a high player count, but it’s reached a new peak for season 1, making the absurd amount of revenue generated by the game in its first month easy to comprehend. Additionally, fans are responding well to the game’s first season and its gigantic offering of content, as it offers a fresh mode, multiple maps, four playable heroes, and a battle pass full of interesting Darkhold-themed attires. Still,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  can learn something from the king of the live-service world.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is understandably the talk of the town at the moment,
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  has thrived for years due to a number of clever decisions made by Epic Games. While adding entirely new forms of play like
  <em>
   Fortnite Festival
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   LEGO Fortnite
  </em>
  has been a draw, as have big events like
  <em>
   Fortnite OG
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  has been incredibly dominant largely due to the way in which it handles its cosmetics. Every time there is a big collaboration,
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ensures it is covering the associated brand thoroughly through several themed bundle items, with players always getting their money’s worth because of this. Sometimes, there are even a few variants of a skin thanks to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ’s styles, a mechanic that
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  would be wise to borrow in order to make its own skins more enticing.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fortnite-rsquo-s-skin-styles-would-be-a-natural-fit-for-marvel-rivals">
  Fortnite’s Skin Styles Would Be a Natural Fit For Marvel Rivals
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-567056942" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-567056942" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-567056942" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-567056942" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-567056942-img" id="article-gallery-1-567056942">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-567056942" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1944539837">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When thinking about how
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ’s skin styles could translate to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , it may be best to look at how the battle royale title handled its own Marvel collab skins. For multiple outfits, including a few of its takes on Spider-Man,
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  gave players the option to fight through the island as an unmasked version of the webslinger. This is exactly what
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  could do with styles, as for any character that wears a mask or helmet with their paid outfit, a second version could be included within the bundle that removes the mask. A few options for removable mask skins already exist in the game, like:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Magneto’s default outfit and its recolors
  </li>
  <li>
   Any of Moon Knight’s costumes
  </li>
  <li>
   Wolverine’s yellow and blue suit from
   <em>
    Deadpool and Wolverine
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Any of Spider-Man’s costumes
  </li>
  <li>
   Any of Iron Man’s outfits, but Superior Iron Man would benefit in particular, as it would look more like the comic book version
  </li>
  <li>
   Star-Lord’s default suit and its recolors
  </li>
  <li>
   Black Panther’s default suit and its recolors
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Characters with half-masks like Iron Fist or lower face coverings like Psylocke and Winter Soldier could also have alternate styles.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="skin-styles-could-do-more-than-unmask-marvel-rivals-39-heroes">
  Skin Styles Could Do More Than Unmask Marvel Rivals' Heroes
 </h3>
 <p>
  While unmasking the iconic heroes of the Marvel universe is one obvious path that developer NetEase could take, it is not the only one.
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  also offered comic book art styles for its Marvel outfits, giving heroes like Daredevil a cel-shaded appearance alongside their default look that matches the traditional
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  art style. While
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ’ gorgeous artwork already resembles a comic book, ruling out a simple cel-shading filter for its character skins, there are still other options to get more out of each cosmetic.
 </p>
 <p>
  Paid skins in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  could start offering multiple color schemes, as it is easy to imagine Wolverine’s Blood Berserker design looking just as good with brown or red as its primary color. Fully black and white versions of certain outfits could be neat to see as well, as they would stand out from
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ’ colorful maps. If
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  were to embrace a Marvel Zombies celebration come Halloween 2026, zombified versions of every skin could be added, with players able to purchase gruesome, rotting versions of their favorite looks as alternate styles. With so many
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  -like options for suit styles in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , hopefully NetEase looks to the most enduring name in the live-service scene to make its cosmetic bundles even more appealing than they already are.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exciting Changes And Additions Confirmed For Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition-confirmed-changes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Improved HUD and UI: Text and menu items in Xenoblade Chronicles X have been upgraded to enhance visibility and clarity.
     </li>
     <li>
      QoL Changes: Quality of life improvements like Quick Recast, Follow Ball enhancements, and level cap removal are being implemented.
     </li>
     <li>
      New Characters and Skells: Brand-new characters and mechs, including Neilnail and Hraesvelg, add exciting content to the forthcoming Switch release.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Due to the ever-increasing popularity of the franchise, MonolithSoft and Nintendo have been hard at work making sure every entry in the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles
   </em>
  </strong>
  series is playable on modern hardware. It started with the stellar remaster of the first game, and back in October 2024, the impossible became a reality when Nintendo announced
  <strong>
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
   </em>
  </strong>
  , launching for the Switch on March 20, 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  As the release date inches closer, Nintendo has continued to reveal changes being made to the core game, and much like the remaster of the first
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles
  </em>
  game, the Wii U entry seems poised to get similar treatment. The game as it was originally released back on Wii U in 2015 was a flawed gem, and if the newest trailer is anything to go by, the Switch version of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is going to be one of the must-play games of 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   As this list discusses both the original version of
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X
   </em>
   on Wii U and the upcoming Switch release, it does contain some small spoilers.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="improved-hud-and-ui">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Improved HUD And UI
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="text-and-menu-items-will-look-much-better">
  Text And Menu Items Will Look Much Better
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-316014417" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-316014417" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-316014417" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-316014417" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-316014417-img" id="article-gallery-1-316014417">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-316014417" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1067425422">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the original Wii U version of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  , the text was a bit small and caused some issues with some players. The UI was also a bit messy, resulting in some problems that, thankfully, the Switch remaster has already addressed.
 </p>
 <p>
  Taking a cue from the remaster of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles
  </em>
  from 2020, the new version of
  <em>
   X
  </em>
  aims to increase and sharpen the text size. Menu text and field notifications have also received an overhaul, as the newest trailer shows the player uncovering Qing Long Glade with a vastly improved display. Everything looks sharp and clean, bringing it more in line with the other
  <em>
   Xenoblade
  </em>
  games on the Switch.
 </p>
 <h2 id="qol-changes">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   QoL Changes
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="various-alterations-and-quality-of-life-improvements-are-coming">
  Various Alterations And Quality Of Life Improvements Are Coming
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-246568473" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-246568473" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-246568473" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-246568473" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-246568473-img" id="article-gallery-2-246568473">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-246568473" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-932191145">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As amazing as
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  was on the Wii U, elements of it feel a bit out of place today and, thankfully, are being fixed for the remaster. In combat, MonolithSoft has added Quick Recast, which will make using arts a bit easier and reduce cooldown times, as well as an on-screen guide for Overdrive combos. The Follow Ball has also been improved, giving the player more information to help in missions. The level cap has also been removed, which stopped at a hard 60 in the original, further opening up the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  When it comes to character customization, MonolithSoft has introduced a few new features worth talking about. The Switch version of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  will allow players to use hairstyles and faces of classic characters in the franchise's history, including Nia and Mythra. These are fairly small changes in the grand scheme of things, but they all add up to MonolithSoft showing a lot of love and attention to the game, which is fantastic to see.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="new-characters-and-skells">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   New Characters And Skells
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="brand-new-characters-and-mechs-are-set-to-debut">
  Brand-New Characters And Mechs Are Set To Debut
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1713917874" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1713917874" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1713917874" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1713917874" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1713917874-img" id="article-gallery-3-1713917874">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1713917874" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1736264764">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the trailers for
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  , MonolithSoft hasn't been shy about showing new content and characters. Some of the most exciting reveals have been the new characters and Skells, the mechs that players can pilot in the huge, expansive world of Mira.
 </p>
 <p>
  New characters include Neilnail, a female Qlurian who appears in the latest trailer, as well as an unnamed Skell pilot. Additionally, new Skells can also be seen, including one known as Hraesvelg, which uses a slick-looking sword. It's amazing to see that MonolithSoft isn't just content with increasing the resolution of the game and calling it a day, but rather is making sure that the game is given the proper treatment and worth playing both for veterans and newcomers.
 </p>
 <h2 id="brand-new-post-game-content">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Brand-New Post-Game Content
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-cliffhanger-on-the-wii-u-version-will-be-resolved">
  The Cliffhanger On The Wii U Version Will Be Resolved
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-300807897" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-300807897" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-300807897" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-300807897" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-300807897-img" id="article-gallery-4-300807897">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-300807897" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1672877653">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The original version of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  , for all of its incredible achievements in open-world design, sadly ended on a cliffhanger. In a post-credits scene that saw Lao wash up on a beach, he was confronted by a mysterious man in black whose identity was never confirmed, leaving a massive loose end that has been dangling since 2015. It has been continuously discussed and theorized for the past decade, but the Switch remaster of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  aims to fix all that.
 </p>
 <p>
  Much like the 2020 Switch remaster of the first
  <em>
   Xenoblade
  </em>
  game, the new version of
  <em>
   X
  </em>
  will feature post-game content that takes place in a new location known as the Floating Continent. And if
  <em>
   Future Connected
  </em>
  , the outstanding post-game from
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles
  </em>
  , is anything to go by, then players are in for something special when the Switch version of
  <em>
   X
  </em>
  releases. And it isn't just about resolving a decade-long cliffhanger, as the post-game seen in the newest trailer indicates, it will be a rather large story expansion, which is incredibly exciting.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 6 Could Shake Up a Series Plot Trend By Following Metaphor: ReFantazio's Lead</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/persona-6-metaphor-refantazio-human-villain-antagonist-better-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_0">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     This article contains spoilers for
     <em>
      Metaphor: ReFantazio
     </em>
     ,
     <em>
      Persona 4
     </em>
     ,
     <em>
      Persona 5 Royal
     </em>
     , and
     <em>
      P5 Tactica
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Though
  <em>
   <strong>
    Metaphor: ReFantazio
   </strong>
  </em>
  's Louis is a cruel aspirant whose ideals are built on the virtues of strength above all else, he himself is not a god. His motivations are rooted in tragedy, his background as an elda is one shared by the protagonist, and his power is gained not through special circumstances, but rather by his own merits. These merits are, of course, a reminder of just how warped his mindset truly is, as his ideals bleed into a type of 'survival of the fittest' mentality that
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's party consistently undermines through their helping of those in need. Still, there's something interesting about the fact that
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  opts for Louis as its consistent villainous force, whose wit and nonchalance (at least, at first) allow him to act without a greater being pulling his strings.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's elda tribe can be considered as close as a stand-in to real life humans (not to be confused with the monstrous, Hieronymous Bosch-inspired humans of the game), then Louis joins the ranks of compelling human antagonists to come out of Atlus titles. Compared to the modern
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  games, his place in
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  's plot is not a pathway for a secret reveal of a malevolent god who has been behind his actions or the state of the world all along. His wielding of magla is a force dependent on the anxieties of the masses themselves, which acts as a natural resource of sorts, showing that people's fears are not discriminatory by tribe. The same rings true for the capacity for corruption, as explored with
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's Sanctist Church and the title's other supporting villains, oscillating between more sympathetic cases like Joanna and ones less so, like Klinger.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-metaphor-refantazio-considers-its-antagonists-without-necessitating-a-god">
  How Metaphor: ReFantazio Considers its Antagonists Without Necessitating a God
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1323352795" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1323352795" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1323352795" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1323352795" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1323352795-img" id="article-gallery-1-1323352795">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1323352795" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-73608591">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-villains-of-metaphor-39-s-world">
  The Villains of Metaphor's World
 </h3>
 <p>
  Just as Joanna deems people to be 'beasts of fear and superstition,'
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's plot considers the many ways that prejudice has taken form in its world, and how it can breed more corruption itself. Louis is a prime example of this, whose moral decay can be explained, though not excused, by the events of his upbringing.
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  keeps itself grounded in critiquing how its tribes act without necessitating some grand god behind it all, and though its plot does conjure up magical twists and turns of its own, it benefits from keeping its scope to Louis and its ancillary antagonists. The capacity for villainous deeds, just as the capacity for good, isn't exclusive to one tribe, showing how the societal dynamics of Euchronia's people are complicated.
 </p>
 <h3 id="gods-as-final-bosses">
  Gods as Final Bosses
 </h3>
 <p>
  Taking a turn to
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  , the necessity of a god as the final boss is something that, for better or worse, has been a mainstay of the series. There is no doubt that the presence of a god has made for some fantastic battles;
  <em>
   Persona 3
  </em>
  's Nyx, for example, remains one of the most iconic fight sequences in the series, while the twist with
  <em>
   Persona 5
  </em>
  's Yaldabaoth and Igor is considered by many fans to be its most compelling. Still, the reveal of a larger god at play can sometimes run the risk of overcomplicating a narrative, evidenced in a title like
  <em>
   Persona 5 Tactica
  </em>
  , which seeks to explain the events of its story through the influence of Salmael, who wishes to uphold humanity's desire for self-preservation.
 </p>
 <h3 id="persona-5-tactica-39-s-take">
  Persona 5 Tactica's Take
 </h3>
 <p>
  Salmael as a plot device is mostly used to explain the circumstances of
  <em>
   Persona 5
  </em>
  <em>
   Tactica
  </em>
  's story: how the Kingdoms came to manifest in Toshiro's struggles, etc. The god being the game's final adversary does let Toshiro actually join the fray as a party member and allows for some unique mashing of previously established mechanics, though it comes at the cost of dissonant pacing and repetitive gameplay; the Phantom Thieves must defeat colour-swapped versions of previous bosses, stretching the plot out beyond its previous focus on Toshiro's traumas, which made for a genuinely compelling story. Of course,
  <em>
   Tactica
  </em>
  is just one example, and many fans will appreciate the type of lore-dive offered in Salmael's reveal, though it should be worth considering whether
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  games wish to break from this pattern.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's something to be said about how great grounded villains can be. There's a reason why characters like Maruki or Adachi are so appreciated, as a villain with profoundly human motivations, or even one who just wants to be evil for the fun of it, can be extremely compelling. Of course, with how
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  handles its gods, there is overlap in its villains' motivations and the higher forces that bring their goals to fruition; the conceit of Personas themselves is one entwined with Philemon, and so gods can never really be absent from the series' stories. With that said, a future title keeping its plot more contained to human adversaries by following in
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's lead could prove advantageous. While
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  has its overtly fantasy setting on its side, the ability to reckon with the existence of gods while keeping them less central to the plot could put greater emphasis on
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  's future villains in a way that brings focus to its narrative scope.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
