<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Reveals Season 2 Battle Pass Rewards</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-season-2-battle-pass-rewards-skins/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Marvel Rivals Season 2 introduces 10 new character skins in the battle pass, including ones for Magik, Psylocke, and Iron Fist.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can expect a Hellfire Gala theme in the upcoming season, with the debut of Emma Frost as a playable character.
     </li>
     <li>
      Team-ups in Marvel Rivals will receive new abilities, adding depth to strategic gameplay across the ever-evolving universe.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has revealed the skins available in the second season's battle pass, showing off new cosmetics for 10 of the shooter's characters. The upcoming
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  season will kick off on April 11, and like previous seasons, players will have a new battle pass to buy and rewards to unlock.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although shorter,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  Season 0 had a battle pass with skins for Black Panther, Punisher, Doctor Strange, Hela, and Mantis. While Black Panther and Mantis were the skins for the first and last tiers, players got the Hela cosmetic free of charge.
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  launched another battle pass with the start of Season 1, adding skins for 10 heroes, with two of these cosmetics being obtained free of charge. The second season of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is approaching, and NetEase has revealed what to expect from the game's next pass.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  has shared a new trailer showing off the 10 skins up for grabs in the Season 2 battle pass. Named “Flower of Krakoa,” the trailer shows Magik and Psylocke with skins based on the X-Men's classic blue and yellow suits, while Iron Fist wears a stylish outfit in white, gold, and red. Unlike Black Widow's previous skin, Natasha Romanoff now gets a cosmetic that has a similar design to the outfit she wore at Hellfire Galla 2022. Luna Snow also appears ready for the festivities, wearing a black and white dress with feather shoulder pads and a moon pendant on her head.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-characters-with-season-2-battle-pass-skins">
  Marvel Rivals Characters With Season 2 Battle Pass Skins
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-e50a18256b1f1fb7" id="emaki-video-player-e50a18256b1f1fb7">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Magik
  </li>
  <li>
   Psylocke
  </li>
  <li>
   Iron Fist
  </li>
  <li>
   Black Widow
  </li>
  <li>
   Luna Snow
  </li>
  <li>
   Cloak and Dagger
  </li>
  <li>
   Captain America
  </li>
  <li>
   Bruce Banner/Hulk
  </li>
  <li>
   Squirrel Girl
  </li>
  <li>
   Spider-Man
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Cloak and Dagger have been given equally stylish skins, with Dagger wearing a purple dress while Cloak gets a beautiful white cape with gold details. Opposite to the previous Captain America skins released by NetEase, Steve Rogers wears a blue and red suit inspired by the First Avenger's appearance at the 2022 Hellfire Gala. Bruce Banner and Hulk have been given skins with social outfits that include a fedora hat, while Squirrel Girl has received a punk makeover, and Spider-Man has got a winter-themed skin that includes a mask with an impressive level of detail.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-427888056" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-427888056" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-427888056" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-427888056" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-427888056-img" id="article-gallery-1-427888056">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-427888056" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1872044528">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The second season of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is still a few days away, and the developers continue to make announcements. Confirming previous claims, the season will have a Hellfire Gala theme and will see the anticipated debut of Emma Frost as the next playable character. As teased by
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , the developers have announced changes to the team-ups, revealing new abilities and adjustments to those already in the game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Fan Shares Birthday Cake Based on the Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-birthday-cake-title-screen/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley fans integrate the game into life events, like birthdays and proposals.
     </li>
     <li>
      A fan received a birthday cake resembling the game, based on the title screen.
     </li>
     <li>
      While players can't celebrate their character's birthday in-game, they bring Stardew Valley into real life.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has shown off a birthday cake based on the game, with a particularly cute design.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fans seem to be very fond of the cake, with several wishing that they were lucky enough to get a birthday cake like it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  is a game loved by millions of gamers, with the indie title having a special place in many fans' hearts. This has led
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  to being integrated into a number of life events, with players doing everything from getting
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  birthday cakes to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  -themed wedding proposals.
 </p>
 <p>
  In this particular case, one fan of the series was lucky enough to get a cute cake based on the game to celebrate their birthday. The cake, shared by Bluecakeee, is based upon the
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  title screen. The title has been replaced with a Happy Birthday message, with the buttons to start the game still present beneath it, with the load button highlighted by the cursor. Although only one photo was shared, the sides of the cake include the sky and clouds seen on the title screen, giving it some three-dimensional appeal.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-fans-react-to-birthday-cake">
  Stardew Valley Fans React to Birthday Cake
 </h2>
 <p>
  Numerous fans of the series have responded to the post, with one of the most common comments being that they wish they had received a
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  birthday cake like this on their own birthdays. One fan pointed out that the load button must have been highlighted since it's a birthday cake and not for a newborn, and Bluecakeee responded that they were glad someone understood the concept they'd had in mind by placing the cursor there. They also responded regarding the cost, saying that they spent $75 to get the cake made.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-43906878" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-43906878" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-43906878" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-43906878" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-43906878-img" id="article-gallery-1-43906878">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-43906878" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1850563647">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While this and other
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  birthday cakes have been instant hits with the community, the amusing thing is that
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  farmers don't have birthdays. The game celebrates the birthday of all the NPCs that players can make friends with, but the player themselves don't get any kind of birthday acknowledgment or a way to choose a day to be their birthday. While some fans would like to see this added to the game, others seem content to bring a piece of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  into the real world by integrating it into their birthday celebrations in real life. If ConcernedApe doesn't add a birthday for the farmer in a future update, perhaps his next game,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  , will include it.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch 2’s Camera Could Hold Hidden Potential</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-camera-gameplay-gimmick-mechanics-body-control/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  Direct gave fans so much new information, and it is easy to overlook the implications of some of the system's new offerings. While the presentation showcased the way that the Nintendo Switch 2’s new camera accessory can be used to improve online chat functionality, the peripheral has potential far beyond this implementation.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The April 2nd Nintendo Switch 2 Direct answered many of the major questions fans had about the upcoming console, providing a release date and revealing some launch games. It also touched on some of the new peripherals for, and capabilities of, Nintendo’s forthcoming console. Among the many surprise announcements in the Switch 2 Direct was the introduction of the Nintendo Switch 2 camera, and the primary application for the device was implied to be connected to the Switch 2’s new GameChat feature. Specifically, the camera peripheral will allow players to add their faces to the chat, enhancing the intimacy of online play. However, the Switch 2 camera might also hold gameplay possibilities that could add new levels to future Nintendo titles, something that was touched on only briefly during the presentation.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-switch-2-camera-could-revolutionize-gameplay">
  The Switch 2 Camera Could Revolutionize Gameplay
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-285321478" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-285321478" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-285321478" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-285321478" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-285321478-img" id="article-gallery-1-285321478">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-285321478" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1376875200">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The only instance in the Switch 2 Direct of the camera being used in gameplay came when the topic shifted to the Switch 2 updates for
  <em>
   Super Mario Party Jamboree
  </em>
  . The trailer revealed that new game modes and minigames will be added to
  <em>
   Jamboree
  </em>
  , and those new offerings will rely on the use of the Switch 2’s new capabilities. For example, players will use the console's mouse-like functionality to pull back wind-up cars, and they will use its microphone to control the game via sound. But perhaps the largest addition to the game is the new Bowser Live mode, which sees players using their entire body to play minigames via the camera. The trailer shows players punching coin blocks, shouting into the mic, and even balancing goombas on their heads. It remains to be seen what other interactions this mode might introduce, but it’s a taste of the type of mechanics that might appear in future Nintendo games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some have been quick to point out that this type of gameplay isn’t entirely new, as full-body movement has been used to control games before on competing consoles via technology like the Xbox Kinect and PlayStation EyeToy. Kinect and EyeToy games were revolutionary in their time for allowing players to use their entire body for various game mechanics, exactly the way that the new
  <em>
   Mario Party Jamboree
  </em>
  minigames do. An important difference, though, is the company behind the technology. PlayStation and Xbox treated this technology as a gimmick, using it in a few games but never fully embracing the idea of including it in a flagship series. Nintendo, on the other hand, is known for fully embracing every gameplay gimmick that its consoles support.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fact that the first Switch 2 title shown to use camera interaction is a
  <em>
   Mario
  </em>
  game demonstrates that Nintendo trusts the technology enough to use it with its most-beloved mascot.
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch Welcome Tour
  </em>
  , despite its controversy, may be another launch title to include camera-based gameplay interactions. If the new modes in
  <em>
   Mario Party Jamboree
  </em>
  are successful, fans could start seeing this technology in more Nintendo titles in the future. The
  <em>
   WarioWare
  </em>
  games have always been used to explore the limits of Nintendo’s new technology, as have the company’s lesser-known series like the
  <em>
   Chibi-Robo
  </em>
  games. So, even though the framework and name of the Nintendo Switch remain, the Switch 2 camera might be an important step in the evolution of Nintendo’s games.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-high-cost-of-nintendo-rsquo-s-advancements">
  The High Cost of Nintendo’s Advancements
 </h3>
 <p>
  Unfortunately, it must be addressed that fans haven’t had the best reception to some news about the Nintendo Switch 2. While the games and technology showcased have mostly been met favorably, the price of Switch 2 accessories hasn’t been. The
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  camera will retail at $49.99 at its launch on June 5th, and some fans are certainly disappointed about the high cost of the console's new games and peripherals. Whatever the cost, though, the Switch 2 camera still holds a world of possibilities for Nintendo’s future.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Open-World Games With Changing Seasons, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-open-world-games-changing-seasons/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Dynamic seasonal cycles in open-world games are rather rare, but the feature can greatly enhance immersion.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some open-world games implement seasonal changes dynamically, while others tie them to the story's progression, like
      <em>
       Mafia 2
      </em>
      or
      <em>
       Hogwarts Legacy
      </em>
      .
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like
      <em>
       Assassin's Creed Shadows
      </em>
      and
      <em>
       Forza Horizon 4
      </em>
      showcase impressive, fully dynamic seasonal cycles, impacting visuals and gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Dynamic seasonal cycles are quite rare in video games, especially in open-world titles. It is easy to see why: while developers can create various biomes and weather conditions — resulting in worlds with lush green forests (spring), snowy mountains (winter), or dry sandy deserts (summer) — it is far simpler to design distinct, unchanging regions rather than essentially crafting four different versions of the same world to shift dynamically over time.
 </p>
 <p>
  This makes open-world games that incorporate seasonal cycles all the more impressive. Creating a natural sense of time passing in the world around players can enhance immersion, impact gameplay, and even add depth to the narrative. Interestingly, not every game with seasonal changes implements them dynamically. In some cases, the entire cycle is tied to the story, shifting gradually as the game progresses and offering more than just visual differences.
 </p>
 <p>
  Below, we'll explore both approaches to seasonal cycles in open-world games, whether through a free-flowing dynamic rotation or a fixed transition for narrative purposes, ranking them by how effectively they utilize the changing seasons, whether purely for aesthetics or in more meaningful ways.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="bully">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Bully
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="return-to-school-with-a-full-year-cycle-tied-to-the-story">
  Return To School With A Full-Year Cycle Tied To The Story
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1076238740" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1076238740" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1076238740" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1076238740" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1076238740-img" id="article-gallery-1-1076238740">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1076238740" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-627633010">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Long before
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  , Rockstar's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bully
   </em>
  </strong>
  used a similar school-year cycle for its open-world setting of Bullworth Academy and the surrounding town, with a full seasonal progression tied to the narrative. As the story unfolds from fall to summer, the environment shifts with autumn leaves, winter snow, and spring greenery. The relatively modest scope of
  <em>
   Bully
  </em>
  allowed the developers to create four distinct versions of the world, enhancing immersion and bringing a lifelike feel to the school experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  , players have no control over the seasonal changes in
  <em>
   Bully
  </em>
  . Additionally, despite the major visual differences, the shifts are largely aesthetic rather than having a significant impact on gameplay. Still, it is a nice touch that was quite ahead of its time in the open-world genre.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mafia-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Mafia 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="features-distinct-time-and-seasonal-gaps-dictated-by-the-narrative">
  Features Distinct Time And Seasonal Gaps Dictated By The Narrative
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-718288336" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-718288336" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-718288336" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-718288336" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-718288336-img" id="article-gallery-2-718288336">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-718288336" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-341347694">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mafia 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  features both a time jump and a seasonal change in its world, though not as a dynamic transition but rather as a point of no return as the story progresses. Still, given how dramatically Empire Bay transforms throughout the game,
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  remains one of the most impressive examples in the open-world genre for such a change.
 </p>
 <p>
  Starting in the winter of the 1940s, the fictional city of Empire Bay is fully explorable between missions, with players free to navigate its snowy streets and icy roads without restrictions. As the story spans several years, the setting shifts to the summer of the 1950s, bringing a vibrant, colorful atmosphere, faster cars, and different driving physics, as vehicles no longer slip on the ice. While
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  's fairly linear story and limited side activities reduce the impact of its seasonal changes, they still contribute to a lively, immersive world that keeps the experience fresh.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hogwarts-legacy">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="another-year-in-school-but-this-time-in-a-wizarding-dream">
  Another Year In School, But This Time In A Wizarding Dream
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1978510463" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1978510463" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1978510463" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1978510463" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1978510463-img" id="article-gallery-3-1978510463">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1978510463" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1088013576">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  True to the
  <em>
   Harry Potter
  </em>
  series,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hogwarts Legacy
   </em>
  </strong>
  naturally incorporates a full seasonal cycle throughout its story. Triggered by key narrative moments, the game begins in summer and progresses through autumn, winter, and spring, with the world's visual appearance changing to reflect the passage of a school year at Hogwarts.
 </p>
 <p>
  Given the vast and beautifully detailed world, players can expect to be constantly amazed by how different the wizarding school, Hogsmeade Valley, and the coastal environments look across the seasons. However, seasons cannot be changed manually. Once the main story concludes, the game locks into spring permanently, which may be disappointing for those who wish to continue exploring and uncovering all the hidden secrets and activities left on the map.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sons-of-the-forest">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Sons Of The Forest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="challenging-survival-in-a-fully-dynamic-open-world-island">
  Challenging Survival In A Fully Dynamic Open-World Island
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-645863541" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-645863541" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-645863541" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-645863541" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-645863541-img" id="article-gallery-4-645863541">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-645863541" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-477806091">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Open-world survival horror
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sons of the Forest
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a notable example of utilizing changing seasons, a feature absent in its predecessor,
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  , to create a more immersive and dynamic survival experience. Set on a sprawling island where players can explore, craft, and build, the game lacks curated missions but maintains a constant threat from its cannibal and mutant inhabitants. The seasonal cycles are not just for show, as they significantly impact gameplay and survival mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Certain food sources and resources are more abundant during warmer seasons but become scarce as late fall and winter approach. However, winter also brings frozen lakes, unlocking new traversal routes to previously inaccessible areas, similar to
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </em>
  . Players must adapt to ever-changing conditions to survive, with no direct control over the seasons in regular gameplay (though season length can be adjusted in custom mode). As a result, the dynamic seasonal system in
  <em>
   Sons of the Forest
  </em>
  plays a crucial role in enhancing both immersion and challenge.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-wilds">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="re-inventing-traditional-seasons-with-a-unique-approach">
  Re-Inventing Traditional Seasons With A Unique Approach
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1116967890" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1116967890" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1116967890" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1116967890" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1116967890-img" id="article-gallery-5-1116967890">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1116967890" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1787110326">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </em>
  </strong>
  introduces its own take on seasonal change mechanics. Instead of following a traditional yearly cycle, the game features an "Environment State" system, which blends seasonal shifts with dynamic weather conditions. Each of the game's large open biomes undergoes three distinct transformations, and after completing the story, players can manually switch between them for a cost.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game's environmental states include Plenty (vibrant, resource-rich landscapes), Fallow (harsh conditions with increased predator activity), and Inclemency (stormy, extreme weather scenarios). These transformations not only alter the world's visuals but also impact monster spawns and resource availability, making the system a rare example of a gameplay-driven seasonal mechanic rather than a purely aesthetic one. This dynamic feature helps
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  create a living, breathing ecosystem that enhances the series' original concept.
 </p>
 <h2 id="forza-horizon-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-best-implementation-of-seasons-in-the-racing-genre">
  The Best Implementation Of Seasons In The Racing Genre
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-456054" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-456054" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-456054" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-456054" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-456054-img" id="article-gallery-6-456054">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-456054" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1712122903">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ever since
  <strong>
   <em>
    Forza Horizon 4
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the seasonal cycle has been a defining feature of the series, enhancing its broad appeal and remaining unmatched in the open-world racing genre. In
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </em>
  , the stylized Great Britain setting features a dynamic seasonal system that rotates weekly in its shared world. Each season brings distinct visual and gameplay changes: winter freezes lakes, creating new driving paths, while in spring, dirt and mud make off-road driving far more challenging for fast cars.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Forza Horizon 5
   </em>
  </strong>
  carries this feature forward, though its Mexico setting doesn't allow for the same stark seasonal contrasts. With a generally warmer climate, the game emphasizes unique weather patterns, such as dust storms in the dry season or tropical rains in the jungle during the wet season. Despite these differences, both games use seasonal shifts to keep their open worlds fresh and engaging, encouraging exploration and ensuring the environments remain dynamic over time.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="assassin-39-s-creed-shadows">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-new-benchmark-for-making-dynamic-seasonal-changes-in-an-open-world">
  A New Benchmark For Making Dynamic Seasonal Changes In An Open World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1441724505" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1441724505" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1441724505" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1441724505" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1441724505-img" id="article-gallery-7-1441724505">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1441724505" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1519901955">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The latest installment in Ubisoft's flagship series,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Assassin's Creed Shadows
   </em>
  </strong>
  , stands as the most impressive open-world game with seasonal cycles to date. The game features a fully dynamic four-season cycle, transforming the look and feel of every corner of 1580s Feudal Japan. From autumn's yellow-red forests to snow-covered pagodas in winter, the world of
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  remains visually stunning and ever-changing throughout the year.
 </p>
 <p>
  Beyond aesthetics, the game also updates its locations and enemies with each passing season, allowing players to revisit areas and earn new rewards. Some story missions are tied to specific seasons for greater narrative impact, temporarily locking players into a particular time of year during key story moments.
 </p>
 <p>
  Notably,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  isn't the first entry in the long-running series to incorporate seasonal changes, though none have done so on such a dynamic scale. Long before
  <em>
   Shadows
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Assassin's Creed 3
   </strong>
  </em>
  took a similar approach to
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  , progressing through different periods and alternating between summer and winter in the 1750s–1780s. The changing seasons in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed 3
  </em>
  affected not just the visuals of the Frontier but also gameplay, making traversal slower and more challenging in snowy conditions.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: How to Get Negan from The Walking Dead</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-how-to-get-negan-walking-dead/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get Negan in Fortnite
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Walking Dead
  </em>
  expands into the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fortnite
   </strong>
  </em>
  universe with yet another skin of an iconic character, although this time, it's not one from the hit AMC show, but instead one from Robert Kirkman's comic pages. With
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  x
  <em>
   The Walking Dead
  </em>
  , players can enjoy a few game modes and now Negan, who comes to relish in the Battle Royale fight against Rick Grimes and others just trying to survive.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Yet, with Negan being one of the greatest villains and greatest characters of
  <em>
   The Walking Dead
  </em>
  , some might want to know how exactly they can get their hands on him and his famed baseball bat Lucille, before they themselves become part of the dead ones he hunts.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-negan-in-fortnite">
  How to Get Negan in Fortnite
 </h2>
 <h3 id="1-500-v-bucks-outfit-2-000-v-bucks-bundle">
  1,500 V-Bucks Outfit / 2,000 V-Bucks Bundle
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-525168558" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-525168558" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-525168558" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-525168558" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-525168558-img" id="article-gallery-1-525168558">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-525168558" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2060022457">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Negan Outfit Link
  </li>
  <li>
   Negan Bundle Link
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players can
  <strong>
   grab Negan from the Item Shop from April 4, 8 PM ET. Negan is priced at 1,500 V-Bucks
  </strong>
  and comes just as a skin with a cel-shaded style, much like the other Image Comics characters from the
  <em>
   Invincible
  </em>
  series. Sadly, Negan doesn't feature as a realistic character designed after Jeffrey Dean Morgan, much like the other AMC
  <em>
   The Walking Dead
  </em>
  skins. Instead, this Negan is modeled after his comic creations by Robert Kirkman, Charlie Adlard, and Cliff Rathburn.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players who want more from this skin can actually buy the
  <strong>
   Negan Bundle for 2,000 V-Bucks, which is only 500 V-Bucks more and comes with 3 additional items
  </strong>
  . These items include the popular Lucille, which is Negan's iconic barbed-wire baseball bat as a Pickaxe, along with a Wrap and a Back Bling.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Negan will be available in the Fortnite Item Shop until April 11, 8 PM ET.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
