<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Gaming Session Interrupted By Real-Life Bear</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-player-real-life-bear-encounter-video/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley has sold over 41 million copies since 2016, making it one of the best-selling indie games.
     </li>
     <li>
      A gamer in California encountered a real-life bear while playing Stardew Valley on their front porch.
     </li>
     <li>
      The bizarre bear interruption has caught the attention of the game's community on Reddit.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While playing
  <strong>
   <em>
    Stardew Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  , one gamer was interrupted by a startling visitor: a real-life bear. Sometimes, real-life events require gamers to step away from playing their favorite games, but few have likely had to take a break from
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  to avoid a run-in with a potentially dangerous wild animal.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since its initial release in 2016,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has become one of the best-selling indie games ever. As of December 2024,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has sold over 41 million copies, according to its official website. With the game available on all sorts of systems, including mobile devices, fans can play the game virtually anywhere they please. While this ease of access is a major perk for some, it has led to occasionally strange situations, including one involving a real-life bear.
 </p>
 <p>
  The bizarre bear encounter happened while a gamer, known as Chay_CanUC on Reddit, was relaxing on their front porch while exploring the mines in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . While the idea of being interrupted by a bear might seem too unbelievable to be true, Chay_CanUC managed to capture the entire encounter on video thanks to a security camera. According to the footage, a large bear appeared near the edge of the gamer’s house and began trying to scale the railing. Catching the bear out of their peripheral vision, Chay_CanUC wasted no time jumping up from their seat and running inside, still holding onto their device that was running
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-player-39-s-unexpected-encounter-with-a-real-life-bear">
  Stardew Valley Player's Unexpected Encounter With a Real-Life Bear
 </h2>
 <p>
  When sharing the surprise interruption on Reddit, Chay_CanUC described their movement when startled by the bear as though they had “drank a triple shot espresso!” This clip has also caught the attention of numerous gamers, with the Reddit post gaining over 11K upvotes. Understandably, many had questions about the bear, as encountering the massive animal while trying to make progress in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  is not something most gamers can say they have experienced. Fortunately, Chay_CanUC gave some additional details in the comments, revealing they lived in the foothills close to a national park in California, helping to explain the sighting. In addition, they said the roof that the bear walked onto at the end of the video was their garage.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-26943055" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-26943055" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-26943055" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-26943055" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-26943055-img" id="article-gallery-1-26943055">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-26943055" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1454148178">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While most
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fans will not have as harrowing of an experience as Chay_CanUC, many in the community have expressed their love for the farming sim game in real-life ways. For example, another fan recently made a gingerbread house version of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  ’s Stardrop Saloon. With thousands of people continuing to play the game on platforms like Steam, it will be interesting to see what other stories fans share in 2025. Hopefully, none will involve coming face-to-face with a potentially dangerous bear.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stalker 2: How To Get An Extended Mag For Integral-A Vector SMG</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stalker-2-how-get-integral-a-vector-smg-extended-mag-attachment/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Integral-A Vector SMGs are some of the most fun weapons to use in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stalker 2: Heart of Chornobyl
   </strong>
  </em>
  due to their extremely high fire rate. They're easier to handle and can shred down almost every enemy you'll encounter in the Zone. However, the fast fire rate means you'll be running out of ammo in that 21-round mag pretty quickly. A great solution to this is finding the extended mag for the Integral-A Vector SMG so you can keep firing for longer and increase sustained DPS.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-an-extended-mag-for-the-integral-a-vector-smg-in-stalker-2">
  How to Get an Extended Mag for the Integral-A Vector SMG in Stalker 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-651325840" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-651325840" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-651325840" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-651325840" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-651325840-img" id="article-gallery-1-651325840">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-651325840" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-427068222">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To get the extended mag for Integral-A Vector SMG, you'll need to do a
  <strong>
   random NPC encounter mission from Vitya Shepherd
  </strong>
  . To find Vitya, you'll need to head over to the Lisovyi location, east of the Yaniv Station base in Stalker 2. Upon reaching the location, you'll hear Vitya call Skif for help, from inside his house in Lisovyi.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Lisovyi also has a hidden underground shelter with a locked door you can open to get valuable loot.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Heading inside the house, you'll find an injured Vitya Shepherd telling Skif about how he got betrayed by his friend. With his dying breath, he'll share the coordinates with his stash so his "friend" doesn't steal for him. Once you have the coordinates to Vitya Shepherd's Stash, you'll need to head to the location to confront Vetal and take the stash for yourself.
 </p>
 <h3 id="reaching-vitya-shepherd-39-s-stash">
  Reaching Vitya Shepherd's Stash
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-983486189" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-983486189" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-983486189" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-983486189" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-983486189-img" id="article-gallery-2-983486189">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-983486189" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-557941905">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Now you must head towards Vitya Shepherd's stash location marked on your map. Once you approach the compound, the main door on the left will be locked, hence you'll need to enter from the right side.
 </p>
 <p>
  After entering the building, you'll find Vetal rummaging through Vitya's belongings on the floor. You can eliminate him quickly here without setting off the explosive wires behind him. From here, you'll need to
  <strong>
   cautiously walk towards the Vitya Shepherd's stash
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Walk while crouched under the tripwire to avoid setting off the explosive barrel on the right.
  </li>
  <li>
   Disarm the tripwire to the left before entering the doorway.
  </li>
  <li>
   Right before you reach the stash, there's another tripwire between the wall and the bed. Disarm it and reach Vitya Shepherd's stash.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <p>
  Opening the stash will allow you to get the High Capacity Integral-A Magazine, which will extend the weapon's capacity from 21 to 31 rounds. This magazine is also compatible with the named variant of the Integral-A Reimann.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon TCG Pocket: Best Celebi Deck Build</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-pocket-best-celebi-deck-build/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The introduction of the Mythical Island expansion set in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon Trading Card Game Pocket
   </strong>
  </em>
  has brought exciting new options to the game to consider alongside those available from the Genetic Apex set. With a series of new cards available, players now have even more flexibility when it comes to building decks for all of their Step-Up or PvP battling needs, including new synergies, strategies, and powerful ace Pokemon.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the many different cards that prove itself to be a viable option is Mythical Island's Celebi ex, which can be used to create some very solid Grass Type decks. This is especially true when paired with specific Pokemon of the same type as Celebi, with a strategy that revolves around buffing the use of a powerful move and the luck of successful coin flips. If you're looking for the best Celebi deck build in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  , all relevant information including a complete card list has been included below.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="best-articuno-deck-in-pokemon-tcg-pocket-explained">
  Best Celebi Deck In Pokemon TCG Pocket, Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="celebi ex" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/celebi-ex.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  , Celebi ex is already quite a solid card as far as Grass Type ace Pokemon go, equipped with a decent 130 HP, and the Powerful Bloom attack, which enables you to flip a coin for every Energy attached to Celebi ex. For each successful coin flip, Celebi will deal 50 damage to the opponent's Active Pokemon. With the most extreme cases of luck, this enables Celebi to KO a staggering amount of potential enemy matchups within a single turn, including some of the biggest powerhouse ex cards in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mythical Island Serperior has an incredible ability which makes Celebi even more viable on the field. This ability, Jungle Totem, causes all Energy attached to your Grass Type Pokemon to be counted as 2x Energy instead of one. With Superior on the bench, Celebi can stack double the amount of energy per turn, and therefore gain additional coin flips to increase the overall average damage, and potentially oneshot some of the highest HP cards.
 </p>
 <p>
  Dhelmise is incorporated as a backup attacking option, as it also synergizes quite efficiently with Superior's Jungle Totem. This means that in a pinch if you can't get Celebi onto the field to begin with, or you're forced to swap out due to the likes of Sabrina, you still have a solid attacking option through Dhelmise's 100 HP and Energy Whip, which can deal up to 100 damage per turn as long as four or more Grass Energy are attached.
 </p>
 <p>
  Lastly, a mix of Trainer and Supporter cards helps to keep Celebi in play as long as possible, with the likes of Potion and Erika there to heal damage, Professor's Research and Poke Ball included to try and draw Snivy and Servine so you can get Serperior on the field ASAP, and Sabrina to try and disrupt a big switch from your opponent.
 </p>
 <h3 id="articuno-ex-18-trainers-deck-build">
  Celebi / Serperior Deck Build
 </h3>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Card Name
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Quantity
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Set &amp; Number
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Celebi ex
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Mythical Island
       </li>
       <li>
        A1a 003
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Snivy
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Mythical Island
       </li>
       <li>
        A1a 004
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Servine
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Mythical Island
       </li>
       <li>
        A1a 005
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Serperior
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Mythical Island
       </li>
       <li>
        A1a 006
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Dhelmise
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x1
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Mythical Island
       </li>
       <li>
        A1a 009
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       X Speed
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Shop Promo #2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Erika
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Genetic Apex
       </li>
       <li>
        A1 219
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Poke Ball
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Shop Promo #5
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Potion
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x1
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Shop Promo #1
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Professor's Research
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Shop Promo #7
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Sabrina
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        x2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Genetic Apex
       </li>
       <li>
        A1 225
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki: How To Get Floral Fleece</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-how-get-floral-fleece-sheep-location/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Floral Fleece In Infinity Nikki
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Floral Fleece Location In Infinity Nikki
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Florasheeps have to be one of the cutest animals to groom in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Infinity Nikki
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Not only are they cute and fluffy, but players can also get a rare crafting material from them, which is the Floral Fleece. Normal rarity materials are used to make normal clothing pieces, while rare and legendary items, like Floral Fleece, can be used to create a rare outfit as well.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While exploring Miraland and collecting different types of materials in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  , Stylists will eventually run out of spots for rare and legendary materials. This is why it’s important to try and collect them daily so to not face trouble later on when the material is asked for a quest. This is important as rare items don't exist in the same quantity as normal items.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki">
  Floral Fleece In Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="floral fleece in infinity nikki" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2160"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row" style="vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Name
      </p>
     </th>
     <td style="border-bottom:1pxsolid#000000;border-left:1pxsolid#000000;border-right:1pxsolid#000000;border-top:1pxsolid#000000;vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Floral Fleece
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row" style="vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <td style="border-bottom:1pxsolid#000000;border-left:1pxsolid#000000;border-right:1pxsolid#000000;border-top:1pxsolid#000000;vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       A fur ball collected from grooming the Florasheep, an animal that is unique to Stonewoods. Fabric made from these fur balls hides the sincere heart of a heart stealer, radiating both vibrancy and warmth.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row" style="vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Location
      </p>
     </th>
     <td style="border-bottom:1pxsolid#000000;border-left:1pxsolid#000000;border-right:1pxsolid#000000;border-top:1pxsolid#000000;vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Stoneville and Abandoned District
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row" style="vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Rarity
      </p>
     </th>
     <td style="border-bottom:1pxsolid#000000;border-left:1pxsolid#000000;border-right:1pxsolid#000000;border-top:1pxsolid#000000;vertical-align:top">
      <p>
       Blue
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Floral Fleece is a rare crafting material in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  and players can get it by grooming a Florasheep. This animal is mostly found in the open fields of flowers but can also rarely be found wandering around in normal grass-filled areas. Although the Florasheep does get a bit suspicious when you approach it, nothing too serious like Socko. Simply run to it and use the grooming ability outfit to brush the sheep and get the item.
 </p>
 <p>
  To unlock the Precise Tracking feature to find out the exact locations of the Floral Fleece, Stylists need to collect 30 Floral Fleece materials. In other words, they need to brush 30 Florasheeps.
 </p>
 <h2 id="floral-fleece-location-in-infinity-nikki">
  Floral Fleece Location In Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <h3 id="floral-fleece-location-1">
  Floral Fleece Location #1
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="floral fleece location 1 in infinity nikki" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-1-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2160"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  From the Stoneville Entrance Warp Spire, head west along the dirt path to see a field of purple bushes. There is only one Florasheep in the location.
 </p>
 <h3 id="floral-fleece-location-2">
  Floral Fleece Location #2
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="floral fleece location 2 in infinity nikki" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-2-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2160"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The next location has a lot of Florasheeps. Travel to Village Fork Warp Spire and you will collect many Floral Fleeces while walking north to the Dye Workshop. In the nearby flower fields, Stylists can collect five Floral Fleeces. As you approach the Dye Workshop building, go behind it to find a Florasheep.
 </p>
 <h3 id="floral-fleece-location-3">
  Floral Fleece Location #3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="floral fleece location 3 in infinity nikki" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/floral-fleece-location-3-in-infinity-nikki.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2160"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Finally, teleport to Beside the Golden Fields Warp Spire and move west towards the Florasheep. Brushing using the ability outfit Bye-Bye Dust to get the Floral Fleece.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelda Fan Builds Hyrule Castle and Temple of Time Out of LEGO</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/zelda-hyrule-castle-temple-of-time-lego-build/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Zelda fan family built epic LEGO Hyrule Castle &amp; Temple of Time in over 200 hours.
     </li>
     <li>
      Builds featured intricate interiors with iconic scenes from Ocarina of Time.
     </li>
     <li>
      Creation inspired fan community, showing the incredible creativity with LEGO.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Zelda
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan and his family have put together an incredible pair of LEGO builds, bringing Hyrule Castle and the Temple of Time to life in LEGO form. The incredible fan tributes to
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  show the incredible creativity that can be achieved with LEGO, so long as builders are willing to put in the time and effort.
 </p>
 <p>
  While there are plenty of LEGO sets that come with directions and a pre-planned finished build, part of the joy of the blocks is building whatever someone puts their mind to. Gamers frequently look to their favorites when coming up with designs for LEGO builds, leading to things like
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  LEGO creations, as well as myriads of other properties. Now, one fan has brought a bit of
  <em>
   Ocarina of Time
  </em>
  to life.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user mognixnet shared their incredible works with the world, revealing two huge builds based on
  <em>
   Ocarina of Time
  </em>
  . Mognixnet and his two children spent over a year working on the builds, ultimately creating Hyrule Castle and The Temple of Time. While creating the exterior of either of these locations at this scale would be impressive enough on its own, the fans didn't stop there, filling out the interiors of both with extreme attention to detail. Fans of the game can scan the images and see iconic areas and scenes throughout, including the room players first meet Zelda herself in.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="zelda-lego-creations-inspire-fellow-builders">
  Zelda LEGO Creations Inspire Fellow Builders
 </h2>
 <p>
  As one might expect, the
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  community has been ecastatic about these creations. Some expressed interest in making their own builds, and asked some questions in the comments, to which the OP shared some additional details about the builds. They got started back in November of 2003, and while he doesn't have an exact number, mognixnet estimates that roughly 120,000 bricks went into the build, and the creations took around 200 hours to bring to life. Mognixnet notes that the structure under the floor was built using other kinds of blocks to save money, which is plenty understandable considering the sheer scope of these builds. While it's not the first unique
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  LEGO build to make waves, it may be one of the largest and most detailed.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2028119810" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2028119810" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2028119810" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2028119810" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2028119810-img" id="article-gallery-1-2028119810">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2028119810" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-525975786">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For those who might want to create something
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  -related with LEGO but are a bit intimidated at the prospect of a project this huge, there is now an official
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  LEGO kit available. Following the steps with pre-selected pieces would be a good way of celebrating the series without the need for over a hundred thousand blocks. Considering the creativity players have shown building complex and creative things in
  <em>
   Tears of the Kingdom
  </em>
  by fusing random objects together, it's no surprise that
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  fans have shown appreciation for the series with LEGO blocks.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
