<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Player Gets Buried Under Pokemon Spawns</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-player-buried-under-shiny-primal-groudon-zorua-spawns/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A Pokemon GO player was drowned in wild Zorua spawns disguised as Shiny Primal Groudon.
     </li>
     <li>
      Other players were swarmed by Sylveon, Santa Hat Pikachu, and Corviknight during Zorua minutes.
     </li>
     <li>
      The community eagerly awaits March 2025 events, including Tier 5 Raids and Max Mondays.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  player has shared an overwhelming occurrence they experienced on the mobile game, involving a wild amount of Shiny Primal Groudon spawns that drowned the map and the player.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  is a great game for fans of the IP to get involved with the community and their real-life surroundings to become the greatest trainer on the map, and fans often discover these comical happenstances that make gameplay eventful.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  is an augmented reality game by Niantic that was released back in 2016, fueled by the users’ GPS to catch, train, and battle virtual Pokemon. The free-to-play title launched with approximately 150 creatures and remains a popular activity within the fandom in 2025. The mobile game recently debuted its 18th season titled Might and Mastery, and
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  also welcomed Nickit and Thievul in time for the upcoming Deep Depths event.
 </p>
 <p>
  Posted on Reddit by dgmiller70, a screenshot from the AR game was shared on the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  subreddit, showing the player surrounded by a sea of Groudon. It may require some patience to catch the rare Shiny Primal Groudon in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , but at first glance, the spawn rate in this player’s session made it seem like an easy feat. However, trainers will be painfully aware that Zorua like to disguise themselves as whatever players’ buddy Pokemon are, which was the case here. Since the player was caught befriending a large buddy Pokemon during Zorua minutes, they became drowned in Zorua spawns posing as the Shiny Primal Groudon.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-player-gets-trapped-in-a-sea-of-shiny-primal-groudon-during-zorua-minutes">
  Pokemon GO Player Gets Trapped in a Sea of Shiny Primal Groudon During Zorua Minutes
 </h2>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players recently celebrated the Beloved Buddies event, and Redditors also noted what buddy Pokemon they were swarmed by during Zorua minutes. Some mentioned they were caught in a horde of Sylveon, Santa Hat Pikachu, and Corviknight, the latter of which was noted as being a cool sight to see. Since Zorua mimics players’ buddies, one Redditor suggested selecting a smaller Pokemon as a buddy during Zorua minutes, such as Magikarp. Furthermore, another player recommended setting Zorua as a buddy, making it easier to identify when a Shiny Zorua appears in the swarm.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-702255303" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-702255303" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-702255303" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-702255303" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-702255303-img" id="article-gallery-1-702255303">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-702255303" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1543231847">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  community has several March 2025 events to look forward to, including Tier 5 Raids spread throughout the month starting with the Legendary birds: Articuno, Zapdos, and Moltres. Mega Raids, Shadow Raids, and Max Battles will also be dotted throughout March, featuring Pinsir, Regice Shadow, Machop, and Charmander, and there will be Max Mondays and Spotlight Hours to indulge as well.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims' Board Game Might Break a Major Franchise Tradition</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sims-board-game-multiplayer-pvp-break-franchise-tradition/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  2025 marks the twenty-fifth anniversary of
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sims
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise. New releases related to
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  have been announced since last year, with a twenty-fifth anniversary extravaganza spanning the latter half of January and early February, and a feature film based on the franchise announced last year. It only makes sense that further ventures for
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  would continue to crop up as the year progresses, and a board game acts as the newest one.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But there are key elements to board games that are very different from
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  ’ various titles. Even though
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game will likely involve or reference the original gameplay of its video game titles, things obviously must be adjusted for the new medium. Therefore, by making a board game based on
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  , some liberties must be taken that could break franchise traditions.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="most-board-games-have-a-very-different-gameplay-style-from-the-sims">
  Most Board Games Have a Very Different Gameplay Style From The Sims
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1937089127" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1937089127" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1937089127" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1937089127" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1937089127-img" id="article-gallery-1-1937089127">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1937089127" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1935509124">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There’s obviously a huge precedent for a simulation-esque board game with
  <em>
   The Game of Life
  </em>
  . The iconic board game, created in 1860 and revamped to the popular modern version in 1960, has allowed players to simulate life on a board for centuries. But a key component to
  <em>
   Life
  </em>
  is its competitive nature, with the winning player being the one with the most money at the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  franchise has never had a true multiplayer mode before, and, by proxy, no competitive stakes against other players. While
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game will likely try to distinguish itself from similar concepts like
  <em>
   Life
  </em>
  , the nature of most board games is competition. Though it is possible that
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game could feature co-op-style gameplay, it might make more sense for Goliath Games, the team behind this new venture, to make the game multiplayer and competitive to give it a hook.
 </p>
 <p>
  In fact, Goliath Games CEO Jochanan Golad has made a few claims that suggest that
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game will subvert the franchise's single-player non-competitive standard. Golad claims that the board game will be a “whole new way to play” and “a new, innovative way to live
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  .” Making the board game a multiplayer competitive experience would fit the bill for both of these quotes. Details about the board game are still in the dark, though it is promised to be an immersive experience with an expected release date of Fall 2025.
 </p>
 <h2 id="project-rene-and-the-sims-board-game-could-share-gameplay-features">
  Project Rene and The Sims Board Game Could Share Gameplay Features
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2079208907" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2079208907" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2079208907" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2079208907" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2079208907-img" id="article-gallery-2-2079208907">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2079208907" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-142136862">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Multiplayer competitive gameplay may not be part of
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  ’ current titles, but it has been promised for the franchise’s next installment. The ever-mysterious
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  has been marketed as an online cross-platform multiplayer version of
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  was expected to be the franchise’s first venture into true multiplayer gameplay, though it seems that
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game may technically usurp this.
 </p>
 <p>
  Goliath Games is not part of
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  ' core development team, but it is quite possible that EA and Maxis could give Goliath Games information about
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  in order to establish the project’s gameplay features in a different medium. After all,
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  has been performing playtests for quite some time, with details about these play tests released to the public in leaks. Datamining efforts have also uncovered secrets about
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Though all leaks should be taken with a grain of salt, both these playtest and datamining leaks suggest that
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  is emphasizing multiplayer gameplay. Playtesters participated in jobs to earn Simoleons with other playtesters. These Simoleons could also be used to purchase clothing or items like coffee from a coffee shop where playtesters were “working.” Perhaps
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game will establish work gameplay alongside other players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately, more details about
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  board game will be released as the year progresses. Whatever form it takes,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sims
   </em>
  </strong>
  board game will almost certainly break the mold that its video game predecessors have established.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Go Muffin Codes (March 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/go-go-muffin-codes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       All Go Go Muffin Codes
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Redeem Go Go Muffin Codes
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get New Go Go Muffin Codes
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Go Go Muffin
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one of the best Idle RPGs for mobile platforms. There are many classes you can play, skills you can use, and items you can collect to equip your character. Also, the game has promo codes and you can redeem them to get some valuable bonuses. In this guide, you will find a list of all the
  <em>
   Go Go Muffin
  </em>
  codes and learn how you can use them to get helpful rewards in-game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated March 6, 2025, by Artur Novichenko:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   Two new codes have been added to this
   <strong>
    Go Go Muffin
   </strong>
   guide, offering a fresh batch of in-game rewards. They provide useful resources like Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food, and Raw Material to help you progress faster. Make sure to redeem them as soon as possible before they expire. Bookmark this guide and check back regularly for the latest codes.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="all-go-go-muffin-codes">
  All Go Go Muffin Codes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Go Go Muffin characters" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="working-go-go-muffin-codes">
  Working Go Go Muffin Codes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    muffiin0303
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
   <strong>
    (NEW)
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    muffin0303
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
   <strong>
    (NEW)
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    WEEKEND2025
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINWEEKEND
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    LUCKSNAKE2025
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PARTYTIME
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    LUCKYMUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GoDanManREAL
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    HAPPY2025
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GOGONattoYT
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINBUDDY
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    TimaeuSSMuff
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    WILDCATMUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    VANOSSMUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you rewards such as Gold, Star EXP, Pet Food and Raw Material.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    DUALBLADE
   </strong>
   – Gives you a Back Attachment Cosmetic.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFIN555
   </strong>
   – Gives you x50 Stellarite, x300 Raw Material, and x10,000 Gold.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINGOGO
   </strong>
   – Gives you x100 Stellarite and x1 Summoning String.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you x100 Stellarite and x1 Summoning String.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINCREATOR
   </strong>
   – Gives you x50 Pet Food, x10,000 Gold, and x100 Star EXP.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    TLPMUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you x10,000 Gold, x1 Star Verses, and x10 Star Exp.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    SUPERMUFFIN
   </strong>
   – Gives you the Super Muffin cape.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    TIMAEUSSGOGO
   </strong>
   – Gives you x50 Pet Food, x1 Summoning String, and x10,000 Gold.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GOGOKAIROS
   </strong>
   – Gives you x50 Pet Food, x1 Summoning String, and x10,000 Gold.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GOGOHAVOC
   </strong>
   – Gives you x1,000 Raw Material, x10,000 Gold, and x2 Exploration Ticket.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINTOP
   </strong>
   – Gives you x1,000 Raw Material, x100 Rune Character, and x20,000 Gold.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="expired-go-go-muffin-codes">
  Expired Go Go Muffin Codes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MUFFINGIFT
   </strong>
   – Gives you x100 Stellarite and x1 Star Verses.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Codes in
  <em>
   Go Go Muffin
  </em>
  are a great source of various useful resources. With their help, you will be able to get things like Gold, Stellarite, and Summoning Strings. All of these items can be really helpful and you definitely shouldn’t miss them.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Seven Deadly Sins: Grand Cross Codes
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-redeem-go-go-muffin-codes">
  How to Redeem Go Go Muffin Codes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Go Go Muffin the codes tab" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The rewards you can get for redeeming
  <em>
   Go Go Muffin
  </em>
  codes are great, but you will need to learn how the redemption process works if you want to get them. Fortunately, it’s not that complicated, and you can claim your bonuses in a few simple steps, which are not very different from most other mobile games. Follow the instructions below to redeem
  <em>
   Go Go Muffin
  </em>
  codes and obtain your rewards:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Launch
   <em>
    Go Go Muffin
   </em>
   and wait for the game to load.
  </li>
  <li>
   After that, tap your profile icon in the top left corner of the screen.
  </li>
  <li>
   In the profile menu, tap the Gear icon to open the Settings menu.
  </li>
  <li>
   Tap the Redeem Code button in the Settings menu.
  </li>
  <li>
   Enter the code you want to redeem in the menu that pops up.
  </li>
  <li>
   Tap the Confirm button. The reward will be sent to your Mail.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-new-go-go-muffin-codes">
  How to Get New Go Go Muffin Codes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Go Go Muffin characters" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/go-go-muffin-codes-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The developers of
  <em>
   Go Go Muffin
  </em>
  constantly add codes to this mobile game, and this article will be updated if any new codes are released. You can bookmark this guide and check it for updates from time to time. It’s definitely worth it as the developers add new bonuses to the game quite often.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Go Go Muffin
   </em>
  </strong>
  is available on mobile devices.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Finals Releases New Update for March 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-finals-new-update-patch-notes-march-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Embark Studios releases The Finals update 5.12.0 for PlayStation 5, Xbox Series X/S, and PC.
     </li>
     <li>
      The latest patch includes a plethora of bug fixes and some minor weapon balance changes.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Model 1887 receives a slight buff, increasing its damage from 11 to 12 per pellet and decreasing the duration of the lever-action animation from 0.85s to 0.8s.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
    <strong>
     The Finals
    </strong>
   </em>
   developer Embark Studios has released a new patch update for its popular first-person
  </span>
  shooter, bringing the title to version 5.12.0 with a plethora of adjustments, balance changes, bug fixes, and more. Season 6 of
  <em>
   The Finals
  </em>
  is due to launch later this month, with a whole host of new content expected for players to jump into. While official details on the new season are scarce, there is a brand-new update to download right now.
 </p>
 <p>
  Information surrounding Season 6 might be limited right now, but those looking to take their skills to the next level will be pleased to know that Embark Studios recently made a major announcement surrounding
  <em>
   The Finals
  </em>
  ' entry into the world of esports. Later this year,
  <em>
   The Finals
  </em>
  players will have the chance to put their skills to the test and take part in open qualifiers for the 2025 Major, a new tournament with a massive prize pool of $100,000. The event will take place in Q4 2025 and will even feature an in-person LAN event. Embark also revealed plenty of new gameplay changes coming with Season 6 to prepare the title for "high-level competition."
 </p>
 <p>
  So, there's definitely plenty to look forward to with Season 6 and a new Major tournament on the horizon, but for those living in the here and now, Embark Studios has just deployed a brand-new update for
  <em>
   The Finals
  </em>
  . The patch is available to download right now on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series X/S, and PC via Steam, bringing the game to version 5.12.0 with plenty of changes. According to the official patch notes, which can be found further down this article, the latest update includes balance changes for the Model 1887 and Recurve Bow, as well as plenty of new bug fixes and improvements.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-517942877" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-517942877" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-517942877" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-517942877" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-517942877-img" id="article-gallery-1-517942877">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-517942877" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-948073801">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Patch 5.12.0 not only increases the Recurve Bow's damage per shot from 120 to 124 when at max draw, but also includes a slight buff to the Model 1887, making it a great contender for a player's medium build in
  <em>
   The Finals
  </em>
  . While the weapon was previously considered an underperformer, Embark Studios is attempting to rectify that as the latest update increases the damage from 11 to 12 per pellet. The studio has also decreased the duration of the lever-action animation from 0.85s to 0.8s, effectively increasing the weapon’s fire rate from 70RPM to 75RPM. Embark says it had weakened the weapon too much with past updates, so these new changes "should nudge it back to a better place."
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from a new store rotation,
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   today's update does not contain any major new content. However, Embark Studios did recently begin teasing
   <em>
    The Finals
   </em>
   ' Season 6 update. Although it's unlikely to appear in the upcoming season, the developers also recently revealed that they would love to create a medieval-style
  </span>
  map for the game, something fans have been requesting for quite some time now.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-finals-update-5-12-0-patch-notes-for-march-6">
  The Finals Update 5.12.0 Patch Notes for March 6
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Balance Changes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weapons
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Model 1887
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increased damage from 11 to 12 per pellet
  </li>
  <li>
   Decreased the duration of the lever-action animation from 0.85s to 0.8s, effectively increasing the weapon’s fire rate from 70RPM to 75RPM
   <em>
    Dev Note: Having now had time to analyse the Model’s performance on live, following our last round of balance changes, we feel we’ve maybe weakened the weapon a little too much. These changes should nudge it back to a better place.
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Recurve Bow
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increased damage per shot, when the bow is at max draw, from 120 to 124. The base damage per shot remains at 60 damage
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Content and Bug Fixes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Animation
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where the Spear’s secondary animation wouldn’t play if activated right after using up all the charges of the previously equipped item
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where the impact animation would continuously play after blocking a shot with the Riot Shield
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Cosmetics
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Victory Shade Set
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Now loops and overwrites colors continuously instead of stopping after 10 eliminations
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where team colors wouldn’t update when changing colorblindness settings or toggling Use Enemy Color
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Concrete Smoke Model 1887 Skin
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where the left hand would remain static in mid-air when playing the Prairie Twirl Deploy Animation
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Gameplay
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that could cause objects to have collision and be invisible if they were destroyed and dematerialized during the same frame
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a bug where the wrong item would be equipped after getting glitched and the item would be unusable
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where attempting to use a Weapon or Gadget immediately after swapping could activate the previously equipped item instead
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where swapping to your Specialization would immediately switch back to your Weapon
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed issue where ADS would stop working
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Maps
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Kyoto
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Small Kyoto destruction tweak to enhance server performance
  </li>
  <li>
   Lowered bamboo stump heights when broken to help with traversal
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where vaults could continuously fall through floor due to the inability to find a solid surface to rest on
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Bernal
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Updated the thickness of cinder block walls for smoother traversal
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Fortune Stadium
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Adjusted collision on beams in the Mall to prevent players from getting stuck in wedge-shaped collisions
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Practice Range
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where the trophies were incorrectly labeled
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where all bots could incorrectly appear as friendlies or enemies
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Skyway Stadium
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where players could walk on invisible collision underneath the ground in the Hotels area
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Las Vegas
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Slightly adjusted the jump pad and a player spawn between Glamora and Eastwood casinos for improved flow
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Performance &amp; Stability
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed a rare crash in the animation system
  </li>
  <li>
   Added support for AMD Anti-Lag 2
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved performance for players experiencing issues due to large friend lists
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Rendering
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Enhanced high and epic-quality reflections in game intro sequences
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where an unintended post-process effect could sometimes appear on player cards
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Settings
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added a "No AA" resolution scaling option that completely disables anti-aliasing and temporal resolution scaling
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where certain video options, including 120Hz mode, would reset to default on Xbox after restarting the game
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where certain input devices or buttons could cause duplicated inputs, preventing players from equipping their specialization by triggering the swap function twice
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Security and Anti-cheat
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Improved detections
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Store
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   In addition to this week's store rotation, we’ve added a .50 Akimbo skin, Monochrome Edge, to the customization menu
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   UI
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed a rare issue where squad members would sometimes not appear in the bottom-left widget and scoreboard during a match
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - Skeleton In The Closet Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-skeleton-in-the-closet-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  has plenty of optional adventures that are well hidden.
  <strong>
   Skeleton in The Closet
  </strong>
  is a side quest where Henry needs to help the Zimburg brothers once more; this time, to recover the stolen chest that they were transporting to Sedletz Monastery. But to do that, Henry will have to deal with a huge enemy camp, and protect these risky Knights from a certain demise.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  If players are having trouble finding this secondary quest, here is all the information they need to know about it, from how to start it, to how to defeat all the annoying Cuman mercenaries, and where to find the stolen chest to complete this quest in a breeze.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-start-skeleton-in-the-closet-in-kcd2">
  How To Start Skeleton In The Closet In KCD2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-678146043" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-678146043" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-678146043" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-678146043" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-678146043-img" id="article-gallery-1-678146043">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-678146043" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2102675857">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To start Skeleton in The Closet, players should have completed Bellatores, a quest granted by Jan Posy of Zimburg in Belany. After completing this side quest and rescuing Miroslav, Jan's brother, they need to wait a few days before Skeletons in the Closte become available. Travel to the Ruins of Zimburg and look for Jan to start the quest.
 </p>
 <p>
  Before completing Skeleton In The Closet, Henry already knew how bold the Zimburg brothers were, especially Posy, the eldest. This time, though, Tugbone suggests a more reasonable approach, much to the discomfort of Jan Posy, who states that is the way of murderers and thieves, not of honorable knights.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-complete-skeleton-in-the-closet-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  How To Complete Skeleton In The Closet In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-614340254" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-614340254" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-614340254" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-614340254" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-614340254-img" id="article-gallery-2-614340254">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-614340254" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1731916068">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It is recommended to take a stealthy approach to beat this enormous camp filled with dangerous mercenaries. Use
  <strong>
   poison
  </strong>
  , long-range arrows, and all the 'dirty tactics' you can to ensure the Cuman camp population drops
  <strong>
   before engaging in melee
  </strong>
  . That way, players can
  <strong>
   prevent any of the brothers from dying
  </strong>
  during the assault, which will result in a
  <strong>
   failed quest
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, if players want to walk the honorable path, they can engage in direct combat with the mercenaries (around 9 in total) but they should
  <strong>
   prevent them from swarming the brothers
  </strong>
  at any cost. The Zimburg brothers will try to do their best to help Henry, but
  <strong>
   if they get surrounded, they will die in no time
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, after the battle is over, players will need to talk to Jan Posy who will tell them to search the camp for the missing chest. Players need to look for the Cuman commander named Sharkan and loot his corpse for the chest keys. Then, go to the main tent and look for the coffer near the right side, open it, and take the Reliquary Quest Item from within.
 </p>
 <p>
  Go back to Zimburg and ask about the Reliquary. He will explain that they have been deprived of their inheritance, and to prove that they are following the tradition and teaching their mother a lesson, they are taking the remains of their dead father to Sedletz Monastery.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though this Secondary Quest is quite straightforward, as with the Bellatores Secondary Quest, it will have a hidden reward. Players can go back to Zimburg Ruins and talk to Jan Posy to learn several new Sword Combos, like the
  <strong>
   False Edge (Tier IV)
  </strong>
  that bypasses the opponents' defense. Also, once players complete Skeleton in the Closet, Jan Posy will offer to train them in the
  <strong>
   Master Grade Polearms
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Swordsmanship
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Heavy Weapon skills
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This is one of the only
  <strong>
   Master Grade trainers
  </strong>
  that players will come across during the adventure, so make sure to save enough Groschen to pay for the training, and go for it. And remember to drink the Fox Potion beforehand, to improve the experience amount earned with the training.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
