<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring: Nightreign Could Be the Start of a Third Pillar for FromSoftware Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elden-ring-nightreign-fromsoftware-multiplayer-co-op-subgenre-good-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Nightreign marks a bold shift for FromSoftware towards multiplayer-focused games with a new cooperative-first design philosophy.
     </li>
     <li>
      FromSoftware is diversifying its game design with Souls games, Armored Core 6, and Nightreign-style multiplayer experiences.
     </li>
     <li>
      Nightreign changes the formula with fast, precise gameplay, potentially making a long-term impact on the co-op gaming market.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For more than a decade, FromSoftware has been renowned for pioneering the Soulslike combat formula, but
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring: Nightreign
   </em>
  </strong>
  could be a sign that something is about to change. As the studio moves away from being associated with only one type of game, despite the huge success of some of the best games like
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  , there is a chance that it may be adopting multiplayer experiences as a new focus going forward.
 </p>
 <p>
  Following on the heels of
  <em>
   Armored Core 6
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Shadow of the Erdtree
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elden Ring: Nightreign
  </em>
  marks the third genre departure in as many years. Whilst it has striven for mechanical diversity in its Soulslike titles, FromSoftware’s releases have been mostly predictable until it revived the mech combat franchise it used to be known for.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fromsoftware-rsquo-s-diversifying-game-design-is-good-for-the-studio">
  FromSoftware’s Diversifying Game Design Is Good for the Studio
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1374176378" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1374176378" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1374176378" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1374176378" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1374176378-img" id="article-gallery-1-1374176378">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1374176378" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-122386445">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  is the first game in FromSoftware’s catalog that puts multiplayer front and center. Many fans have often pondered what could be done with a Soulslike formula for a multiplayer environment, with some going as far as making mods like seamless co-op for
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  to specifically enhance this aspect. It is a welcome surprise then that
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  takes such a bold step toward embracing a cooperative-first design philosophy, and one that will surely have its competitors taking notes.
 </p>
 <p>
  But where
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  is a spin-off of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Armored Core 6
  </em>
  could not be more different. Before the studio even took on the mastermind of the Soulslike genre, Hidetaka Miyazaki, it was deep into the mech-based combat of
  <em>
   Armored Core
  </em>
  . As it has brought the series out of its long slumber to much acclaim, FromSoftware has found itself with three distinct pillars to build upon: Soulslike action-adventure,
  <em>
   Armored Core
  </em>
  mechs, and
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
    Nightreign-
   </em>
   style
  </span>
  multiplayer.
 </p>
 <p>
  The clearest sign that the studio is branching out, though, comes from Miyazaki himself, who said FromSoftware was not making a sequel to
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . As the genre was FromSoftware’s bread and butter, the news is certainly surprising, but if it’s really planning on leaving the formula to rest for a while, that may not be such a bad thing. Given the revolutionary shift that the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  series made to third-person action RPGs, redirecting those efforts might mean different genres benefit from the studio’s expertise.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  isn’t exactly a Soulslike anymore - and that may be exactly what is needed right now. By blending Soulslikes and Roguelikes, with a sprinkling of Battle Royale,
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  has its own distinct identity. FromSoftware should focus on creating more of these different experiences going forward, if not even let other studios take up the Soulslike mantle.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-nightreign-can-forever-change-a-crowded-co-op-market">
  How Nightreign Can Forever Change a Crowded Co-op Market
 </h3>
 <p>
  The network test revealed that
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  is changing the formula. Players are encouraged to be fast and precise, reinterpreting the try-and-try-again difficulty format the studio is known for as new runs, akin to a Roguelike. Those who got to experience the test remarked how engaging this new style is, and knowing FromSoftware’s knack for finding a good gameplay loop, it’s certain to make other developers sit up and take notice.
 </p>
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Nightreign
  </em>
  gets support for many years to come, it is possible that it may even have a similar impression as the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  series. It's hard to tell if this will spawn a "Nightreignlike" sub-genre, most likely not, but there could be some conspicuous new trends emerging if it is a long-term hit.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a lot of highly successful co-op games being actively supported at the moment, and many of those were instant disruptors, like the breakout success of
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  . If Nightreign could just match this success, it would already be a good way to break into the co-op scene, but with the
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  IP and FromSoftware’s name on the box, it may well grow big.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March 21 is Going to Be a Big Day for Bleach Fans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/bleach-rebirth-of-souls-game-roster-release-date-march-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Bleach: Rebirth of Souls releases on March 21 for PC, PS4, PS5, and Xbox Series X, offering 31 playable characters.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game recaps the Bleach story from the first arc to the Arrancar arc.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game features single-player, local multiplayer, and online PvP.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Friday, March 21 is going to be an exciting day for
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  fans, as that's when the new game
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
   </em>
  </strong>
  hits the market.
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  is one of the "big three" in anime alongside
  <em>
   Naruto
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   One Piece
  </em>
  , though it hasn't enjoyed quite as much success as those two franchises. The mid-2000s were the height of
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  's popularity, with numerous video games released based on the franchise.
  <em>
   Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  is coming at a time when there hasn't been a proper console game in over a decade, making its release especially exciting for longtime fans of the anime and manga series.
 </p>
 <p>
  The mid-2000s were a great time to be a
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  fan, with new manga volumes, anime episodes, and video games for fans to check out on a regular basis. On the video game front, fans were treated to games like
  <em>
   Bleach: The Blade of Fate
  </em>
  on the Nintendo DS, which is actually one of the highest-rated DS games, as well as its sequel,
  <em>
   Bleach: Dark Souls
  </em>
  . The DS also saw the strategy RPG
  <em>
   Bleach: The 3rd Phantom
  </em>
  , though it wasn't quite as well-received as its predecessors. As far as other gaming systems go, there was
  <em>
   Bleach: Shattered Blade
  </em>
  on the Wii, numerous Japanese-exclusive
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  PSP games, and
  <em>
   Bleach: Soul Resurrection
  </em>
  on the PS3, which launched in 2011.
 </p>
 <p>
  Recent years have seen
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  video games largely relegated to the mobile space, but that's going to change with
  <em>
   Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  on March 21. A 3D fighting game developed by Tamsoft and published by Bandai Namco Entertainment,
  <em>
   Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  is releasing for PC, PS4, PS5, and Xbox Series X. The game's story recaps the
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  story from the first arc to the Arrancar arc. The game features 31 playable characters, online battles, and local multiplayer, which should make it a well-rounded fighting game option for
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  fans.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="when-is-the-bleach-rebirth-of-souls-release-date">
  When is the Bleach: Rebirth of Souls Release Date?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-304583575" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-304583575" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-304583575" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-304583575" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-304583575-img" id="article-gallery-1-304583575">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-304583575" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-305196824">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Friday, March 21 for PC, PS4, PS5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series X
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="bleach-rebirth-of-souls-roster">
  Bleach: Rebirth of Souls Roster
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Byakuya Kuchiki
  </li>
  <li>
   Coyote Starrk
  </li>
  <li>
   Genryusai Shigekuni Yamamoto
  </li>
  <li>
   Gin Ichimaru
  </li>
  <li>
   Grimmjow Jaegerjaqueze
  </li>
  <li>
   Ichigo Kurosaki
  </li>
  <li>
   Ikkaku Madarame
  </li>
  <li>
   Izuru Kira
  </li>
  <li>
   Kaien Shiba
  </li>
  <li>
   Kaname Tosen
  </li>
  <li>
   Kenpachi Zaraki
  </li>
  <li>
   Kisuke Urahara
  </li>
  <li>
   Mayuri Kurotsuchi
  </li>
  <li>
   Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck
  </li>
  <li>
   Nnoitra Gilga
  </li>
  <li>
   Rangiku Matsumoto
  </li>
  <li>
   Renji Arabarai
  </li>
  <li>
   Rukia Kuchiki
  </li>
  <li>
   Saijin Komamura
  </li>
  <li>
   Shinji Hirako
  </li>
  <li>
   Shuhei Hisagi
  </li>
  <li>
   Shunsui Kyoraku
  </li>
  <li>
   Sosuke Aizen
  </li>
  <li>
   Sui-Feng
  </li>
  <li>
   Szayelaporro Granz
  </li>
  <li>
   Tier Harribel
  </li>
  <li>
   Toshiro Hitsugaya
  </li>
  <li>
   Ulquiorra Cifer
  </li>
  <li>
   Uryu Ishida
  </li>
  <li>
   Yasutora Sado
  </li>
  <li>
   Yoruichi Shihoin
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  fans excited to play the first proper console game release that the series has seen since 2011 have a few different options when it comes to purchasing the game. The standard version of the game costs $59.99, but the $84.99 Deluxe Edition includes the base game, the Season Pass (which comes with four playable characters, one week early access for DLC characters, and Two-Type Soul Crystal Set 1), Rebirth of Souls Version Costume Set, Two-Type Soul Crystal Set 2, and Two-Type Soul Crystal Set 3. The $99.99 Ultimate Edition comes with all of that plus the Thousand-Year Blood War Costume Set. Those that pre-order the game regardless of version will be treated to the Thousand-Year Blood War: Toshihiro Hitsugaya &amp; Yoiruichi Shihoin Costume Set.
 </p>
 <p>
  The jury is still out on the quality of
  <em>
   Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  , but its March 21 release date should still make it an exciting day for
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  fans regardless. Perhaps its release will be the start of a renaissance of
  <em>
   Bleach
  </em>
  video games on consoles, though that likely depends on its success.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FC 25 Releases Update 11</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ea-sports-fc-25-update-11/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Title Update 11 for EA Sports FC 25 focuses on bug fixes, not major gameplay changes.
     </li>
     <li>
      Previous patches, like Title Update 10, made significant alterations to gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      EA continues to update FC 25 to enhance gameplay and address fan concerns.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Electronic Arts has just released Title Update 11 for
  <strong>
   <em>
    EA Sports FC 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The new update is not as big as some previous ones, and it focuses on solving glitches that previously plagued
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  was released in September 2024. The game is the latest entry in the popular soccer franchise previously known as
  <em>
   FIFA
  </em>
  before EA lost the rights to use the brand. Since the game’s release, EA Sports has been putting out regular updates, fixing glitches, and adding new content to
  <em>
   FC 25
  </em>
  to keep the fanbase engaged.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, Electronic Arts has released the new Title Update 11 for
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  , which is already available on all platforms except the Nintendo Switch. Unlike some previous patches, Title Update 11 does not make significant alterations to gameplay, instead focusing more on correcting bugs that previously appeared in modes such as Ultimate Team and Career Mode. Some examples of specific problems that were fixed include an issue where the Min and Max prices on the Ultimate Team’s Transfer Market could not be adjusted, Ground Passes being less accurate than intended, or players continuously committing unintended Professional Fouls. Also, the game’s UI and elements such as badges, balls, and banners were improved.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-263083857" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-263083857" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-263083857" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-263083857" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-263083857-img" id="article-gallery-1-263083857">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-263083857" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2083036202">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The new update comes on the heels of
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  ’s Title Update 10. Also known as the Legends Return Update, this previous patch was more significant than the current one, as it made multiple gameplay changes to the soccer game. Some of them included Precision Lob Passes being toned down, clearance headers becoming more reliable, as well as improving the AI of defenders.
 </p>
 <p>
  These updates are part of EA’s continued efforts to polish
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  and improve the title’s popularity. Last year, EA concluded that
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </em>
  performed below expectations, affecting the revenue of the publisher due to not selling nearly as many units as intended.
 </p>
 <p>
  As it patches the current title, EA is already looking at the future of the
  <em>
   EA Sports FC
  </em>
  franchise. EA recently acquired TRACAB Technologies, a tech company that specializes in the collection of data from real-world soccer games. By introducing its technology in future games,
  <em>
   EA Sports FC
  </em>
  may feature even more realistic gameplay than before, especially concerning how the players move during matches. At the moment, however, it’s still unknown which will be the first
  <em>
   EA Sports FC
  </em>
  game to use this new tech.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="h-fc-25-title-update-11-patch-notes">
  FC 25 Title Update 11 Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Ultimate Team
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Addressed the following issue:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   In certain situations, the Min and Max prices could not have been adjusted when attempting to list Items on the Transfer Market.
  </li>
  <li>
   Addressed instances of missing UI elements and inconsistent UI formatting.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Gameplay
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Addressed the following issues:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   In some instances, a Ground Pass was less accurate than intended in situations where the passer and receiver were not under pressure by defenders.
  </li>
  <li>
   Sometimes, the ball carrier could have slowed down unintentionally when turning during a dribble performed while sprinting.
  </li>
  <li>
   When passing the ball, the player switches to the receiver did not always occur if the passing animation was interrupted by certain inputs.
  </li>
  <li>
   On rare occasions, players could have entered a state where they continuously committed unintended Professional Fouls.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clubs
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Addressed the following issues:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The match intro in Clubs Rush showed the same team name and abbreviation for all players.
  </li>
  <li>
   The Team Tactics button callout did not always function as intended on the Team Tactics screen.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Career Mode
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Addressed the following issues:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Addressed instances of incorrect fixtures occurring for some competitions when using Live Start Points.
  </li>
  <li>
   Incorrect competition results and standings could have displayed on the last day of the season.
  </li>
  <li>
   After completing the requirements for a task in Manager Career, the task could have continued to show as active in the Task List.
  </li>
  <li>
   An incorrect placeholder team could have appeared in Club Transfers.
  </li>
  <li>
   A stability issue could have occurred when simulating matches from the Central Hub.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   General, Audio, and Visual
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Made the following changes:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Updated some badges, balls, banners, flags, cameras, scarves, stadiums, tifos, trophies, celebrations, hair, and kits.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Addressed the following issues:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Addressed instances of various stability issues that could have occurred.
  </li>
  <li>
   Addressed instances of placeholder and missing text.
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Changes Introduced In Rainbow Six Siege X</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/rainbow-six-siege-x-best-changes-introduced/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Siege X introduces revamped lighting for a darker, grittier feel.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new audio system improves spatial awareness and tracking.
     </li>
     <li>
      Advanced rappel system and 6v6 Dual Front game mode added.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Rainbow Six Siege X
   </strong>
  </em>
  introduces a major
  <strong>
   overhaul to the game's lighting, audio, and mechanics
  </strong>
  , raising the stakes of what it truly means to play a team-based tactical shooter. As
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  grew in scope over the last ten years, both in terms of gameplay meta and operator roster, the need to streamline the tactical experience became even more evident.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege X
  </em>
  , Ubisoft addresses several complaints that players have had for a long time now,
  <strong>
   including operator bans, visual and audio improvements, and free access
  </strong>
  . Here are eight of the best changes introduced in
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege X
  </em>
  that offer a breath of fresh air to both veterans and newcomers alike.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="map-lighting-overhaul">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Map Lighting Overhaul
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="revamped-lighting-engine-that-adds-a-layer-of-grittiness-to-the-game-39-s-atmosphere">
  <strong>
   Revamped Lighting Engine That Adds A Layer Of Grittiness To The Game's Atmosphere
  </strong>
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1794287876" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1794287876" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1794287876" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1794287876" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1794287876-img" id="article-gallery-1-1794287876">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1794287876" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1139378708">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Reminds Of Old Siege:
   </strong>
   The new lighting engine
   <strong>
    makes the game look darker and grittier while retaining clarity
   </strong>
   . In a way, the new lighting system will remind veterans of the familiar old feeling of playing
   <em>
    Rainbow Six Siege
   </em>
   during its initial years of release.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Graphical technology has improved drammatically in the last ten years, and
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  had to catch up to industry standards, bringing the game in line with other competitive shooters. As part of the visual enhancement,
  <strong>
   Siege X will launch with four maps that benefit from improved lighting
  </strong>
  , changing the look and feel of these maps and making them grittier and darker.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can expect to see better reflections and shinier surfaces on these maps. With the launch of Siege X, the following maps will receive visual enhancements:
  <strong>
   Kafe Dostoyevsky, Chalet, Bank, and Clubhouse.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="revamped-audio">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Revamped Audio
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="improved-audio-tech-ensures-better-sound-propagation-amp-tracking">
  Improved Audio Tech Ensures Better Sound Propagation &amp; Tracking
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-569190319" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-569190319" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-569190319" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-569190319" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-569190319-img" id="article-gallery-2-569190319">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-569190319" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1885447494">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Sharper Spatial Awareness
   </strong>
   : The revamped audio system ensures players can clearly distinguish enemies above, below, inside, or outside the map.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  One of the longrunning player complaints in
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  is the inconsistent sound propagation at times. Players will have difficulty determining whether the sound they hear is coming from above or below, leading to inaccurate judgment and round losses.
 </p>
 <p>
  The new audio system
  <strong>
   aims to improve audio propagation and reverberation for better tracking of enemy locations
  </strong>
  . Sounds played in large halls, small rooms, inside the map, or outside will have distinct audio cues, offering players much-needed spatial awareness before committing to any action.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="advanced-rappel">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Advanced Rappel
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="rappeling-windows-will-never-be-the-same">
  Rappeling Windows Will Never Be The Same
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-170398375" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-170398375" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-170398375" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-170398375" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-170398375-img" id="article-gallery-3-170398375">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-170398375" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-361708262">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Dynamic Rappel Movement:
   </strong>
   Advanced rappel lets players run and loop around walls, giving them greater mobility and confidence when engaging enemies while rappelling.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Rappelling windows in
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  has always been a gamble. Those rappelling have
  <strong>
   limited mobility and are easy to predict by veteran players
  </strong>
  . Rappelling players are also easily flanked by defender runouts. However,
  <em>
   Siege X's
  </em>
  <strong>
   advanced rappel system allows players increased mobility and maneuverability while rappelling.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  With the new rappel system, players can run along walls and loop around corners to quickly access chokepoints and reposition to hold flanks. The ability to quickly loop around buildings and access a new window to cut off escaping defenders would allow attackers better map control without even having to enter a building.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dual-front-game-mode">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Dual Front Game Mode
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="6v6-casual-game-mode">
  6V6 Casual Game Mode
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1051739324" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1051739324" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1051739324" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1051739324" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1051739324-img" id="article-gallery-4-1051739324">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1051739324" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1960172025">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Attackers &amp; Defenders Unite
   </strong>
   : A permanent 6v6 mode where, for the first time, attacking and defending operators unite in low-stakes, casual matches.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Siege X
  </em>
  introduces a brand new,
  <strong>
   permanent 6v6 Dual Front game mode
  </strong>
  that
  <strong>
   allows both attackers and defenders to team up for an interesting gameplay experience
  </strong>
  . The Dual Front mode is a modified version of the Domination game mode, often seen in
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  . Dual Front games are set on a larger map called District, exclusive to this mode.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unlike the traditional casual and ranked modes, operators are allowed to respawn in the Dual Front mode. A team is declared victorious if they manage to sabotage two map objectives. While
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  had a few limited-time events where attackers and defenders collaborated in unique gameplay modes, they were often limited to using specific weapons or gadgets. However, in Dual Front,
  <strong>
   operators from both sides are free to use their full kit of equipment (weapons and gadgets) to create unique synergies.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="per-round-operator-bans">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Per Round Operator Bans
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="teams-now-ban-one-operator-each-side-per-round">
  <strong>
   Teams Now Ban One Operator Each Side Per Round
  </strong>
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1859564298" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1859564298" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1859564298" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1859564298" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1859564298-img" id="article-gallery-5-1859564298">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1859564298" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1495342821">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Fresh Bans Every Round
   </strong>
   : Per-round operator bans let teams strategically ban operators instead of locking them out of the match entirely.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  One of the biggest drawbacks of the pick and ban system in
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  was that some operators always ended up being banned from ranked games. Powerful operators like Jackal, Thatcher, and Mira were often banned from most matches, which led to rising discontent among players, especially those who enjoyed playing them.
 </p>
 <p>
  The new per-round operator ban aims to alleviate the shortcomings of the old pick and ban system. In
  <em>
   Siege X
  </em>
  , each team gets to ban one attacker and one defender per round. The bans are cleared each time teams switch sides, and players can ban operators all over again.
 </p>
 <h2 id="improved-destruction">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Improved Destruction
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="maps-are-more-interactive-with-destructible-items">
  <strong>
   Maps Are More Interactive With Destructible Items
  </strong>
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1670150451" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1670150451" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1670150451" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1670150451" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1670150451-img" id="article-gallery-6-1670150451">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1670150451" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-501215291">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Destructible Map Elements
   </strong>
   : Maps laced with fire extinguishers and gas pipes that can be destroyed to cut off lines of sight or deny map control.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Siege X
  </em>
  , players can now find their favorite maps laced with destructible items, which Ubisoft refers to as
  <strong>
   destructible ingredients
  </strong>
  . These items include fire extinguishers and flammable gas pipes. Shooting fire extinguishers results in the nearby area being flooded by smoke,
  <strong>
   cutting off lines of sight
  </strong>
  . Any operator trapped in the explosion radius will also suffer a disorienting effect. Flammable pipes, when shot at, emit red flames that damage anyone trying to run past them. The flames slowly turn blue, and eventually,
  <strong>
   the pipe explodes, covering the nearby area with flames and denying access until the flames are out.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  The new destructible ingredient element is a welcome addition to
  <em>
   Siege X
  </em>
  , offering a breath of fresh air to some of the popular maps that the community holds dear. In addition, metal detectors can now be disabled with EMP grenades and explosives, adding another layer of strategy to the game.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="communication-wheel">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Communication Wheel
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="effective-communication-without-reliance-on-microphone">
  Effective Communication Without Reliance On Microphone
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-2019896704" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-2019896704" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-2019896704" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-2019896704" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-2019896704-img" id="article-gallery-7-2019896704">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-2019896704" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1917911215">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Quick Communication Wheel
   </strong>
   : The new communication wheel lets players issue essential commands and ping locations without relying on voice chat, making team coordination smoother and more efficient.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Siege
  </em>
  is best played when all five teammates have access to voice communication, enabling better coordination when executing a strategy. However, not everyone is comfortable using voice chat and often rely on text chat to get their message across. The communication wheel is a new addition coming in
  <em>
   Siege X
  </em>
  that
  <strong>
   aims to improve team communication and cohesion regardless of whether players have access to a microphone or not.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  The communication wheel includes a bunch of common action terminologies, such as breach, clear, and thanks. Players can use the communication wheel to ping certain locations on the map and relay the information to everyone on the team.
 </p>
 <h2 id="free-access-to-siege">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Free Access To Siege
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="siege-goes-free-to-play-with-some-restriction">
  Siege Goes Free-To-Play, With Some Restriction
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-567157875" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-567157875" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-567157875" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-567157875" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-567157875-img" id="article-gallery-8-567157875">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-567157875" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1063872524">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Jump In For Free
   </strong>
   :
   <em>
    Siege X
   </em>
   becomes free, offering access to casual, arcade, and unranked game modes, with Ranked and Siege Cup reserved for level 50 players and those who opt for a premium upgrade.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Starting Year 10 Season 2,
  <strong>
   players can enjoy
   <em>
    Siege X
   </em>
   for free across all available platforms
  </strong>
  . However, they are limited to casual, arcade, Dual Front, and unranked game modes while using free access. Those who wish to test their mettle on the competitive side of
  <em>
   Siege
  </em>
  , like Ranked and Siege Cup, will need to
  <strong>
   first hit level 50 and then upgrade their accounts
  </strong>
  for a yet-to-be-announced premium price.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players who are already at or
  <strong>
   above level 50 will not be required to upgrade their accounts
  </strong>
  . They can continue competing in Ranked and Siege Cup as usual. Veterans will also receive
  <strong>
   exclusive rewards (cosmetics)
  </strong>
  for having played
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  in the last ten years.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fields of Mistria: How to Change Day Length</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fields-of-mistria-how-change-day-length/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fields of Mistria
   </strong>
  </em>
  , players start by helping Adeline rebuild parts of the town while also raising pets, building a farm, completing museum sets, and going on adventures. However, the in-game days can feel too short, quickly lowering your character’s energy and forcing them to sleep—particularly when you're in the middle of a quest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This day cycle can also limit how much of the map you get to see in a single day. Thankfully, a recent update now lets you adjust the day length to your preference. So, for those curious, here's
  <strong>
   how to change the daytime speed in
   <em>
    Fields of Mistria
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria">
  How To Change Day Length In Fields Of Mistria
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-777445304" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-777445304" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-777445304" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-777445304" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-777445304-img" id="article-gallery-1-777445304">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-777445304" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1072216702">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As mentioned above, you can easily increase the duration of your day in
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  . With two Main Menu settings in the game, players might get confused about which one to enter. Like audio and controls settings, you need to open the in-game Main Menu to swap your day time speed. To be more precise, to change your Day Time length in
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  , you need to
  <strong>
   open the journal page's settings
  </strong>
  (ESC key), click on
  <strong>
   Accessibility
  </strong>
  , and then
  <strong>
   pick one of three Day Time Speed options
  </strong>
  from the side menu.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once done, you’ll need to go back to your house and sleep to enable the settings, as your
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  days won’t become longer immediately. When your character wakes up the next day, the day's length will change based on the option you selected. Now, you can walk around the map and explore different parts of the town without the clock hitting midnight too soon. Also, players can complete story quests, fulfill requests, or simply enjoy their time in the game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Just a quick heads-up — if you slow down the time, it might take you longer to finish quests and progress further since you will receive quest letters and recipes in your mailbox the following day.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="which-day-time-speed-option-in-fields-of-mistria-is-the-best">
  Which Day Time Speed Option In Fields Of Mistria Is The Best?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to change day length in fields of mistria " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-change-day-length-in-fields-of-mistria-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you’re wondering which Day Time Speed you should choose in
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  , then an important thing to remember is that it depends on your gameplay. Farmers looking for a calm experience can pick the third option, while those aiming to complete the story quickly should stick with the default mode. Here’s an idea of how long each day lasts in
  <em>
   Fields of Mistria
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Standard:
   </strong>
   About 12 Minutes
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Longer:
   </strong>
   Around 14 Minutes
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Longest:
   </strong>
   Likely 15 Minutes
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
