<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Best Famous Last Words In Final Fantasy, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-franchise-series-best-famous-last-words-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Final Fantasy characters deliver impactful final lines, from villain redemptions to heroic farewells.
     </li>
     <li>
      Kuja in FF9 admits faults in defeat, contrasting his power-hungry nature with acknowledgment.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Final Fantasy series features emotional farewells, with Tidus embracing mortality and Ward's silent farewell.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While Square Enix's
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  series has become industry-renowned for some of the most captivating narratives of the medium, it arguably remains that some of its dialogue can come across as pulpy at best. However, with a history spanning multiple decades, the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  franchise has shown a tendency to bestow some of its characters with some seemingly momentous final lines of dialogue.
 </p>
 <p>
  From series-defining villains casting no doubt as to their evil plans with monologue-heavy final moments to heroes accepting their fate with bittersweet reflection, the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  series has often allowed their characters the luxury of a notable exit from the franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Spoiler Warning: The following entries will delve into some major narrative spoilers.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="kuja-final-fantasy-9">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Kuja (Final Fantasy 9)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-central-villain-sees-the-error-of-his-way-as-he-is-put-to-rest">
  The Central Villain Sees The Error Of His Way As He Is Put To Rest
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1611141353" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1611141353" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1611141353" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1611141353" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1611141353-img" id="article-gallery-1-1611141353">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1611141353" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1430413398">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "After you guys beat me, I had nothing left... nothing more to lose. Then, I finally realized what it means to live... I guess I was too late."
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Despite his place as
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 9
  </em>
  's central antagonist, with great ambitions to control the 2000 role-playing game's world of Gaia, Kuja's position is ultimately reversed within his final moments at the game's narrative climax. Upon his defeat by the player, as he lies dying at the feet of the game's protagonist, Zidaine, his power-hungry insanity seemingly dissipates as he acknowledges his fragility and the foolhardiness of his plans of domination.
 </p>
 <p>
  What results is an arguably anticlimactic conclusion to the game's dark conflict, as Kuja pivots to a seeming antihero with the acknowledgment that his powers of sorcery and manipulation were for nothing. As such, his dying words not only impact the player but also resolve a character arc that — on a second playthrough — weaves itself through the game's themes and central conflict.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tella-final-fantasy-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Tella (Final Fantasy 4)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-act-of-self-sacrifice-is-compounded-by-a-plea-for-redemption">
  An Act Of Self-Sacrifice Is Compounded By A Plea For Redemption
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1355371773" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1355371773" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1355371773" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1355371773" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1355371773-img" id="article-gallery-2-1355371773">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1355371773" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1875636382">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "I brought this on...myself. Letting hate consume me so. Please...avenge...Anna."
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Considering 1991's
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 4
  </em>
  is seemingly often revered as one of the series' best-looking and hardest-hitting entries of the decade-spanning JRPG series, it's arguably no surprise that the last moments of one of the party's most unique characters continues this pedigree. After the elderly mage Tellah commits to casting Meteor on the crystal-hungry evil mage Golbez, despite the risk it poses to his frail mortality, to save his companions, he is left hoping that his sacrifice was not in vain.
 </p>
 <p>
  In defeating Golbez and redeeming himself in his mind for the death of his daughter Anna, Tellah fulfills his personal goal of retribution and speeds his younger party members to see the game's conclusion. As such, with the self-sacrifice and grief-induced determination of the elderly mage's actions, his final words of fulfillment and peace are meaningful not only to the party but to the player.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="remedi-final-fantasy-tactics-advance">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Remedi (Final Fantasy Tactics Advance)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-transformative-antagonist-is-ultimately-revealed">
  The Transformative Antagonist Is Ultimately Revealed
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1834153828" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1834153828" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1834153828" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1834153828" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1834153828-img" id="article-gallery-3-1834153828">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1834153828" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-8147956">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "I am the wish-gatherer. I am the world-maker. Desire is the thread that binds the worlds together."
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  With her role as
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Tactics Advance'
  </em>
  s central antagonist, Remedi — the Queen of Ivalice — is core to the 2003 spin-off installment's position as "one of the best handheld strategy games of all time." As a result, her transformative and climactic confrontation with the game's protagonist and party not only acts as the game's culminating combat scenario but also the narrative peak of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Tactics Advance'
  </em>
  s 45-hour-long strategic campaign.
 </p>
 <p>
  Existing within the dream world of Ivalice, Remedi's ethereal being is merely a conduit for Li-Grim, and upon her defeat, the 'wish gatherer' and 'world maker' of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Tactics Advance
  </em>
  is revealed. Compounded by her mortal frailty and ultimate defeat by the player's party, Remedi's final proclamations of her magical power are a fitting climax to the game's grand handheld adventure.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tidus-final-fantasy-10">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Tidus (Final Fantasy 10)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-tender-final-moment-as-the-hero-39-s-mortality-is-laid-bare">
  A Tender Final Moment As The Hero's Mortality Is Laid Bare
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1076716978" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1076716978" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1076716978" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1076716978" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1076716978-img" id="article-gallery-4-1076716978">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1076716978" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1696395808">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "Yuna, I have to go. I'm sorry I couldn't show you Zanarkand. Goodbye!"
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Considering the overwhelming strength and plot-relevance of the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  series' anthological protagonists, it comes as no surprise that most of the franchise's heroes are alive and kicking after their respective installments. However, in flipping this customary indefatigability, 2001's
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  's Tidus' final moments are spent in quiet reflection at the game's narrative conclusion.
 </p>
 <p>
  After developing and proving the worth of not only his abilities but his blossoming relationship with Yuna, Tidus' role within the cyclical conflict of Sin and his ultimate fate is revealed. In one of the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  series' most notable final moments, Tidus not only embraces his mortality but bids a final farewell to his companions — ultimately apologizing for the limited time he was able to spend with them all and the promises he is unable to fulfill.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bahamut-final-fantasy-15-the-dawn-of-the-future">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Bahamut (Final Fantasy 15: The Dawn Of The Future)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-heroic-savior-turned-alt-history-villain-in-a-tie-in-novelization">
  A Heroic Savior Turned Alt-History Villain In A Tie-In Novelization
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-353338711" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-353338711" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-353338711" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-353338711" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-353338711-img" id="article-gallery-5-353338711">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-353338711" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-437287202">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "Though guided by the Light, they war among themselves and defile the Star. How could mortals hope to survive alone in a godless world?"
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Despite his position as the god of war and a core figure within the multifaceted narrative of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15
  </em>
  and its related media, Bahamut remains one of the 2016 Action JRPG's most recognizable entities. As a result, while his ethereal position in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15
  </em>
  is ultimately bolstered by the game's protagonist Noctis, in the game's final moments, the alternative-history companion novel by Emi Nagashima portrays his defeat.
 </p>
 <p>
  2019's
  <em>
   Final Fantasy XV: The Dawn of the Future
  </em>
  reframes Bahamut's omnipotent power directed towards the defeat of the Scourge as Eos' ultimate antagonist. As a result, Bahamut's godly omniscience and role as a greater power are reinterpreted through the lens of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15
  </em>
  's greatest villain — meaning that his flowery monologuing regarding the mortality of humanity and his role as Eos' savior is more similar to a tyrannical deity than a heroic creature.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kefka-final-fantasy-6">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Kefka (Final Fantasy 6)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-video-gaming-39-s-most-recognizable-bad-guys-spouts-a-cruel-monologue">
  One Of Video Gaming's Most Recognizable Bad Guys Spouts A Cruel Monologue
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1463996557" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1463996557" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1463996557" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1463996557" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1463996557-img" id="article-gallery-6-1463996557">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1463996557" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1256084933">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "I'll destroy everything! I'll create my own empire...of death! [...] but what fun is destruction if no 'precious' lives are lost?"
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  With the status of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  's Kefka as "the greatest mad villain Final Fantasy has ever concocted," and the tendency for antagonists across art to seemingly spout some of the most hard-hitting dialogue of any character, Kefka's final words before his defeat are arguably some of video gaming's most revered. Standing before the player's party as a god-like being and wielding the Light of Judgement against the world of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  , Kefka's madness-riddled victory is accompanied by a plethora of gloating and arrogance fitting for a demigod.
 </p>
 <p>
  Proclaiming his position as the god of his newly-formed 'kingdom of death' while basking in the pain and suffering he inflicts, Kefka's final moments before the party initiates the battle that will ultimately defeat him are some of the series' — and the video game industry's — most influential.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chaos-final-fantasy">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Chaos (Final Fantasy)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-series-39-first-villain-who-formed-an-innovative-time-loop">
  The Series' First Villain Who Formed An Innovative Time Loop
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1948978615" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1948978615" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1948978615" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1948978615" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1948978615-img" id="article-gallery-7-1948978615">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1948978615" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1285700428">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "After 2,000 years I will be forgotten, and the Time Loop will close. I will live forever, and you shall meet doom!"
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Despite its age, 1987's
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  not only introduced the video game industry to one of its most recognizable properties but "paved the way for a series that never rested on its laurels." This was not only a result of tight world-building and expansive scope, but also a time-weaving antagonist that seemingly remains one of the series' most influential villains. The once-revered Cornelian warrior Garland, who ultimately soaked up the power of the Four Fiends and transformed into the beast-god Chaos, is menacing not only in his scale but also in his ability to create a time loop that uniquely tests the player's party and the world of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  With the time loop closed and Chaos faced with the possibility of his mortality, he proclaims that he will not be defeated and strives to defeat the Warriors of Light in that moment. Although he is finally bested, Chaos' creativity and villainy not only established the NES original as a classic for the system but the series as one that would continue to surprise and delight players.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ward-final-fantasy-8">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Ward (Final Fantasy 8)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-side-story-strongman-who-loses-his-voice-in-helping-his-friends">
  The Side-Story Strongman Who Loses His Voice In helping His Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1149868094" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1149868094" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1149868094" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1149868094" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1149868094-img" id="article-gallery-8-1149868094">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1149868094" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-267222052">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    "It...was...fun...you...guys...La...guna...Ki...ros...It...was...fun..."
   </strong>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  With as rich a history of varied settings and themes as
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  has, it is seemingly no surprise that many of the franchise's companion characters have garnered similar — or even greater — adoration from fans as the series' protagonists. This acclaim is so great that "even those who join the party for a short time often leave a strong impression" — as arguably is the case for
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 8
  </em>
  's ultimately mute party member Ward.
 </p>
 <p>
  During his final mission when in the ranks of the Galbadian Army, Ward's strongman physique and strong-but-silent demeanor are taken to their logical extreme as he loses his voice as a result of his injuries. Although he does not succumb to his injuries, the fact that his last words before his vocal cords are irrevocably damaged are 'it was fun,' said to his comrades and friends, Kiros and Laguna, is fittingly short but sweet for the muscular soldier.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 76: Best Garden Gnome Locations</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-76-best-garden-gnome-locations-weekly-challenge/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There are lots of items that can be collected and broken down into their core components in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 76
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Some give the player rare materials that can be used for crafting, while others are commonly required to complete certain daily and weekly challenges. Garden gnomes can be found dotted around Appalachia.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  They come in a variety of different styles, but they all get broken down for the same core materials. Garden gnomes aren't exactly the most useful items in the game. However, since players will need to collect garden gnomes from time to time to complete challenges, they do have a purpose. This guide will go over the best locations to find garden gnomes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="guaranteed-spawn-locations-for-garden-gnomes">
  Guaranteed Spawn Locations For Garden Gnomes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Garden Gnomes In A Shed" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/garden-gnomes-in-a-shed.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are a few locations on the map where you can find garden gnomes. While these are guaranteed spawn locations, it's important to note that if another player has recently picked up a gnome from one of the locations, then it isn't going to be there when the next person comes along.
  <strong>
   Hopping servers or using a private server with a
   <em>
    Fallout 1st
   </em>
   membership can help prevent other players from getting to the spawn points first
  </strong>
  . Some of the best locations for getting garden gnomes can be seen below:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Fort Defiance
   </strong>
   : 4 gnomes can be found on the southeastern side of Fort Defiance. Open up the map and follow the road heading south of Fort Defiance. Once you reach the makeshift bridge, you'll find 4 garden gnomes around a body on a life raft to the right of the bridge.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    General's Steakhouse:
   </strong>
   Head to the backyard of General's Steakhouse. You don't need to go through the building, simply go around and to the rear of the property. In the garden, you'll find five in the garden and two more in the shed at the back of the garden.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Huntersville
   </strong>
   : Fast travel to Huntersville. Head up the hill and go to the rear of the first house you see on the right side. Behind the house, you'll see a garden gnome burying a plushie in the backyard. Also, there's a small shack in the garden that usually contains 6 gnomes. You can typically expect to walk away from this area with 7 gnomes.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Hornwright Testing Site #2:
   </strong>
   Travel to Hornwright Testing Site #2 and go west. You'll come across two abandoned cars. Around both of these cars, you'll find garden gnomes. Provided nobody else has taken them, you'll find a total of 12 gnomes in this area.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  These aren't the only locations where you'll find garden gnomes. However, they are the locations that spawn the most gnomes. If you want to find a couple of extra gnomes, then you can visit one of the following locations:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Watoga High School:
   </strong>
   On the roof - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Watoga Station:
   </strong>
   On a table northeast of Watoga Station - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Watoga Emergency Services:
   </strong>
   Inside the building on the third floor, on a chair - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    R&amp;G Station:
   </strong>
   Inside the caravan - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Vault-Tec Agricultural Research Center:
   </strong>
   Inside the greenhouse behind the building and in the basement - around 3 gnomes.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Fort Atlas:
   </strong>
   In a garden located just south of Fort Atlas - 2 gnomes.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Valley Galleria:
   </strong>
   In a stroller to the left of the entrance - 2 gnomes.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Flatwoods:
   </strong>
   Inside the shack in the community garden - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Hornwright Summer Villa:
   </strong>
   Inside the greenhouse - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Overseer's Home:
   </strong>
   At the bottom of the stairs on a box - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Big Fred's BBQ Shack:
   </strong>
   Inside the shack - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Lakeside Cabins:
   </strong>
   Near the flagpole on the property - 1 gnome.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Rollins Labor Camp:
   </strong>
   On a table in the camp - 1 gnome.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="other-ways-of-getting-garden-gnomes">
  Other Ways Of Getting Garden Gnomes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="4 Garden Gnomes" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/4-garden-gnomes.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not as lucrative as the locations mentioned above, there are a couple of other ways that you can pick up a few garden gnomes. The first is as random rewards. Completing daily quests in the Mire Region can occasionally award you a garden gnome.
  <strong>
   You can also purchase them from robot vendors every now and then
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
  </strong>
  Some robot vendors have a chance of having a gnome in their inventory, while others will only have garden gnomes for sale if another player has recently sold some to the vendor. You can also buy them from other players by either setting up a trade or through their CAMP vendor. However, there's never a guarantee that any player will have any for sale. Forums like Market76 can be a great place to set up trades with other players.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="uses-for-garden-gnomes">
  Uses For Garden Gnomes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A Garden Gnome's Components" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-garden-gnome-s-components.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Garden Gnomes aren't the most useful items in the game. However, as mentioned, they are needed for completing daily challenges. Typically, when one of these challenges pops up, you'll need to collect 5 garden gnomes. Since these challenges are only live for 24 hours, it can be pretty tricky to track down enough gnomes since most players will be on the hunt for them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   To help boost your odds, it's better to try and get the challenge completed as soon as it drops or a couple of hours before it ends
  </strong>
  . During these times, there tend to be fewer players searching for them, although that's not a guarantee. One other thing you can do to help increase your chances of finding gnomes is to visit locations that only have one or two gnomes. While it will take you longer to complete the challenge, most players tend to only visit areas with lots of gnomes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Outside of their use as a daily challenge item, you can do two things with them. The first is to scrap them. Scrapping a garden gnome will give you 1 ceramic and 3 concrete. While these aren't the most useful resources, they do still have their uses in construction.
 </p>
 <p>
  The second use is as display items. Certain display units can hold garden gnomes. There are three different gnome types in the game:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Red Garden Gnome
  </li>
  <li>
   Blue Garden Gnome
  </li>
  <li>
   Broken Garden Gnome
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Aside from their appearance, there are no differences between them in terms of scrap output. But some players like to collect one of each type to have displayed at their CAMP.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tekken 8 Season 2's Throw Damage Controversy Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tekken-8-season-2-throw-damage-controversy-explained/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  It should come as no surprise that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Tekken 8
   </em>
  </strong>
  has many fans dedicated to mastering its combat by learning about different characters along with the best movement and attack options for each one. To ensure that everyone continues to enjoy playing despite knowing everything they believe they should, the game's developer, Bandai Namco Studios, provides updates that change important things like the timing of inputs for certain moves or how long it takes for one to land. While these often help balance the game's combat meta, there are instances where some players believe they miss the mark. A good example would be the season 2 patch for
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  and its controversial change to the throw mechanic.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  During the March 23
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  Talk live stream, the developers made multiple announcements regarding the season 2 update for
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  . Although it provided many things to look forward to, such as the
  <em>
   Atelier Yumia
  </em>
  collaboration DLC and a new
  <em>
   Pac-Man
  </em>
  45th anniversary stage, one piece of news that caused a significant commotion from fans was the change to the throwing mechanic: players who successfully break throws are punished by receiving chip damage. Many people have voiced their concern about the change, forcing Bandai Namco Studios to respond in a way that hopefully satisfies
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  's playerbase.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-tekken-8-rsquo-s-throw-mechanic-is-so-polarizing">
  Why Tekken 8’s Throw Mechanic is So Polarizing
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-892367301" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-892367301" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-892367301" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-892367301" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-892367301-img" id="article-gallery-1-892367301">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-892367301" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1692304147">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With the recent release of
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  's season 2 update, players are finding themselves in the difficult position of adapting to the changed throw mechanic. Though some see it as a new way of livening up the combat experience, others see it as a detriment because of what it implies:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Being able to break a throw move requires skill and timing, and being punished for successfully breaking free can make the skilled execution feel somewhat pointless
  </li>
  <li>
   Situations where one could have lived and made a comeback by successfully breaking a throw will be less likely, reducing players' options for surviving and staying in a match
  </li>
  <li>
   It reinforces the idea that players can be as aggressive as they want with little punishment on the aggressor. The Season 2 update promised to fix overaggression by adding more defensive positions, so this change is counterintuitive
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A big reason why
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  remains one of the most popular and relevant fighting games is because of how fair and enjoyable its gameplay combat is, regardless of whether one is a newbie or veteran. The addition of chip damage for successfully breaking out of throw moves arguably takes away some of that fairness for both sides, making many wish for the mechanic to revert to the way it was before.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-bandai-namco-studios-plans-to-address-tekken-8-39-s-throw-mechanic-controversy">
  How Bandai Namco Studios Plans To Address Tekken 8's Throw Mechanic Controversy
 </h3>
 <p>
  After seeing community feedback, Bandai Namco Studios has made plans to readjust
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  's throw mechanic. The news has certainly caught the attention of many, as it showed that the developer has come to understand how much it could affect the game and its playerbase. The chip damage will be removed in May, before the
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  World Tour 2025, with a subsequent patch that rewards the throw initiator with one point of health. The addition of recovering slightly after a throw may be due to the season 2 patch's inclusion of widening the break-out window, ensuring that it's fair for both the giver and the receiver.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  recently passing an impressive sales milestone, it's clear that the game can continue being a juggernaut in the fighting game genre so long as it can communicate well with its community. Players have been vocal that the controversial change to the throw mechanic is a move that could go against that, and Bandai Namco Studios' response shows that it's willing to do what's necessary to undo any damage.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tekken 8 Players Unhappy With Season 2 Update</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tekken-8-season-2-update-controversy-backlash/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Season 2 update for Tekken 8 introduces a new character and other content.
     </li>
     <li>
      Unfortunately, changes in the Season 2 update have not been popular.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players want to see major changes made to the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Tekken 8
   </em>
  </strong>
  has released its Season 2 update, and the community is unhappy with the changes.
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  Season 2 has been mired in controversy since before it even launched. Originally, there were plans to add chip damage to throw breaks, but that decision was reversed after fan outcry.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  Season 2 update is now available. Season 2 expands the roster with the addition of Anna Williams, Nina Williams' sister, and introduces a new Fight Pass. Eight new ranks have been added after God of Destruction, all ranks obtained by players in Season 1 have been reset, and the loss/gain of points in ranked matches has been adjusted. Plus, multiplayer has received matchmaking improvements to ensure that gamers face opponents of the same skill level. However, the reaction to
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  Season 2 has been less than enthusiastic.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  players are unhappy following the release of the Season 2 update.
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  player Arslan Ash expressed their frustration after playing the new season, saying that players “were so ungrateful with Season 1.” Stephen “Speedkicks” Stafford, another competitive player of the Bandai Namco title, called for an emergency fix before the start of the Tekken World Tour 2025 with nerfs for “literally every character on the roster.”
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  pro player Akhil “Tetsu” Kakar wasn't too excited about the update either and is considering switching to
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  or the new
  <em>
   Fatal Fury
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="tekken-8-launches-season-2-update-faces-instant-backlash">
  Tekken 8 Launches Season 2 Update, Faces Instant Backlash
 </h2>
 <p>
  With the Season 2 update,
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  characters have gained new moves and buffs to existing ones, changing their power level significantly. The devs introduced defensive improvements but gave the roster tools to counter them. The fighters gained even more 50/50 options, a type of move that forces the defender to choose a type of block and have a 50% chance of being hit. As a result of the changes, players found game-breaking interactions, new "touch of death" combos, and are now saying that “if all the fighters are broken, nobody is.” The reflection of the update has also been felt on Steam, with
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  dropping to “mostly negative” ratings once again.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2128342776" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2128342776" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2128342776" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2128342776" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2128342776-img" id="article-gallery-1-2128342776">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2128342776" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1514695075">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  So far, neither Bandai Namco nor
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  director Katsuhiro Harada has commented on the reaction of players to the Season 2 update. In the meantime, players hope that the developers will address the community's complaints, and that adjustments to improve the gameplay experience will be released in future updates.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Ops 6 Zombies: All Shattered Veil Wall Buy Locations</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/black-ops-6-bo6-zombies-shattered-veil-wall-buy-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Season 3 brings the next major content drop for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  , packed with tons to explore right at launch, alongside additional content rolling out throughout the season and the mid-season update. Players can dive into various maps and modes for Multiplayer on day one, including the return of Shooting Range, as well as trying out additional weapons like the HDR Sniper Rifle.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But that's not all—Zombies fans can jump into the next chapter of the saga with the Shattered Veil map. Featuring terrifying new foes to beat and an Easter Egg quest to complete, there's plenty to grind for. As with previous Zombies maps, Shattered Veil also includes various Wall Buys, giving players access to a range of weapons to aid in the fight.
  <strong>
   Here is every Wall Buy location in the Shattered Veil.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="gs45">
  GS45
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-295984756" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-295984756" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-295984756" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-295984756" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-295984756-img" id="article-gallery-1-295984756">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-295984756" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1462348279">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   GS45
  </strong>
  is often regarded as just a common pistol, which is fitting given its location in Shattered Veil's spawn room. However, Pack-a-Punch it, and players have in their hands an explosive classic weapon. Players can find the GS45 etched onto
  <strong>
   the side of the bridge at the center of the Garden Pond
  </strong>
  , right as they load into the Shattered Veil.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tanto-22">
  Tanto .22
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1724648056" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1724648056" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1724648056" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1724648056" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1724648056-img" id="article-gallery-2-1724648056">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1724648056" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1194184297">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Tanto .22
  </strong>
  is a slow-firing, hard-hitting Submachine Gun that excels in medium-range combat. Players can
  <strong>
   find it in the Conservatory
  </strong>
  , which is accessible by taking a left after reaching the Lower Terrace from the Garden Pond. The weapon is located just
  <strong>
   near a staircase leading to the Upper Terrace.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kompakt-92">
  Kompakt 92
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-116747639" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-116747639" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-116747639" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-116747639" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-116747639-img" id="article-gallery-3-116747639">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-116747639" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-942947526">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Kompakt 92
  </strong>
  is a Submachine Gun with an incredibly high fire rate, even before applying Double Tap. Players can
  <strong>
   find it at Shem's Henge
  </strong>
  , positioned in front of the large stone in the southwest section of the area.
 </p>
 <h2 id="marine-sp">
  Marine SP
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-424179641" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-424179641" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-424179641" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-424179641" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-424179641-img" id="article-gallery-4-424179641">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-424179641" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1730558802">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Marine SP
  </strong>
  is a pump-action Shotgun that is sure to hit like a truck when paired with the best attachments. The Marine SP can be
  <strong>
   purchased over at the Motor Court
  </strong>
  , and is mounted on the side of a pile of wooden crates just opposite the mansion, beside a burning truck.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ames-85">
  AMES 85
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-804498571" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-804498571" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-804498571" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-804498571" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-804498571-img" id="article-gallery-5-804498571">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-804498571" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1535331440">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   AMES 85
  </strong>
  is a reliable Assault Rifle, one that sparks a striking resemblance to the Galil. Players can find it
  <strong>
   within the Grand Foyer
  </strong>
  of the mansion, just
  <strong>
   behind the skeleton of a Tyrannosaurus Rex.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="ak-74">
  AK-74
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-286553698" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-286553698" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-286553698" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-286553698" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-286553698-img" id="article-gallery-6-286553698">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-286553698" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-887798152">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   AK-74
  </strong>
  is a hard-hitting Assault Rifle capable of shredding through zombies with ease. Players can find it in the East Foyer, positioned directly to the right of the AMES 85 Wall Buy.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="level-ii-armor-vest">
  Level II Armor Vest
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-787926630" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-787926630" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-787926630" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-787926630" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-787926630-img" id="article-gallery-7-787926630">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-787926630" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-101604864">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If players are looking to upgrade their armor plate storage from one to two plates, the
  <strong>
   Level II Armor Vest
  </strong>
  is essential. It can be found in two locations. The first is
  <strong>
   within the Library
  </strong>
  , accessible by progressing through the East Foyer and past Stamin-Up.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1609623761" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1609623761" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1609623761" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1609623761" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1609623761-img" id="article-gallery-8-1609623761">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1609623761" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1463334832">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The second Level II Armor Vest Wall Buy is
  <strong>
   located in the Nursery
  </strong>
  , directly opposite the PHD Flopper Perk Machine. Both vests can be
  <strong>
   purchased for a fixed price of 4,000 Essence.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="swat-5-56">
  SWAT 5.56
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1026523385" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1026523385" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1026523385" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1026523385" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1026523385-img" id="article-gallery-9-1026523385">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1026523385" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1727379184">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   SWAT 5.56
  </strong>
  is a burst fire Marksman Rifle by default, packing a punch with every shot. The SWAT 5.56 can be
  <strong>
   found over at the Study
  </strong>
  , just
  <strong>
   opposite the Library
  </strong>
  , where the Level II Armor Vest can be found.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="lr-7-62">
  LR 7.62
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1420024825" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1420024825" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1420024825" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1420024825" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1420024825-img" id="article-gallery-10-1420024825">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1420024825" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1596860445">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   LR 7.62
  </strong>
  is a bolt-action Sniper Rifle that provides players with a powerful explosive weapon when Pack-a-Punched. Players can
  <strong>
   find it over at the Rear Patio
  </strong>
  , directly
  <strong>
   behind the Double Tap Perk Machine.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="aek-973">
  AEK-973
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1939871593" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1939871593" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1939871593" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1939871593" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1939871593-img" id="article-gallery-11-1939871593">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1939871593" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1451179123">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   AEK-973
  </strong>
  is yet another burst fire Marksman Rifle that players can get their hands on, this time
  <strong>
   found within the West Hallways
  </strong>
  , just along the corridor past the Death Perception Perk Machine.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xm4">
  XM4
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-317570305" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-317570305" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-317570305" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-317570305" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-317570305-img" id="article-gallery-12-317570305">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-317570305" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1726051502">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   XM4
  </strong>
  is an excellent Assault Rifle, serving as the jack-of-all-trades in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  . Players can
  <strong>
   find the XM4 wall buy over in the West Hallways
  </strong>
  , in the corridor accessible by the left staircase from the Tyrannosaurus Rex skeleton.
 </p>
 <h2 id="level-iii-armor-vest">
  Level III Armor Vest
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1420328857" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1420328857" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1420328857" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1420328857" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1420328857-img" id="article-gallery-13-1420328857">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1420328857" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-104717029">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For players seeking maximum protection against the undead horde, the
  <strong>
   Level III Armor Vest
  </strong>
  is the ultimate upgrade. The Level III Armor Vest can be found in two locations. The first can be
  <strong>
   found in the Banquet Hall
  </strong>
  , just before reaching the elevator.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1531052741" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1531052741" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1531052741" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1531052741" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1531052741-img" id="article-gallery-14-1531052741">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1531052741" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-188893814">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The second can be
  <strong>
   found within the Service Tunnel.
  </strong>
  This Armor Vest allows players to equip up to three armor plates and can be
  <strong>
   purchased for 14,000 Essence.
  </strong>
  However, if players already have the Level II Armor Vest, they can upgrade at a discounted price of 10,000 Essence.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="gpmg-7">
  GPMG-7
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1476420358" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1476420358" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1476420358" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1476420358" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1476420358-img" id="article-gallery-15-1476420358">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1476420358" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1816033631">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   GPMG-7
  </strong>
  is the go-to Light Machine Gun in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Zombies. Players can find the GPMG-7
  <strong>
   within the Mainframe Chamber
  </strong>
  , in
  <strong>
   the stairway just ahead of the Crafting Table
  </strong>
  leading up to Pack-a-Punch.
 </p>
 <h2 id="asg-89">
  ASG-89
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1339772319" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1339772319" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1339772319" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1339772319" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1339772319-img" id="article-gallery-16-1339772319">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1339772319" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-757711703">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The final Wall Buy that players can acquire is the infamous
  <strong>
   ASG-89
  </strong>
  Shotgun, often regarded as one of the best weapons in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Zombies. Players can
  <strong>
   find the ASG-89 within the Supply Depot
  </strong>
  , which is accessible at the very end of the Supply Tunnel. Players can also find a teleporter in this area, which will take them all the way back to the Garden Pond.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
