<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Gamer Finds Creative Use for Broken PS1</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ps1-lamp-keychain-diy-idea/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A gamer repurposed a broken PS1 as a lamp, showcasing an unusual use for the console.
     </li>
     <li>
      The PS1 sold over 102 million units, offering players a plethora of classic titles to enjoy.
     </li>
     <li>
      The gamer also made a keychain out of a PlayStation accessory.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A gamer has found a practical purpose for a broken
  <strong>
   PlayStation 1
  </strong>
  , repurposing it as a functional lamp. Beyond the lamp, they even found a new use for what appeared to be a controller connector, turning it into a keychain. While gaming consoles break down eventually, this PS1 gamer has shown that their usefulness can continue well past their intended functionality.
 </p>
 <p>
  The PlayStation 1 was released in Japan in 1994 and helped usher in the 3D era of console gaming. As a rival to the N64 and Sega Saturn, the PS1 enjoyed a library of classic titles. From
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  to
  <em>
   Spyro the Dragon
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Crash Bandicoot
  </em>
  , and many others, players had no shortage of options when gaming on the console. The sundry list of titles contributed to the PS1 becoming one of the best-selling video game consoles of all time, selling over 102 million units. With so many PS1s out in the wild, some gamers have found unique uses for the machines as they wear out.
 </p>
 <p>
  One gamer, known as K00BN00B on Reddit, recently shared the creative idea they devised to reuse a broken PS1. Specifically, the player thought the console would work well as the base of a lamp, sharing pictures of their custom design. Besides the PS1, the gamer had what appeared to be an original PlayStation controller at the base of the lamp pole. According to K00BN00B, they were looking for the right shade to complete the look. In addition, they repurposed a controller connector as a keychain by adding a ring to it. When sharing the design on Reddit, K00BN00B revealed they found the broken PS1 on eBay, claiming it was a good place to find old consoles for DIY projects.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="gamer-39-s-custom-lamp-made-out-of-a-broken-playstation-1">
  Gamer's Custom Lamp Made Out of a Broken PlayStation 1
 </h2>
 <p>
  Many gamers were intrigued by the custom lamp design, with the post gaining hundreds of upvotes. One fan pointed out the keychain idea, noting how the repurposed connector for the PS1 controller could be inserted into the PlayStation, making for a place to keep keys from getting lost. Another user said that a blue shade for the lamp would compliment the grey console. Regardless of what K00BN00B uses to cap off the design, the PS1 lamp looked like it would fit nicely into a retro gaming room setup.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1844469264" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1844469264" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1844469264" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1844469264" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1844469264-img" id="article-gallery-1-1844469264">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1844469264" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-727206111">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Giving new life to broken-down consoles by repurposing them as furniture can be a nostalgic way to put a gaming-themed twist on a room. With many generations of video game consoles having been released over the decades, it will be interesting to see if Reddit users like K00BN00B craft other items out of dilapidated PlayStation, Xbox, or Nintendo products in the future.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 Is an Example of Sequel Exposition Done Right</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-exposition-sequel-backstory-flexible-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  As far as first-time sequels go,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  is right up there with the best of them. It doesn't try to reinvent the wheel or make controversial, short-sighted changes like implementing live-service features; rather, it takes what works in the first
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  and elevates it, fleshing it out in ways that are beneficial, unexpected, or both.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A particular aspect of
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's sequel status that deserves praise is how it ushers in new players. Sequels to story-focused games have a difficult line to walk: they often aim to be both satisfying for returning players and welcoming for first-timers who don't want to jump into the previous game beforehand. As one might expect, this balance can be hard to strike, and attempts to do so can often come at the cost of compromising the experience for one or both demographics. The best sequels, therefore, manage to make their stories accessible to new players, but elevated for returning ones, who may better understand the emotional or narrative context of certain plot elements.
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  does this, but it goes a step further, offering a strong blueprint for other story-driven RPGs moving forward.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2-strikes-a-perfect-middle-ground-with-its-exposition">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 Strikes a Perfect Middle-Ground with Its Exposition
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1258683117" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1258683117" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1258683117" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1258683117" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1258683117-img" id="article-gallery-1-1258683117">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1258683117" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-914728290">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-player-steers-kingdom-come-deliverance-2-39-s-exposition">
  The Player Steers Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2's Exposition
 </h3>
 <p>
  In the early hours of
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  , the player will spend quite a bit of time talking with NPCs, who will often ask Henry personal questions about his past. For instance, after the introductory setpiece, Henry and Hans will spend time with Pavlena and Bozhena, a daughter and mother who have taken them in. To make conversation, Hans will prompt Henry to tell stories about the two times he saved his life. Players can then either choose to tell an abridged version of these events, which occurred in the first game, or go into more detail, with the game offering several opportunities to abandon the longer version at key points.
 </p>
 <p>
  Another example of this can be seen even earlier, when Henry is asked about Teresa, the primary love interest of the first
  <em>
   Kingdom Come
  </em>
  . This interaction goes a bit deeper though, as players can effectively define the current relationship status of Henry and Teresa, albeit somewhat loosely. Now, other games, like
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  , have offered dialog-integrated exposition dumps like these, allowing players to shape the game world through NPC interactions, but
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  goes a bit further thanks to its frivolity: it gives players insight into smaller, less plot-relevant details of the first game, which goes a long way toward making the story more emotionally impactful and believable.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     It should be noted that these example exchanges rely on
     <em>
      KCD2
     </em>
     's strong writing. They wouldn't work nearly as well if the dialog didn't come across as naturally as it does.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="how-kingdom-come-deliverance-2-39-s-exposition-synergizes-with-its-player-driven-narrative">
  How Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2's Exposition Synergizes with Its Player-Driven Narrative
 </h3>
 <p>
  Aside from the obvious benefits of immersion and respecting returning players' time, being able to decide how much of Henry's backstory to learn helps
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  better balance its main story and open-ended role-playing experience. Of course, the game will never be as "choose your own adventure" as something like
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  , since Henry is a predefined character, but if players want to forge their own path in this sequel, they have some level of control over how much narrative baggage they want to carry from the first game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Story-driven games, especially RPGs, have a tendency to hold players' hands a bit too much, repeating information ad nauseam or erasing ambiguity altogether. On the other side of the spectrum, the narratives of games like
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  can sometimes be intimidating for newcomers, as there aren't enough opportunities to dig into smaller aspects of previous entries.
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  is in the middle of these two extremes, perfectly positioned at the intersection of informative and flexible.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Landing Safely!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-landing-safely/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player scores a huge multi-elimination in Apex Legends and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citizen Sleeper: Where to Get Scrap Components</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/citizen-sleeper-where-get-scrap-components-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Scrap Component Uses
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Where to Find Scrap Components
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Eye is the large space station that you are trapped on in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Citizen Sleeper
   </strong>
   .
  </em>
  Its distance from other planets leaves many characters stranded looking for a way off the station while struggling to get by. You'll have to carefully manage your resources as you go about meeting new people. It will be a struggle to survive the early stages of
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  ​​​​​​and stay afloat.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Scrap Components are an item that can be found on the Eye. Continue reading this guide to learn where you can get Scrap Components in
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper.
  </em>
  You will also find out why Scrap Components can be so valuable to your character's survival on the Eye.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="scrap-component-uses">
  Scrap Component Uses
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1596246295" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1596246295" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1596246295" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1596246295" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1596246295-img" id="article-gallery-1-1596246295">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1596246295" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1169125966">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Scrap Components have a few important uses in
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper.
  </em>
  There are a few story threads that require you to find Scrap Components to make progress in them. Eight pieces of Scrap Components are necessary to help the refugees in Episode: FLUX. You can save up enough Scrap Components early and hold onto them to help out the Refugee Flotilla later.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Self Repair perk can be very important if you find yourself low on condition with very few dice rolls. Once you've spent two skill points to acquire this perk, you can use Scrap Components to repair your condition at any available player home. You can also sell Scrap Components at the Ort Exchange in the Bright Market area. Trading any Scrap Components will net you some Cryo currency to spend elsewhere.
 </p>
 <h2 id="where-to-find-scrap-components">
  Where to Find Scrap Components
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1750309191" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1750309191" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1750309191" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1750309191" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1750309191-img" id="article-gallery-2-1750309191">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1750309191" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-729596241">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Eye has suffered a collapse and splintered, leaving many chances for people to scavenge scrap from the station's damaged surface. Here are all the ways you can get Scrap Components in
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper.
  </em>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   2/3 chance to get Scrap Components when getting Positive Results from the
   <strong>
    Forensic Trawl
   </strong>
   action in Drago's Yard.
  </li>
  <li>
   2/3 chance to get some when purchasing salvage from a
   <strong>
    Scrap Freighter.
   </strong>
   These Scrap Freighters will occasionally dock at the Rotunda north of the Empty Container.
  </li>
  <li>
   Receive Scrap Components when earning a Positive Result from the
   <strong>
    Collecting Tithes
   </strong>
   action in Rabiah's Ward.
  </li>
  <li>
   You can farm Scrap Components after taking the Founder's Ferry to the Greenway. Get a Positive Result from the Gather Scrap action at
   <strong>
    The Wastes
   </strong>
   area north of the Commune.
  </li>
  <li>
   Unlock the
   <strong>
    Efficient Extractor
   </strong>
   Perk to have a chance to receive Scrap Components whenever you make an Engineer action.
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - How to Increase Reputation</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-how-get-increase-reputation/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Reputation
   </em>
  </strong>
  plays a key role in how the world sees Henry, and how easy it will be for players to trade, bargain, haggle, and convince NPCs to help them. It also alters the dialogue options, and how Guards react when they see Henry.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The more Reputation Henry has, the better he will fare in the Old Bohemian lands. So, with that in mind, players should learn how to increase their Reputation, the faster, the better. So, take a look at this guide and simple tips to gain fame and fortune real quick.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="unwritten-rules-of-reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  Unwritten Rules Of Reputation In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Reputation in Kingdom Come Deliverance II" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/reputation-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-ii.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Reputation can be earned in several ways throughout the gameplay, and like other mechanics like experience gain, or healing, it has a couple of secrets that aren't too complex to figure out, but players should keep in mind to make things easier. Here's a summary of the unwritten rules of reputation in the game:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Can be gained or lost at any point during the game.
  </li>
  <li>
   The only way to keep Henry's reputation at a high level is to maintain proper conduct and please others.
  </li>
  <li>
   The maximum level of Reputation per Area/Faction is 100.
  </li>
  <li>
   Each Area maintains a general level of reputation, so players will carry their reputation from one place to the other.
  </li>
  <li>
   When committing certain actions against the law or decorum, Henry will lose his reputation in that area and will need to regain more in the same place to recover his standing.
  </li>
  <li>
   Actions like haggling and trading give a small amount of reputation, but failing haggling will displease traders, thus, diminishing reputation.
  </li>
  <li>
   Crafting also gives a small boost to reputation.
  </li>
  <li>
   Saving people on the roads or during random encounters (Fast-Travel) will improve Henry's reputation.
  </li>
  <li>
   Stealing or committing murder on the roads will diminish Henry's reputation.
  </li>
  <li>
   Trespassing will reduce a certain amount of reputation after ignoring the initial warning of the 'owners' or Guards.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="how-to-increase-reputation-fast-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  How To Increase Reputation Fast In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-26476131" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-26476131" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-26476131" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-26476131" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-26476131-img" id="article-gallery-1-26476131">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-26476131" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1516214312">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To
  <strong>
   gain reputation fast
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2,
  </em>
  players should try completing secondary quests/objectives, and follow the Main Story Quest. But, as they do, they should also
  <strong>
   Trade
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Haggle
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Craft
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Eliminate Bandits
  </strong>
  as much as possible.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fastest way to earn reputation without going out of the cities is to Craft Weapons, Horseshoes, and Armor, or to craft Potions, Brews, and Food. Once players have many of these items, they can go to different traders and offer their goods, haggling and
  <strong>
   accepting trades for less money
  </strong>
  to further increase their reputation.
 </p>
 <p>
  This way, it won't take too long for them to max out Henry's reputation score. But be careful, certain factors like Hygiene, Charisma, and if players have committed certain acts against the law can also impede them from gaining reputation in certain places.
 </p>
 <p>
  Try to avoid committing murder as much as possible, even accidental deaths during brawls can chip away at all of the player's hard-earned reputation in an instant, so be careful.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
