<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic The Hedgehog: 6 Antagonists Who Became Heroes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sonic-the-hedgehog-antagaonist-villain-became-heroes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sage from
      <em>
       Sonic Frontiers
      </em>
      questions her programming after witnessing Sonic's kindness.
     </li>
     <li>
      Jet the Hawk eventually allies with Sonic in
      <em>
       Sonic Riders
      </em>
      after being obsessed with treasure.
     </li>
     <li>
      Blaze puts her stubbornness aside in
      <em>
       Sonic Rush
      </em>
      to save both her and Sonic's universes.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   Sonic the Hedgehog
  </strong>
  has defeated more than his fair share of bad guys over the course of the franchise, but while Eggman may continue to cause chaos no matter how many times he's taken down, not every antagonist has been so stubborn. Though it's not all that common, there have been a few antagonists in
  <em>
   Sonic
  </em>
  games who, despite starting as enemies to the Blue Blur initially, end up abandoning their malicious ways to become a fully fledged hero in the story.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are many reasons why an antagonist can have a change of heart, whether it be due to seeing the effects of their actions, finding a new purpose in life, or simply receiving a few encouraging words from Sonic himself.
  <strong>
   Though these
   <em>
    Sonic
   </em>
   characters may have seemed like villains at first, they quickly end up becoming valuable allies to the protagonist
  </strong>
  after they come to see the errors of their ways.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="sage">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Sage
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="after-witnessing-sonic-39-s-kindness-and-morality-sage-questions-her-programming">
  After Witnessing Sonic's Kindness And Morality, Sage Questions Her Programming
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2143936759" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2143936759" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2143936759" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2143936759" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2143936759-img" id="article-gallery-1-2143936759">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2143936759" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1519962406">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though
  <strong>
   Sage
  </strong>
  acts as the main antagonist for much of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Sonic Frontiers'
   </strong>
  </em>
  story, constantly giving Sonic cryptic warnings and summoning gigantic Titans for him to take down, she doesn't exactly seem all that evil. In fact, any time Sage watches Sonic bonding with his friends, she begins to question her programming. Eventually, she realizes all she wants is to be a part of a loving family, and as a sign of thanks, she allies with Sonic to face off against The End.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sage actually plays a crucial role at the end of the game as she is the only one who can manage to convince Eggman to put his pride aside and strategize a plan with Sonic once The End begins corrupting the world. Sage even makes a heroic sacrifice in the climactic battle to help Sonic fend off The End once and for all. Needless to say, if Sage hadn't had a change of heart, one can only imagine the state the world would have ended up in.
 </p>
 <h2 id="jet-the-hawk">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Jet The Hawk
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="jet-39-s-obsession-with-babylonian-treasure-takes-a-back-seat-when-he-39-s-forced-to-ally-with-sonic">
  Jet's Obsession With Babylonian Treasure Takes A Back Seat When He's Forced To Ally With Sonic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-894663456" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-894663456" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-894663456" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-894663456" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-894663456-img" id="article-gallery-2-894663456">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-894663456" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-932232910">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the beginning of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic Riders
   </em>
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Jet
  </strong>
  comes across as a shady and mysterious rider who quickly becomes a thorn in the side of Sonic and the crew after stealing an Emerald. Jet's dream of finding the Babylonian treasure brings out his arrogant and selfish side for much of the story, though eventually, he does begrudgingly decide to ally with Sonic to take down a menacing foe known as the Babylon Guardian.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the following two
  <em>
   Riders
  </em>
  games, Jet again slowly transforms from antagonist to ally and becomes more of a rival to Sonic, always eager to challenge him to one final race to prove his Extreme Gear skills to the Blue Blur. It's understandable why there is so much hype about Jet making his long-awaited comeback in
  <em>
   Sonic Racing: CrossWorlds
  </em>
  , as he's become a real fan favorite despite how long he's been away.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="blaze-the-cat">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Blaze The Cat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="blaze-puts-her-stubbornness-aside-to-save-both-her-and-sonic-39-s-universes">
  Blaze Puts Her Stubbornness Aside To Save Both Her And Sonic's Universes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-626937221" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-626937221" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-626937221" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-626937221" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-626937221-img" id="article-gallery-3-626937221">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-626937221" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1011959968">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If there's one word that would summarize
  <strong>
   Blaze
  </strong>
  , it would have to be stubborn. When running into Sonic early on in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic Rush
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Blaze seems less than inclined to tell him anything about who she is or where she's from, even getting into a brawl with the hedgehog because she refuses to let him help her. However, Blaze and Sonic eventually come to realize that they are actually from different timelines, and with two Eggmans on the loose, the cat needed to put her stubbornness aside to have any hope of stopping them.
 </p>
 <p>
  After an intense fight between her and Sonic, Blaze finally lets her guard down, realizing that there's too much at stake to be playing games. Blaze has been a recurring character in the series since her debut, appearing in
  <em>
   Sonic Generations
  </em>
  as Sonic's ally, though their relationship hasn't always been so peachy.
 </p>
 <h2 id="silver-the-hedgehog">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Silver The Hedgehog
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-time-travelling-hedgehog-who-warms-to-sonic-over-time">
  A Time-Travelling Hedgehog Who Warms To Sonic Over Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-883780964" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-883780964" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-883780964" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-883780964" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-883780964-img" id="article-gallery-4-883780964">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-883780964" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-6566760">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Silver
  </strong>
  is a hedgehog who travels into the past to try and find a way to prevent his world from being obliterated by a terrifying monster known as Iblis. Initially, Silver thinks that Sonic is the one to blame for everything going wrong, making him just one of several antagonists who show up to slow the Blue Blur down in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic 06
   </em>
  </strong>
  . However, unlike Mephiles, Silver begins to warm up to Sonic, especially after learning the truth that the hedgehog isn't actually the cause of things to come.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a result, he, Sonic, and Shadow decide to form a temporary alliance, activating their Super forms to overwhelm Mephiles' final transformation, Solaris. Though Silver has only made brief appearances here and there since
  <em>
   Sonic 06
  </em>
  , it seems likely he will be the star of one of the future
  <em>
   Sonic
  </em>
  movies, and it will be amazing for longtime fans to see this antagonist turned hero on the big screen for the very first time.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="knuckles">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Knuckles
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="knuckles-39-naivety-was-on-full-display-when-eggman-tricked-him-into-opposing-sonic">
  Knuckles' Naivety Was On Full Display When Eggman Tricked Him Into Opposing Sonic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1672024361" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1672024361" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1672024361" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1672024361" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1672024361-img" id="article-gallery-5-1672024361">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1672024361" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1879250134">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It can be hard to believe these days, but there was once a time when
  <strong>
   Knuckles
  </strong>
  <strong>
   the
  </strong>
  <strong>
   Echidna
  </strong>
  was an antagonist; at least, until Sonic managed to make him realize that he had been tricked by Eggman. In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Knuckles is led to believe that Sonic is on his way to Angel Island so he can steal the Master Emerald for his own selfish needs. As a result, he and the Blue Blur clash numerous times, until, in
  <em>
   Sonic &amp; Knuckles
  </em>
  , Eggman tries to pull a fast one by taking the Master Emerald for himself.
 </p>
 <p>
  After realizing he had been duped by the doctor, Knuckles leads Sonic to Sky Sanctuary, and also takes on Mecha Sonic all by himself, making him a true hero. Since then, Knuckles has been the powerhouse of Team Sonic, and is always giving his all to protect his friends from danger with his immense strength and durability.
 </p>
 <h2 id="shadow-the-hedgehog">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Shadow The Hedgehog
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="shadow-begins-to-see-sonic-as-more-of-a-rival-than-an-enemy">
  Shadow Begins To See Sonic As More Of A Rival Than An Enemy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1259774682" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1259774682" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1259774682" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1259774682" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1259774682-img" id="article-gallery-6-1259774682">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1259774682" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-678258467">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though
  <strong>
   Shadow
  </strong>
  may be more than willing to help Sonic and the gang save the world in many of the modern
  <em>
   Sonic
  </em>
  games, this wasn't always the case. Back in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic Adventure 2
   </em>
   ,
  </strong>
  when Shadow was first introduced, the mysterious hedgehog was on a mission to destroy the entire world due to his brainwashing and distorted memories of Maria. As a result, he is set up as the main villain for much of the game; that is, until he begins to regain his memories.
 </p>
 <p>
  After working alongside Sonic to prevent the planet from being obliterated, Shadow survives his fall from space and begins to warm up to his blue counterpart. While Shadow would end up becoming an unlikely hero by the end of that game, he would also unite with Sonic at the end of
  <em>
   Sonic Heroes
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Sonic 06,
  </em>
  becoming a villain who showcases heroic qualities whenever the world is in danger.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37-Year-Old Studio Behind Myst Lays off Half Its Staff</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/myst-riven-cyan-worlds-lay-offs-half-staff/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Cyan Worlds, developer of Myst, laid off 12 staff, affecting audio, quality assurance, art, and community management positions.
     </li>
     <li>
      Myst, released in 1993, remains popular with a 2020 Oculus VR remake and Steam and Xbox ports in 2021.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite layoffs, Cyan Worlds remains committed to future projects and the upcoming PlayStation release of Firmament in April.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Cyan Worlds, the developer behind the timeless PC point-and-click adventure games
  <em>
   <strong>
    Myst
   </strong>
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Riven
  </em>
  , announced it has laid off 12 staff members, or roughly half the team. The
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  developers stated that the layoffs would take effect at the end of March and asked other studios to reach out about hiring the ones affected.
 </p>
 <p>
  Originally released in September 1993 on the Macintosh OS before making its way to Windows 3.1 in March 1994,
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  was designed by brothers Rand and Robyn Miller.
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  received a remake in 2020 for Oculus VR headsets and was subsequently ported to Steam and Xbox consoles in 2021. Set on the titular island of Myst, players must solve various puzzles to fully unlock the island's mysteries and backstory. The game's setting is further divided into smaller worlds called Ages. Examples of Ages that
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  players can explore include the Mechanical Age and the Stoneship Age. Unlike most PC games at the time,
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  has no violence and imposes no time limits to solve the game's challenging puzzles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite its reputation for crafting beloved dark fantasy puzzle games, the developers behind
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  made an announcement no studio wants to make. As reported by PC Gamer, Cyan Worlds announced on social media that a dozen staff members were laid off, effective at the end of March. The studio's leadership stated the decision was made after doing what it could to avoid the situation, but the current state of the video game industry forced their hand. The affected positions specialized in fields like audio, quality assurance, art, and community management. Cyan Worlds said that all affected members received severance packages, and it asked other development studios to reach out and hire anyone affected.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="myst-developers-cyan-worlds-announces-layoffs">
  Myst Developers Cyan Worlds Announces Layoffs
 </h2>
 <p>
  Cyan Worlds remained committed to getting more financing for future projects and bringing some stability to the studio. Some of the affected former Cyan staffers consented to listing their contact information and LinkedIn pages via a Google Spreadsheet that the company put together. In response,
  <em>
   Myst
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Riven
  </em>
  fans expressed their sympathies and hoped for the best for those affected. Unfortunately, Cyan Worlds is just the latest studio to announce layoffs, following larger teams like Ubisoft and
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  developer Crystal Dynamics in laying off various staff members.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2044786165" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2044786165" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2044786165" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2044786165" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2044786165-img" id="article-gallery-1-2044786165">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2044786165" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1225824032">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Additionally, Cyan Worlds assured fans that the PlayStation release of
  <em>
   Firmament
  </em>
  , an Unreal Engine 5 adventure game, is still scheduled to arrive sometime in April, despite the recent layoffs. Hopefully, Cyan Worlds will one day recover from its current financial situation.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims 4: Handiness Skill Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-sims-4-handiness-skill-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Handiness Skill is part of
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sims 4
   </em>
  </strong>
  base game and has been around since the game launched. Most Sims will acquire the Handiness Skill throughout their lives without even meaning to. Even if they never master it or practice it beyond household repairs every now and then, it is still one of the most essential skills.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This guide will tell players what they need to know about the Handiness Skill in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , including how to first acquire it, how to level it up, and what unique perks they can unlock as they go.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-sims-4-handiness-skill-overview">
  The Sims 4 Handiness Skill Overview
 </h2>
 <h3 id="what-do-you-unlock-at-every-level-of-the-handiness-skill">
  What Do You Unlock At Every Level of the Handiness Skill?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1165728040" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1165728040" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1165728040" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1165728040" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1165728040-img" id="article-gallery-1-1165728040">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1165728040" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-818024066">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Handiness Skill is a major skill in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , which means players have to reach Level 10 to master it. Here are the various interactions they will gain access to as they level up the Handiness Skill:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Skill Level
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Unlocks
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Interactions:
        </strong>
        <ul>
         <li>
          Salvage parts from piles of junk
         </li>
         <p>
         </p>
        </ul>
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Basic plumbing upgrades
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft furniture at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Social interactions:
        </strong>
        <ul>
         <li>
          Talk about Handiness
         </li>
         <p>
         </p>
        </ul>
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Increases chances of finding rare Upgrade Parts
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft more sculptures at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       4
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Advanced plumbing upgrades
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft end tables at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Decreases chances of getting electrocuted while repairing an item
       </li>
       <li>
        Basic kitchen upgrades
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft large sculptures at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Social interactions:
        </strong>
        <ul>
         <li>
          Brag about Handiness
         </li>
         <li>
          Mentor other Sims in Handiness
         </li>
         <p>
         </p>
        </ul>
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Craft dining tables at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <li>
        Increases chances of finding rare Electronic Parts from Salvaging
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       7
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Upgrades plumbing objects twice as fast
       </li>
       <li>
        Advanced kitchen upgrades
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       8
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Basic electronic upgrades
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft instruments at the Woodworking Table if they have reached Level 8 in an instrument
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       9
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Advanced electronic upgrades
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft tubs at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       10
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Guaranteed rare parts from Salvaging
       </li>
       <li>
        Craft toilets at the Woodworking Table
       </li>
       <li>
        Upgrades kitchen objects twice as fast
       </li>
       <li>
        Break open the Abandoned Cave Entrance and visit Forgotten Grotto in Oasis Springs
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-level-up-the-handiness-skill-in-the-sims-4">
  How to Level Up the Handiness Skill in The Sims 4
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1735250263" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1735250263" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1735250263" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1735250263" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1735250263-img" id="article-gallery-2-1735250263">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1735250263" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-643993357">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Handiness Skill is very practical, and since it's part of Sims' day-to-day life, they will most likely unlock it sooner or later. Nevertheless, it is still important to understand which actions will grant Sims the Handiness Skill in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  ​​​​​​​
  <strong>
   In
   <em>
    The Sims 4
   </em>
   , Sims can obtain the Handiness Skill by repairing items, reading Skill books, or using the Woodworking Table
  </strong>
  . Once a Sim reaches Handiness Skill Level 2, it'll be much easier for them to continue improving, as they will gain access to upgrades.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Sims can learn the Handiness Skill faster if they are feeling focused.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-sims-4-handiness-skill-cheat">
  The Sims 4 Handiness Skill Cheat
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="handiness skill level 10 cheat code the sims 4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/handiness-skill-level-10-cheat-code-the-sims-4.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There is no faster way to obtain the Handiness Skill than to simply cheat for it. Here is the cheat code for the Handiness Skill in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    stats.set_skill_level Major_Handiness [X]
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Firstly, players have to enable cheats and then insert this code into the cheat console. The [X] must be replaced by the level that they want to reach. So, if players want to max out the Handiness Skill, they must input the following code: "
  <strong>
   stats.set_skill_level Major_Handiness​​​​​​​ 10
  </strong>
  ". However, if they just want to quickly reach Level 2 to unlock the ability to perform plumbing upgrades, they can simply input the code "
  <strong>
   stats.set_skill_level Major_Handiness 2
  </strong>
  ".
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Horror Games Where Making Noise Matters</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/horror-games-where-making-noise-matters/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sound plays a crucial role in enhancing the immersive horror experience in games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some titles like "Don't Scream" and "A Quiet Place" require players to remain silent for survival.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like "Dead By Daylight" and "Left 4 Dead 2" use sound cues strategically to add intensity to gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For a horror game to stand out from the competition, it needs come across as immersive and believable. One way developers go about achieving this is by making sound an important part of the core gameplay. While it's not uncommon for horror games to include bait mechanics, where players can toss out a rock while sneaking around an area to cause a distraction, some titles have taken this to the extreme, forcing players to be more strategic when it comes to navigating their environments.
 </p>
 <p>
  Placing more focus on sound has also resulted in some experimental horror experiences that don't play like anything else out there right now, giving horror fans an experimental alternative to dive into. It's time to look at the best horror titles where noise truly matters in the moment-to-moment gameplay.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="don-39-t-scream">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Don't Scream
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="survive-in-a-creepy-forest-without-making-a-noise">
  Survive In A Creepy Forest Without Making A Noise
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2032193077" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2032193077" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2032193077" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2032193077" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2032193077-img" id="article-gallery-1-2032193077">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2032193077" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-586513639">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On the surface, the goal of
  <em>
   Don't Scream
  </em>
  seems simple: survive in a dark and gloomy forest for 18 minutes. However, there's a catch. If the game catches the player shouting or screaming into their mic, the story will automatically restart. Remaining quiet is far from easy when tons of unsettling ghosts and ghouls are creeping around the forest, waiting for their chance for a quick jump scare.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Don't Scream
  </em>
  is immensely fun to play in a dark room with the lights off to ramp up the challenge even more. Only the most hardened of horror fans will be able to make it through
  <em>
   Don't Scream
  </em>
  without making a peep. The game is a shining example of how audio can be utilized in horror games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Until Dawn
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="in-certain-moments-only-silence-amp-stillness-can-save-the-characters">
  In Certain Moments, Only Silence &amp; Stillness Can Save The Characters
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-820778863" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-820778863" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-820778863" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-820778863" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-820778863-img" id="article-gallery-2-820778863">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-820778863" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1981553953">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the core of
  <em>
   Until Dawn's
  </em>
  gameplay are the choices that players make along their journey. Once the crew find themselves face to face with the main enemies of the game, noise starts becoming a much bigger deal. At several points in the game, the motion sensor on the PlayStation controller will show up on the screen, and if players move the controller too far out of the area, the character on the screen will make a noise, attracting the enemy their way and potentially getting them killed in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  These sections become even more intense once the Wendigo show up. They are incredibly sensitive to sound, meaning even the snap of a twig can result in the death of a character.
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  is fondly remembered for its unique gameplay systems and memorable characters, and with noise playing such a big factor, it adds a lot to the intensity of the gameplay.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dead-rising-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Dead Rising 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-random-noise-can-catch-the-horde-39-s-attention">
  A Random Noise Can Catch The Horde's Attention
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1668138163" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1668138163" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1668138163" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1668138163" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1668138163-img" id="article-gallery-3-1668138163">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1668138163" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1137190597">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since
  <em>
   Dead Rising 3
  </em>
  was a launch title for the Xbox One, it makes use of the Kinect that was sold alongside the console at the time. While players can use this to manually wave over fellow survivors with the motion sensor, the Kinect will also pick up on any sound. This can be a blessing or a curse, depending on the situation.
 </p>
 <p>
  If a group of zombies is lurking in an area and refusing to move out of the way, letting out a quick "over here" will make them disperse, so Nick can go and grab some new resources for building weapons and vehicles. On the other hand, crunching down on a snack a bit too hard can end up proving disastrous when a swarm of enemies turns around. Ultimately, this ends up making the game feel much more immersive.
 </p>
 <h2 id="a-quiet-place-the-road-ahead">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   A Quiet Place: The Road Ahead
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-must-monitor-their-sound-levels-to-avoid-being-targeted">
  Players Must Monitor Their Sound Levels To Avoid Being Targeted
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-939739850" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-939739850" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-939739850" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-939739850" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-939739850-img" id="article-gallery-4-939739850">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-939739850" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-442169406">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Early in the story of
  <em>
   A Quiet Place: The Road Ahead
  </em>
  , players will receive the phonometer. This handy tool registers how much noise Alex is making when moving around and collecting resources. Any time the light starts to creep into the red, the lightning-fast monsters will race towards Alex to take her out, resulting in an immersive and intense gameplay experience that stands out for how unforgiving it is.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are even moments in the game where the monsters walk next to Alex without even knowing she's there. If players try to make a fast getaway, they'll be lucky to escape with their life intact. While
  <em>
   The Road Ahead
  </em>
  is a must-play for fans of
  <em>
   The Quiet Place
  </em>
  movie franchise, it's still worth checking out for non-fans who want to enjoy a short but fun and unique horror experience that prides itself on being challenging.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dead-by-daylight">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Dead By Daylight
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sound-is-the-biggest-giveaway-of-a-survivor-39-s-position">
  Sound Is The Biggest Giveaway Of A Survivor's Position
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2074269312" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2074269312" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2074269312" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2074269312" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2074269312-img" id="article-gallery-5-2074269312">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2074269312" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1941763550">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While all the Killers in
  <em>
   Dead by Daylight
  </em>
  possess special abilities that make it easier for them to snoop out the Survivors, the biggest giveaway about a player's location will always be noise. If a survivor is in a wounded state, for example, their grunts and moans will make it difficult for them to avoid the Killer until they are healed by their teammates.
 </p>
 <p>
  This also applies to the generators, which can get loud once they're up and running. Some experienced players will even use generator noises to fool the Killer, such as setting one up and leaving it active so that the small buzzing noise causes a distraction. New Killers may be added to the game at a consistent rate, but no matter how strong or powerful they may be, sound is always going to be what they pay the most attention to while on the hunt.
 </p>
 <h2 id="left-4-dead-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="set-off-a-car-alarm-and-get-hounded-by-bloodthirsty-zombies">
  Set Off A Car Alarm, And Get Hounded By Bloodthirsty Zombies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1064276194" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1064276194" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1064276194" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1064276194" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1064276194-img" id="article-gallery-6-1064276194">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1064276194" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1845840145">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though players are free to try and run-and-gun their way through a campaign in
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  , they'll quickly find that it's an easy way to get surrounded and killed by hordes of regular and special infected zombies. Instead, the better approach is to take things slow and stick with the team. This includes avoiding any of the sound alarms that will occasionally pop up, such as car alarms, which will attract the full force of the horde if set off.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now and again, these sound cues will be unavoidable, meaning players will need to grab all the ammunition and health packs they can to make it through the wave of enemies in one piece. There's even a Special Infected zombie named the Witch who can rip a survivor to shreds if they make too much noise when walking around her. Sound matters a lot in
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2,
  </em>
  and is just one of many mechanics that make the game so fun and exciting to play.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="amnesia-the-bunker">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Amnesia: The Bunker
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="even-the-smallest-noise-will-attract-the-dreaded-stalker-beast">
  Even The Smallest Noise Will Attract The Dreaded Stalker Beast
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-60935376" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-60935376" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-60935376" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-60935376" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-60935376-img" id="article-gallery-7-60935376">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-60935376" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-2074662000">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Amnesia: The Bunker
  </em>
  may only feature a single enemy, but the terrifying behemoth who stalks the dark corridors of the underground bunker possesses an incredible sense of hearing. As a result, players must try to find their way through the bunker, solving puzzles and collecting resources as they go, all while keeping noise to a minimum, which is far from an easy task.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, there are numerous points in the game where an area has to be opened through the use of explosives, though how the players go about doing this is up to them and their level of creativity. Even the flashlight, which can only be charged up by pulling on a string, needs to be used cautiously. While
  <em>
   Amnesia: The Bunker
  </em>
  is fairly light on story, the intense sound-focused gameplay makes it well worth trying out.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alien-isolation">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Alien: Isolation
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-xenomorph-will-scurry-towards-any-noises-it-detects">
  The Xenomorph Will Scurry Towards Any Noises It Detects
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1351622259" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1351622259" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1351622259" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1351622259" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1351622259-img" id="article-gallery-8-1351622259">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1351622259" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-168607024">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For much of
  <em>
   Alien Isolation,
  </em>
  players will be defenseless when coming up against the Xenomorph, and will need to rely on their motion scanner to help them keep track of its movements. The problem is, using the radio scanner too much will give away the player's position because of its constant pinging noise. Meanwhile, a random flashbang or gunshot will instantly catch the attention of the stalker enemy without even needing to wait around.
 </p>
 <p>
  While this can make even the act of walking around a challenge in and of itself, players are encouraged to use the Alien's keen sense of hearing to their advantage too. If there's a room full of humans, for example, making a little ruckus and letting the Alien clear out the area can be an effective strategy, though it's not easy to pull off. This is just one example of the many ways players can toy around with the sound in the popular survival horror classic.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Most Emotional Battles In JRPGs, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-most-emotional-jrpg-battles-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Boss fights in JRPGs require tactical thinking and evoke emotions like rage and joy.
     </li>
     <li>
      Music and storytelling elevate boss fights like Dolcinaea in Octopath Traveler 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      Emotionally charged battles, like against Yunalesca in FFX, add depth and investment.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  JRPGs are no strangers to their fair share of amazing boss fights that will force players to employ everything they've learned to defeat these imposing foes. The combat of these games requires that players use tactical thinking to overcome and defeat these climactic foes.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes some JRPG boss fights all the more memorable is when emotions are spiking during these battles. Rage, anger, and joy are just a few of the emotions that these games manipulate to get players invested in these incredible boss fights.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Spoiler Warning: due to the nature of these dramatic battles, each entry will delve into various narrative spoilers for their respective JRPGs.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="dolcinaea-octopath-traveler-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Dolcinaea (Octopath Traveler 2)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-music-crescendoes-in-an-uplifting-and-epic-battle">
  The Music Crescendoes In An Uplifting And Epic Battle
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Dolcinaea in Octopath Traveler 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-28-mar-2025-06-01-pm-3448.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Octopath Traveler 2
  </em>
  's music does a lot of the heavy lifting (along with its HD-2D visuals, of course) when getting players hyped up for its boss battles, which is why the fight against Dolcinaea is so memorable. In a bid to remind this singer about the beauty of the stage and how magical a performance can be, Agnes puts on a show for the ages as the music crescendoes with a beautiful vocal track.
 </p>
 <p>
  It makes for what is possibly the best final chapter boss fight in terms of emotions and spectacle. After a hard-fought battle, Dolcinaea can't help but be moved by Agnes' performance as she finally sees the light and concedes defeat.
 </p>
 <h2 id="magus-chrono-trigger">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Magus (Chrono Trigger)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-climactic-boss-fight-against-a-major-antagonist-where-a-lot-of-things-are-at-stake">
  A Climactic Boss Fight Against A Major Antagonist Where A Lot Of Things Are At Stake
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Magus from Chrono Trigger" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/magus-from-chrono-trigger.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Magus is built up as the major antagonist of
  <em>
   Chrono Trigger
  </em>
  , with Frog having a personal grudge against this foe for cursing him. After Crono's "death," players get to interact with Magus and are given the option of fighting him.
 </p>
 <p>
  While players can refuse this battle, accepting will initiate a tough one-on-one battle between Magus and Frog. Victory will ensure that Frog will be freed from his curse, although he will only regain his human form at the end of the game after this emotional battle to get his life back.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="yunalesca-final-fantasy-10">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Yunalesca (Final Fantasy 10)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="auron-39-s-speech-fires-players-up-for-this-tough-fight">
  Auron's Speech Fires Players Up For This Tough Fight
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Yunalesca before battle in FF10" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mixcollage-07-nov-2024-02-47-pm-8043.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Lady Yunalesca is supposed to be a revered deity looking out for humanity, but the party is well aware of her treachery by the time they encounter her in the Zanarkand ruins. She lied to the summoners and all of humanity about the teachings of Yevon, trapping Spira in a cycle of violence that has ravaged them for centuries.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hearing Auron motivate the party to fight against fate and defeat Yunalesca for good is a rousing affair that heightens the emotions of this tough boss battle. It's one of the best speeches before a boss battle that proves once again why Auron is hailed by many as one of the greatest
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  characters of all time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="goro-akechi-persona-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Goro Akechi (Persona 5)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="akechi-is-fired-up-and-questions-the-value-of-friendship-during-this-chaotic-battle">
  Akechi Is Fired Up And Questions The Value Of Friendship During This Chaotic Battle
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Goro Akechi approaches the Phantom Thieves with ulterior motives in Persona 5" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/goro-akechi-approaches-the-phantom-thieves-with-ulterior-motives-in-persona-5.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Goro Akechi is a genius detective who prefers working alone, which is why it's odd to see him team up with the Phantom Thieves. However, it doesn't take long for the group to figure out that he's the one causing people to go psychotic, almost tanking the reputation of the Phantom Thieves in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  The boss battle against him in Shido's Palace is one of the best moments in
  <em>
   Persona 5
  </em>
  . He laughs at the idea of friendship, projecting his insecurities onto Joker and his party as they engage in a hellacious battle. It's an emotional fight that ends with Akechi sacrificing himself to save the party in a heartbreaking moment, even if this sacrifice is cheapened somewhat after his return in
  <em>
   Persona 5 Royal
  </em>
  's final semester.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ardyn-izunia-aka-ardyn-lucis-caelum-final-fantasy-15">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Ardyn Izunia, AKA Ardyn Lucis Caelum (Final Fantasy 15)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ends-on-an-emotional-note-as-noctis-purges-the-starscourge-from-the-world">
  Ends On An Emotional Note As Noctis Purges The Starscourge From The World
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ardyn in Final Fantasy 15" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/final-fantasy-15.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ardyn Izunia is one of the most tragic JRPG villains of all time, although that's no excuse for his atrocious actions in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15
  </em>
  . He serves as a thorn in Noctis' side, made even worse by the fact that he's related to Ardyn since they're part of the same family.
 </p>
 <p>
  Realizing that he needs to sacrifice his body and mind to eliminate Ardyn for good, Noctis bids farewell to his friends before defeating Ardyn and using the Ring of the Lucii to end the Starscourge for good. Seeing him one final time in the afterlife after this moment is emotional enough as is, but it's the post-credits scene that will make fans bawl after they hear Noctis proclaim his love for his friends before he heads to Insomnia for the final time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ryo-aoki-aka-masato-arakawa-yakuza-like-a-dragon">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Ryo Aoki, AKA Masato Arakawa (Yakuza: Like A Dragon)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ichiban-knocks-some-sense-into-the-young-master">
  Ichiban Knocks Some Sense Into The Young Master
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ryo Aoki AKA Masato Arakawa in Yakuza: Like a Dragon" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mixcollage-25-feb-2025-07-07-pm-9190.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  did a great job of doing justice to Ichiban Kasuga, a new character who needed to hit the ground running and avoid the mistakes that turned
  <em>
   Judgment
  </em>
  's Yagami into such an unlikable protagonist. His earnestness and goofy nature made him a perfect main character for the
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  series, but what made him all the more compelling was his ability to become emotional at the drop of a hat when the story required him to become serious.
 </p>
 <p>
  Him forgiving Nanba is a great moment in its own right, but it's the rousing speech he delivers to his former master, Masato Arakawa, at the end of the game that will make fans shed a tear. Instances like these are why many people consider
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  to boast one of the best stories told in the series, which is a massive achievement.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="jenova-life-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Jenova Life (Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-boss-fight-that-blindsides-players-right-after-a-sudden-tragedy">
  A Boss Fight That Blindsides Players Right After A Sudden Tragedy
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Jenova Life in Final Fantasy 7" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mixcollage-04-mar-2025-09-00-pm-2552.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Jenova Life is a boss fight that comes out of nowhere, barely letting players process Aerith's death in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  . The sight of Sephiroth's sword impaling their favorite healer is still fresh in their minds during this battle.
 </p>
 <p>
  It doesn't help that Aerith's theme plays throughout this emotional boss fight, with the party members refusing to crack their victory pose after defeating Jenova Life. What follows is a touching moment as Cloud bids farewell to Aerith before the party is forced to move on.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-final-stand-against-the-shinra-soldiers-crisis-core-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   The Final Stand Against The Shinra Soldiers (Crisis Core: Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="zack-puts-it-all-on-the-line-to-save-cloud">
  Zack Puts It All On The Line To Save Cloud
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Zack Fair during the Final Fantasy Crisis Core Ending" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/crisis-core-ending.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Everyone knew how
  <em>
   Crisis Core
  </em>
  would end, but that doesn't prepare them for the manner in which Zack meets his end. After trying to escape with Cloud, his friend's mako poisoning prevents the spiky-haired blonde from making this escape any easier.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a result, the Shinra Troopers pursuing the duo eventually catch up, and Zack makes a heroic final stand as he takes on a wave of Shinra troopers, incurring a ton of damage in the process. Seeing the DMW break cements Zack's fate, who's left mortally wounded and passes on the Buster Sword to Cloud in a tragic moment as the protagonist of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  inadvertently takes on the memories of his fallen comrade.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
