<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tetris 99 is Crossing Over with Xenoblade Chronicles X</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tetris-99-xenoblade-chronicles-x-crossover/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Tetris 99's 46th Maximus Cup partners with Xenoblade Chronicles X.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players compete to earn points and are rewarded with a special theme after accumulating enough.
     </li>
     <li>
      The cup will begin on March 14, 2025 and run until March 18, 2025.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Nintendo has revealed
  <strong>
   <em>
    Tetris 99
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s 46th Maximus Cup will be joining forces with
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  , and the start date is closer than players think.
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  's Maximus Cup is a recurring event in the popular puzzle game, dating back to the very first cup that took place in March 2019. Players compete for prizes and gain points by entering into matches, and usually, the top 999 competitors with the most points are awarded My Nintendo Gold Points and a new theme depending on the crossover, including
  <em>
   Fire Emblem
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Super Kirby Clash
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  was launched in 2019 by Arika and Nintendo, serving as an online multiplayer version of the original Tetrominoes novelty.
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  was an earlier release in 2015 and part of the
  <em>
   Xeno
  </em>
  metaseries, based on the open-world planet of Mira where players complete quests, unlock new regions, and gather resources after joining the BLADE unit to protect humanity.
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  has become one of the most experimental Nintendo Switch exclusives, alongside
  <em>
   Nintendo Labo
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Endless Ocean Luminous
  </em>
  , for its bold move to capitalize on the battle royale formula.
 </p>
 <p>
  Following the puzzle game’s cup tradition,
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  will be crossing over with
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  for the 46th Maximus Cup competition, similar to Nintendo’s pairing of its IPs last year when
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Splatoon
  </em>
  joined forces for the 42nd Maximus Cup. The cup will begin on March 14, 2025, and run until March 18, 2025, offering players the chance to earn the special
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  theme to celebrate the upcoming release of the game’s
  <em>
   Definitive Edition
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="tetris-99-39-s-46th-maximus-cup-will-crossover-with-xenoblade-chronicles-x">
  Tetris 99's 46th Maximus Cup Will Crossover With Xenoblade Chronicles X
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X special theme
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    March 14 - March 18, 2025
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  With plenty of exclusive game franchises under its belt, Nintendo previously hosted a
  <em>
   Super Mario All-Stars
  </em>
  -themed event in
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  , and fans of the Japanese publisher’s portfolio are keen to see the trend continue. One Twitter user thought
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  ’s Mira setting was perfect to wipe out Tetrominoes, and others were happy they didn’t have to wait too long for this union.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-97079408" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-97079408" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-97079408" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-97079408" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-97079408-img" id="article-gallery-1-97079408">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-97079408" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1546629338">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In addition to
  <em>
   Tetris 99
  </em>
  ’s crossover event with
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  , fans of the Monolith Soft-created action RPG have another reason to get excited in March.
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is launching a
  <em>
   Definitive Edition
  </em>
  for the Nintendo Switch on March 20, which will feature enhanced visuals and new story content. Some of the fresh content includes a mysterious incident, a new enemy faction, and the return of the Ares Skell within a new floating continent setting, plus the arrival of new characters, a mecha, and enhanced gameplay systems.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds Fan Shares an Interesting Detail About Photo Mode</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monster-hunter-wilds-photo-mode-pose-alma/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players can capture unique moments with Alma in Monster Hunter Wilds' photo mode.
     </li>
     <li>
      Capcom's attention to detail in photo mode, like Alma posing or waving, helps the setting feel alive.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans appreciate the immersive world of Monster Hunter Wilds, with NPC interactions adding depth to the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </em>
  </strong>
  fan pointed out that Alma poses for pictures when the player uses the game's photo mode.
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  has proven to be a big hit for Capcom, with many gamers praising the title for its cinematic combat and rich open world.
 </p>
 <p>
  The photo mode in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  gives players the opportunity to capture moments they might otherwise miss, allowing them to craft the perfect screenshot to share with friends. Photo modes have become increasingly popular in recent years and, because of this, some developers have dedicated a lot of resources to making them as rewarding as possible. Many people are already praising the photo mode in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , which appears to be pushing the boundaries of interactivity between the characters and the player. Many fans were pleasantly surprised to see Capcom do something similar.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent post on Reddit, LexGoSketch shared a video of Alma posing with one of her archaeological artifacts when the player used photo mode in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  to snap a screenshot of her. It came as a surprise, as the gamer didn't expect Alma to change her demeanor at all. Other fans jumped in to say they'd experienced similar things, such as Alma taking off her glasses for a photo. One person claimed that Alma would do the same while riding a Seikret, and another person pointed out that she strikes a completely different pose if the hunter is in the shot with her.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="alma-strikes-a-pose-when-using-photo-mode-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  Alma Strikes a Pose When Using Photo Mode in Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <p>
  One fan added that they tried to take a photo of their hunter by themselves, only to have Alma enter the frame waving while riding her Seikret in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  . Many fans were enamored with the amount of detail Capcom put into the game's photo mode, suggesting that the interactions with Alma really helped bring the setting to life.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1790913685" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1790913685" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1790913685" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1790913685" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1790913685-img" id="article-gallery-1-1790913685">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1790913685" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1827756296">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Outside of photo mode, some players shared that Alma and NPC hunters will applaud and cheer after a hunt if the player decides to use an emote. One fan said that, when they allowed the game to idle, Alma began waving at the screen instead of the hunter. Gamers have also noted that the hunter's Palico in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  also has a lot of unique interactions with the world, such as napping on wagons or even moving lumber within the base camp. With so many little details to observe, many players seem to be enjoying their time with Capcom's latest action RPG.
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: Smash N' Grab Jewelry Store Locations</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-smash-grab-jewelry-store-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Lawless season of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fortnite
   </strong>
  </em>
  is all about scoring heaps of gold and then spending that cash on fancy new weapons. One of the key ways to earn gold is by breaking into this season's bank vaults, but those heists tend to draw a lot of attention from rival players and the gang members working for this season's main antagonist, Fletcher Kane. There is another less intense way to steal some gold thanks to the ability to rob Smash N' Grab Jewelry Stores.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  These establishments have popped up all over Fortnite and contain plenty of gold bars for players to stash into their pockets. Although robbing a Smash N' Grab is quicker and easier than breaking into a vault, that doesn't mean that committing these robberies is a simple task. This guide will reveal their locations as well as how to steal everything inside that isn't nailed down.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-smash-n-39-grab-jewelry-stores">
  Where To Find Smash N' Grab Jewelry Stores
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1109792258" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1109792258" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1109792258" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1109792258" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1109792258-img" id="article-gallery-1-1109792258">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1109792258" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1971670001">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are 5 Smash N' Grabs spread across the map. They are fixed structures in the world, which means that they don't spawn in. So if players are fast, they could theoretically hit every store in one round. Here's where you can find them:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Middle of Whiffy Wharf
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    North of Pumped Power near a Burd gas station
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    West side of Hopeful Heights
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Northwest side of Canyon Crossing
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Southwest of Outlaw Oasis at the Yokina Boardwalk landmark near a Reboot Van
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Technically, there are 6 Smash N' Grab locations as one can be found within Crime City. However, this one always appears to be looted when the game starts, which is likely because it's based in the most crime-ridden location on the map.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="how-to-rob-a-smash-n-39-grab-jewelry-store">
  How To Rob A Smash N' Grab Jewelry Store
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="fortnite peabody stealing gold from smash n grab" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fortnite-robbing-jewelry-store.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Each of these jewelry stores will have at least two enemy guards patrolling the area. These are the same guards who protect bank vaults, and they can be killed easily with regular gunfire. After they're dealt with, it's time to start looting. Inside the store are glass display cases that can be interacted with. Doing so will break them open for piles of gold bars. In addition to these cases, there will usually be a safe or cash register that can be opened for even more gold.
 </p>
 <p>
  While these robberies are much easier than bank vault heists, breaking the cases will trigger an alarm that features a loud siren and flashing red lights. This doesn't seem to summon any additional guards, but it can alert enemy players so be sure not to linger. Grab the gold and get out of there.
 </p>
 <p>
  Bank vaults do contain more gold than a Smash N' Grab, but the relative ease of knocking over one of these stores makes it worth doing. Smashing all of the display cases and opening the safe or cash register inside of the store can earn around 400 gold. Sometimes stores will even have both a cash register and a safe, which means even more gold for the player.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Renovator: Origins - Official Console Release Date Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/the-renovator-origins-official-console-release-date-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Renovator: Origins is a first-person psychological horror game developed by Peace_Studio. See the official console release date trailer here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected: Cry of the Wild - Official Announcement Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/unexpected-cry-of-the-wild-official-announcement-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A romantic yacht trip turns into a fight for survival in Unexpected: Cry of the Wild. Don't miss the official announcement trailer.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
