<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Reveals Impressive Stats for 2024</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/minecraft-2024-player-stats/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mojang releases a new Minecraft video revealing stats and records set in 2024.
     </li>
     <li>
      2024's major content updates played a role in the major stats achieved in Minecraft this year.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Mojang revealed several impressive stats about
  <strong>
   <em>
    Minecraft
   </em>
  </strong>
  in 2024, including the number of blocks broken and biomes visited throughout the year. 2024 also marked the 15th anniversary of
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  , which is still one of the most actively played games in the world across multiple platforms.
 </p>
 <p>
  2024 saw the release of multiple new updates for
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  , and Mojang committed to releasing more
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  updates on a consistent basis. These updates include Armored Paws, Tricky Trials, The Garden Awakens, and Bundles of Bravery, which brought new creatures, content, and items for
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  players to enjoy. When coupled with the
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  marketplace, players had an incredible amount of content to explore in 2024, and the community achieved equally amazing feats as the year wraps up.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mojang released a new video titled "Minecraft 2024: A year in blocks" to highlight the many achievements and stats that
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  players contributed to this year. 347 billion blocks were broken in
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  this year, along with 44 million Armadillo scutes picked up after
  <em>
   Minecraft's
  </em>
  Armored Paws update launched in April 2024. 1.3 million wolf armor, 491,000 Crafters, and 2 million Maces were crafted in 2024, and 24 million vaults were opened by solo players and groups in
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  . While preparing wolf armor, players have tamed over 100 million wolves and defeated a total of 20 million breezes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="mojang-reveals-impressive-minecraft-stats-for-2024-in-a-year-in-blocks-video">
  Mojang Reveals Impressive Minecraft Stats for 2024 in A Year in Blocks Video
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-f485698cb7b7c83a" id="emaki-video-player-f485698cb7b7c83a">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   347 billion blocks broken
  </li>
  <li>
   44 million Armadillo scutes picked up
  </li>
  <li>
   1.3 million wolf armor crafted
  </li>
  <li>
   491,000 Crafters crafted
  </li>
  <li>
   2 million Maces crafted
  </li>
  <li>
   24 million vaults opened
  </li>
  <li>
   20 million breezes defeated
  </li>
  <li>
   53 million eyeblossoms collected
  </li>
  <li>
   39 million Hardcore deaths recorded
  </li>
  <li>
   85 million biomes visited
  </li>
  <li>
   1.4 million bundles dyed
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Additionally, 53 million eyeblossoms were collected in
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  this year.
  <em>
   Minecraft's
  </em>
  beloved Hardcore mode was also highly active in 2024, with Mojang recording 39 million player deaths in this mode. 85 billion biomes were visited across all of
  <em>
   Minecraft's
  </em>
  modes, and players dyed 1.4 million bundles.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1643118491" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1643118491" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1643118491" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1643118491" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1643118491-img" id="article-gallery-1-1643118491">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1643118491" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-657373359">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Mojang did not reveal any of the new updates or expansions releasing in 2025 yet, but
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  looks set to have another eventful year if the studio plans on maintaining its output of new content and features for the game. It's possible that some of 2025's first new
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  updates won't be as big as 2024's Armored Paws and The Garden Awakens updates, but it's likely that multiple minor updates will be released to build up toward that first major expansion of the year.
 </p>
 <p>
  While waiting for new updates,
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  players can score some savings in the New Year's Sale, which discounts several user-created add-ons in the
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  marketplace. The sale is live through January 7, 2025, at 10:00 AM PT, so fans still have a few weeks left to save on content and select Character Creator items.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Falling Gracefully!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-falling-gracefully/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player downs a helicopter with mines and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Effect's Show Has a Huge Decision to Make Regarding Its Adaptation of the Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/mass-effect-tv-show-big-decision-tone-comedy-serious-horror/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The widely lauded
  <em>
   <strong>
    Mass Effect
   </strong>
  </em>
  game franchise is set for a TV adaptation on Amazon, though most specifics of the show are still shrouded in mystery. Whether this will be more of a
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  situation (that is, a critical darling or a flop) remains to be seen, but it's hard to deny the sci-fi franchise's cinematic potential.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_1">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The
     <em>
      Mass Effect
     </em>
     adaptation will be penned by
     <em>
      Fast and Furious 9
     </em>
     writer Daniel Casey and produced by Avi Arad, whose CV includes everything from the Sam Raimi
     <em>
      Spider-Man
     </em>
     movies to the recent
     <em>
      Uncharted
     </em>
     film.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  For the uninitiated, the original
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  trilogy follows Commander Shepard, a member of the Systems Alliance Navy, which represents the interests of Earth and all human space colonies. Shepard traverses the Milky Way, nurturing relationships with various human and non-human powers, in an effort to thwart the Reapers, an existential, seemingly unstoppable threat. It's a thrilling and high-stakes narrative, but it's just as defined by its small, intimate moments as by its bombastic battles and live-or-death decisions. Given the series' emphasis on player choice, it's been generally believed that the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  show will center on a new conflict within the broader world of the IP, but with a healthy dose of the games' DNA, both in terms of narrative content and tone.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-mass-effect-tv-show-39-s-tone-will-be-one-of-its-defining-factors">
  The Mass Effect TV Show's Tone Will Be One of Its Defining Factors
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1831101321" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1831101321" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1831101321" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1831101321" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1831101321-img" id="article-gallery-1-1831101321">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1831101321" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1160060563">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-tone-of-mass-effect-in-a-nutshell">
  The Tone of Mass Effect, In a Nutshell
 </h3>
 <p>
  As previously mentioned, the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  trilogy, as well as
  <em>
   Andromeda
  </em>
  , balances between existential stakes and small character-building moments, but most players would agree that the latter is most vital to the series' identity.
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  's cast of NPCs is consistently likable, for the most part at least, and their individual arcs are a treat to watch unfold. From the shy but determined Tali to the jocular but damaged Garrus,
  <em>
  </em>
  the friends and foes that
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  players make during their time with the series are central to its narrative meat. Without these lovable and complex companions, the life-or-death nature of the plot's main conflict wouldn't be nearly as impactful.
 </p>
 <p>
  But it's hard for a story to endear characters to audiences without moments of levity, which is why
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  is never all doom and gloom, all the time. Indeed, from small-scale conversations, to charmingly awkward romantic interactions, to satirical plot beats like those of the
  <em>
   Citadel
  </em>
  DLC, the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  games excel at offering an even blend of sincere, dramatic, comedic, and intriguing. This is what makes the series work so well, and it will also be the toughest thing for the show to get right.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-the-mass-effect-show-might-handle-adapting-the-series-39-tone">
  How the Mass Effect Show Might Handle Adapting the Series' Tone
 </h3>
 <p>
  Whether the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  TV show follows Shepard's story or is totally removed from the events of the games, the aforementioned tonal elements could make or break the experience. If the show is all about gunning down aliens or making heroic sacrifices, then it runs the risk of being just another sci-fi action show, but if it leans too far into comedy or lightheartedness, then it could lack a vital edge. Finding a way to recreate the lightning in a bottle nature of the original
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  games could be an uphill battle, but one that could be extremely worthwhile if it's won.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's also something to be said about the overall atmosphere and, for lack of a better term, vibe of
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  . The synth-driven, almost psychedelic soundtrack of the games, for instance, goes a long way toward giving it a constant allure and sense of character, and the TV show may want to replicate this as well.
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  has also never been afraid of exploring dark and difficult subject matter, so this same kind of fearlessness could benefit the show in myriad ways.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Scrolls Fan Gets Real-Life Skyrim Fork for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elder-scrolls-fan-real-life-skyrim-fork-christmas-gift/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A fan's unique Christmas gift of a Skyrim fork replica showcases creativity and dedication to the game.
     </li>
     <li>
      Skyrim's popularity has led to a creative fanbase with inside jokes and real-life replicas of in-game items.
     </li>
     <li>
      The custom fork is impractical but amusing, mirroring the game's quirky nature in a unique way.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  fan received a unique and amusing gift for Christmas from their boyfriend in the form of a lifelike replica of the forks used by the NPCs in
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim
   </strong>
   .
  </em>
  The gift, while not likely to be very functional in real life, showcases some strong attention to detail and serves as a unique decorative prop as opposed to the usual swords, shields, and other weapons found in the
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  series.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the whole franchise has been a staple in the RPG genre for decades,
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim
  </em>
  is easily the most popular game in the series, garnering numerous new versions and consistently high player numbers. As such, it may come as no surprise that the game's fanbase has a multitude of inside jokes and creative people who set out to bring its many items and elements to life.
 </p>
 <p>
  One such fan is the boyfriend of Reddit user saltsyrebad, who made a real-world replica of the forks found in
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  and gifted it to them for Christmas in a show of creativity and dedication to the game. The fork only has two prongs on it, making it likely difficult to use properly as an actual utensil, but its rustic-looking metallic exterior and overall size shows off a high attention to detail when compared to the in-game version.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="a-skyrim-fan-39-s-gift-recreates-an-amusing-in-game-item">
  A Skyrim Fan's Gift Recreates An Amusing In-Game Item
 </h2>
 <p>
  It is unclear exactly how they made the fork originally, as it appears to be fashioned out of real metal, but it is also possible that a 3D printer was involved at some point to nail down the proportions better. Fans largely expressed amusement towards the item, with many mentioning how impractical it looked as a usable item in real life, with others making cheeky references to specific mechanics from
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  <em>
   .
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  While the fork is largely useless in-game as well, serving as little more than set dressing, the player has the ability to equip it as a weapon, though it will deal very minor damage compared to actual swords, magic, or the like. That being said,
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  is full of exploits that let the player become ultra-powerful, which includes the ability to enchant even the weakest items with extremely strong magical perks that can do a ton of damage.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-246378649" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-246378649" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-246378649" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-246378649" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-246378649-img" id="article-gallery-1-246378649">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-246378649" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1436356209">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In any case, the fork can be an amusing way to deal damage in the game and doubles as something of an inside joke within the
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  community. There are other, more practical creations as well, though, such as one fan who made the Dragon Priest Masks from
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  out of wood.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Battlefield 1 Roadkilling!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-battlefield-1-roadkilling/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players score eliminations with vehicles in Battlefield 1 and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
