<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Players Can Claim 2 Free Operator Skins, But There's a Catch</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-how-to-get-free-operator-bundle-ps-plus/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 players who are subscribed to PlayStation Plus can now claim a free Season 2 bundle.
     </li>
     <li>
      The bundle includes two operator skins, three weapon blueprints, and much more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans are annoyed by the bundle as it includes operator skins that players have previously paid for.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  players can now claim a free Season 2 bundle that includes 2 operator skins, 3 weapon blueprints, double XP tokens, and much more. Unfortunately, there is a catch, as this Season 2 bundle can only be claimed by
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  players on PlayStation 4 or PlayStation 5 who are also subscribed to the platform's popular subscription service, PS Plus.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   Fans have been left somewhat baffled by the new PS Plus bundle, as
   <em>
    Call of Duty
   </em>
   's publisher, Activision, is now owned by Sony's competitor, Microsoft. In October 2023, Microsoft officially completed its acquisition of Activision-Blizzard, which cost a massive $68.7 billion and was the biggest acquisition in video game history. Now that Activision is under the Microsoft umbrella, many of the studio's titles have begun making their way to Xbox Game Pass, including the recently released
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
   . However, despite the acquisition now being over a year old, it looks like PS Plus users are still getting some extra
   <em>
    Call of Duty
   </em>
   benefits that Xbox users aren't.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-free-black-ops-6-season-2-bundle-with-ps-plus">
  How To Get Free Black Ops 6 Season 2 Bundle With PS Plus
 </h2>
 <p>
  On February 4, a new bundle for
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Season 2 made its way to the PlayStation Store. Unlike many other
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  bundles, this one can be claimed for free, but only by users who are currently subscribed to PlayStation Plus. The bundle includes 2 operator skins, 3 weapon blueprints, 2 animated emotes, a weapon charm, a weapon reticle, an emblem, a background, 2 stickers, 2 double XP tokens (1 hour), and 2 double weapon XP tokens (1 hour). To claim the bundle, subscribe to PlayStation Plus and visit the store page for the bundle to redeem it. The contents of the bundle will then be added to the user's
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  account, but it is worth noting that the terms and conditions of the bundle state that the pack is not cross-platform supported.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1867024553" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1867024553" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1867024553" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1867024553" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1867024553-img" id="article-gallery-1-1867024553">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1867024553" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-754342567">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  players aren't happy with the recently released bundle, as the included operator skins have already been made available in other paid bundles. In the past, any PS Plus exclusive bundles included operator skins and cosmetics that cannot be purchased elsewhere, but that no longer seems to be the case with the latest release. Over on Reddit, user Nedtheshred said, "Wow, the one pack I spent money on is now free, fantastic work." User That_Wet_Banana69 also expressed their frustrations, saying, "Only skin I paid for too…. frustrating." Many others were left confused as to why Xbox Game Pass subscribers also aren't receiving the same bundle, calling it "stupid."
 </p>
 <p>
  With the price of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  bundles continuing to increase, it's no surprise that some players are annoyed about Activision giving away operator skins that were previously included in paid bundles. While most bundles cost between 2,000 and 2,400 COD Points, a recent leak revealed that an upcoming bundle will cost 3,300 COD Points, making it the most expensive one in
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
   </em>
  </span>
  ​​​​​​history. Although fans are clearly growing frustrated with the increasing costs, Activision is continuing to push its luck further and further with the community.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onimusha 2: Samurai's Destiny Remastered - Announcement Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/onimusha-2-samurais-destiny-remastered-announcement-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Onimusha 2: Samurai's Destiny is being remastered! The game is set to release on PC, PlayStation 4, Nintendo Switch, Xbox One, and Steam, later in 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Pokemon Legends: Z-A Could Be a Godsend for Pokemon GO</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-legends-z-a-pokemon-go-new-mega-evolutions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon Legends: Z-A
   </strong>
  </em>
  has remained one of Nintendo’s most anticipated games of 2025. The follow-up to 2022’s
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Arceus
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  looks to build on that game’s unique gameplay mechanics to create a new definitive
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  game. It also looks to be one last big hurrah for the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  franchise on the Nintendo Switch before the Nintendo Switch 2 is ready to go.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Most excitingly,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  is set to return players to the Kalos region, an area that has not been explored in any of the mainline games since 2013’s
  <em>
   Pokemon X and Y
  </em>
  . Fans of the sixth generation of mainline
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  should be ready to re-explore Lumiose City, as the game puts that city in a major narrative spotlight. This new title will likely be a boon for the Nintendo Switch, but it could also do wonders if it works in tandem with another popular
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  title.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-legends-z-a-could-factor-into-pokemon-go">
  Pokemon Legends: Z-A Could Factor Into Pokemon GO
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-662592905" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-662592905" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-662592905" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-662592905" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-662592905-img" id="article-gallery-1-662592905">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-662592905" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-728532980">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="pokemon-go-still-champions-mega-evolutions">
  Pokemon GO Still Champions Mega Evolutions
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  making a return to the Kalos region will do wonders for the ever-popular mobile game
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . This is thanks largely to
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  being one of the only modern
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  titles that still champions Mega Evolution. The Mega Evolution mechanic first appeared in the original Kalos-based entries,
  <em>
   Pokemon X and Y
  </em>
  , but later entries have done away with Mega Evolutions in favor of new forms and features entirely.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , however, has continued to implement Mega Evolutions as a major part of its gameplay. Unlike
  <em>
   Pokemon X and Y
  </em>
  , where Mega Evolutions come thanks to a Mega Stone, Pokemon can evolve into these forms in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  once enough Mega Energy has been charged up. Once they evolve, they can maintain their Mega Form for eight real-world hours, whereas
  <em>
   Pokemon X and Y
  </em>
  only Mega Evolved Pokemon briefly during battles.
 </p>
 <h3 id="pokemon-legends-z-a-39-s-new-megas-could-make-it-into-pokemon-go">
  Pokemon Legends Z-A's New Megas Could Make It Into Pokemon GO
 </h3>
 <p>
  Clearly,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  has a great crossover opportunity with
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  thanks to Mega Evolutions. The initial trailer for
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  makes it clear that Mega Evolutions will play into the new game, which is to be expected from a game that takes place in the region that introduced them. With this new game looking to revive Mega Evolutions,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  could take advantage of that.
 </p>
 <p>
  After all, this new mainline entry will most likely introduce several brand-new Mega Evolutions for Pokemon that never received these forms in the past. Thus,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  could take advantage of this and immediately add many of these new Mega Evolutions to its current roster. This would be a great promotional opportunity for
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  to build on the hype of
  <em>
   Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  while also aiding its current implementation of these forms.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Clearly,
     <em>
      Pokemon Legends: Z-A
     </em>
     has a great crossover opportunity with
     <em>
      Pokemon GO
     </em>
     thanks to Mega Evolutions.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="pokemon-legends-z-a-could-influence-next-year-39-s-kalos-tour">
  Pokemon Legends: Z-A Could Influence Next Year's Kalos Tour
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  ’s release could also influence the future of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , especially with the recurring Tour events that arrive close to every Pokemon Day and celebrate each
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  region. Though 2025 will be the year of the Unova Tour, 2026 will be the beginning of the Kalos Tour. While
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A’
  </em>
  s 2025 release window might drive a wedge in some of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  ’s plans, a late-year release would put it reasonably close to the mobile game’s Kalos tour, creating a great promotional opportunity for the two titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  2025 is shaping up to be an exciting year for
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  , as this new game should help close out the Nintendo Switch’s life on a high note. Its exciting return to Kalos also bodes well for other sectors of the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  franchise, especially
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , which should tie in nicely with
  <em>
   Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  ’s reintroduction of Mega Evolutions. There’s a great cross-selling opportunity at play here, and hopefully, The Pokemon Company won’t let it slip.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monopoly GO: Best Strategy for High Roller Flash Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monopoly-go-best-strategy-high-roller-flash-event-how-play/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Monopoly GO High Roller, Explained
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Best Strategy for High Roller in Monopoly GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monopoly GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  retains its core mechanics of rolling dice and collecting rent, it takes things up a notch by introducing Flash Events, like the
  <strong>
   High Roller
  </strong>
  . This time-limited booster motivates players to achieve as much as possible within the given window. Since the High Roller event has a limited time, players need to act quickly and efficiently to take full advantage of it. Read on for a detailed explanation of how the High Roller works and the best strategy to capitalize on it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="monopoly-go-high-roller-explained">
  Monopoly GO High Roller, Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1199017311" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1199017311" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1199017311" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1199017311" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1199017311-img" id="article-gallery-1-1199017311">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1199017311" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1264402783">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  During the High Roller event, you can earn a special
  <strong>
   dice multiplier that can go as high as x1000
  </strong>
  , if you have the dice for it. The increased dice count allows you to score more points in one go and complete events and tournaments more quickly.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like other flash events in
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  , the High Roller event also
  <strong>
   has a limited duration and can run from five to ten minutes at a time
  </strong>
  . When triggered, you can amp up the dice multiplier during the High Roller to score bigger rewards and progress through the events and tournaments much faster.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, if you’re not getting good numbers with the higher multiplier and not landing on your desired tiles
  <strong>
   , you can quickly burn through your dice pool
  </strong>
  . As such, you need to carefully plan and execute the right strategy during the High Roller flash event.
 </p>
 <h2 id="best-strategy-for-high-roller-in-monopoly-go">
  Best Strategy for High Roller in Monopoly GO
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-756582f64b704032" id="emaki-video-player-756582f64b704032">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  First things first, it’s important to understand that a High Roller event can be intense, which is why you need to think clearly to make calculated decisions. The trick is to plan your moves carefully during the High Roller event to maximize its benefits.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, if the objective for the main event is to land on Tax and Utility tiles, you should only raise the multiplier when your token is nearing the left side of the board. There are a bunch of these tiles in close proximity, and you’ll have a better chance of landing on them with the higher multiplier. Raising the multiplier earlier in the game, when you're far from the target tiles, increases the risk of losing dice.
 </p>
 <p>
  Similarly, if your goal is to collect tokens from pickup tiles, you should raise the multiplier only when you’re closer to a cluster of pickup tiles. This way, you can get the most rewards and use the High Roller to the max. Remember to adjust your strategy accordingly. If you're not making significant headway, consider lowering your multiplier to avoid wasting dice in
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter - How To Find &amp; Beat Harat Bluefang</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tails-of-iron-2-how-find-beat-harat-bluefang/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Find Harat Bluefang In Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Tips On Beating Harat Bluefang In Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Similar to the first game's optional boss,
  <strong>
   Ratnor Rodentson
  </strong>
  , the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter
   </strong>
  </em>
  introduces its own challenging optional boss to fight. The battle against
  <strong>
   Harat Bluefang
  </strong>
  can be tough, especially on higher difficulties, but the real challenge lies in locating the four Runestone Keys needed to unlock the Tomb where he resides.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Runestones are not only well hidden but also require significant story progression to access new quests and areas where they can be found. This guide provides details on the locations of the Runestone Keys and tips for defeating Harat Bluefang inside the Tomb.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-find-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter">
  How To Find Harat Bluefang In Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="How To Beat Harat Bluefang In Tails of Iron 2 Whiskers of Winter 6" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/how-to-beat-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter-6.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are four Runestone Keys located throughout the northern realms of Ratdom:
 </p>
 <h3 id="silver-runestone-key-location">
  Silver Runestone Key Location
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-930105587" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-930105587" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-930105587" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-930105587" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-930105587-img" id="article-gallery-1-930105587">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-930105587" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1604672405">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   Ancient Runestone from a pillar that surrounds the Tomb. The worm symbol represents metal, or treasure.
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  The first Runestone Key is acquired
  <strong>
   automatically through the main story
  </strong>
  when you make your way to the left of the Castle gate in the Outskirts. Upon arriving at the Tomb for the first time,
  <strong>
   you'll spot a blue shimmer on the ground
  </strong>
  —the Silver Runestone Key. You can insert the Runestone Key at any point during the game.
 </p>
 <h3 id="earth-runestone-key-location">
  Earth Runestone Key Location
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-604845631" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-604845631" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-604845631" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-604845631" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-604845631-img" id="article-gallery-2-604845631">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-604845631" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1388608915">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   Ancient Runestone from a pillar that surrounds the Tomb. The worm symbol represents the deepth earth.
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  For the third Runestone Key, progress through the main story until you receive the "
  <strong>
   A Farmer for the Keep
  </strong>
  " main quest. This is a lengthy mission that involves rescuing a Badger. Upon completing the quest,
  <strong>
   you will acquire the Elder WereOwl Skull
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-313486203" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-313486203" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-313486203" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-313486203" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-313486203-img" id="article-gallery-3-313486203">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-313486203" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-60667748">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fast travel to the
  <strong>
   Slither Scale Pit
  </strong>
  and take the left path until you reach
  <strong>
   a pedestal where you can place the Skull
  </strong>
  . This will open the door behind it, allowing you to
  <strong>
   grapple across and obtain the Earth Runestone Key
  </strong>
  . You can also open the chest on the lower platform to obtain a Saphire.
 </p>
 <h3 id="death-runestone-key-location">
  Death Runestone Key Location
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1914940201" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1914940201" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1914940201" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1914940201" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1914940201-img" id="article-gallery-4-1914940201">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1914940201" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-946820971">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   Ancient Runestone from a pillar that surrounds the Tomb. The worm symbol represents the dead.
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  For the Death Runestone Key, complete the main quest "
  <strong>
   Tuck's Emporium
  </strong>
  ." This unlocks the ability to build the Shop using the Builder,
  <strong>
   allowing you to purchase the Runestone from Tuck
  </strong>
  for 10 Coins. You can upgrade the Shop to the maximum level, which unlocks a Trophy/Achievement and also adds more items and gear available for purchase from Tuck.
 </p>
 <h3 id="life-runestone-key-location">
  Life Runestone Key Location
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1502214802" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1502214802" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1502214802" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1502214802" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1502214802-img" id="article-gallery-5-1502214802">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1502214802" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-161884285">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   Ancient Runestone from a pillar that surrounds the Tomb. The worm symbol represents life.
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  For the last Runestone Key, collect all the Tarot Cards in the game and
  <strong>
   complete Merlin's quest by returning them
  </strong>
  . Merlin will then reward you with the Life Runestone Key. Most of these Tarot Cards are purchasable from merchants across the different areas of the game, except for the
  <strong>
   Knight Card, which can be found on a corpse in The Rift
  </strong>
  . Some of the merchants will only become available once you have completed their designated quests.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tips-on-beating-harat-bluefang-in-tails-of-iron-2-whiskers-of-winter">
  Tips On Beating Harat Bluefang In Tails of Iron 2: Whiskers of Winter
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-834370325" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-834370325" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-834370325" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-834370325" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-834370325-img" id="article-gallery-6-834370325">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-834370325" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1992967588">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you have acquired all the Runestone Keys, travel back to the Tomb of King Harat Bluefang and
  <strong>
   place the Runestones in their slots
  </strong>
  . This will unlock the door, allowing you to descend and face the boss. If you are attempting the fight after completing the main story and have level 3 gear, the battle will feel far less challenging. The boss deals poison and electric damage, so equip armor with resistance to those elements to minimize the impact of his attacks.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_27">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Harat Bluefang takes additional damage from fire, so switching to a high-level fire weapon and preparing fire traps will give you an advantage.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  The boss is not very aggressive, with slow and simple attacks that can be easily avoided by dodging. However,
  <strong>
   watch out for Poison Spit
  </strong>
  , as it can cover a small area of the arena in poison for an extended time, limiting your movement. Your ranged weapon will be quite useful whenever the boss is far away from you.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-613395824" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-613395824" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-613395824" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-613395824" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-613395824-img" id="article-gallery-7-613395824">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-613395824" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1982477326">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As the boss loses health, he switches his weapon to a bow for ranged attacks and a Two-Handed Axe for close combat. He also
  <strong>
   calls down lightning strikes from the sky
  </strong>
  , which are fairly easy to dodge.
  <strong>
   Be cautious not to greed for extra hits
  </strong>
  , as the scariest aspect of this boss is how hard his attacks hit. If you are unable to close the distance while he’s shooting arrows, it’s
  <strong>
   better to use your Shield
  </strong>
  to continually block rather than risk taking damage.
 </p>
 <p>
  At times, the boss will shout and follow it up with a charge forward. Make sure to dodge into the boss, not away from him, as dodging backward will still result in getting hit by the attack.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once the boss has been defeated, he will drop the following rewards:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Bluefang's Axe
   </strong>
   (One-Handed Weapon)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Steel Wall
   </strong>
   (Sheild)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Iron Point
   </strong>
   (Two-Handed Weapon)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Iron Sight
   </strong>
   (Ranged Weapon)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Gold Horn
   </strong>
   (Helm)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Gold Scale Armour
   </strong>
   (Cuirass)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Iron Shoulders
   </strong>
   (Pauldrons)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Coins
   </strong>
   x25
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Gold Ingot
   </strong>
   x5
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Silver Ingot
   </strong>
   x5
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Iron Ingot
   </strong>
   x10
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Diamond
   </strong>
   x2
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Saphire
   </strong>
   x1
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Ruby
   </strong>
   x1
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Emerald
   </strong>
   x3
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
