<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization 7's Most Dramatic Moments Are Missing a Key Ingredient</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/civilization-7-new-narrative-moments-lackluster-music-cinematic-narration/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Civilization 7
   </strong>
  </em>
  has arguably broken the mold more so than any entry that's come before it. While past
  <em>
   Civs
  </em>
  have continued to add to the same formula and refine its core mechanics with each new entry,
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  makes some significant changes to it, some for better and some for worse.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Along with dramatic changes to the core series formula, such as
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  's three-Age system and the decoupling of leaders and Civs,
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  has also made a wealth of smaller changes and additions. One of these is the introduction of new narrative elements that pop up regularly during the course of a match. These narrative moments are a really neat addition to
  <em>
   Civilization
  </em>
  's gameplay loop, but they still could've used a little longer in the oven.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="civilization-7-39-s-dramatic-moments-fall-flat">
  Civilization 7's Dramatic Moments Fall Flat
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2079845051" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2079845051" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2079845051" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2079845051" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2079845051-img" id="article-gallery-1-2079845051">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2079845051" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2091545493">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="civilization-7-39-s-new-narrative-elements-are-a-step-forward-for-the-franchise">
  Civilization 7's New Narrative Elements Are a Step Forward for The Franchise
 </h3>
 <p>
  Celebrations have been a part of
  <em>
   Civilization
  </em>
  's gameplay loop since the 1991 original and its "We Love the King Day," which granted players a temporary population boost if they had no unhappy citizens. These Celebrations are fun, simple events that add a little bit of narrative spice to the game, and they've slowly been joined by similar events over the years.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  goes all in on narrative events.
  <em>
   Civilization 6: Gathering Storm
  </em>
  's natural disasters make a return in the most recent entry, destroying players' town and city tiles in dramatic fashion at random intervals.
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  also introduces new "Narrative Choices," whereby players are prompted to make a decision between receiving one of two resources, a decision that's wrapped in some light narrative context.
 </p>
 <p>
  The most notable narrative-based addition in
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  is the "Crisis Event" mechanic. At the end of each Age, players will be presented with some kind of crisis that gradually affects their entire empire, such as a plague that slowly reduces happiness and degrades the health of all nearby units. To battle this crisis, players are given a set of unique Crisis Policies that come with both a positive and negative effect.
 </p>
 <p>
  In theory,
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  's Crisis Events are a great addition to the series' core gameplay loop, adding a sudden calamity that forces even the most seasoned
  <em>
   Civ
  </em>
  players to think carefully about their next moves. Unfortunately, in practice, these events aren't nearly as dramatic as they first seem.
 </p>
 <h3 id="civilization-7-39-s-new-narrative-elements-don-39-t-feel-as-special-as-they-should-be">
  Civilization 7's New Narrative Elements Don't Feel As Special As They Should Be
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  's Crisis Events (and Narrative Choices) are an unfortunate case of "tell don't show." When players are presented with a Crisis Event, it takes the form of a simple text box in the center of the screen. Aside from the slight red hue behind the text, there's nothing that immediately denotes the severity of the Crisis Event to the player.
 </p>
 <p>
  While a natural disaster in
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  results in a few-second dramatic camera-pan across the scene, and the completion of a Wonder results in a brief voice over from narrator Gwendoline Christie,
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  's Crisis Events are met with virtually no fanfare. There's no change in music, no discernible difference in soundscape, and barely any visual indicators that a Crisis Event is happening (the aforementioned plague appears as a faint green cloud hovering around the player's tiles). As such,
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  's Crisis Events don't hit nearly as hard as they should, which is a shame given how engaging the new mechanic can be.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Innovative Indie FPS Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/the-most-innovative-indie-fps-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Modern indie first-person shooters blend innovative gameplay styles for diverse player preferences.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Players Have a New Way to Earn Units</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-how-to-earn-units/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Marvel Rivals will soon allow players to convert Chrono Tokens into Units.
     </li>
     <li>
      The conversion rate hasn't been announced, and this will only work for players who have purchased the luxury version of the battle pass.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game will release its mid-season update on February 21.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  NetEase Games surprised
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans by announcing that players will soon have the ability to convert Chrono Tokens into Units in the popular hero shooter.
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is on the cusp of a major mid-season update scheduled for release on February 21. The upcoming patch will introduce numerous balance changes, a fresh map, and the remainder of The Fantastic Four.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a free-to-play title,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  has a few currencies that allow players to engage with the game's rewards. Chrono Tokens are earned through challenges, and they allow fans to redeem items within the current battle pass. Units, on the other hand, can be earned through both limited challenges and achievements. All of the shop's cosmetics can be purchased with Units, making it one of the most sought after currencies in the game. Lattice is the third currency in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  and can only be acquired through the battle pass or by purchasing it with real money. Lattice is the most versatile currency, as it can be used in place of Chrono Tokens or Units.
 </p>
 <p>
  NetEase Games recently released Dev Vision Vol. 4, which detailed several changes coming in the second half of Season 1: Eternal Night Falls. The developers highlighted the fact that they will be changing the way Chrono Tokens function once people finish
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' battle pass. While they didn't specify the conversion rate, the developers did state that gamers would be able to trade excess Chrono Tokens for Units. However, this will only work for players who have purchased the luxury version of the battle pass.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-players-can-convert-chrono-tokens-into-units">
  Marvel Rivals Players Can Convert Chrono Tokens Into Units
 </h2>
 <p>
  Many fans took to the comments to express enthusiasm about the change, stating that they had an abundance of Chrono Tokens left over in Season 0. While a large portion of the community wanted to keep their Chrono Tokens for future battle passes, this solution has also proven to be a popular one. Some gamers are already excitedly planning how they'll spend their units within the game's shop, with a few mentioning that they'll be picking up skins for The Thing and Human Torch in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-346089254" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-346089254" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-346089254" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-346089254" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-346089254-img" id="article-gallery-1-346089254">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-346089254" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1769537570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fans looking to acquire more Units in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  should focus on completing the game's Heroic Journey achievements. In addition to earning hundreds of Units to use in the title's store, players will be able to claim free skins for both Storm and Star-Lord. With so much content just around the corner, many gamers are excited about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite - Chapter 6 Season 2 Lawless Cinematic Gameplay Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/fortnite-chapter-6-season-2-lawless-cinematic-gameplay-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Fortnite Chapter 6 Season 2 Launch Trailer
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Dead Redemption 2: 8 Things You Should Avoid After Arthur's Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/red-dead-redemption-2-arthur-diagnosis-tb-things-avoid/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Major spoilers ahead for
   <em>
    Red Dead Redemption 2!
   </em>
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The ending of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Red Dead Redemption 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s fifth chapter has Arthur Morgan diagnosed with tuberculosis, a disease with no cure that he transmitted after a fight with the rancher Thomas Downes all the way back in chapter 2. As Arthur faces his own sickness and his own mortality, it’s time for him to rethink how he lives his life if he’s to push on for a little longer.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a few things players should avoid in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  after Arthur is diagnosed with tuberculosis, as TB is not a pretty sight, and those now with it will want to ensure Arthur is of the best health possible so he can try and survive and get the Van der Linde gang away from the Pinkertons in the wake of so much death and pain.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="smoking-cigarettes-amp-cigars">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Smoking Cigarettes &amp; Cigars
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-will-cough-heavily-after-inhaling-all-that-smoke">
  Arthur Will Cough Heavily After Inhaling All That Smoke
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan smokes" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-smokes-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Arthur might indulge in the tobacco craze of 1899 by sucking up a few cigarettes now and then, especially since it refills his Dead Eye cores. However, after his diagnosis, cigarettes will make him violently cough, and sometimes, even have him enter into an uncontrolled coughing fit that shows just how sick he is.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur’s Dead Eye core may drain 20% faster now that he has tuberculosis, but that’s no reason to go around and chain-smoke cigarettes just to try and get a rare cigarette card from a packet. Arthur’s sickness cannot be cured by tobacco, and pushing him into coughing fits doesn’t help him.
 </p>
 <h2 id="excessive-sprinting">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Excessive Sprinting
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-tires-easily-and-sprinting-leads-to-exhaustion">
  Arthur Tires Easily, and Sprinting Leads to Exhaustion
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan sprints" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sprints-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With a core drain speed of +20%, Arthur is going to see his sprinting occur in shorter bursts, and after every mild sprint, he’s definitely going to be wheezing and feel the burn of the exercise. Arthur is far weaker now than he was before his diagnosis, so running around everywhere is only going to make him feel worse, so try to stay close to your trusty horse.
 </p>
 <p>
  Riding on a horse is a lot faster than sprinting anyway, and it’s far safer for Arthur to be riding a horse than it is to be running as fast as he can with his own legs. Excessive sprinting will drain his cores and tire him out, leading to exhausted moments of rest.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="consuming-too-much-food">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Consuming Too Much Food
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="gluttony-won-rsquo-t-provide-additional-benefits">
  Gluttony Won’t Provide Additional Benefits
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan eats" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-eats.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Now that Arthur is sick, he’s going to see less benefits from food and drink. This means his cores will not fully replenish, and his weight will constantly worsen. There are no more opportunities for Arthur to have a stocky perfect weight or even an obese weight, as he will drop pounds like flies as his body slowly starts to eat at him and make him weaker and skinnier.
 </p>
 <p>
  As such, don’t force food down Arthur’s throat, as it isn’t going to make him put on weight, and it’s just going to result in further coughing fits as players try to shovel hot and dry food into his mouth with sharp alcoholic liquids. While players should eat to refill their cores, they shouldn’t overindulge, as there’s no benefit from it anymore.
 </p>
 <h2 id="refusing-to-bathe">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Refusing to Bathe
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="staying-clean-grants-increased-stamina-and-a-moment-of-calm">
  Staying Clean Grants Increased Stamina and a Moment of Calm
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan in the bath" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-bath.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Just because Arthur is sick, doesn’t mean he shouldn’t take care of himself. A bath in 1899 is only 25 cents, and if Arthur doesn’t bathe, NPCs might make an odd comment on his smell, and even Susan Grimshaw will slap and force Arthur to freshen up. Arthur Morgan can bathe at any of the following locations:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Saints Hotel, Valentine
  </li>
  <li>
   Welcome Center, Strawberry
  </li>
  <li>
   Rhodes Parlour House, Rhodes
  </li>
  <li>
   Bastille Saloon, Saint Denis
  </li>
  <li>
   Van Horn Depot, Van Horn Trading Post
  </li>
  <li>
   Gunsmith, Annesburg
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Bathing isn’t just a great way to keep the dirt and blood off of Arthur’s face, but it also allows him to enjoy a temporary increase in stamina once he is scrubbed clean. Besides the health benefit, Arthur deserves a moment of rest where he can enjoy the clearing of his sinuses and the heated waters of peace.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="failing-to-let-arthur-rest">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Failing to Let Arthur Rest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="while-sick-arthur-needs-plenty-of-rest-to-keep-his-health">
  While Sick, Arthur Needs Plenty of Rest to Keep His Health
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan sleeping" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-sleeping.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since cores drain faster with Arthur’s sickness, and he is far more exhausted and tired from the energy he drains in his daily activities as an outlaw, it’s probably a good idea to not go around Bluewater Marsh and ride late into the night and into the early hours of the morning. Instead, let Arthur rest some.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur can sleep practically anywhere with the right camp set up, and sleeping allows Arthur to regain some of his core as he will become well rested. On top of the gameplay aspects, it’s nice to let Arthur go to sleep instead of staying awake for days on end, which surely isn’t good for his health.
 </p>
 <h2 id="searching-for-a-cure">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Searching For A Cure
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="in-1899-there-was-no-cure-for-tuberculosis">
  In 1899, There Was No Cure for Tuberculosis
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan drinks a health tonic" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-drinks-a-health-tonic.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Arthur Morgan cannot be cured of tuberculosis in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  , and as such, it’s time to listen to Arthur’s own words:
  <em>
   <strong>
    We can’t change what’s done, we can only move on.
   </strong>
  </em>
  Arthur is dying – he knows it, the gang knows it, and sadly, you need to know it too. As such, there’s no point in attempting to waste time in finding a cure that simply does not exist, and Arthur isn’t going to have 40+ years to wait for the cure.
 </p>
 <p>
  While players can drink healthy tonics to reap some benefits to their cores, it’s not going to cure them completely, and Arthur is still going to get sicker as each day passes by. Let Arthur enjoy the time he has left instead of worrying about a cure that doesn’t come into play until the 1940s.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="acting-bitter-amp-refusing-to-accept-what-rsquo-s-happened">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Acting Bitter &amp; Refusing to Accept What’s Happened
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="picking-random-fights-and-refusing-the-road-to-redemption-isn-rsquo-t-arthur-morgan">
  Picking Random Fights and Refusing the Road to Redemption Isn’t Arthur Morgan
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan brawling" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-brawling.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sure, Arthur Morgan is a bad man who has done some terrible things. A robber, a killer, and an outlaw for life – Arthur Morgan knows he isn’t going to make it to Heaven, and he’s known for years that he’s walking this Earth as a doomed soul waiting for damnation. However, just because Arthur’s life is going to be taken by an illness instead of a bullet, doesn’t mean he has to take his anger out on the innocent.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur can still be a bad and greedy man who cares about money, but why bother with the stress and mayhem that come with shooting and fighting innocent folk? Instead, players should help Arthur help others with the time he has left, and perhaps discover that he can indeed be a good man at the end of it all.
 </p>
 <h2 id="battling-against-harsh-climates">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Battling Against Harsh Climates
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="harsh-cold-and-sweltering-heat-is-bad-for-the-health">
  Harsh Cold and Sweltering Heat is Bad for the Health
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="arthur morgan in the cold" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/arthur-morgan-in-the-cold.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Being overdressed or underdressed for certain climates is a death sentence already without tuberculosis, especially when the snowy mountains of Ambarino reach below zero, and Arthur will need a thick coat to get him through a day in the wild. The same can be said for the hot regions of the South in Lemoyne, where just a shirt and pants are enough to make Arthur sweat.
 </p>
 <p>
  With such hot or cold weather, the fluctuating temperatures are no good for Arthur’s illness, so players (if they want to roleplay more accurately) should avoid sending Arthur out to these regions equipped with the wrong clothes, or, they should stop heading out there altogether.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
