<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tariffs Hurt Japanese Video Game Company Stock</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/trump-tariffs-japanese-video-game-industry-impact/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stocks at several Japanese video game companies have dropped after President Trump announced a new tariff scheme.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sony's stock has fallen by 12.98% month-over-month on the Tokyo Stock Exchange, while Nintendo is down 8.11%.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sony and Nintendo are adapting supply chain strategies to mitigate tariff impacts on future products.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Stocks at major Japanese video game companies like
  <strong>
   Sony
  </strong>
  and Nintendo have fallen after US President Donald Trump implemented a far-reaching new tariff scheme. Concerns around potential tariffs and their impact on the game industry have circled ever since Trump's election, and now those effects are taking shape. Japanese gaming giant Sony has seen a considerable dip in its stock price after the US enacted a 24% reciprocal tariff against the country, and it's not the only one to take a hit from these actions.
 </p>
 <p>
  A previous report estimated that tariffs could make the PS5 Pro cost nearly $1,000 if Trump's proposed 60% tax on Chinese imports went into effect. Under the newly passed legislation, China faces a 34% reciprocal tariff on top of an older 20% charge, bringing the total levy on goods from the nation up to 54%. While that's less than what the 2024 report suggested, and it's still unclear how Sony will respond in terms of its pricing, the tax hike was enough to impact investors.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the time of writing, Sony's stock has fallen by 12.98% month-over-month on the Tokyo Stock Exchange. Nintendo has not seen quite as significant a drop but is still down 8.11%. While both companies are still in the green over the past six months, Nintendo and Sony began seeing noticeable drops in late March and early April 2025, right around the time when President Trump unveiled his new tariff plan. Neither company has yet to announce any pricing changes for their hardware to account for these losses, but Nintendo delayed Switch 2 pre-orders in the US following the tariff announcement to "assess the potential impact."
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="sony-and-nintendo-stocks-fall-month-over-month-after-tariffs-take-effect">
  Sony and Nintendo Stocks Fall Month-Over-Month After Tariffs Take Effect
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-798129580" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-798129580" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-798129580" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-798129580" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-798129580-img" id="article-gallery-1-798129580">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-798129580" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1840943250">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Earlier this year, Sony revealed it was increasing its US stock of PS5 consoles as part of a supply chain strategy to bypass the impact of tariffs. Only time will tell how effective an adaptation that shift was, but it could at least provide some temporary relief for gamers worried about rising console prices. While higher tariffs don't automatically mean new systems and games will cost more, companies have historically raised prices in line with the impact supply chains feel from import taxes. Having enough stock already within the US would let Sony keep prices steady because it wouldn't import as much, but future consoles may not get by so easily, and it's unclear what will happen once this stock runs out.
 </p>
 <p>
  Similarly, Nintendo has said it expects the tariff impact on the Switch 2 to be minimal, thanks to a change in its manufacturing strategy. However, the company planned to avoid tariffs by moving some production from China to Vietnam and Cambodia. Those nations now face 46% and 49% import duties, respectively, which may hinder the efficacy of this plan. While those rates are lower than the overall tax Chinese imports face, they're still among the highest of the new tariffs. What Nintendo and other video game companies will do in response is uncertain for now, but if stock prices are any indication, the near future may be a bumpy ride for the Japanese gaming industry.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery Reveals Its Most Popular Hogwarts Houses</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/harry-potter-hogwarts-mystery-most-popular-house/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Gryffindor ranks as the most popular Hogwarts house in Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery, followed by Slytherin, Ravenclaw, and Hufflepuff.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players have collectively logged over 94 billion minutes of playtime, earned 2 trillion house points, and cast 7.3 billion spells during the game's seven-year history.
     </li>
     <li>
      Special anniversary content updates for Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery include new storylines, creatures, and sweepstakes opportunities.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In celebration of its seventh anniversary,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
   </em>
  </strong>
  has unveiled a number of special in-game events and its most popular Hogwarts houses, with Gryffindor sitting in the number one spot.
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  has continued to release seasonal content updates, and the latest offerings on the way for the Wizarding World mobile game look to expand the title's greatest strengths even further.
 </p>
 <p>
  First launched in 2018 for both Android and iOS,
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  was the first officially licensed game that allowed players to customize their own character and experience the life of a student at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. With an active player base loading up the game on a daily basis, the next big updates for
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  are marking a very special occasion while finally answering some long-standing questions.
 </p>
 <p>
  In honor of
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  celebrating its seventh anniversary on April 25, developer Jam City announced new content updates, fun gameplay statistics, and the answer to which Hogwarts houses are the most popular. Since the release of
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  in 2018, players have logged over 94 billion total minutes of playtime, earned over two trillion collective house points, cast 7.3 billion spells, and adopted over 73 million magical creatures. It should come as no surprise that Harry Potter's Hogwarts house, Gryffindor, ranked as the most popular, followed by Slytherin, then Ravenclaw, and lastly Hufflepuff. Looking to keep these statistics climbing further through the anniversary celebrations, Jam City has shared a sneak peek at the new content and locations to explore in
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="gryffindor-is-the-most-popular-harry-potter-hogwarts-mystery-house">
  Gryffindor is the Most Popular Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery House
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1904855757" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1904855757" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1904855757" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1904855757" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1904855757-img" id="article-gallery-1-1904855757">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1904855757" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-845527117">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As part of the anniversary event,
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  players can look forward to a new Hogwarts Diary story featuring the founders of the magical school. They will also be able to track down and capture a Horned Serpent in the Creature Reserve and a "spiny" beast in the Open Ocean with an April update. Adding to previous Beyond Hogwarts expansions to
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  , the anniversary celebration will bring back the "Flight of the Weasleys" Special Adventure on April 23. Several sweepstakes opportunities will also be available via in-game postbox messages, giving
  <em>
   Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
  </em>
  fans a number of ways to celebrate the big anniversary.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Harry Potter
  </em>
  franchise continues to expand its video game offerings, with a rumored sequel to
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  stirring audience discussion and major anniversary celebrations keeping fans engaged with existing titles. Interested players can stay tuned for more
  <strong>
   <em>
    Harry Potter: Hogwarts Mystery
   </em>
  </strong>
  updates and other Wizarding World news.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation Wants to Know What Fans Think of the Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/playstation-nintendo-switch-2-sony-survey/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sony is surveying some PlayStation users about the Nintendo Switch 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      The survey explores player interest in buying the Switch 2, possible changes in the perception of Nintendo and Sony, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sony may be accruing consumer insight about the Switch 2 to formulate a strategy for the rumored next-gen PlayStation handheld console.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In light of the recent
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  reveal, Sony is sending out surveys to PlayStation users about the newest contender in the console market. The survey puts forth various questions concerning the Switch 2, and this may help shape PlayStation's approach to its own long-rumored next-gen handheld console.
 </p>
 <p>
  Just last week, Nintendo finally delivered a deluge of information about the Switch 2 in a dedicated Direct presentation. The brand-new handheld system's feature set received a full breakdown, and various new first-party and third-party games were announced for the Switch 2. It was undoubtedly a hugely notable event for the games industry, and while third-party publishers and platform holders rarely comment directly, it appears one of Nintendo's largest competitors is doing its own reconnaisance.
 </p>
 <p>
  Over on Twitter, credible leaker eXtas1s recently posted images of a Sony survey that has been circulating among PlayStation Network users, asking for their opinions on the newly-unveiled Nintendo Switch 2. The survey dives into several aspects of the Switch 2 and its reveal presentation, including how interested players are in buying one, whether it has altered their perception of Nintendo or Sony, and which specific features of the handheld console are most intriguing to them. There's even a question about Nintendo's priority-based pre-order process for the Switch 2, indicating Sony is looking at both the hardware and consumer behavior.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="sony-39-s-nintendo-switch-2-survey-may-benefit-the-rumored-upcoming-playstation-handheld-console">
  Sony's Nintendo Switch 2 Survey May Benefit the Rumored Upcoming PlayStation Handheld Console
 </h2>
 <p>
  While surveys like these aren't anything novel, especially in the wake of a major hardware debut, Sony's set of questions appear a bit more deliberate than meets the eye. Over the past year, there have been numerous rumors of Sony developing a new PlayStation handheld console, supposedly to launch alongside its primary next-gen console - the PS6. Therefore, Sony may be on a mission to gather as much consumer insight as possible about the Switch 2 in order to facilitate a smooth debut for its rumored next-gen PlayStation handheld.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1303749835" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1303749835" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1303749835" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1303749835" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1303749835-img" id="article-gallery-1-1303749835">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1303749835" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1268265939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sony's handheld efforts have seen massive success in recent years thanks to the PlayStation Portal remote player, so it seems very likely that the gaming giant is working on a full-blown PlayStation portable console. The timing is rather interesting, though, since Microsoft has also confirmed development of the first-ever Xbox handheld system. It wouldn't be surprising if, in the coming years, the handheld console market features competition from every major platform holder, in addition to hardware manufacturers like Asus, Lenovo, MSI, and more.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Schedule 1 Map &amp; All Key Locations</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/schedule-1-full-map-all-key-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Schedule 1
   </em>
  </strong>
  map is fairly small when compared to a lot of other modern video games, but navigating it can still be a little confusing. The lack of a mini-map doesn't help in this regard, nor does the fact that players are unable to see the full
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  map on their in-game smartphone without scrolling the screen around.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The following guide contains a complete map of Hyland Point, which should make it much easier for players to get from A to B. Key locations like properties and businesses have been marked with different colors to make it easier for players to find them. A little further down the page, they'll find another
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  map with only these key locations included.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="complete-schedule-1-map">
  Complete Schedule 1 Map
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg" decoding="async" height="4096" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-properties-and-businesses.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="4096"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     On the
     <em>
      Schedule 1
     </em>
     map shown above, the names of properties that the player can buy are written in green, while purchasable businesses are written in red. All other building names are written in white.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="all-properties-and-businesses-in-schedule-1">
  All Properties and Businesses in Schedule 1
 </h2>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="">
  <img alt="schedule-1-map-key-locations" data-image-id="1471214" height="4096" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/schedule-1-map-key-locations.jpg" width="4096"/>
 </h2>
 <ol>
  <li>
   <strong>
    RV
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Bungalow
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Docks Warehouse
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Motel
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Sweat Shop
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Barn
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Laundromat
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Car Wash
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Taco Ticklers
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Post Office
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ol>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Players can use
     <em>
      Schedule 1
     </em>
     console commands to instantly travel to one of the game's purchasable properties and businesses, even if they don't own it yet. To do so, they'll simply need to type "teleport " followed by the name of the place they want to fast travel to without any spaces, so "teleport dockswarehouse" or "teleport tacoticklers".
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Addresses Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour Controversy</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-welcome-tour-why-isnt-it-free/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour, a tech demo for the new system, will cost $9.99, sparking controversy among players.
     </li>
     <li>
      The company is defending the game's price, explaining that it contains much more content than meets the eye.
     </li>
     <li>
      Pre-orders for the Switch 2 in the US have been delayed due to the impact of recently enforced tariffs.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Nintendo has addressed the ongoing controversy related to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
   </em>
  </strong>
  , as players are frustrated that the new system's tech demo won't be included for free. It was previously confirmed that
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  would cost $9.99, and the company is now defending this decision, offering new insight into what the title will include.
 </p>
 <p>
  During a lengthy Direct livestream on April 2, fans were given their first proper look at the Nintendo Switch 2, including the new console's specs, initial game lineup, and more. Eager gamers got their first glimpse at the first round of first-party titles coming to the Switch 2 at or around launch, including
  <em>
   Mario Kart World
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Donkey Kong: Bananza
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Kirby Air Riders
  </em>
  . Numerous ports were also detailed, including many graphically intense games such as
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Intergrade
  </em>
  . While initial feedback was positive, Nintendo has faced pushback after not divulging the Switch 2's price during the hour-long stream, while also keeping the price of games under wraps.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fans got their first look at
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
   </em>
  </span>
  ​​​​​​during the stream, a tech demo and "virtual exhibition" of the new console and its many capabilities and secrets. Controversy quickly broke out, however, when players learned that the title wouldn't be included for free, and would instead cost $9.99. Many pointed out that
  <em>
   Astro's Playroom
  </em>
  was included with every PlayStation 5 for free as a way to highlight the DualSense controller. Now, in an interview with IGN, Nintendo of America's Vice President of Product and Player Experience, Bill Trinen, is defending this choice. Trinen stressed that there is much more to
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  than meets the eye, and that players with an interest in the console's tech and specs will find the title particularly rewarding. He also stressed how much work and care the development team put into it, stating that "$9.99 is not an exorbitant price."
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="nintendo-switch-2-welcome-tour-is-for-players-more-interested-in-the-system-rsquo-s-specs">
  Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour Is for Players More Interested in the System’s Specs
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1107987609" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1107987609" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1107987609" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1107987609" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1107987609-img" id="article-gallery-1-1107987609">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1107987609" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-781437038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  However, many fans will likely not be pacified by this response. The base console will cost $449.99, with certain Switch 2 games costing $80 for digital and $90 for physical copies, something that has caused an uproar in the gaming community. Additionally, Switch 2 game upgrades will be sold separately, and the system's GameChat feature will only be available to those with a Nintendo Switch Online subscription after its trial period ends in March 2026.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although the new console is slated to release worldwide on June 5, Switch 2 pre-orders in the US have been delayed due to the "potential impact" of President Trump's tariffs. Pre-orders were initially planned to begin on April 9, and it's currently unclear when they will start.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
