<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Apex Legends Reveals Mid-Season 23 Update Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/apex-legends-mid-season-23-update-patch-notes-mirage-loba-alter/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The mid-season update for Apex Legends will bring buffs for Mirage, Loba, and Alter, along with changes to weapons and gear.
     </li>
     <li>
      The patch notes reveal updates like Mirage's ability to heal while cloaked and Loba starting with 99% Ultimate charge.
     </li>
     <li>
      A new event, Astral Anomaly, brings back the launch royale LTM across multiple maps and adds new cosmetic rewards.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With Season 23 of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Apex Legends
   </em>
  </strong>
  roughly halfway complete, Respawn Entertainment has revealed the mid-season update patch notes. With the update releasing on January 7, the developer has teased what is coming to
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  , including significant buffs for Mirage, Alter, and Loba, among numerous other changes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like with previous seasons,
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  has featured several limited-time events in Season 23: From the Rift. Recently, Respawn announced Astral Anomaly as the next event for the battle royale, which will bring new cosmetics and an LTM to the game. Specifically,
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  is bringing back the launch royale LTM, letting players relive a similar experience to how the game was at launch. However, this time, players have access to the mode on World’s Edge, Olympus, Storm Point, Broken Moon, and E-District, along with the returning Kings Canyon. In addition to this event content, the developer is implementing many balance changes as part of a mid-season update.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ahead of Astral Anomaly, Respawn has unveiled the patch notes for the mid-season update for Season 23. The update is expansive, and some changes could have a noticeable impact on the battle royale, including buffs for several characters in
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  . Starting with Mirage, the Legend is receiving some improvements to his Passive ability, such as being able to cloak while healing. In addition, his level 2 upgrades have been replaced with Boozle-Eye and Renaissance Man; the former scanning targets who shoot decoys, and the latter letting him use world interactions for all other classes.
 </p>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-b57bdb39499e1e59" id="emaki-video-player-b57bdb39499e1e59">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The mid-season update will also see Loba start matches with a 99% Ultimate charge, up from 50%. This will allow her team to access her Black Market immediately after landing on the map. Among other changes to Loba's kit in
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  , her Tactical will have two charges and reduced toss and recovery times, meaning she can get out of dangerous situations more easily. She is also receiving changes to her upgrades. Beyond Mirage and Loba, Alter is getting buffs to her Ultimate and level 3 upgrades, allowing her to have more than one Void Nexus at a time. Furthermore, Pathfinder will be hit with a nerf, and Horizon and Vantage will receive tweaks with the new update as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  Respawn is also making alterations to a few weapons in
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  , including a buff for the Peacekeeper and a nerf for the Mastiff. In addition, the Charge Rifle will receive buffs to magazine size along with projectile size, speed, and gravity. It will also be able to use the Select Fire attachment. Finally, the RE-45 had its damage increased to 13, formerly 12. Meanwhile, the gold weapon rotation will feature the Charge Rifle, Prowler PDW, Nemesis Burst AR, G7 Scout, and CAR SMG.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1580122816" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1580122816" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1580122816" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1580122816" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1580122816-img" id="article-gallery-1-1580122816">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1580122816" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-875268085">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the entire change list is extensive, a few other notable balance updates include giving everyone on a team EVO when opening a Care Package and making alterations to ring lethality. Furthermore, the game will add a new Accelerator attachment for the Nemesis Burst AR, G7 Scout, and CAR SMG, boosting EVO and Ultimate charge from damage given. Time will tell how these changes and the rest of the ones mentioned in the patch notes impact the game in the remainder of Season 23.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="apex-legends-mid-season-update-patch-notes">
  Apex Legends Mid-Season Update: Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <h3 id="balance-updates">
  BALANCE UPDATES
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Care Package
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Opening a Care Package now grants EVO to the entire team instead of just the opener
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Gold Weapon Rotation
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Charge Rifle, Prowler PDW, Nemesis Burst AR, G7 Scout, CAR SMG
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Ring Lethality
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Support Perk benefits will be disabled once a player reaches the Ring Lethality Warning time limit
   <ul>
    <li>
     Revive Expert benefits will still maintain a long cooldown before re-use after being used inside the ring
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="attachments-amp-ordinance">
  ATTACHMENTS &amp; ORDINANCE
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Accelerated Weapons
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  NEW Accelerator: stock on the Nemesis Burst AR, G7 Scout, and CAR SMG
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increases EVO gained from damage
  </li>
  <li>
   Increases Ultimate charge from damage
  </li>
  <li>
   Knocks grant 30% ult charge as long as an Accelerator weapon is equipped
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: We are trying something fresh with this new Hop-Up and adding it to the base of these weapons by default. An ability like increased EVO and Ult charge gains makes the biggest impact when acquired early in a match, so we wanted to try and provide that exciting gameplay without the need to hunt for a rare item.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Arc Star
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Players will now be notified with a “STUCK” message when they have been stuck with an Arc Star
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: It can sometimes be difficult to know if you’ve been stuck by an Arc Star in the heat of combat. This messaging should help take the guess work out of making the right play.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Hop Ups
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added Select Fire
   <ul>
    <li>
     Equippable on Prowler PDW and Charge Rifle
    </li>
    <li>
     Adds a togglable automatic firing mode
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="weapons">
  WEAPONS
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Charge Rifle
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increased ammo capacity
   <ul>
    <li>
     Base Ammo: 6
    </li>
    <li>
     White Mag:7
    </li>
    <li>
     Blue Mag: 8
    </li>
    <li>
     Purple Mag: 9
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Increased projectile size at closer ranges
  </li>
  <li>
   Increased projectile speed
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved recoil
  </li>
  <li>
   Maximum damage for range scaling now achieved at 200m (was 300m)
  </li>
  <li>
   Reduced projectile gravity
  </li>
  <li>
   Now takes Select Fire Hop-Up
   <ul>
    <li>
     Alternate fire: automatic firing mode
    </li>
    <li>
     Damage reduced by 25%
    </li>
    <li>
     Increased fire rate
    </li>
    <li>
     Recoil improvements when in auto
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: The Charge Rifle is an absolute monsoon of a gun in the right hands, but it can be a bit tricky to get the hang of. We are taking a pass at making the Charge Rifle more approachable by increasing magazine capacity, adjusting recoil, lowering the range to get max damage, and adding the Select Fire Hop-Up into the mix.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Mastiff
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Aim down sights blast pattern tightening reduced
  </li>
  <li>
   Blast Pattern size increased
  </li>
  <li>
   Increased the time before the Mastiff is ready to fire when raising
  </li>
  <li>
   Raise and lower times slightly increased
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: The Mastiff has proven particularly strong this season and its consistency at range is a big part of that. We are smoothing out some timing issues which allowed niche double Mastiff builds to deal higher than average DPS and pulling some power out of its range by widening the blast pattern and ADS tightening.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Peacekeeper
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Choke speed significantly increased
  </li>
  <li>
   Increased projectile speed
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: When it comes to good range shotguns we want the Peacekeeper’s choked shot to be the main talking point so we’re speeding it up and making the projectiles fly faster. This should drastically improve its performance at range, particularly around hitting moving targets.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   RE-45
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Damage increased to 13 (was 12)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: The RE-45 has taken a backseat since Akimbo took the stage. This damage bump should help it feel a bit more viable within the current meta.
  </em>
 </p>
 <h3 id="legends">
  LEGENDS
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Alter
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Void Nexus
   <ul>
    <li>
     Cooldown reduced to 120s (was 180s)
    </li>
    <li>
     No longer times out by default
    </li>
    <li>
     Range increased to 300m (was 200m)
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Upgrades: Level 3
   <ul>
    <li>
     Eternal Nexus: removed, moved into base kit
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Multidimensional: grants a second Void Nexus and both can exist at the same time
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="5" cellspacing="0" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Launch: Level 3
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Eternal Nexus
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Void Nexus no longer times out.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Mid-Season: Level 3
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Multidimensional
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Grants a second Void Nexus. Both can exist at the same time.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: We have made a small change to allow more flexibility with Alter’s Ult. We have more plans for her in the near future, but wanted to release a small change to see if players find more use with her updated Ult.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Horizon
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Gravity Lift
   <ul>
    <li>
     Adjusted visual effects of the lift to reduce visual load on the battlefield
    </li>
    <li>
     Adjusted audio of players in the lift to be more noticeable
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Loba
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Black Market
   <ul>
    <li>
     Ultimate starts with 99% charge (was 50%)
    </li>
    <li>
     Added griefing protection
    </li>
    <li>
     Can now be remotely picked-up
    </li>
    <li>
     Can now grab banners (does not consume a Black Market usage)
    </li>
    <li>
     Can now open vaults without a key, but no EVO is awarded
     <ul>
      <li>
       Stealing vault loot no longer breaks Black Market, but can only be done by Loba and will still set off the alarm
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Can once again take loot from Explosive holds
    </li>
    <li>
     Removed delay after placing Black Market before it becomes useable
    </li>
    <li>
     Small meds (shield cells and syringes) no longer consume a Black Market usage
    </li>
    <li>
     Trials, Big Maude, and Caustic Labs loot no longer appears in Black Market
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Burglar’s Best Friend
   <ul>
    <li>
     Now has two charges
    </li>
    <li>
     Reduced Tac toss time slightly and recovery time significantly
    </li>
    <li>
     Reduced sound FX and VFX on thrown bracelet
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Eye for Quality: Loba can ADS when unarmed to see the loot UI for items highlighted by her passive
  </li>
  <li>
   Upgrades: Level 2
   <ul>
    <li>
     High Value: removed
    </li>
    <li>
     Market Expansion: removed
    </li>
    <li>
     Shopping Spree: moved to Level 2, reworked to allow entire squad to take 3 items from a friendly Black Market
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Wolf’s Claws: gain speed boost and significantly faster weapon draw after a teleport
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Upgrades: Level 3
   <ul>
    <li>
     Tactical Upgrade: removed
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Brand New Bag: entire squad receives gold backpacks when selected
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Escape Artist: Loba can regenerate 50 shield HP after teleporting with her Tac, damage stops the regen
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="5" cellspacing="0" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Launch: Level 2
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       High Value
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Increase Tactical height and range.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Market Expansion
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Increase Ultimate range by 25%.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Mid-Season: Level 2
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Wolf's Claws
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Gain speed boost and faster weapon draw after teleport.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shopping Spree
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Squad can take 3 items from a friendly black market.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Launch: Level 3
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shopping Spree
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Loba can take an extra item from Black Market Boutique.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tactical Upgrade
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -5 second tactical cooldown.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Mid-Season: Level 3
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Brand New Bag
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Squad gains gold backpacks.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Escape Artist
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       After teleporting, regen 50 shields. Damage interrupts.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: Many of Loba's changes aim to improve some of the cumbersome qualities around her kit and make her abilities more responsive. Her Ult being faster and granting free small meds gives her potency in her support style, while her two Tac charges and faster recovery make her more slippery and evasive. Just as a master thief should be. However, her upgrades are where we believe players can really lean into these two angles depending on their play preference or squad makeup. A more support-focused Loba can keep her team stocked with her improved Shopping Spree and Brand New Bag or she can flex into a more skirmishing style with Wolf's Claws and Escape Artist. It’s a pretty substantial makeover for Loba and we’re eager to see players strut her onto the podium.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Mirage
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Now You See Me…
   <ul>
    <li>
     Now also cloaks when using a healing consumable item
     <ul>
      <li>
       Cloak is removed by damage, ability use, or dropping the heal action
      </li>
      <li>
       Cloak has a 5 sec cooldown that begins after exiting the cloaked state
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Entering cloak now only takes 1s (was 1.5s)
    </li>
    <li>
     After a revive, Mirage now has increased speed while cloaked
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Upgrades: Level 2
   <ul>
    <li>
     Battpack: removed
    </li>
    <li>
     More Me: removed
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Boozle-Eye: Bamboozles now also scan the target who shot the clone
    </li>
    <li>
     NEW Renaissance Man: gain access to all other Classes’ world interactions: Assault Bins, Care Package scans, Survey Beacons, and Ring Consoles
     <ul>
      <li>
       Mirage and his team will ONLY gain EVO for these interactions if the squad also has a member of that class
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="5" cellspacing="0" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Launch: Level 2
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Battpack
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Carry an extra battery per slot. See battery count in Death Boxes.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       More Me
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Extra Clone in Ult. Cooldown reduced by 30s.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="2">
      <p>
       <strong>
        From the Rift Mid-Season: Level 2
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Boozle-Eye
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Bamboozles now also scan enemies.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Renaissance Man
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Gain access to all class consoles, bins, beacons and package scans.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: Mirage is a much loved Legend who is seen as having too little team utility and too easy to detect amidst his clones. We are aiming to challenge those notions in the sunset of this support season by giving him a "jack-of-all-trades" access to bins and beacons, and more ways to escape with his cloaking abilities. We expect players to find him more useful as squad support and utility flex, and are eager to see some of the really creative ways you can now escape and re-engage. Is the world prepared for this Mirage-a-flage?
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pathfinder
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Grappling Hook: cooldown increased to 30s (was variable)
  </li>
  <li>
   Insider Knowledge
   <ul>
    <li>
     Reduced Max Cooldown earned from Scanning Care Packages
    </li>
    <li>
     Reduced zipline change gained by Scanning Care Packages
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Upgrade - Zipline Zen: damage reduction reduced to 25% (was 50%)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dev Note: Despite a heavy support season, Pathfinder has remained as a highly picked Legend and often the main flex pick of a squad looking for rotations. We’ve pulled back the immediate Ult gains from scanning Care Packages which, alongside his Zipline Zen upgrade, gave him and his team frequent and safer rotations. We have also adjusted his grapple cooldown to encourage players to make more tactical choices with his abilities and seed the way for other Legends to step into his role in different comps.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Vantage
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Sniper’s Mark: reloading with an Ult Accelerant uses new animations and keeps the weapon active
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="modes">
  MODES
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Launch Royale
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Replicator spawns are enabled
   <ul>
    <li>
     Each Legend can craft teammate banners at a Replicator
    </li>
    <li>
     Craft Level 1 Armor at a Replicator
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Opening a bin will guarantee you a weapon if you have no weapons
  </li>
  <li>
   Ring Timings Adjusted
   <ul>
    <li>
     Wait time between rounds will better match current values
    </li>
    <li>
     The closing speed of the ring will be faster
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Map Rotation: Kings Canyon, World’s Edge, Olympus, Storm Point, Broken Moon, &amp; E-District
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Rift Relics Continue
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  The items available in Rift Relics will be updated regularly, adding an additional weapon to the lineup as well as rotating the available Boost Kits.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Boost Kits
   <ul>
    <li>
     Newly added
     <ul>
      <li>
       Upgraded: unlocks and activates all Legend Upgrades while equipped
      </li>
      <li>
       Emergency Smoke: release a vision obscuring smoke cloud at your location when you receive damage
      </li>
      <li>
       Map Hack: occasionally pings enemies within range on your minimap for you and your allies
      </li>
      <li>
       Phase Rewind: activating this sends you back to a previous location
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Returning
     <ul>
      <li>
       Hover: ADS in the air will allow the player to hover, keeping them afloat and steadying aim
      </li>
      <li>
       Void Reflex: damage that would knock a player instead sends them into the Void for several seconds, returning at critical health
      </li>
      <li>
       Reactive Regen: Health/Shield bars regen over time
      </li>
      <li>
       Squad Heal: using a health/shield consumable also applies it to nearby teammates
      </li>
      <li>
       Nessies: summon Nessie companions to fight on your behalf
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Relic Weapons
   <ul>
    <li>
     Newly added
     <ul>
      <li>
       Relic Pulse Blade: an enhanced version of the throwing knife that incorporates a small scan at the impact location and increased damage
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Charged Sentinel: keep your Shield Cells, this Sentinel is always charged
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Charged Rampage: Thermite Grenades are for throwing, this Rampage is always fired up
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic EVA-8 + Double Tap
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Devotion + EMP: do additional damage to surrounding enemies when you break an enemy’s shield (the more damage done, the more powerful the EMP)
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Charge Rifle: the original Charge Rifle on release
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Returning
     <ul>
      <li>
       Relic Alternator: Launch Royale variant modified with Disruptor Rounds
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Mastiff: Launch Royale variant
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic L-Star: Launch Royale variant with high fire rate and limited mag capacity
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Spitfire: Launch Royale variant with fast reload, improved hipfire, and heavy ammo
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Wingman: Launch Royale variant with Skull Piercer
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic Prowler: Launch Royale Select Fire (automatic) variant with high power scope
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic G7 Scout: Launch Royale variant with sniper scope
      </li>
      <li>
       Relic 30-30 Repeater: players heal for a percentage of the damage dealt to enemies and monsters
       <ul>
        <li>
         If the player succeeds in landing a headshot, health and armor are immediately highly refilled
        </li>
        <li>
         Embedded Dual Loader
        </li>
        <li>
         Mag size of 12
        </li>
        <li>
         Skullpiercer Hop-Up
        </li>
        <p>
        </p>
       </ul>
      </li>
      <li>
       EPG-1: single fire, direct energy propelled launcher
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="map-rotations">
  MAP ROTATIONS
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pubs &amp; Ranked
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   E-District
  </li>
  <li>
   Olympus
  </li>
  <li>
   World’s Edge
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Mixtape
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   January 7-January 20, 2025
   <ul>
    <li>
     TDM: Skull Town, Monument, Zeus Station
    </li>
    <li>
     Control: Production Yard, Thunderdome, Lava Siphon
    </li>
    <li>
     Gun Run: Wattson, Fragment, The Core
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   January 21-February 10, 2025
   <ul>
    <li>
     Big TDM: Thunderdome, Skull Town
    </li>
    <li>
     Control: Production Yard, Lava Siphon
    </li>
    <li>
     Gun Run: Skull Town, Fragment
    </li>
    <li>
     Lockdown: Zeus Station, The Core
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="ranked">
  RANKED
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   RP Value Tuning
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  We identified an issue where RP buckets and matchmaking were not fully aligned which led to some unexpected overlaps in ranks during matches. For example, players of similar skill levels could appear in different tiers, creating confusion when higher-tier players showed up in lower-tier matches. We've adjusted the system to better align RP buckets with matchmaking to fix this. As part of this adjustment, players will lose less RP and maintain progression closer to what was originally intended. Thank you for your understanding as we continue improving the Ranked experience!
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Rookie IV to Silver IV: no RP value changes
  </li>
  <li>
   Silver IV to Silver III: decreased to 500 RP (was 600RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Silver III to Silver II: decreased to 500 RP (was 600RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Silver II to Silver I: decreased to 500 RP (was 600RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Silver I to Gold IV: increased to 750 RP (was 600RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Gold IV to Gold III: increased to 750 RP (was 700RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Gold III to Gold II: increased to 750 RP (was 700RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Gold II to Gold I: increased to 750 RP (was 700RP)
  </li>
  <li>
   Gold I to Platinum IV: increased to 750 RP (was 700)
  </li>
  <li>
   Platinum IV to Platinum III: 750 RP (was 800)
  </li>
  <li>
   Platinum III to Platinum II: 750 RP (was 800)
  </li>
  <li>
   Platinum II to Platinum I: increased to 1000 RP (was 800)
  </li>
  <li>
   Platinum I to Diamond IV: increased to 1000 RP (was 800)
  </li>
  <li>
   Diamond IV to Diamond III: increased to 1000 RP (was 900)
  </li>
  <li>
   Diamond III to Diamond II: increased to 1000 RP (was 900)
  </li>
  <li>
   Diamond II to Diamond I: increased to 1000 RP (was 900)
  </li>
  <li>
   Diamond I to Master: increased to 1000 RP (was 900)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="bug-fixes">
  BUG FIXES
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added a buffer to tap strafes to combat automated movement tech at high frame rates
  </li>
  <li>
   Charge Rifle weapon UI no longer occasionally displays when in ADS with a high power optic
  </li>
  <li>
   First draw animation no longer plays with Akimbos after every death in Mixtape
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a rock wall on Broken Moon that players could hide inside of
  </li>
  <li>
   Low shield voicelines no longer plays when no Shield Core is equipped
  </li>
  <li>
   Out of bound timers will once again trigger while using Rampart’s Sheila while mounted
  </li>
  <li>
   UI icons should no longer sway off center on ultrawide
  </li>
  <li>
   Weapon mastery XP will now count correctly when Akimbo weapons are being held
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="legends">
  LEGENDS
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Alter
   <ul>
    <li>
     Loot in Death Boxes can now be pinged while using Alter’s passive
    </li>
    <li>
     Passive prompt should no longer show up without looking at a Death Box occasionally, including after respawning
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Caustic
   <ul>
    <li>
     Fixed an issue with barrels not deploying on top of one another
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Lifeline
   <ul>
    <li>
     D.O.C. Halo will no longer be destroyed by various large doors
    </li>
    <li>
     D.O.C. VFX and SFX will not linger longer than expected after expiring
    </li>
    <li>
     First person audio will no longer play on squadmates when D.O.C. is deployed to herself
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Newcastle
   <ul>
    <li>
     Now properly breaks free of Ash’s snare when using Ult and doesn’t hover awkwardly in the air
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="quality-of-life">
  QUALITY OF LIFE
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Adjustments to EVO points gained from consecutive revives
  </li>
  <li>
   Dropped loot on the rising walls on World’s Edge will now pop off the wall after it finishes raising rather than stick to it
  </li>
  <li>
   Healing option now defaults to cells instead of syringes
  </li>
  <li>
   “Incoming Voice Chat Volume" menu option is now available on consoles and the maximum value has been raised from 100% to 200% (values above 100% will attempt to boost quiet players)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="graphics">
  GRAPHICS
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   DirectX 12 is now the default version on PC. Data from the last couple of seasons has shown that the typical player will have better performance and stability in DX12, as discussed in our Reddit post.
   <ul>
    <li>
     Players on Steam can still select DX11 as a startup option, and players on the EA App or Epic Game Store can use DX11 with the commandline argument --anticheat_settings=SettingsDX11.json.
    </li>
    <li>
     Note: compiling shaders for the very first time can take a while for both DX11 and DX12, but players newly switching to DX12 may take a while to connect to the lobby for the first time.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   This patch also includes improvements and fixes for DX12:
   <ul>
    <li>
     Added support for AMD Anti-Lag 2: this option will be enabled by default in the Video Settings for players with compatible AMD GPUs. Internal testing found that in situations where the game is bottlenecked by GPU performance, Anti-Lag 2 improved in-engine input latency by roughly 25%.
    </li>
    <li>
     Black borders should no longer continue to show the Steam Overlay or visual artifacts when using aspect ratios different from your monitor.
    </li>
    <li>
     Game cursor should now be centered when opening a menu while using a game resolution different from your monitor's native resolution.
    </li>
    <li>
     Inventory menu should no longer jump around when using a controller (sorry, House of Pain).
    </li>
    <li>
     Removed the "Dynamic Streaming Budget" toggle from Video Settings since it should be left on for virtually all players. This option generally has no effect unless your GPU runs out of VRAM, and in these situations it can save performance degradation. It can still be disabled in the videoconfig.txt file.
    </li>
    <li>
     Significantly improved performance of streaming geometry data to the GPU, especially on low-end systems, reducing stuttering and missing in-game models.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Fighting Game Characters For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fighting-game-characters-for-beginners/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Beginners should start with easier-to-play characters like
      <em>
       Tekken's
      </em>
      Hwoarang,
      <em>
       Street Fighter's
      </em>
      Cammy, or
      <em>
       Guilty Gear's
      </em>
      May to improve their fighting game skills.
     </li>
     <li>
      Using characters like Ryu, Ken, or Scorpion can help beginners with their fundamentals and provide a strong jumping-off point.
     </li>
     <li>
      Defensive characters like Asuka Kazama and mixup characters like Blanka offer unique playstyles that cater to different beginner preferences.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Fighting games can be quite difficult. Players have to get good, or they won’t get to even play. Weaker players can be forced to endure essentially a minute to ninety-second long cutscene of their character getting beaten up. Some characters have key moves that require frame-perfect or near-frame-perfect timing to pull off.
 </p>
 <p>
  All of this makes fighting games extremely daunting for beginners. How do they get better if they can barely pull off a dragon punch? How can a player pull off a combo if doing so seems like rocket science? For most beginners, starting characters matter. While characters such as Tekken’s Kazuya might seem really cool, starting with him will be extremely difficult for newcomers. Sometimes, it’s best to pick a beginner-friendly character and move up.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="tekken-hwoarang">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Tekken: Hwoarang
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-side-of-mash">
  A Side Of Mash
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1025148439" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1025148439" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1025148439" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1025148439" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1025148439-img" id="article-gallery-1-1025148439">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1025148439" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2037582291">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hwoarang is a staple of the
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  series. Having been in the series since
  <em>
   Tekken 3
  </em>
  he’s a good pick for any beginner who wants some longevity in their character. As for how he plays, all that’s needed is to pick up the controller, figure out the kick buttons and mash them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, it is more complicated than that. Hwoarang is hyper-aggressive and relies on mashing to pressure his opponents into stupid mistakes. This low bar for entry makes him one of the game's most popular characters. His only downsides are that he becomes harder to play with against a more experienced opponent and that his divergence from the fundamentals of
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  makes it hard to use him as a jumping off point into other characters.
 </p>
 <h2 id="street-fighter-cammy">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Street Fighter: Cammy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-human-missile">
  A Human Missile
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1323768212" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1323768212" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1323768212" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1323768212" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1323768212-img" id="article-gallery-2-1323768212">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1323768212" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1705800150">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For those who want to leap across the screen and play extremely offensively, Cammy is the girl. Her moveset is lighting fast, allowing players to bombard the opponent with a flurry of long-range, hard-hitting moves making her one of the franchise's strongest characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  She is the perfect character for any beginner who is struggling with Street Fighter’s “zoners”, the characters that use projectiles to keep opponents away. Moves such as Quick Spin Knuckle and Cannon Strike can be used to punish passive players. Cammy’s normals are excellent, so once a special move has gotten her in she can really pressure the opponent.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="guilty-gear-may">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Guilty Gear: May
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="attack-of-the-killer-dolphins">
  Attack Of The Killer Dolphins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-367316669" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-367316669" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-367316669" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-367316669" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-367316669-img" id="article-gallery-3-367316669">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-367316669" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1593000774">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  May is on the surface a cutesy, fun character, but beneath that facade is one of the most aggressive characters in the entirety of
  <em>
   Guilty Gear
  </em>
  . A charge character, meaning she only has to hold down or back for a period before pressing up or forward depending on the move; Her inputs are a matter of timing rather than complex finger motions.
 </p>
 <p>
  With her sidekick “Mr Dolphin” May can turn a match into hell for her opponent. Constant cries of “Totsugeki” bounce around the arena as she forces the other character into the corner. Her ease of use and hyper-aggressive playstyle make her a great choice for anyone looking to start playing
  <em>
   Guilty Gear.
  </em>
 </p>
 <h2 id="street-fighter-ryu-ken">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Street Fighter: Ryu/Ken
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="classics-never-die">
  Classics Never Die
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-301504314" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-301504314" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-301504314" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-301504314" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-301504314-img" id="article-gallery-4-301504314">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-301504314" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1558353180">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Ryu and Ken have historically been extremely similar. And even though
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  has given them both differing new moves, they’re still very similar. The progenitors of the “Shoto” archetype in fighting games, Ken and Ryu rely on Hadoukens, Shoryukens, and Tatsu Kicks to create a very well-rounded moveset.
 </p>
 <p>
  Beginners have two choices here, Ryu is more defensive, relying on fireballs to chip opponents away at a distance, but has the tools to hold his own up close. Ken, on the other hand, has weaker fireballs, but his Shoryukens are much stronger, leading to a more aggressive playstyle. Both are extremely rewarding to play and will take players far in their fighting game journey.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tekken-asuka-kazama">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Tekken: Asuka Kazama
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="defensive-rage">
  Defensive Rage
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1456570180" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1456570180" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1456570180" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1456570180" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1456570180-img" id="article-gallery-5-1456570180">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1456570180" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-510508203">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Asuka is
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  ’s angriest Kazama. Once slated as the protagonist of the series, she has since been passed over for Jin Kazama, her cousin. Asuka is still a
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  mainstay, featuring in every game since
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  <em>
   5.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Her playstyle is extremely defensive. Asuka works by turning the opponent’s momentum against them. Her Sabaki parries can toss opponents around the room, and her counter-hit moves can easily launch an overly aggressive character into a combo. She’s perfect for beginners who are struggling against more offensive playstyles.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mortal-kombat-scorpion">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Mortal Kombat: Scorpion
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="get-over-here">
  Get Over Here
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-718271968" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-718271968" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-718271968" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-718271968" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-718271968-img" id="article-gallery-6-718271968">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-718271968" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1798064346">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Mortal Kombat is generally considered on the easier end of fighting games.The dial in combo system and lower emphasis on footsies makes the game much more accessible than most other franchises.
 </p>
 <p>
  That being said, a mainstay of the franchise and one of the more beginner-friendly characters, Scorpion is a blast. Visually stylish and iconic as they come. Scorpion’s moves can vary from game to game due to the nature of the series, but Scorpion tends to be on the easier end of the roster.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="street-fighter-blanka">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Street Fighter: Blanka
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="green-and-fierce">
  Green and Fierce
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1035240612" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1035240612" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1035240612" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1035240612" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1035240612-img" id="article-gallery-7-1035240612">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1035240612" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-534341047">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <p>
  Blanka is an extremely entertaining and extremely simple character. His gameplan is to confuse his opponent and aggressively throw himself around the room.
 </p>
 <p>
  Blanka’s moveset is very mix-up heavy, confusing and frustrating his opponents to open up their guard and pressure them into making mistakes. Mixup characters are usually among the harder characters to play in fighting games, but Blanka’s moveset is visually very similar, requiring the opponent to guess his next move, without knowing how to set up many mind-games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="guilty-gear-giovanna">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Guilty Gear: Giovanna
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-size-of-the-dog-in-the-fight">
  The Size Of The Dog In The Fight
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1319780051" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1319780051" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1319780051" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1319780051" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1319780051-img" id="article-gallery-8-1319780051">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1319780051" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1390611610">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <p>
  Giovanna is unique on this list as she is new to
  <em>
   Guilty Gear
  </em>
  , appearing only in its most recent iteration,
  <em>
   Guilty Gear Strive
  </em>
  . A secret agent with a wolf spirit helping her fight, Giovanna is visually pretty unique.
 </p>
 <p>
  Giovanna is what’s known in fighting games as a “rushdown” character. She plays an aggressive, pressure-based game, forcing her opponent back into a corner. She has a lot of moves reminiscent of Cammy from
  <em>
   Street Fighter,
  </em>
  avoiding projectiles and using strong normals to keep her opponent guessing.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tekken-jack">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Tekken: Jack
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="metal-meets-face">
  Metal Meets Face
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-216489326" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-216489326" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-216489326" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-216489326" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-216489326-img" id="article-gallery-9-216489326">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-216489326" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-363788577">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Jack is one of
  <em>
   Tekken’s
  </em>
  oldest and most enjoyable characters. Boasting a comedic look and personality, Jack can be a blast to play. His moveset is relatively easy to learn by
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  standards, and he goes all the way back to the first game in the series so that he can be used no matter the entry.
 </p>
 <p>
  Jack is a mix between a mid-ranger, and a grappler. His arms afford him a very long range, combined with a quick counter-hit move that allows him to knock down overly aggressive opponents. Meanwhile, should players choose to Jack can deploy a plethora of grabs up close that give him a more offensive edge. Combine with some joke moves and Jack becomes a balanced and funny character that any beginner can pick up and play.
 </p>
 <h2 id="feng-wei">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Feng Wei
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="strongest-there-is">
  Strongest There Is
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-32188149" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-32188149" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-32188149" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-32188149" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-32188149-img" id="article-gallery-10-32188149">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-32188149" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1884777220">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Feng is a secondary villain from the
  <em>
   Tekken
  </em>
  series and he is one of the best characters in the series for beginners.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can expect a fundamental-based, all-rounder with an emphasis on mixups and counter hits. Feng also comes with a variety of advanced techniques such as snake dashing and a stylish moveset full of flashy kung fu antics. He’s also a very strong character despite being nerfed. A perfect choice for any beginner looking for a character that will hold up both as a beginner and a pro.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Reveals Mister Fantastic Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-mister-fantastic-gameplay/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mister Fantastic will debut in Marvel Rivals Season 1 using his intellect to fight Dracula.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Fantastic Four will be introduced in Season 1, with The Invisible Woman coming first.
     </li>
     <li>
      Developer NetEase Games plans to release major updates in the middle of each three-month season.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  NetEase Games has released its first look at gameplay for Mister Fantastic in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The hero will be using his intellect in the fight against Dracula as the game's story heats up. Mister Fantastic will arrive when
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  launches Season 1: Eternal Night Falls on January 10 at 1 AM PST.
 </p>
 <p>
  The developers have confirmed that all members of The Fantastic Four will be making their debut in Season 1, but they won't arrive at the same time. Along with Mister Fantastic, The Invisible Woman will join
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  with the launch of the new season. It's expected that Human Torch and The Thing will arrive six or seven weeks later. NetEase Games stated that seasons are expected to last roughly three months, with a major update coming in the middle of each one.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  has released a trailer giving players a first look at gameplay for the Duelist Mister Fantastic. The gameplay sees Reed Richards stretching his arms to punch foes, even grabbing two enemies and slamming them together. He can also be seen puffing up his body, giving him a wildly muscular look as he pummels foes in a similar fashion to Hulk. His ultimate ability seems to show him jumping up and slamming down on the enemy team over and over again, not unlike The Winter Soldier. Some players are expecting to see The Fantastic Four launch with a Seasonal Bonus in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , though that is just speculation at this point.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-shows-off-gameplay-footage-of-mister-fantastic">
  Marvel Rivals Shows off Gameplay Footage of Mister Fantastic
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-64530a5fc7b6730f" id="emaki-video-player-64530a5fc7b6730f">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While there's very little official information about some of the other Fantastic Four members, the ability kit for
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Human Torch was leaked recently. According to the post, Human Torch will be able to create walls of flame to help control areas of the battlefield. He'll also be able to team up with Storm to create fire tornadoes, which could be deadly for their enemies. Leakers also claim to have found evidence that The Thing will be a Vanguard in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , though his ability kit remains a mystery.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2132798155" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2132798155" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2132798155" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2132798155" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2132798155-img" id="article-gallery-1-2132798155">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2132798155" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1516955262">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It was recently rumored that characters like Blade and Ultron may come to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  in the near future, but the developers have stated that The Fantastic Four will make up all of the characters debuting in Season 1. While many leakers believed the game was going to launch with Ultron as part of the starting roster, they now expect that the villain has been delayed to Season 2 or beyond. Many players were also surprised when the developers didn't mention Blade, given that Dracula is one of his fiercest foes. With so much new content coming soon, many players are enthusiastic about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best FMV Mystery Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-fmv-mystery-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      FMV games like Immortality create immersive experiences through found footage storytelling with unexpected twists.
     </li>
     <li>
      At Dead of Night offers a terrifying experience in a hotel setting with real-life chase sequences and jump scares.
     </li>
     <li>
      Contradiction is a cozy murder mystery game with an eccentric detective and mechanic of uncovering contradictions in witness statements.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  FMV (Full Motion Video) games incorporate live-action video as an essential storytelling or gameplay element. The truly wonderful and innovative FMV games use the unique features of video to enhance the gameplay, rather than being just a gimmick. Mysteries are perfectly suited to the FMV form.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mysteries afford plenty of wonderful opportunities to incorporate found footage and have logical spaces in which there might be cameras involved, such as in phones, interrogation rooms, and movie sets. This is a carefully selected list of the most intriguing FMV mystery games that reward creative thinking and puzzle solving.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="svoboda-1945-liberation">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Svoboda 1945: Liberation
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="quot-people-don-39-t-care-about-what-happened-50-years-ago-quot">
  "People Don't Care About What Happened 50 Years Ago"
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-567991019" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-567991019" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-567991019" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-567991019" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-567991019-img" id="article-gallery-1-567991019">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-567991019" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2030670650">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer
   </strong>
   : Charles Games
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released
   </strong>
   : 2021
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms
   </strong>
   : PC, Switch, and Mac
  </li>
  <li>
   Website
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Svoboda 1945: Liberation
  </em>
  is a thoroughly researched and intricately crafted historical mystery FMV. The player is investigating a local schoolhouse in a small village to see if it is eligible for historical heritage protection. It turns out that the player character has an unexpected connection with the area and begins investigating what happened to their grandfather in the village. The mystery surrounds events in the aftermath of World War 2.
 </p>
 <p>
  The stories are fictionalized versions of real accounts of those who witnessed similar events. It won’t be for everyone, but those who love a good mystery with a few emotional gut punches will love this. The acting is wonderful, and the story is fascinating. Subtitles are essential for those who don’t speak Czech.
 </p>
 <h2 id="return-to-zork">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Return to Zork
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="want-some-rye-course-y-39-do">
  Want some rye? Course y'do!
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1530604156" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1530604156" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1530604156" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1530604156" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1530604156-img" id="article-gallery-2-1530604156">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1530604156" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2112851112">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer
   </strong>
   : Activision
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released
   </strong>
   : 1993
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms
   </strong>
   : PC
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players looking for a smooth gaming experience should probably steer clear of this FMV classic. But it has some of the most iconic moments in FMV video game history, including perhaps the most annoying, yet strangely charming, game-over cutscene in video games to date. It is a point-and-click FMV mystery with a strange cast of characters. The story and aesthetic go in some truly bizarre directions that are worth pushing through the clunky mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  A lot of the older brilliant FMV games from the 90s, such as the
  <em>
   Zork
  </em>
  games, are absolute classics that any fan of the genre would appreciate. However, the puzzles are often obtuse and the controls are unwieldy. While they are not recommended for newcomers to the genre, they deserve a list all their own.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="at-dead-of-night">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   At Dead of Night
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="here-39-s-jimmy">
  Here's Jimmy!
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-391117315" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-391117315" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-391117315" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-391117315" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-391117315-img" id="article-gallery-3-391117315">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-391117315" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-81705066">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   At Dead of Night
  </em>
  is one of the few truly terrifying FMV games to be released in the past 5 years. Players have to navigate a hotel straight out of
  <em>
   The Shining
  </em>
  while being chased by a serial killer named Jimmy. The game uses FMV in many of the scenes in which the main character Maya is navigating the hotel, something which is less common in FMV games. This creates the illusion (and anxiety) of a real-life chase-and-hide sequence,
 </p>
 <p>
  Maya must uncover the mysteries of Jimmy’s past in order to escape from him. This includes communicating with ghosts and finding clues through a scrying mirror. Hiding in bathrooms from Jimmy is a genuinely harrowing experience and the sudden fright from jump scares is well-earned.
 </p>
 <h2 id="simulacra">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Simulacra
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="you-are-not-anna">
  You Are Not Anna
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-275237589" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-275237589" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-275237589" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-275237589" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-275237589-img" id="article-gallery-4-275237589">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-275237589" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1809137011">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer
   </strong>
   : Kaigan Games OÜ
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released
   </strong>
   : 2017
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms
   </strong>
   : Android, iOS and Windows
  </li>
  <li>
   Website
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The player-character finds a lost phone on their doorstep. Curiosity gets the better of them, and they start looking through it. Little do they know, but by doing so they are becoming embroiled in the mysterious disappearance of the phone’s owner. The plot is unraveled through discovering a string of passwords, data, and other clues to progress to the next stage.
 </p>
 <p>
  The best way to experience Simulacra is on mobile for maximum immersion. At times, it truly feels like sifting through a haunted phone. The sequels are quite good, but none quite capture the unexpected horror of the original.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="contradiction">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Contradiction
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ever-seen-this">
  Ever Seen... This?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1632998955" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1632998955" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1632998955" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1632998955" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1632998955-img" id="article-gallery-5-1632998955">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1632998955" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-389293819">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer
   </strong>
   : Baggy Cat
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released
   </strong>
   : 2015
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms
   </strong>
   : iOS and Windows
  </li>
  <li>
   Website
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Contradiction
  </em>
  takes a page out of the classic FMV game handbook. It is a cheesy cozy murder mystery with an eccentric detective character and a cast of deceitful suspects. A college student is murdered in the small village of Edenton and Detective Jenks is sent to investigate.
 </p>
 <p>
  Jenks has a bizarre questioning style and as he questions witnesses, their responses get logged into a notebook. The player then compares the answers to previous statements and looks for contradictions to uncover the truth. The narrative of the game feels like a
  <em>
   Midsomer
  </em>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
    Murders-
   </em>
   style
  </span>
  British cozy crime drama and manages to keep the player engaged until the end.
 </p>
 <h2 id="her-story">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Her story
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="quot-clearly-it-rsquo-s-murder-quot">
  "Clearly It’s Murder"
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-830009789" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-830009789" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-830009789" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-830009789" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-830009789-img" id="article-gallery-6-830009789">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-830009789" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1430620932">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Her Story
  </em>
  is the FMV game that revitalized and changed the genre forever. It showed the potential of FMV to tap into the found footage that had become popular in horror cinema after
  <em>
   The Blair Witch Project
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Her Story
  </em>
  takes it a step further, using dated police technology to further enhance the believability of the footage. The player is tasked with searching through a police database to solve a murder. The unsettling soundscape includes office noises that indicate a world outside the screen and dynamic piano music that shifts according to the significance of the footage found.
 </p>
 <p>
  The search system works well and players can tag specific words to follow up on later. As with many of these mystery games, there isn’t a lot of replayability, but like Sam Barlow’s other work, players may find themselves scouring through the videos looking for any that they missed. It has aged very well and is definitely a must-play for FMV enthusiasts and murder mystery game fans alike.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="immortality">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Immortality
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="what-happened-to-marissa-marcel">
  What Happened To Marissa Marcel?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-96252555" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-96252555" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-96252555" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-96252555" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-96252555-img" id="article-gallery-7-96252555">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-96252555" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1140339787">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To explain the brilliance of
  <em>
   Immortality
  </em>
  is to give too much away. The basic premise is that the player has access to footage of an emerging film star named Marissa Marcel who disappeared before the films she starred in were ever released. By sorting through the footage, the player reconstructs the mysterious truth of what happened to her.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are genuine surprises and beautifully executed twists that lean into the unique qualities of FMV found footage as a medium. The acting is fantastic, and the production of the footage deftly positions each clip within a particular era. It is a little tricky to navigate the interface at times, but players will adjust quite quickly to the mechanics.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alan-wake-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Alan Wake 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <p>
  Short Film Yötön Yö And Alan Wake The Musical
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-552405514" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-552405514" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-552405514" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-552405514" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-552405514-img" id="article-gallery-8-552405514">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-552405514" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-32229762">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As a developer who deftly plays with the conventions of gameplay and the expectations of the player, Remedy’s FMV sequences in
  <em>
   Alan Wake 2
  </em>
  weren’t a complete surprise. But the live-action musical number was something no one expected. The game transitions into live action on multiple occasions and the medium is used to great effect in demonstrating Alan’s tenuous grip on reality.
 </p>
 <p>
  In fact, the live-action sections in The Dark Place seem far less real than Saga’s sections, which are ostensibly more grounded in reality. The musical sequence and the short film sequence feel more like magical realism than a gritty detective story. It really solidifies the stylistic and narrative similarities between the
  <em>
   Alan Wake
  </em>
  franchise and
  <em>
   Twin Peaks
  </em>
  (one of its inspirations).
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Of Us 2: Best Weapon Upgrades, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-last-of-us-2-best-weapon-upgrades/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Upgrading weapons in
      <em>
       The Last of Us Part 2
      </em>
      is crucial for maximizing efficiency and survival, especially in Ellie's and Abby's chapters.
     </li>
     <li>
      The rangefinder upgrade for the bow helps players mark the distance of enemies, improving accuracy and reducing missed shots.
     </li>
     <li>
      Upgrading the semi-auto pistol's stability allows for better headshots in stealth, while also preserving bullet and suppressor durability.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As Ellie takes a path of vengeance in
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Last of Us Part 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , she’s going to need a fair few weapons to get through threats of both human and infected alike. Players can find an abundance of weapons in
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  that will aid on their odyssey, but what’s even better, is when they find an upgrade bench. Utilizing scrap that has been scavenged throughout the chapters, players can upgrade their weapons at a bench, which will see some desirable effects.
 </p>
 <p>
  Scrap is a limited resource in
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  , so players are going to want to choose the best weapon upgrades wisely for the Ellie and Abby chapters, making sure that they are getting the most out of their weapons, and even the worst threats on offer won’t stand a chance.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on January 6, 2025, by Jake Fillery:
   </strong>
   The best weapon upgrades in The Last of Us 2 are essential for those within the Ellie and Abbie chapters so that they do not face an early and grizzly death at the hands of infected and survivors. Bringing along scrap and a decent gun to a workbench can mean the difference between life and death, especially when some upgrades should be prioritised first so that the best guns in The Last of Us Part 2 are given the attention they deserve to make every combat encounter easier.
  </em>
 </p>
 <h3 id="best-weapon-upgrades-for-ellie">
  Best Weapon Upgrades for Ellie
 </h3>
 <p>
  Ellie’s chapters will find her unlock specific weapons for her arsenal, separate to Abby’s. These weapons can be upgraded to maximize the efficiency against humans and infected alike, as Ellie’s odyssey to find and kill Abby rages through Seattle.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="bow-ndash-rangefinder">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Bow – Rangefinder
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="mark-the-distance-of-enemies-on-the-reticle">
  Mark The Distance Of Enemies on The Reticle
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="bow rangefinder upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175803-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 80 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The bow is easily one of the best weapons in
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  . It hits hard and is a silent killer. Yet, aiming with the bow might cause trouble for some players. Luckily, the rangefinder upgrade means that players will automatically mark the distance of their enemies on the reticle of the bow, meaning fewer missed shots and better accuracy.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bow-ndash-draw-speed">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Bow – Draw Speed
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="faster-draw-time-when-using-the-bow">
  Faster Draw Time When Using the Bow
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="bow draw speed upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/bow-draw-speed-upgrade.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Ellie's talent with a bow should not be understated, and it's a great weapon that players shouldn't sleep on. The bow is Ellie's primary stealth weapon when she doesn't have the required materials for a silencer on the semi-auto pistol, and it also deals a lot more damage, and the arrows can be re-obtained. As such, having a faster draw speed means the draw and knocking speeds are greatly increased to make sure Ellie is constantly firing arrows with deadly flair.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="pump-shotgun-ndash-fire-rate">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Pump Shotgun – Fire Rate
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="55-fire-rate">
  +55% Fire Rate
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="pump shotgun fire rate upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175812-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 40 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Ellie’s shotgun is a powerhouse, but considering it’s more of a close-range weapon, it’s only really useful against hordes of infected. To beat these ghastly fungus foes, upgrading the fire rate is a solid choice, as players will be able to fire their shots quicker, ensuring they aren’t beaten and bitten to death.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bolt-action-rifle-ndash-damage">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Bolt-Action Rifle – Damage
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="25-damage">
  +25% Damage
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="bolt action rifle damage upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175824-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 100 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The bolt-action rifle may not be the most handy weapon in Ellie’s arsenal, due to its slow firing power and the fact that its loud bullet firing gives away Ellie’s position, but with an improvement to damage, players can take out Shamblers and Bloaters from a distance without having to worry about their face getting ripped off.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="semi-auto-pistol-ndash-stability">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Semi-Auto Pistol – Stability
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="35-stability">
  +35% Stability
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="semi auto pistol recoil upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175835-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Whilst most upgrades for the semi-auto pistol are good, stability is perhaps the best
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  upgrade for this weapon, specifically because it’s the only gun that Ellie can use with a craftable silencer.
 </p>
 <p>
  With better stability, players won’t miss their headshots when in stealth, meaning they won’t lose a bullet and durability on their suppressor.
 </p>
 <h2 id="semi-auto-pistol---capacity">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Semi-Auto Pistol - Capacity
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="10-bullets-in-a-magazine">
  10 Bullets in a Magazine
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="semi-auto pistol capacity upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/semi-auto-pistol-capacity-upgrade.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Semi-Auto Pistol will be Ellie's most common weapon. Ammo is extremely accessible and easier to find than other guns, so players might find themselves using this old reliable gun, which is why it's never a bad idea to stay on top of upgrades for it. One of the best upgrades is Capacity, which allows players to increase the 6-bullet magazine to a total of 10 bullets, which both means more collectible ammo for the reserves, and a larger capacity to make sure a missed shot won't be the end of Ellie's life.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="revolver-ndash-damage">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Revolver – Damage
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="40-damage-25-accuracy">
  +40% Damage, +25% Accuracy
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="revolver damage upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120175845-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 70 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Replacing the barrel of the revolver will provide it with more powerful shots. Not only will there be a near 50% damage increase, but the addition of better accuracy makes this upgrade well worth the asking price, especially when the revolver already kicks hard. This upgrade will easily take care of Shamblers, and perhaps even Bloaters.
 </p>
 <h3 id="best-weapon-upgrades-for-abby">
  Best Weapon Upgrades for Abby
 </h3>
 <p>
  Abby’s chapters have exclusive weapons separate from Ellie, and it’s best to focus on these following upgrades first to make sure that she survives her violent bout in Seattle and pray for that a dreaded confrontation with Ellie never happens.
 </p>
 <h2 id="semi-auto-rifle-ndash-4x-scope">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Semi-Auto Rifle – 4x Scope
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="press-the-x-button-to-use-a-zoom-in-scope">
  Press The X Button To Use A Zoom-In Scope
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="semi auto rifle 4x scope upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174845-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 80 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The semi-auto rifle is a powerful weapon, paired with its instant-kill headshot capability, players have a great weapon on their hands.
 </p>
 <p>
  Yet, the 4x scope only makes it better and more reliable, as players can use this scope to get a better look at enemies, whether they are stalkers, peeking their heads, or scavs far off in the distance waiting to get a shot with their bow and arrow. Controlling the battlefield with range is a great idea.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="semi-auto-rifle">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Semi-Auto Rifle
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="total-of-12-bullets-in-a-magazine">
  Total of 12 Bullets in a Magazine
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="semi-auto rifle capacity upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-47-pm-4040.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 60 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Ammo is vital, especially for Abby who needs to fight off infected, Scars, her own WLFs, and her hunter, Ellie. To make things just a smidge easier, the ammo capacity upgrade for the Semi-Auto Rifle will be worth some scrap, due to how players can have 12 bullets in a magazine rather than 9. Not only does this allow players to shoot more bullets without reloading, but it also provides more carry capacity for this ammo type.
 </p>
 <h2 id="crossbow-ndash-stability">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Crossbow – Stability
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="55-stability">
  +55% Stability
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="crossbow stability upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174855-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The crossbow is a rather efficient stealth weapon, due to the arrows being fired with utter silence. However, the crossbow can be quite the burden to aim, so focusing on a stability upgrade will mean that players are less likely to miss their shots, and alert enemies to their position, whilst also making sure that they don’t break arrows by missing their targets.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="double-barrel-shotgun-ndash-damage">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Double Barrel Shotgun – Damage
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="30-damage">
  +30% Damage
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="double barrel upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174906-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 60 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Abby’s double-barrel shotgun will see a powerful kick added to its design thanks to a damage upgrade. The double-barrel shotgun already has powerful potential with each blast, as well as a decent range, so adding even more means that players can get extra careless when it comes to the more tank-like enemies in
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="hunting-pistol-ndash-damage">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Hunting Pistol – Damage
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="25-damage">
  +25% Damage
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="hunting pistol upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174927-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 80 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The hunting pistol has its own skill set for a reason, and that’s because it can hit extremely hard if players know where to shoot and what upgrades to get. Extending its damage with this upgrade, players will make quick work of Bloaters and Shamblers by firing from a safe distance, whilst never losing the damage that they crave.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="military-pistol-ndash-fire-rate">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Military Pistol – Fire Rate
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="50-increase-to-fire-rate">
  +50% Increase to Fire Rate
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="military pistol fire rate upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/mixcollage-05-jan-2025-06-45-pm-6950.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Ammo is a resource that all players will need to survive, as not every Scar and Infected can be taken down with Abby's brutal punches and chokehold. As such, it's a good idea to invest into the default weapon, the Military Pistol, and its Fire Rate upgrade. While it might eat up ammo, it's going to give players a faster pull of the trigger so that missing a shot isn't a harsh penalty against sprinting enemies that need a good bullet to the head.
 </p>
 <h2 id="military-pistol-ndash-capacity">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Military Pistol – Capacity
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="4-magazine-capacity">
  +4 Magazine Capacity
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="military pistol capacity upgrade" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/the-last-of-us-tm-part-ii_20240120174918-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Costs: 50 Scrap
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The default pistol for Abby, upgrading the magazine size means that players can have more shots in their weapon for when the tough gets going. Abby will face her fair share of hordes of infected and scars, so extending the capacity of the pistol means less reload time, and more bullets to fire into heads.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
