<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons and Dragons Adapting Popular Campaign Into a Novel</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/dungeons-and-dragons-ravenloft-heir-of-strahd-popular-campaign-novel/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Penguin Random House partners with Dungeons and Dragons for the first Ravenloft novel in 17 years.
     </li>
     <li>
      Curse of Strahd, a popular gothic horror adventure, inspires the new novel Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd.
     </li>
     <li>
      The novel is set for release on May 1.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Penguin Random House is teaming up with
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dungeons and Dragons
   </strong>
  </em>
  to release
  <em>
   Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd
  </em>
  , a new novel inspired by the iconic
  <em>
   Curse of Strahd
  </em>
  adventure. Written by award-winning author Delilah S. Dawson, this book marks the first novel set in the
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  realm of Ravenloft in 17 years.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though Wizards of the Coast has released more than two dozen official adventures over the last 10 years, few have reached as much popularity among
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  fans as
  <em>
   Curse of Strahd
  </em>
  . A brutal gothic horror adventure featuring the eponymous vampire lord within the Domain of Dread known as Barovia,
  <em>
   Curse of Strahd
  </em>
  is a part of Ravenloft, a campaign setting released back in 1983 during
  <em>
   1st Edition D&amp;D
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, Wizards of the Coast is preparing to release a new
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  novel set in Ravenloft and featuring Count Strahd von Zarovich.
  <em>
   Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd
  </em>
  is an epic horror story following a group of five adventurers transported to Barovia under mysterious circumstances. Shortly after arriving, Fielle the Human Artificer, Kah the Kenku Cleric, Rotrog the Orc Wizard, Alishai the Tiefling Paladin, and Chivarion the Drow Barbarian receive an invitation to Castle Ravenloft from Strahd himself, where they must band together if they want to survive their stay at the macabre manse.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="ravenloft-heir-of-strahd-ndash-first-ravenloft-d-amp-d-novel-in-17-years">
  Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd – First Ravenloft D&amp;D Novel in 17 Years
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-708252535" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-708252535" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-708252535" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-708252535" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-708252535-img" id="article-gallery-1-708252535">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-708252535" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1981474248">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd
  </em>
  is written by Delilah S. Dawson, a New York Times bestselling author known for penning franchise tie-ins like
  <em>
   Star Wars: Phasma
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Disney Mirrorverse: Pure of Heart
  </em>
  , and the
  <em>
   Minecraft Mob Squad
  </em>
  series, as well as original works like
  <em>
   The Violence
  </em>
  and the
  <em>
   Blud
  </em>
  series. The novel is being published by Penguin Random House, which has put out other
  <em>
   D&amp;D
  </em>
  books, including
  <em>
   Heroes’ Feast: Flavors of the Multiverse
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Spelljammer: Memory’s Wake
  </em>
  , and two tie-in novels to the
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons: Honor Among Thieves
  </em>
  film.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <em>
    Fairest Friends,
   </em>
  </p>
  <p>
   <em>
    I pray you accept my humble Hospitality and dine with me tonight at Castle Ravenloft. It is rare we receive Visitors, and I do so Endeavor to Make your Acquaintance. The Carriage shall bear you to the Castle safely, and I await your Arrival with Pleasure.
   </em>
  </p>
  <p>
   <em>
    Your host,
   </em>
  </p>
  <p>
   <em>
    Strahd von Zarovich
   </em>
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  There have been many other
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  books set in Ravenloft over the years, beginning with Christie Golden’s
  <em>
   Vampire of the Mists
  </em>
  in 1991. However, the last novel set in Ravenloft –
  <em>
   Black Crusade
  </em>
  by Ari Marmell – was released in 2008, but the last one featuring Count von Zarovich was
  <em>
   I, Strahd: The War Against Azalin
  </em>
  from 1998. This makes
  <em>
   Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd
  </em>
  the first Ravenloft novel in 17 years, and the first one featuring the vampire lord in 27 years.
 </p>
 <p>
  This new
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  novel is set to release on May 13.
  <em>
   Ravenloft: Heir of Strahd
  </em>
  is available for pre-order from Amazon, Barnes &amp; Noble, and many other booksellers for $30 hardcover, $20 as an audiobook, or $15 as an ebook.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Saved by the Gods!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-saved-by-the-gods/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player takes out a helicopter with a semi in GTA and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPO: How To Extract</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/repo-how-extract/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  As befits a survival horror,
  <strong>
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has many monsters that want to kill you. But avoiding them is only part of your mission, as the most important task is finding valuable loot to sell. So, in this guide, we will tell you how to extract in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Extractor is a collection point for all the items you find. This is the only way to earn money and fulfill your quota. However, it can be a little hard for beginners to figure out how this device works, especially on more difficult levels.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-extract-in-repo">
  How To Extract in REPO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO Extractor " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you have completed the tutorial in the main menu of
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  , then you know what the Extractor looks like. This device has a small square area in which you need to put all the valuables you find. When the total value of all items reaches or exceeds the quota, the Extractor will start a three-second cooldown, after which it will extract them from
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  and allow you to safely leave the level.
 </p>
 <p>
  Also, you do not want to stand in the Extractor area, as you will be crushed, and you will simply die. In addition, if you place the head of knocked-down teammates in the area before fulfilling the quota and extracting items in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  , they will respawn with one HP. After this, you will only have to go to the truck and send a message to Taxman about the successfully completed job.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is important to note that the further you progress, the more difficult your tasks in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  will be. This applies not only to the size of the quota but also to the number of Extractors. You can easily find out about this by looking at the upper right corner of the screen. There, under your quota, the number of all Extractors is displayed and how many of them you have used. But they do not all spawn at the same time. Instead, the next Extractor will appear on the map only after you have used the previous one. As for the quota, it is the same for each Extractor on the level.
 </p>
 <h2 id="repo-extraction-tips">
  REPO Extraction Tips
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO Extractor " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-extract-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the beginning of each round in this awesome game, you get a random quota to complete. Depending on the loot found, you can complete it for 10 items or even one. But of course, more valuable items are either extremely fragile or very heavy. Therefore, you should definitely use the cart that spawns at the beginning of the round near the truck.
 </p>
 <p>
  It will give you several huge advantages, such as safe transportation and large carrying capacity. All sorts of cups, bottles, vials, and the like break after one or two hits, so they should be immediately put in the cart.
 </p>
 <p>
  Also, sometimes your team can find loot worth more than your entire quota. Such items are usually so heavy that they can only be lifted by two or even three people, so it is better to use a cart to move them.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 25 Most Powerful Video Game Heroes Ever (From Weakest To Strongest)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/most-powerful-video-game-heroes-ever/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Adol Christin is an expert swordsman who defeated giants and monsters, displaying exceptional energy levels and stamina.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sonic The Hedgehog's speed and super forms helped him defeat powerful enemies in the Sonic universe.
     </li>
     <li>
      Samus from Metroid is a powerful fighter with advanced technology in her suit, granting her a wide range of impressive abilities.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In the world of video games, anything is possible. Players can be anyone from a goose that annoys a village to a god that saves the world. It's also true that some of the most beloved characters are also very powerful. Thus, it begs the question, who is the most powerful among them?
 </p>
 <p>
  As with all fiction, a character's strength and abilities can change as the story advances. This is also very much down to interpretation from the personal perspectives of fans and creators. However, based on accomplishments, these candidates tend to rank as the most powerful heroes in gaming.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated March 4, 2025, by Michael Llewellyn:
   </strong>
   A list of who is the most powerful will always be subjective, as there is always an argument and counter-argument for their abilities and strengths. However, it's always fun to debate, even if no ranking system can be considered definitive. This list has been updated to include more powerful heroes from video games that fans can argue over.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="adol-christin---the-ys-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   25
  </span>
  <span>
   Adol Christin - The Ys Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-experienced-warrior-who-defeated-giants-and-god-like-enemies">
  An Experienced Warrior Who Defeated Giants And God-Like Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-210309216" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-210309216" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-210309216" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-210309216" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-210309216-img" id="article-gallery-1-210309216">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-210309216" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-987791244">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Without powers, Adol from the
  <em>
   Ys
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  ​​​​​​series is a powerful expert swordsman who has defeated giants, monsters, and more. His energy levels, speed, and stamina significantly surpass those of his friends and party members. However, Adol is a vulnerable human and frequently needs time to recover from his injuries after getting shipwrecked. That said, he has overcome several events that would have killed a normal human.
 </p>
 <p>
  Adol was tortured, weakened, and compelled to battle in a coliseum-like arena. against a giant monster with low-level equipment and still defeated it. Perhaps his most significant accomplishment came when he critically wounded a Demi-Galba in
  <em>
   Ys 6: The Ark Napishtim
  </em>
  with nothing but a steel sword. The monsters can only be defeated with a special metal called Emelas.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sonic-the-hedgehog">
  <span class="item-num">
   24
  </span>
  <span>
   Sonic The Hedgehog
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-speedster-with-access-to-super-powered-forms-nbsp">
  A Speedster With Access To Super Powered Forms
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1956585720" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1956585720" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1956585720" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1956585720" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1956585720-img" id="article-gallery-2-1956585720">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1956585720" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1774348207">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The least powerful of the most powerful characters is the Sega mascot himself, Sonic the Hedgehog. He has impressive skills, such as super speed, spin attacks, and more. However, his more impressive abilities often require specific criteria to be met. For example, his most famous, the Super Sonic, requires him to have all the Chaos Emeralds.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a powerful video game character, Sonic often needs external factors and relies on Chaos Emeralds to assess his true potential. However, his super forms have allowed him to defeat powerful bosses in the Sonic universe.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="samus---the-metroid-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   23
  </span>
  <span>
   Samus - The Metroid Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-powerful-fighter-with-a-super-suit">
  A Powerful Fighter With A Super Suit
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-906118505" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-906118505" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-906118505" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-906118505" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-906118505-img" id="article-gallery-3-906118505">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-906118505" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-185434604">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Samus from the
  <em>
   Metroid
  </em>
  series is a bounty hunter and the last remaining piece of the Chozo legacy. After her parents were killed, Samus was raised by the highly advanced Chozo. She is gifted with their technology, namely, her highly advanced suit, which gives her numerous impressive abilities.
 </p>
 <p>
  Her abilities include firing missiles with laser beams, freezing enemies solid, transforming into a ball, dropping bombs, dropping super bombs, and making force fields that allow her to survive in space, lava, and underwater. While powerful, Samus is like the Iron Man of Nintendo. Her physical strengths come from the powers obtained from her super suit.
 </p>
 <h2 id="master-chief---the-halo-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   22
  </span>
  <span>
   Master Chief - The Halo Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-genetically-enhanced-super-soldier">
  A Genetically Enhanced Super Soldier
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1650424576" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1650424576" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1650424576" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1650424576" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1650424576-img" id="article-gallery-4-1650424576">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1650424576" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-726851731">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Master Chief is a genetically engineered super-soldier who underwent rigorous training and was given advanced armor capable of surviving a fall from space. He is like a one-person army, defeating hordes of alien enemies with enhanced strength, size, speed, and tactical intelligence.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Master Chief possesses exceptional skill with almost any weapon and has demonstrated a remarkable ability to quickly understand how to utilize alien weapons. He has unparalleled endurance, having survived numerous wars on a global scale.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="lenneth-ndash-valkyrie-profile-or-valkyrie-profile-lenneth">
  <span class="item-num">
   21
  </span>
  <span>
   Lenneth – Valkyrie Profile (Or Valkyrie Profile: Lenneth)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="becomes-a-goddess-of-creation">
  Becomes A Goddess Of Creation
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1870554665" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1870554665" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1870554665" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1870554665" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1870554665-img" id="article-gallery-5-1870554665">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1870554665" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-322464288">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Lenneth is a Valkyrie and a Goddess of Fate, revered as a bringer of life and a harbinger of death. As a powerful battle maiden with control over life and death, she should be recognized as one of gaming's strongest characters. Lenneth is a powerful swordswoman and archer capable of defeating the undead and raising the souls of killed warriors to fight by her side.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Valkyrie Profile
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Lenneth gains powers similar to Odin's, controlling human life and expanding her divine abilities. After a world-ending event, she restored life to Midgard and became one of the most powerful Norse gods. This makes her a match for any warrior on this list.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alucard---castlevania">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Alucard - Castlevania
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-half-vampire-half-human-with-extraordinary-powers">
  A Half-Vampire/Half-Human With Extraordinary Powers
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-995539069" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-995539069" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-995539069" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-995539069" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-995539069-img" id="article-gallery-6-995539069">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-995539069" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1343981525">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Alucard is the half-human son of the legendary vampire Dracula. He possesses the superhuman strength, speed, and telekinetic powers of a vampire and very few of their weaknesses. In addition to his physical traits, Alucard possesses dark magic mastery comparable to that of Dracula, including the ability to shapeshift, transforming into poison mist, bats, wolves, and a giant gargoyle invulnerable to damage.
 </p>
 <p>
  The lore suggests that Alucard possesses a final form similar to Dracula but avoids using it to distance himself from his father. His powers are nearly limitless, but he has weaknesses, as shown in
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night.
  </em>
  Water, electricity, and poison can harm him; however, Alucard can overcome these vulnerabilities with relics..
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="yuri---shadow-hearts">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Yuri - Shadow Hearts
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="can-transform-into-multiple-demon-forms">
  Can Transform Into Multiple Demon Forms
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-438406788" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-438406788" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-438406788" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-438406788" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-438406788-img" id="article-gallery-7-438406788">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-438406788" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1158893337">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Shadow Hearts
   </strong>
  </em>
  games are set in a Lovecraftian alternate universe during the First World War. Yuri is the protagonist of the first
  <em>
   Shadow Hearts
  </em>
  game and a dual protagonist in
  <em>
   Shadow Hearts: Covenant.
  </em>
  He is referred to as a Harmonixer in the
  <em>
   Shadow Hearts
  </em>
  universe and can take on the form of demons he has defeated in combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even without transforming into a demon form, Yuri is a powerful fighter who can defeat opponents with his fists. In
  <em>
   Shadow Hearts
  </em>
  lore, Yuri has the highest sanity meter, meaning he can stay in Demon form longer than other Harmonixers and utilize all their elemental powers in combat.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cloud---final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Cloud - Final Fantasy 7
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="final-fantasy-39-s-most-iconic-hero-is-also-a-powerhouse">
  Final Fantasy's Most Iconic Hero Is Also A Powerhouse
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1552216580" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1552216580" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1552216580" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1552216580" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1552216580-img" id="article-gallery-8-1552216580">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1552216580" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1190165572">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Cloud is a long-time favorite of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Final Fantasy 7
   </strong>
  </em>
  fans and the protagonist of arguably the most popular entry in the franchise. Even though Cloud never officially made it to SOLDIER, he had the physical capabilities. Cloud is a natural swordsman, given his ability to go toe-to-toe with Sephiroth and other characters in the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  universe through the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Dissidia
  </em>
  series.
 </p>
 <p>
  Due to Hojo's experiment with Jehova cells, Cloud gained Zack's abilities, skills, and strength.
 </p>
 <p>
  As the story progresses, Cloud develops into a stronger character, highlighted by his battle in the skies with Sephiroth in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7: Advent Children,
  </em>
  showcasing Cloud's almost god-like powers. Unfortunately, Cloud's self-doubt and reliance on his friends can make him vulnerable to the other beings mentioned here.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="clive-rosfield---final-fantasy-16">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Clive Rosfield - Final Fantasy 16
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="can-transform-and-use-the-power-of-summons">
  Can Transform And Use The Power Of Summons
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-155892517" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-155892517" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-155892517" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-155892517" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-155892517-img" id="article-gallery-9-155892517">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-155892517" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1933588072">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Clive Rosfield is the protagonist of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Final Fantasy 16
   </strong>
  </em>
  and is already ranked by fans as one of the strongest characters in the universe. He is a powerful warrior who can match anyone with a sword, fights his enemies with little to no help from a supporting cast, and can utilize the powers of Eikons - summons.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like Yuri from
  <em>
   Shadow Hearts
  </em>
  , Clive absorbs and utilizes the elemental powers of other characters in the story with the Eikons he defeated. Clive can merge the capabilities of multiple Eikons without damaging his body or psyche. However, he does have a limit on how long he can use the semi-dominant form of his powers. He only uses his maximum power when fighting other Eikons, but he would be a match for most of the characters in this list.
 </p>
 <h2 id="talion---shadow-of-mordor-war">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Talion - Shadow of Mordor/War
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-powerful-immortal-warrior-with-unmatched-skill">
  A Powerful Immortal Warrior With Unmatched Skill
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-2027893649" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-2027893649" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-2027893649" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-2027893649" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-2027893649-img" id="article-gallery-10-2027893649">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-2027893649" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-2059896942">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As the hero of the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Shadow of Mordor
   </strong>
  </em>
  series, Talim may rank as one of the most powerful characters in
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  universe. The character is not considered canon, but if he were to make it in the official lore, he could be more powerful than Sauron.
 </p>
 <p>
  Talim is immortal in the game and can fall in battle several times, only to reemerge stronger and exact revenge on the enemies who killed him. Skillwise, the Ranger is almost unmatched, but his immortality is limited to completing his mission and bringing down evil.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="death---darksiders-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Death - Darksiders 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="has-the-power-to-defeat-angels-and-demons">
  Has The Power To Defeat Angels And Demons
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1464854692" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1464854692" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1464854692" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1464854692" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1464854692-img" id="article-gallery-11-1464854692">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1464854692" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-2029574535">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As one of the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse, Death is arguably the most powerful character in the
  <em>
   Darksiders
  </em>
  series. Admittedly, he lost some of his powers at the start of the game, but Death is still a character that transcends life itself.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Darksiders
   </strong>
  </em>
  comics, Death was the only character capable of defeating War and even cutting off his arm. Death is almost invulnerable, and at the height of his powers, he can come back from the dead.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kaim---lost-odyssey">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Kaim - Lost Odyssey
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-immortal-warrior-and-a-one-man-army">
  An Immortal Warrior And A One-Man Army
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1328596028" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1328596028" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1328596028" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1328596028" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1328596028-img" id="article-gallery-12-1328596028">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1328596028" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1609956030">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Kaim is the immortal main protagonist of the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Lost Odyssey
   </strong>
   .
  </em>
  Despite his quiet demeanor, he is a powerful warrior capable of defeating armies single-handedly without breaking a sweat, as evidenced in the opening scenes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite his empathy that develops slowly through the story, his years as an immortal have desensitized him emotionally, making him an efficient killer in battle. He can withstand powerful attacks from mages and tank-like war machines. More interestingly, he emerged from a devastating meteor strike that wiped out two armies on the battlefield without sustaining a scratch.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="raiden---metal-gear-rising">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Raiden - Metal Gear Rising
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-cyborg-ninja-that-can-cut-a-tank-in-half-nbsp">
  A Cyborg Ninja That Can Cut A Tank In Half
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1812541428" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1812541428" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1812541428" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1812541428" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1812541428-img" id="article-gallery-13-1812541428">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1812541428" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-241819349">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When one thinks of the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Metal Gear
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise, Snake is usually the character that comes to mind. However, as powerful characters go, Raiden from
  <em>
   <strong>
    Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
   </strong>
  </em>
  is on another level compared to other characters in the same universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  He is a cyborg who has power over how much pain he can feel in battle, can jump from missile to missile while they are in mid-flight, lift tank-sized machines, cut through anything, and more. Raiden's strength and abilities greatly depend on his cybernetic enhancements, putting him lower down the list than other characters pushed by magic.
 </p>
 <h2 id="delsin-rowe-ndash-infamous-second-son">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Delsin Rowe – Infamous: Second Son
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="can-absorb-the-power-of-other-superpowered-beings">
  Can Absorb The Power Of Other Superpowered Beings
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-192092568" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-192092568" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-192092568" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-192092568" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-192092568-img" id="article-gallery-14-192092568">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-192092568" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-578058700">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The third entry in the PlayStation-exclusive series
  <strong>
   <em>
    Infamous
   </em>
  </strong>
  introduced gamers to its new protagonist, Delsin Rowe. Delsin is comparable to Rogue from the
  <em>
   X-Men
  </em>
  franchise in that he can absorb and use the abilities of other super-powered people known as Conduits.
 </p>
 <p>
  This makes Delsin a pretty powerful character in any universe, and as far as superpowers go, he is capable of unlimited power within reason. He does, however, have a cooldown time after using his powers. This means that as strong as he is, he does not quite match some of the more elite members of this list.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="starkiller-ndash-star-wars-the-force-unleashed">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Starkiller – Star Wars: The Force Unleashed
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="possesses-power-to-defeat-the-most-powerful-jedi-and-sith">
  Possesses Power To Defeat The Most Powerful Jedi And Sith
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1136384535" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1136384535" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1136384535" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1136384535" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1136384535-img" id="article-gallery-15-1136384535">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1136384535" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-219555305">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Released in 2008,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Star Wars: The Force Unleashed
   </strong>
  </em>
  is an action-adventure game focusing on a brand-new protagonist known as Starkiller, or his birth name, Galen Marek. Marek was trained in secret as Darth Vader's apprentice. Vader planned to use Marek to overthrow the Emperor.
 </p>
 <p>
  Starkiller defeated four hidden Jedi, Darth Vader, and even the Emperor in combat in the first game. He mastered seven variations of lightsaber combat to exploit the weaknesses of all his enemies. Furthermore, he had almost god-like Force powers - as displayed when he pulled a Star Destroyer out of the sky. Unsurprisingly, the Starkiller character is no longer considered canon since Disney took control of the franchise.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alex-mercer-ndash-prototype">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Alex Mercer – Prototype
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-shapeshifter-that-can-destroy-the-world">
  A Shapeshifter That Can Destroy The World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-846358699" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-846358699" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-846358699" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-846358699" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-846358699-img" id="article-gallery-16-846358699">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-846358699" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-669746044">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As a superhero/supervillain title from the same studio, the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Prototype
   </strong>
   games
  </em>
  are considered successors to the fantastic
  <em>
   Hulk: Ultimate Destruction
  </em>
  . As a result, Alex Mercer plays and feels very much like The Hulk if he was enhanced with the abilities of Marvel's Venom - all thanks to the Blacklight virus.
 </p>
 <p>
  Very few games provide the kind of power fantasy that the
  <em>
   Prototype
  </em>
  series does, and when fully powered, Mercer has world-destroying abilities. Thanks to the virus that created his powers, he has limitless strength, shapeshifting abilities, superhuman speed, and is almost indestructible thanks to his regeneration abilities.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dante---the-devil-may-cry-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Dante - The Devil May Cry Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-superbeing-who-can-destroy-ancient-demons">
  A Superbeing Who Can Destroy Ancient Demons
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-77856211" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-77856211" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-77856211" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-77856211" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-77856211-img" id="article-gallery-17-77856211">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-77856211" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-418019829">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Dante is a paranormal being, able to freeze time, withstand attacks from inter-dimensional entities, and repel demons one hundred times his size. The son of Sparda has enhanced strength and speed and is skilled with a blade. Moreover, Dante can transform into a powerful demon for a limited time.
 </p>
 <p>
  He has been known to rip the souls out of enemies without harming their bodies (which allows him to kill things that cannot die). Despite his relaxed demeanor, Dante is a powerful and intense fighter who combines immeasurable skills with guns and a blade.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bayonetta---the-bayonetta-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Bayonetta - The Bayonetta Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-powerful-witch-with-immeasurable-strength">
  A Powerful Witch With Immeasurable Strength
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-212148734" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-212148734" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-212148734" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-212148734" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-212148734-img" id="article-gallery-18-212148734">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-212148734" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-795537800">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bayonetta is a Bullet Witch with a ton of abilities up her sleeve. She is an immortal who makes light work of traveling through space and re-entering Earth's atmosphere. She has immeasurable strength, as displayed when she throws skyscrapers and tanks around like toys.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, Bayonetta can master any weapon, summon demons, she can shapeshift, control time, and more. She proved powerful enough to defeat a god after her battle with Jubileus. Perhaps more interesting, Bayonetta has no time limit on her powers, arguably making her even more powerful than Dante from the
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  series.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="doomslayer---the-doom-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Doomslayer - The Doom Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-god-like-warrior-with-the-power-to-destroy-the-lords-of-hell">
  A God-Like Warrior With The Power To Destroy The Lords Of Hell
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-109050854" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-109050854" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-109050854" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-109050854" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-109050854-img" id="article-gallery-19-109050854">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-109050854" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-884573873">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Doom Slayer is the protagonist of the iconic
  <em>
   Doom
  </em>
  series. He is frequently regarded as one of the most powerful video game characters of all time. The Doom Slayer received his superhuman abilities from celestial beings and the nephilim, which also grants him immortality. Although he can be harmed, he will always rise again and continue his fight.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Doom Slayer has a wide list of defeated demons and entities. He killed the Hell's strongest champion, the Titan, and potentially millions and more of demons. The only thing that holds him back is the gap between the protagonist's reported strengths and his actual ability in-game without cheats activated. Of course, this wouldn't make for a very enjoyable game if the Doom Slayer could easily destroy everything in his path. However, compared to some characters on this list who have limitless strength and the power to destroy multiverses and gods, it's debatable whether or not he's stronger than characters like Kratos or the Demi-Fiend.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kratos---the-god-of-war-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Kratos - The God Of War Series
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-spartan-warrior-who-became-a-god">
  A Spartan Warrior Who Became A God
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-385237560" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-385237560" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-385237560" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-385237560" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-385237560-img" id="article-gallery-20-385237560">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-385237560" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-294419816">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Kratos is often considered the strongest video game character due to his kill count of gods. He successfully killed the entire Greek pantheon. Kratos is a god and a slayer of gods from Greek and Norse mythologies. While a lot of characters on this list have killed gods, it is Kratos who makes it look easy.
 </p>
 <p>
  He has been to Hell multiple times and fought his way out. His opponent's magic, size, intelligence, and strength proved fruitless against the rage of Kratos. He is a battle-hardened warrior with experience in war and epic battles against gods and titans.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Gives Unown Clever Paldean Regional Form</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-unown-paldean-regional-variant/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Unown gets a new exciting Paldean redesign based on the letter "Ñ" from the Spanish alphabet
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans are loving the new design and suggest adding variants based on languages and regions
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite Unown's uniqueness, it hasn't seen updates since Gen 3, and Game Freak may not introduce new forms.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has given Unown an overhaul, giving the unique Pokemon a Paldean regional form. The redesign is drawing attention from the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  community, and highlights a Pokemon that hasn't seen an update in quite some time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unown was definitely an unusual Pokemon when it was introduced into the series, flipping the concept of "catching 'em all" on its head by introducing 26 unique forms of a single Pokemon variety back in Gen 2. While Unown has never been hugely powerful as a Pokemon, the challenge of capturing every single Unown has been a bit of added fun for players, and it seems that some would be happy to see a 29th variant of the Pokemon join the fray, judging by the reaction to this fanart.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan HertzBurst has shared their redesign of Unown, giving the Pokemon a Paldea-themed overhaul that's quite appropriate. Traditionally, Unown has had 28 forms, with each one either being a letter of the Latin alphabet or punctuation marks. This Paldea variant would add a 29th form, giving the Pokemon a design based on the "Ñ" of the Spanish alphabet. Given that Paldea is based upon the real-world Iberian Peninsula, which encompasses Spain, it's a fitting concept that would have been neat to see in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  . The "Ñ" version of Unown is extremely similar to the existing "N" version, but with an extra prong sticking up out of the eye with the letter's tilde over it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fans-suggest-new-unown-forms">
  Pokemon Fans Suggest New Unown Forms
 </h2>
 <p>
  Viewers have been quite supportive of this piece of fanart, praising the artist's design and execution alike. It's generated quite a bit of conversation in the community, with some pointing to this as being an example of a missed possibility in the actual games. Players have suggested that Unown could have received variants based on regions and languages, potentially adding Greek letters, Egyptian hieroglyphs, and even katakana, hiragana, or kanji-based forms, given the game's Japanese roots and Japan-like locales in some titles. However, others have also pointed out the drawbacks, as adding new variants of Unown for multiple languages and regions could create an overwhelming number of them to actually try and catch.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1734174919" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1734174919" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1734174919" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1734174919" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1734174919-img" id="article-gallery-1-1734174919">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1734174919" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-817026861">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While Unown drew a lot of attention when it was first introduced into the series for its unique qualities and a featured role in the third
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  film, it hasn't gotten much love since. Although Unown has appeared in more recent titles, it hasn't received any new forms since Generation 3. Considering the missed opportunities pointed out by fans, it seems unlikely that Game Freak will actually update the Pokemon with more designs based on letters. Thankfully, artistically-minded fans can always show the community what could have been if things had taken a different turn during game development.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
