<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite Leak Reveals New TMNT Crossover Cosmetic Details</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-leak-tmnt-crossover-pizza-shredder-cosmetics/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fortnite leaks are hinting at further details about the heavily rumored Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles crossover.
     </li>
     <li>
      The crossover will reportedly add pizza and Shredder cosmetics that will be available in both Rocket League and Fortnite.
     </li>
     <li>
      Previous leaks have also hinted at several new TMNT skins coming alongside a new vehicle in the Turtles' "Party Wagon"
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new leak from
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  reveals some of the cosmetics players will be able to pick up during the upcoming
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  collaboration. The massively popular battle royale from Epic Games has become renowned for the wide range of crossover content found throughout the beloved shooter. Fans can take to the battlefield in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  wearing skins based on everything from
  <em>
   Family Guy
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Naruto
  </em>
  to popular celebrities and musical artists like Eminem and Mariah Carey. Now, a fan-favorite cartoon franchise will be one of the game's next crossovers.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  first welcomed the iconic
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  franchise into the fray in late 2023 as part of its annual "WinterFest" event. The first wave of cosmetics featured skins based on each of the four titular turtles, with their trusted reported companion April O'Neil also receiving her own skin during the collaboration. The crossover would later receive another wave of skins, with iconic antagonist Shredder added to the game as a skin for the aptly-named "Cowabunga" event. A new leak is now suggesting that the Turtles are headed back to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  with more in store.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fortnite-leak-teases-new-tmnt-crossover">
  Fortnite Leak Teases New TMNT Crossover
 </h2>
 <p>
  A recent update shared by prominent
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  leaker ShiinaBR is teasing fans with details for
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  's next
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  collaboration. According to the leak, the upcoming
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  crossover will feature both a cosmetic based on pizza and a new Shredder cosmetic that will be added to
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  . The post reveals that the
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  crossover items will be usable within
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  as well, though it does not directly confirm what the cosmetics will be. A release window for the crossover was not shared as part of the
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  leak.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1880678482" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1880678482" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1880678482" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1880678482" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1880678482-img" id="article-gallery-1-1880678482">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1880678482" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-603064862">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The return of
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  has already seen multiple leaks about what the crossover will bring. Previous leaks have hinted at several potential
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  skins coming to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  during the event, including classic characters like Casey Jones, Bebop, and Rocksteady. As mentioned previously, the crossover is also heavily rumored to be bringing new cosmetics to
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  as well, teased to be adding the Turtles' iconic "Party Wagon" as a vehicle.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  's newest
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  crossover will join a stacked lineup of rumored collab content for the battle royale. The battle royale has seen several rumors about an upcoming
  <em>
   King of the Hill
  </em>
  crossover, said to be bringing a skin based on Hank Hill with more likely to follow.
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  has also seen several anime events run during recent months, including crossovers with fan-favorite franchises like
  <em>
   Jujutsu Kaisen
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Kaiju No. 8
  </em>
  . The rumored
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  crossover will mark the welcome return of a beloved crossover for many
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  fans.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25 Player Creates Hilarious Kane Variants</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-kane-variants-player-creations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Kane's classic 90s costume in WWE 2K25 inspires fan recreations.
     </li>
     <li>
      WWE 2K25's character creation suite allows fans to replicate classic superstars like Kane's iconic 1997 appearance.
     </li>
     <li>
      Bloodline and Deadman edition pre-orders offer early access to WWE 2K25.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Kane’s classic 90s costume has inspired many imitators on the independent wrestling circuit, and a
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  player has recreated them in-game. While everyone else has to wait until March 14 to dive into
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , those who pre-ordered the special Bloodline or Deadman editions can already check out the latest installment in the
  <em>
   WWE 2K
  </em>
  series. The Bloodline-centric 2K Showcase Mode and new multiplayer Island are the main attractions this year, but there is also plenty of fun to be had with
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  ’s classic character creation suite.
 </p>
 <p>
  One particularly popular use for
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  ’s character creation tools is to replicate classic superstars who still aren’t featured in the game’s official roster - such as Kane’s iconic masked variant from his original debut in the late 90s. Much to the disappointment of fans who grew up during the Big Red Machine’s classic run, only his modern-day masked appearance and unmasked costume from 2010 have been included as playable characters in the past few
  <em>
   WWE 2K
  </em>
  titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Luckily, Kane’s original mask and bodysuit are available for use in the
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  character creation suite, allowing fans to not only recreate the classic Big Red Machine, but many of the color schemes worn by other wrestlers paying homage to him outside of WWE. Reddit user SuperGwarioBros took the opportunity to do exactly that, showing off their custom renditions of Kane’s original 1997 appearance, the indie wrestler Blue Kane (or “Blue Pain” as he is sometimes called), the peppermint-themed Kandy Kane, the pink-and-teal colored Gayne, the white-clad Kokane, and a green variant named “Hurrikane” - an apparent tribute to Kane’s fellow WWE superstar and former tag-team partner The Hurricane.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wwe-2k25-player-recreates-indie-kane-impersonators">
  WWE 2K25 Player Recreates Indie Kane Impersonators
 </h2>
 <p>
  There are plenty of other Kane variants that could serve as great inspiration for
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  players, such as the appropriately-named Yellow Kane. Other Reddit users in the comment section of SuperGwarioBros’s r/WWEGames post have jokingly compared the many existing Kane clones to the Power Rangers or the different color-swapped ninjas of the
  <em>
   Mortal Kombat
  </em>
  franchise, and even joked about completely unrelated people like English soccer player Harry Kane eventually joining the list.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-865778569" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-865778569" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-865778569" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-865778569" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-865778569-img" id="article-gallery-1-865778569">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-865778569" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-78551038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While many of these fans wish that Kane’s 1997 variant was readily available as part of
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  ’s playable roster, they are nonetheless excited for the new game and its many possible dream matches - including a hypothetical confrontation between Kane and legendary TNA superstar Abyss. There will be plenty of other surprise roster additions and future DLC when
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  finally launches in full later this week, and some players who pre-ordered the game are already enjoying the carnage and chaos of the latest wrestling sim.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25: How to Download Custom Superstars</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-how-get-download-custom-superstars-wrestlers-characters/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  WWE 2K games have an extensively detailed creation suite where players can create their own custom Superstars, GMs, arenas, move sets, and a ton of other content. In fact,
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  has expanded MyRISE mode, which allows for deeper custom Superstar creation. These creations can then be uploaded and shared with the wider community. Other players can browse, download, and use these custom creations in their own games. If you’re wondering how, this guide breaks down how you can download Custom Superstars and expand your
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  roster.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-download-custom-superstars-in-wwe-2k25">
  How To Download Custom Superstars in WWE 2K25
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1528723256" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1528723256" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1528723256" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1528723256" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1528723256-img" id="article-gallery-1-1528723256">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1528723256" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1569278937">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  takes the Custom Superstar experience to new heights by allowing players to craft both a male and female wrestler. MyRISE now uses multiple shared save slots for both your male and female creations. This means you can manage and progress both characters within the same save files.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like previous titles, you can share your creations with other players online and even download custom Superstars created by others. Here’s a step-by-step guide to downloading custom Superstars in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Head to the Online tab from the
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
   main menu. To access the Online menu, press R1 on a PlayStation controller or RB on an Xbox controller.
  </li>
  <li>
   In the Online section, look for and select "Community Creations."
  </li>
  <li>
   Once in Community Creations, you'll see a few options, namely Downloads, Uploads, and Image Manager.
  </li>
  <li>
   Click on Downloads. You'll then be presented with categories of downloadable content. Select "Superstars."
  </li>
  <li>
   Here, you can browse through the available options and download your favorite wrestlers. You can also filter options to find specific Superstars.
  </li>
  <li>
   Browse through the list of available Custom Superstars and select a Superstar to view a preview.
  </li>
  <li>
   If you find a Superstar you want to add to your roster, hit the "Download" button. You can also upvote them.
  </li>
  <li>
   Once downloaded, the custom Superstar will be available for use in various game modes.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-7c0cba3ff25b3e83" id="emaki-video-player-7c0cba3ff25b3e83">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     In addition to browsing a creator's current content, you can also add them to favorites. This way, you can easily find and access their future uploads and creations.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="wwe-2k25-the-island-mode">
  WWE 2K25 The Island Mode
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's "The Island" mode (exclusive to Xbox Series X|S and PlayStation 5) has a unique take on custom Superstars. The character you create in this builder is specific to "The Island" mode. It's separate from the custom Superstars you might create for other modes like MyRISE or regular exhibition matches.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelda Fan Shows Off Wildly Obscure Wind Waker Memorabilia</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/zelda-wind-waker-memorabilia-popcorn-bag/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A fan shared a rare 2003 promotional popcorn bag from AMC Theaters.
     </li>
     <li>
      The bag's darker, gritty theme contrasts with the game's art style.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite an initial mixed reception, fans' opinions of the game have warmed over the years.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker
   </em>
  </strong>
  fan has shown off what they call the most obscure piece of memorabilia they own: a promotional popcorn bag from AMC Theaters. The
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  franchise has been around for a long time, so there's a lot of strange and rare merch floating around out there that some people have held onto for decades. These promotional pieces are particularly interesting for titles like
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker
  </em>
  , which didn't get the warmest reception upon release but have since become fan favorites.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite being one of the highest-selling
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  games of all time,
  <em>
   The Wind Waker
  </em>
  got off to a bit of a shaky start. As the first GameCube entry in the series, it had a lot to live up to, and fans initially found its cartoonish aesthetics to be an unpleasant surprise after the darker N64 titles and a grittier Zelda demo showing off the GameCube's capabilities at Space World 2000. Still, it became one of the franchise's most beloved games as time went on, and people warmed up to its cell-shaded art style.
 </p>
 <p>
  The darker, grittier theme many expected is on full display in Redditor rawcookiedough's promotional
  <em>
   Wind Waker
  </em>
  popcorn bag. According to the post, it's from around 2003, the same year the game came out, making its relatively pristine condition an impressive feat for a 20-plus-year-old disposable bag. More interestingly, though, is how the artwork does not line up with the game's actual visuals or themes.
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  creator Shigeru Miyamoto originally wanted
  <em>
   Wind Waker
  </em>
  to look more realistic, and so did many fans at the time, so the bag is an interesting bit of history, showing off the darker promotional material that likely led to the disappointment people felt once they saw what the game actually looked like.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="redditor-shows-off-wind-waker-popcorn-bag-from-2003">
  Redditor Shows Off Wind Waker Popcorn Bag From 2003
 </h2>
 <p>
  It's also intriguing how Nintendo promoted the game through a movie theater item, despite there being no tie-in film. The company is now working on a
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  movie to come out sometime before 2030, but at the time, there was no such thing in the works. As others in the comments pointed out, though, that kind of marketing wasn't unusual for the era. Game promotions weren't always as closely tied to the game's content as they are now, and campaigns had to appeal to all kids, not just dedicated gamers, to make an impact, as the industry wasn't as big or well-established as it is today.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1878405354" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1878405354" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1878405354" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1878405354" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1878405354-img" id="article-gallery-1-1878405354">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1878405354" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-730141852">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's unclear if Nintendo will go the promotional popcorn bag route again, but
  <em>
   The Wind Waker
  </em>
  could get some new developments in the near future. Some think that 2025 could be ideal for a
  <em>
   Wind Waker
  </em>
  Switch port to finally come out, given the release of the Switch 2. That may be little more than wishful thinking for now, but if the excitement around a popcorn bag is proof of anything,
  <em>
   Zelda
  </em>
  's first GameCube title still has plenty of fans.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Death Stranding 2 May Be More of a Psychological Journey Than a Physical One</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/death-stranding-2-psychological-themes-introspective-story/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Death Stranding 2: On the Beach shifts focus from physical to psychological battles, addressing deeper psychological warfare.
     </li>
     <li>
      Death Stranding 2 could center on personal stories rather than physical traversal, offering a more introspective gaming experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      Death Stranding 2 might involve intentional harm as players visit the Beach, reflecting a deeper psychological narrative.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It has now been over five years since
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  introduced players to one of the strangest worlds and gameplay loops in gaming history by putting them into the shoes of Sam Porter Bridges — a porter tasked with reconnecting America by delivering cargo to various locations across the fractured world. Despite being innovative and bold,
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  's delivery-style gameplay loop was largely divisive, causing many to label the game as a "walking simulator." However, regardless of the controversy,
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  managed to deliver an incredibly compelling narrative and approach to gameplay, now tasking its sequel,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
   </strong>
  </em>
  , with living up to its name.
 </p>
 <p>
  Based on what has been revealed so far for
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
  </em>
  , Sam has somehow been called back into action, despite his decision at the end of the first game to live an isolated life and focus on raising Lou. In the footage, Sam can be seen traversing various environments in the same way that he did in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , meaning the first game's gameplay loop is set to return. That being said, there is reason to believe that, whereas the first game focused on Sam's task of reconnecting America through a physical journey, the sequel's story might be more psychological than physical.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="death-stranding-2-39-s-story-appears-to-shift-from-physical-to-psychological">
  Death Stranding 2's Story Appears to Shift From Physical to Psychological
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-234541595" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-234541595" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-234541595" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-234541595" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-234541595-img" id="article-gallery-1-234541595">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-234541595" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1545068049">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="while-death-stranding-was-about-physical-traversal-the-sequel-may-be-about-psychological-warfare">
  While Death Stranding Was About Physical Traversal, the Sequel May Be About Psychological Warfare
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  was all about physical traversal, to the point that probably about 98% of its gameplay involved traveling somewhere. After all, Sam's responsibility was to reconnect America through using his ability to make physical delivery runs between locations. However, now that America has been reconnected following the events of
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , it may not make sense for
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's narrative to primarily focus on what Sam is capable of accomplishing through making deliveries. Instead,
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's story might be less about the physical challenges that come with rebuilding and more about the psychological toll of the journey.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hideo Kojima is known for his deep, introspective storytelling, and
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  is a perfect example of that.
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , though, already appears as though it will delve even deeper into the psyche, especially given its subtitle, "On the Beach." After all, the Beach in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  is described as a reflection of the subconscious, so
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  is likely to emphasize psychological warfare even more than its predecessor. This will prove especially true if a substantial part of
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's story actually plays out on the Beach itself.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     This doesn't mean the delivery gameplay loop will be lost entirely in
     <em>
      Death Stranding 2
     </em>
     , only that it might have less to do with the story than it did in the first game. If a part of
     <em>
      Death Stranding 2
     </em>
     's gameplay sees players regularly returning to the Beach, it could involve them intentionally putting themselves in harm's way, as Sam's death would send him to the Beach.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="death-stranding-2-39-s-story-may-be-more-personal-than-the-first-game">
  Death Stranding 2's Story May Be More Personal Than the First Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  Should
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  get even more introspective than its predecessor, it could be a far more personal story than the first game. While the first
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  was largely about Sam reconnecting America and had his character arc developing alongside that,
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's story structure could be the opposite of that. In other words, rather than
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's story being about Sam's purpose, it might instead be all about Sam himself, as well as
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  's other characters. This would, as a result, make it a more psychological story than a physical one.
 </p>
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
  </em>
  embraces an even more introspective narrative than its predecessor, it has the potential to offer a much different experience from the first game while still maintaining its themes. Where
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  was a journey of physical reconnection, its sequel may shift the focus even further inward, exploring the lasting effects of Sam's past and the deeper implications of the Beach as a psychological battleground.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
