<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How To Find Dr. Garrow In Atomfall</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/how-find-dr-garrow-atomfall-location/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Out of all the characters you can meet in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Atomfall
   </strong>
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   Dr. Garrow
  </strong>
  may be the most mysterious. Her involvement in the experiments that led to the events of
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  is often shrouded in secrecy. Many documents detailing her work are redacted, so if you want answers from her, you're going to have to find her.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Locating Dr. Garrow requires finding a downed helicopter, working with the military, and staging a prison break. Here's how to follow the trail and speak with this enigmatic scientist.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-find-dr-garrow-in-atomfall">
  How to Find Dr. Garrow In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-398724065" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-398724065" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-398724065" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-398724065" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-398724065-img" id="article-gallery-1-398724065">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-398724065" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2106932569">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   In Casterfell Woods, there will be a helicopter crash that can be found at the coordinates 24.9 E, 88.3 N.
  </strong>
  Upon investigating this crash, you'll find an audio recording that Garrow made titled "Log: Mayday." She'll mention how she's the sole survivor of the crash and that she's heading to a nearby village to seek help. She
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   refers to
   <strong>
    Wyndham Village
   </strong>
   ,
  </span>
  where you need to go next.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, Garrow will not be in the village. You'll need to travel to the
  <strong>
   Village Hall, which is located at 33.4 E, 79.3 N in Wyndham Village.
  </strong>
  Inside will be the leader of the Protocol military unit,
  <strong>
   Captain Sims.
  </strong>
  He'll question you about your origins and ask for information.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Various side quests occur in Wyndham Village, such as a murder in St. Katherine's Church or what's happening at the village bakery.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  If you cooperate with Sims and give him intel about either of these leads,
  <strong>
   he will reveal that he had Dr. Garrow imprisoned at the Skethermoor Prison
  </strong>
  for tampering with their defenses. He will then give you clearance to enter the prison and interrogate Dr. Garrow.
  <strong>
   This prison can be found at coordinates 41.1 E, 70.8 N in the Skethermoor region.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-free-dr-garrow-from-skethermoor-prison">
  How To Free Dr. Garrow From Skethermoor Prison
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-225749734" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-225749734" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-225749734" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-225749734" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-225749734-img" id="article-gallery-2-225749734">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-225749734" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1975902709">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When you enter Skethermoor Prison, it's a good idea to be on your best behavior. This place is swarming with Protocol soldiers, and there's a B.A.R.D. Robot that guards the jail cells.
  <strong>
   Dr. Garrow will be held in the Loading Bay on the lower level of the prison
  </strong>
  , which is being used to imprison dangerous individuals in solitary confinement.
 </p>
 <p>
  When you reach Dr. Garrow, you can ask her a few questions. If you want to work with her to get out of the quarantine zone, she'll tell you that you need to let her out of her cell by using the controls in the
  <strong>
   Master Control Room
  </strong>
  . However, this room won't be accessible as you must reroute power to the door to reach the control console.
 </p>
 <p>
  To do this, you'll need to find a tool called the
  <strong>
   Signal Redirector
  </strong>
  , which is how Dr. Garrow was able to deactivate the Protocol's machinery. She will tell you that it was taken away from her by the soldiers, and you need to retrieve it.
  <strong>
   It's stored in the Security Room, to the left of the entrance to the Loading Bay.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  There will be a storage area in this room, where you will find the Signal Redirector and some other items worth picking up. One such item is the
  <strong>
   Security Keycard
  </strong>
  , which you'll need in addition to the Redirector. Be sure to grab that, too.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now that you have the Signal Redirector,
  <strong>
   head across from the Security Room to find the Master Control Room.
  </strong>
  It will be locked, but
  <strong>
   you can crawl through a hole in the wall to the right.
  </strong>
  Once you're in, you can open up the Electric B Room with the Security Keycard to obtain the Firearms Mastery Manual, which will grant you the ability to learn skills related to wielding guns.
 </p>
 <p>
  Then,
  <strong>
   you'll need to use the Signal Redirector on an electrical box with a yellow light. Aim the Redirector at the box, then use it to reroute power to the door to the Control Room.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Use the Security Keycard to get inside the Control Room. There will be a case on a desk containing a Training Stimulant and the crafting recipe for an Explosive Lure. Then head up some stairs to find a
  <strong>
   console with a lever on it.
  </strong>
  Prepare yourself for some combat, as pulling this lever
  <strong>
   will release all prisoners, including Dr. Garrow
  </strong>
  . Unsurprisingly, this will anger the Protocol and turn the soldiers against you. This will include the B.A.R.D Robot on the upper level.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_19">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     There is a Pneumatic Tube in the Control Room. If you need to store or retrieve any items, you should do so before freeing Dr. Garrow.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pull the lever, and Dr. Garrow will be freed from her cell.
  </strong>
  However, don't expect her to help you in the ensuing prison riot, as she'll escape through an entrance to The Interchange that will be locked when you approach it. You'll now have to fight your way out of the prison and the Protocol Camp outside to escape to safety.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you escape the prison,
  <strong>
   you can find Dr. Garrow in the Central Processor room inside The Interchange,
  </strong>
  where you can ask her even more questions that she'll likely refuse to answer.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Triumphant Light Cards That Changed Pokemon TCG Pocket's Meta</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ptcgp-pokemon-pocket-triumphant-light-meta-change-cards-explainer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Triumphant Light miniset dominates the meta by enhancing multiple established decks significantly.
     </li>
     <li>
      Cards like Crobat and Sudowoodo introduce new synergies and counter strategies, reshaping the meta.
     </li>
     <li>
      Impactful new cards like Irida and Arceus ex from Triumphant Light usher in new successful deck archetypes.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket'
   </em>
  </strong>
  s Triumphant Light could be considered the most impactful miniset since the game's launch. To put that in perspective, the previous miniset, Mythical Island, only managed to improve a couple of already successful decks. And none of those enhanced decklists were significantly promoted or demoted.
 </p>
 <p>
  This isn't the case with the Triumphant Light miniset, as its release has done it all: It has relegated some dominant setups, has pushed a few low-ranking decks to the top, and has opened up new synergies that were not possible before.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   TCG Pocket
  </em>
  players may wonder which cards from Triumphant Light have had the biggest impact on the metagame. The following list points out some of them and explains why they are the most influential cards in the A2a set.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-list-39-s-criteria-and-stat-calculations">
  The List's Criteria and Stat Calculations
 </h3>
 <p>
  Any Pokemon, Supporter, Item, or Tool card that has somehow enhanced a deck or introduced strong new synergies has been selected for this list and ranked by its impact on the metagame.
 </p>
 <p>
  The stats shown under each entry have been extracted from recent
  <em>
   TCG Pocket
  </em>
  tournaments. These numbers may change and could differ slightly from those on tournament-tracking sites like Limitless TCG.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="crobat">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Crobat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-darkrai-ex-that-needs-no-energy">
  A Darkrai ex That Needs No Energy
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="crobat in pokemon tcg pocket." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/crobat-pokemon-tcg-pocket.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Meta Share
   </strong>
   : ~ 2%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Win Rate
   </strong>
   : ~ 48.5%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Darkrai ex in the Space-Time Smackdown expansion introduced long-range damage as a meta strategy. With its unique ability, Darkrai ex dealt 20 damage to the enemy's Active Pokemon whenever a Dark-type Energy was attached to it—an ideal move for inflicting Bench damage. However, Triumphant Light's Crobat proved that there's a better way to do the same.
 </p>
 <p>
  A2a Crobat comes with a Link Ability that is activated when Arceus or Arceus ex is in play. When activated, Crobat deals 30 chip damage to the enemy's Active Pokemon from either the Bench or Active Spot, without needing extra Energy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Crobat's alliance with Arceus ex illustrates its significant impact on the metagame, contributing to one of the top-performing decks in the game, with an impressive 48.5% win rate.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sudowoodo">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Sudowoodo
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-new-anti-meta-card">
  The New Anti-Meta Card
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1450172151" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1450172151" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1450172151" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1450172151" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1450172151-img" id="article-gallery-1-1450172151">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1450172151" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-798296757">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Meta Share
   </strong>
   : ~ 52.5%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Win Rate
   </strong>
   : ~ 9.5%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Sudowoodo has undoubtedly been one of the most influential cards in the Triumphant Light era. This anti-meta Pokemon has perfect synergy with the previous set's overlooked Fighting-type duo—Rampardos &amp; Lucario—making it the best response to the current top-performing decks, especially Arcues ex lineups.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes Sudowoodo an excellent counter card is its 30-damage advantage against ex cards. Since its base damage is 20, Sudowoodo does 50 damage to ex cards, which goes up to 70 if the defending Pokemon is weak to the Fighting type. But that's not all. As a Fighting Pokemon, Sudowoodo also synergizes with Lucario's buff, increasing its potential damage output to 110 with just one Energy!
 </p>
 <p>
  Sudowoodo's addition to the game boosted Rampardos &amp; Lucario's setup to the top of the meta, making it the second-best in PvP and tournaments. For context, Sudowoodo increased the duo's meta share by +500%.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_24">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     During the Space-Time Smackdown era, Rampardos and Lucario accounted for just 1.17% of the metagame, while Sudowoodo helped expand that to 7.47%.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="irida">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Irida
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-best-healer-of-the-current-meta">
  The Best Healer of the Current Meta
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1921169736" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1921169736" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1921169736" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1921169736" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1921169736-img" id="article-gallery-2-1921169736">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1921169736" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-382695917">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Meta Share
   </strong>
   : ~ 3.5%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Win Rate
   </strong>
   : ~ 47%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket'
  </em>
  s Supporter cards are known to shake up the meta, As demonstrated by Cyrus in the Space-Time Smackdown set— Which led many to call it overpowered. It's no surprise, then, that one of the most influential cards from Triumphant Light is the new healer support card, Irida.
 </p>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-0c089090afb13f15" id="emaki-video-player-0c089090afb13f15">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are a couple of unique things about Irida that enable her to build creative synergies (e.g., her synergy with Leafeon ex &amp; Celebi ex). For one, Irida heals any Pokemon with at least one Water-type Energy attached, regardless of its type. Secondly, Irida's healing effect is not limited to a single card, unlike most previous healers. Instead, she heals all Pokemon in play that meet her requirements. For example, if the player has four Pokemon with Water-type Energy, Irida will heal 40 damage from each, totaling up to 160 HP.
 </p>
 <h2 id="leafeon-ex">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Leafeon ex
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-grass-type-with-water-type-synergy">
  A Grass-type with Water-type Synergy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-165054184" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-165054184" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-165054184" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-165054184" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-165054184-img" id="article-gallery-3-165054184">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-165054184" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-14729766">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Meta Share
   </strong>
   : ~ 3.5%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Win Rate
   </strong>
   : ~ 47%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Leafeon ex took the place of Exeggutor ex in Celebi ex setups. But there's more to it: Leafeon ex's Energy-generating ability actually led to the formation of a new Grass-type meta that's surprisingly powered with Water-type Energy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Currently, players are pairing up Leafeon ex with Celebi ex, but instead of the usual Grass-type Energy, they use Water-type. This is because both Leafeon ex and Celebi ex need only one Grass-type Energy to function, with the rest of their requirements being Colorless. Additionally, Leafeon ex can easily supplement this need by using its ability and freeing up the Energy Zone for another Energy type—in this case, Water.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ramping Leafeon ex and Celebi ex with Water-type Energy allows the new healer, Irida, to synergize with them. Irida enhances the main Pokemon's longevity, keeping them on the board long enough to outlast opponents.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="arceus-ex">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Arceus ex
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-destroyer-of-darkrai">
  The Destroyer of Darkrai
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2042357462" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2042357462" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2042357462" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2042357462" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2042357462-img" id="article-gallery-4-2042357462">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2042357462" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1111104472">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Meta Share
   </strong>
   : 53.5%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Top Deck's Win Rate
   </strong>
   : 20%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Unsurprisingly, the most meta-breaking card from the Triumphant Light has been the miniset's face: Arceus ex. This Pokemon ended Darkrai ex and Magnezon's reign over
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  's meta in a few days, becoming the most popular deck with a 54% win rate.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arceus ex owes its success to two factors. As a Colorless Pokemon, it has a broad range of synergies, and Dialga ex's Energy-generating ability perfectly complements its ultimate attack. With the ability to discount retreats, Shaymin has also played a critical role in Arceus ex's rise to the top. But the duo of Dialga ex and Arceus ex has proven effective even without this practical Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once the player puts Dialga ex in the Active Spot and places Arceus ex on the Bench, only two Steel-type Energies are needed to start dealing damage and ramping Arceus ex. Dialga ex's ability, Metallic Turbo, allows the player to deal 30 damage and generate two Energies for another Pokemon—which is clearly going to be Arceus ex.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Solve The St. Katherine's Church Lead In Atomfall</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/trust-morris-atomfall-st-katherine-lead-church-solution-solve-how/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Atomfall's
   </strong>
  </em>
  Wyndham Village would be rather peaceful if it wasn't full of Protocol soldiers harassing its citizens. As if a military occupation wasn't bad enough, there's been a murder in the village, and you may be the only one competent enough to solve it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   The St. Katherine's Church Lead
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  has quite a few players involved, as well as a few different resolutions. Here's how to find the murderer and get the best rewards.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-start-the-st-katherine-39-s-church-lead-in-atomfall">
  How To Start The St. Katherine's Church Lead In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="atomfall vicar mchenry standing over maisie's corpse" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall_20250319133555.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   St. Katherine's Church is located within Wyndham Village at the coordinates 33.0 E, 78.8 N on the map.
  </strong>
  Upon entering the church, you'll see
  <strong>
   Vicar McHenry
  </strong>
  and a parishioner named Pamela Shaw standing over the murdered corpse of a woman named
  <strong>
   Maisie Higgins.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Talk to the vicar, and he'll want you to keep the murder quiet as he doesn't want the Protocol to get involved. Neither McHenry nor Pamela will be much help,
  <strong>
   but if you interact with Maisie's corpse, you'll find a Bloodied Note.
  </strong>
  It'll be from Maisie and mention how she was investigating someone up by
  <strong>
   Mereview Hotel from inside a nearby cottage
  </strong>
  . Since that's the only clue about who the murderer is, it's time to head over there.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-investigate-maisie-39-s-murder-in-atomfall">
  How To Investigate Maisie's Murder In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1215253346" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1215253346" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1215253346" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1215253346" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1215253346-img" id="article-gallery-1-1215253346">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1215253346" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1393188510">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Mereview Hotel is located in the northwest part of Wyndham Village. However, that's not where we need to go.
  <strong>
   You need to head to a cottage near the hotel located at the coordinates 31.4 E, 82.1 N.
  </strong>
  You'll be trespassing when you enter this building since the Protocol has labeled the cottage as condemned. Be cautious and sneak inside the building.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   You'll find a note titled "Recent Movements."
  </strong>
  This will be written by Vicar McHenry with instructions for Maisie to be on the lookout for people acting strange. Maisie will have scribbled notes of her own saying that an unidentified man had gone past the hotel, over a stream, and into a rat-infested cellar.
 </p>
 <p>
  The note will tell you this man went right,
  <strong>
   but you'll actually need to go past the hotel and to the left and crawl under a fence. Then head over the stream, head to the right up some stone steps, and there will be an abandoned building on the right.
  </strong>
  There will be some
  <strong>
   blue cellar doors
  </strong>
  on the other side of it that will lead you to the
  <strong>
   Brewery Cellar.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  As the note said,
  <strong>
   this cellar will be infested with rats who can poison you if they do too much damage.
  </strong>
  Use a melee weapon to take them out, and then make sure to grab the
  <strong>
   crafting recipe for Molotov Cocktail
  </strong>
  s on the wall.
  <strong>
   Behind the wall that the recipe was nailed to is a hole you can crawl under.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  On the other side will be a note titled
  <strong>
   "Kill The One They Call Maisie."
  </strong>
  This note will reveal that the killer is
  <strong>
   Morris Wick
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   the owner of the Village Shop.
  </strong>
  He's been working for the Druids of Casterfell Woods, who ordered the killing of Maisie because she was spying on Morris.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_15">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Before you leave the cellar, there will be a room that's been boarded up. You can crawl underneath the boards, and on the other side will be a B.A.R.D. Crate with a Training Stimulant inside, as well as another note titled "Captain Sims Doesn't Suspect A Thing" that further incriminates Morris.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-solve-the-st-katherine-39-s-church-lead-in-atomfall">
  How To Solve The St. Katherine's Church Lead In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="atomfall st katherine's church lead endings" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/vlcsnap-2025-03-24-17h17m12s305.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  We now know who Maisie's murderer is. However, that doesn't mean that Vicar McHenry is completely innocent. He was taking money from the villagers and getting Maisie to spy on them. He also offers you a reward for "taking care of" Morris, although he never explicitly asks you to murder him. All that's left to do is to go to the Village Shop and confront Morris.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a few ways to resolve the St. Katherine's Church Lead that will earn you different rewards. Here's how they turn out:
 </p>
 <h3 id="kill-morris">
  Kill Morris
 </h3>
 <p>
  After revealing to Morris that you know he killed Maisie, you can threaten to report him to the Protocol. This will enrage him and make him attack you. If you kill him, you can loot his body for some items and then report back to Vicar McHenry. He'll thank you for finding a resolution and give you the
  <strong>
   Vicar's Key.
  </strong>
  Head upstairs, and you'll find a locked chest. Use the key to find an
  <strong>
   Atomic Battery
  </strong>
  inside. There will also be a note titled "Fruitful Trade" that shows how the vicar acquired the battery.
 </p>
 <h3 id="banish-morris-from-the-village">
  Banish Morris From The Village
 </h3>
 <p>
  If you tell Morris to leave the village, he'll eventually do so after some protesting. From here, things go the same way as killing Morris, with you returning to the vicar for a reward. It's unknown if Morris shows up anywhere else.
 </p>
 <h3 id="bargain-with-morris">
  Bargain With Morris
 </h3>
 <p>
  If you choose to bargain with or pragmatically let Morris get away with the murder, he'll give you the
  <strong>
   Crafting Manual
  </strong>
  , which will teach you new skills related to crafting. He'll also tell you where to find
  <strong>
   Mother Jago
  </strong>
  , an important NPC located in Casterfell Woods. This solution will anger Vicar McHenry, who will refuse to have anything else to do with you. However, aside from upsetting the vicar, there doesn't seem to be a downside to trusting Morris.
 </p>
 <h3 id="report-the-murder-amp-morris-to-captain-sims">
  Report The Murder &amp; Morris To Captain Sims
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Captain Sims
  </strong>
  is the leader of the Protocol.
  <strong>
   He's stationed at the Village Hall.
  </strong>
  At any point during this questline, you can go to him and report the murder. At that point, Protocol soldiers will be stationed inside the church, and Vicar McHenry will again angrily refuse to talk to you. You can also report Morris, which will see him get carted away and his shop taken over by soldiers. If you choose this option,
  <strong>
   you won't get the Vicar's Key or the Crafting Manual
  </strong>
  . However, you will earn Captain Sims' trust, which is important if you want to gain access to the Skethermoor Prison
  <strong>
   .
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h3 id="getting-all-the-rewards">
  Getting All The Rewards
 </h3>
 <p>
  There is a way to get every reward from this lead. First, go to Morris and let him get away with the murder to get the Crafting Manual as well as Mother Jago's location. Then, report back to Vicar McHenry. If you really want the Atomic Battery, you can kill the vicar and loot the key off of his body.
 </p>
 <p>
  After that, you can still go to Captain Sims and report the murder to get on his good side. It's not the most moral of options, but it does score you a battery, some new skills, and potentially advances two main storylines all at the same time.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds Player Shares Helpful Chart for the Game's Food System</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monster-hunter-wilds-chart-food-system-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      One Monster Hunter Wilds fan created a helpful chart that breaks down all the benefits of the game's food system.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can take part in a promotion to link their Capcom ID to Monster Hunter Wilds to receive a free item pack.
     </li>
     <li>
      Many fans are looking forward to Title Update 1 and the content it will add to the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </em>
  </strong>
  player has created a helpful chart breaking down the intricacies of the game's food system to help other gamers receive the maximum amount of benefits when they cook meals. Players looking to get the most out of their gaming experience may want to consider linking their Capcom ID to
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , as there's currently a promotion that rewards gamers with an item pack for doing so.
 </p>
 <p>
  Many fans are eagerly awaiting the release of Title Update 1 for
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , which will introduce the fearsome monster Mizutsune, a multiplayer hub, and more. Capcom has planned a showcase for March 25, giving gamers their first look at what's on the way in the popular action RPG. Some people are hoping to see a form of player housing added to the title, as they would like to be able to display trophies and show off endemic life that they've managed to capture. These were features included in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter: World
  </em>
  , which means Capcom could be planning to add them at some point in the future.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent post on Reddit, Dibilowas shared a helpful chart breaking down every aspect of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  ' food system. The infographic details all the benefits fans can expect to receive when choosing a ration, primary ingredient, and secondary ingredient. In addition to breaking down all the ingredients used when cooking a meal for oneself, the chart also gives players a look at the various buffs granted when sitting down to eat a meal with one of the game's various factions. They even went over every random skill gamers can benefit from, as village meals grant players two random skills alongside their usual buffs.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-wilds-rsquo-complex-food-system-is-simplified-with-a-helpful-chart">
  Monster Hunter Wilds’ Complex Food System Is Simplified With a Helpful Chart
 </h2>
 <p>
  Many fans were excited to see
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  ' cooking benefits broken down in such a simple way, with some thanking Dibilowas for going through the trouble of making the chart. Several people joked that they never had a real grasp of what all the different ingredients did and simply cooked whatever was available to them.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-158970789" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-158970789" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-158970789" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-158970789" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-158970789-img" id="article-gallery-1-158970789">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-158970789" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2071151795">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Some players have questioned whether cooking is worth it in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , as preparing the best meals often involves going out into the open-world to collect rare ingredients. While it may not seem beneficial to cook elaborate meals during the game's main campaign, numerous fans have claimed that cooking is worth the trouble when facing off against endgame monsters. With so much content to enjoy and the Title Update 1 on the way, many gamers are feeling optimistic about the future of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition: How To Change Class</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xenoblade-chronicles-x-how-switch-classes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   Changing classes in
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition
   </em>
  </strong>
  is crucial to enhancing characters and sustaining game progress, which opens up new abilities and boosts their combat potential. Also, the mechanics of this JRPG let players craft unique builds that offer a strong edge during many fights on Mira, ensuring broader strategic options.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  So, understanding how class switching works helps players refine their approach, be it offensive, defensive, or support. Also, knowing each class’s specific benefits is key to overcoming tricky foes and boosting progression, so even though the process is easy, discovering how to change classes in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is essential for leveling up and trying different playstyles.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-change-classes-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x">
  How to Change Classes In Xenoblade Chronicles X?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Class change menu showing party members’ levels and ranks in Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/class-change-menu-showing-party-members-levels-and-ranks-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fortunately, the process of changing classes in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is simple, though some prerequisites apply on the first attempt. It is necessary to reach level 10 as Drifter, the starting class, before unlocking other paths; once that is done, follow the steps below to pick the new option that best suits the character:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Press + on the controller
  </li>
  <li>
   Select the Party option, then Classes
  </li>
  <li>
   In that menu, choose the new class
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Once players reach level 10 with Drifter in this JRPG, three paths become available: Striker, Commando, or Enforcer. Each one has its own playstyle and sets of abilities, so it is wise to try each until finding a favorite, though one of the best starter options in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition
  </em>
  is Striker, due to decent DPS and a straightforward approach.
 </p>
 <h3 id="why-change-classes-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x">
  Why Change Classes In Xenoblade Chronicles X?
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Narukami character stats and Enforcer class arts and skills displayed in Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/narukami-character-stats-and-enforcer-class-arts-and-skills-displayed-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Besides trying different paths, changing classes in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is vital for leveling characters during this JRPG. While the protagonist’s level determines which gear is usable and unlocks some quests, the class level grants access to new Skill Arts, and they increase overall damage and expand strategic variety in combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  Classes also evolve throughout the adventure, which unlocks fresh routes once they reach higher ranks. For instance, when Striker hits its max rank, two new paths appear, so it is wise to track progression to avoid wasted EXP, and remember that each protagonist’s class also decides which weapons they can use and which Skill Arts they have access to.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Switching classes in Xenoblade Chronicles X doesn’t have any cost and can be done at any time outside of battle.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Another key detail about classes in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition
  </em>
  is that once a class hits its max tier, or Tier 3, the protagonist gains full expertise with that weapon. Afterward, that weapon remains usable even if the new path does not include it as part of the Standard Armors, which grants more customization for the Cross.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-change-classes-for-allies-in-xenoblade-chronicles-x">
  How To Change Classes For Allies In Xenoblade Chronicles X?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2047143703" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2047143703" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2047143703" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2047143703" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2047143703-img" id="article-gallery-1-2047143703">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2047143703" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1493099506">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike the JRPG protagonist, who can switch to any class, allied NPCs lack that same freedom. Generally, it is impossible to change classes for party members in
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X Definitive Edition
  </em>
  because they stay locked to the class they start with when joining the party, and they remain in that role until the end.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, that does not mean allies are weaker or less flexible than the protagonist. Even with fewer options, they gain two exclusive abilities known as Signatures Arts, so even if two characters share the same class, like Elma and Neilnail, each one features a distinct playstyle with its own skills and builds.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
