<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>WoW: The War Within - Great Vault, Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Endgame content is where you can get the best possible gear that is currently available in
  <strong>
   <em>
    World of Warcraft
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Whether you are doing Raids, Mythic+, or Delves, this how you improve your character's power once you've hit level cap. Yet no matter how good you are, there is one thing that will always stand between you and endgame loot: RNG (short for random number generation).
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The gear that drops is entirely random. As such, you are at the mercy of whether something that drops is an upgrade or not. Fortunately, there is a way to alleviate the pain caused by RNG and that is through the Great Vault.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on March 12, 2025 by Paul Woodward:
   </strong>
  </em>
  The Great Vault gets updated every time a new Season starts. Whether you are a dedicated Mythic+ dungeon runner, a raider, or someone who just likes to do Delves, there is always a reason to fill out as many slots in the Great Vault as possible. Even if there is nothing you want, you can add another socket to your gear or get some upgrade materials if needed.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="great-vault-explained">
  Great Vault, Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="wow great vault explained update 1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wow-great-vault-explained-update-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Great Vault has been around since
  <em>
   Shadowlands
  </em>
  , and it is essentially a weekly reward system. The location of the Great Vault varies, but for
  <em>
   The War Within
  </em>
  , it is located at the bank in Dornogal. When you right-click on the Great Vault, you will see a menu with three rows with the following information:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Raids
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Defeat two Raid Bosses (World bosses don't count)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Defeat four Raid Bosses
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Defeat six Raid Bosses
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Dungeons
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete one Heroic, Mythic, or Timewalking Dungeon
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete four Heroic, Mythic, or Timewalking Dungeons
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete eight Heroic, Mythic, or Timewalking Dungeons
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       World
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete two Delves or World Activities
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete four Delves or World Activities
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Complete eight Delves or World Activities
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  When you complete one of the objectives above, an item from the loot table of that activity is added to the Great Vault. This is indicated by the check mark and glowing sphere as depicted in the image above. The item level of each item is determined based on the difficulty of the activity you completed. The item level can be improved by completing activities at a higher difficulty.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, say you killed two bosses in the most recent raid on LFR difficulty (Liberation of Undermine in Season 2). The result will be an item with an item level of 624 being added to the Great Vault. Later that week, you go into Liberation of Undermine with your guild and kill two bosses on Normal difficulty. This will upgrade your previously unlocked item in the Great Vault to item level 636.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite being able to add items to the Great Vault, you won't be able to claim them until the next weekly reset. At that point, you will be able to pick one item. The amount of items in the Great Vault will depend on how many activities you complete or raid bosses you killed. If you complete six of the nine objectives, you will have six items to choose from. Alternatively, if you did everything you will have nine items to choose from.
 </p>
 <h2 id="what-to-do-if-nothing-is-an-upgrade">
  What To Do If Nothing Is An Upgrade
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="wow the war within great vault explained 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/wow-the-war-within-great-vault-explained-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As the Season progresses, it is entirely possible to end up in a situation where all of your available rewards are not upgrades. If that happens, you can choose the reward at the bottom of the menu, and you will get Algari Token of Merit instead. You can earn up to six Algari Tokens of Merit per week. Algari Token of Merit can be used to purchase items from Ardgaz, the NPC that stands right next to the Great Vault. His inventory is as follows.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Item Name
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Cost
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Chest of Gold
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2 Algari Tokens of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Golden Valorstone
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1 Algari Token of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Triumphant Satchel of Carved Crests
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1 Algari Token of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Celebratory Pack of Runed Crests
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2 Algari Tokens of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       S.A.D.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6 Algari Tokens of Merit
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon TCG Heat Wave Arena Cards Leak</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-heat-wave-arena-cards-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon TCG leak reveals upcoming Heat Wave Arena cards with Cynthia, Garchomp, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Leak includes 29 secret cards with stunning art of popular Pokemon like Rotom and Shaymin.
     </li>
     <li>
      Destined Rivals, the next expansion, will follow Heat Wave Arena with 182 cards, including new trainers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak has revealed cards in anticipation of the release of Heat Wave Arena. Coming out in Japan on March 14, this will be the ninth
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  Japanese subset part of the
  <em>
   Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  era. It will come as a booster box with 30 packs featuring Cynthia and Garchomp, Ethan and Ho-Oh, and Arven and Mabosstiff.
 </p>
 <p>
  Previously, another
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  leak revealed some of the upcoming cards, showing beautiful artwork highlighting Cynthia, one of the franchise's most beloved characters, and her Pokemon. Weeks later, cards from the new subset were revealed, showing impressive cards such as the Cyndaquil evolution line, Garchomp ex, and Mabostiff. Now, a new
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  leak brings even more information about what the upcoming subset has in store for fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  PokeBeach has shared a leak revealing all 29 secret cards fans will encounter in Heat Wave Arena. Reinforcing previously leaked information, the set will feature Cynthia's Roserade full art card, with more full art cards of other popular Pokemon such as Rotom and Shaymin. Another part of the leak that catches the eye is the presence of several cards of well-known trainers with their Pokemon, such as Ethan's Typhlosion and Ho-Oh, Ethan's Mabosstiff and Greedent, and an impressive gold variant of Cynthia's Garchomp ex.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-leak-reveals-heat-wave-arena-39-s-coveted-secret-rares-cards">
  Pokemon GO Leak Reveals Heat Wave Arena's Coveted Secret Rares Cards
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-776936054" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-776936054" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-776936054" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-776936054" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-776936054-img" id="article-gallery-1-776936054">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-776936054" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2020696530">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While Heat Wave Arena hits shelves in Japan later this week, players in the west will have to wait a little longer. The new cards will be part of the
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  Destined Rivals set, which will be released on May 30. This will be the tenth major expansion of Gen 9, and in addition to the Heat Wave Arena cards, it will have the ones from the Glory of the Rocket Gang expansion, and from the Starter Sets Marnie's Morpeko &amp; Grimmsnarl ex and Steven's Beldum &amp; Metagross ex, bringing the expansion to a total of 182 cards excluding the Secret ones.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the meantime, fans will see a new set arrive in the coming weeks. On March 28, Journey Together, the ninth English-language
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  expansion of the
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  cycle, will be released, bringing more than 180 cards for players to collect. This set will see the return of Pokemon's Trainer cards, focusing on the pocket monsters owned by N, Iono, Lillie, and Hop. This will be the first time since EX Team Magma vs Team Aqua that the mechanic has appeared in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25 Seems to Have Cut Different Underground Match Variants</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-underground-match-variants-triple-threat-fatal-four-way-removed/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A PC user has uncovered hidden Underground match types, including Triple Threat and Fatal Four-Way.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans hope modding will allow updates for WWE 2K25, such as fixing typos, adding new content, and accessing unreleased assets in the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Several variations of
  <em>
   <strong>
    WWE 2K25
   </strong>
  </em>
  's Underground match look to have been made inaccessible in the game. As many players have opted to purchase early access to
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  via its special editions, many hidden details have been discovered by the most eager WWE games supporters. These discoveries include upcoming MyFaction characters, removed Superstars, and even assets that were originally planned for the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  One new feature that made it to the game is
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's Underground match. It's a slight variant of the one-on-one match that sees ring ropes removed and winning conditions being limited to KO or submission. While it hasn't really been a staple on WWE television in a while, its inclusion in the game has been welcomed by many, especially those looking for new features. And although the actual Underground matches that have happened on WWE TV were limited to one-on-one bouts, it seems the developers of
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  were exploring other possibilities.
 </p>
 <p>
  Twitter user dot_discovery shared their findings of a Triple Threat and a Fatal Four-Way Underground match hidden deep within
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's code on the PC. While the discovery is still in its early stages, dot_discovery assumes that content or modes like these could be possible additions to the next iteration of the game. As dot_discovery normally deals with the modding of games, the only way to access the secret variants of Underground is by using a tool on the PC. Fans from the comments section were disappointed that additional match types from
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  had been cut, especially since more options meant even more possibilities.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wwe-2k25-underground-match-types-that-have-been-cut">
  WWE 2K25 Underground Match Types That Have Been Cut
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-828459120" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-828459120" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-828459120" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-828459120" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-828459120-img" id="article-gallery-1-828459120">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-828459120" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-445336751">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Triple Threat Underground Match
  </li>
  <li>
   Fatal Four-Way Underground Match
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  In addition to these findings, dot_discovery also shared that there's a possibility to replace the NPCs surrounding the mat. The extent of currently available mods is still unfounded, but many fans are already hoping that they will have free rein over all aspects of the game. One specific area of concern is the addition or replacement of in-game graphics. With players finding many weird typos in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , the hope is that modding could help update many of the misspelled logos.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, as the case may be, PC players are already in a different boat with regard to cross-platform connectivity. While PCs may have access to these hidden contents via specific tools, console players will probably never be able to even see the said discoveries. This is partly because of several concerns regarding modding and hacking. Fans already know this to be part of the reason why
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's The Island is not available on PC. The PC's possibilities could otherwise expose content that was not intended to be accessed at the moment. Whether intended for this year's game or the following year's, the WWE Universe will have to wait to see if a patch to give access to the Underground match variants or other hidden assets will ever arrive.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official Resident Evil Plushies Give Cute Makeover to Iconic Monsters</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/resident-evil-plushies-cute-monsters-licker-dog-hunk/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Resident Evil has released plushies of iconic monsters in a cute design, unlike their terrifying game counterparts.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans are eager for new remakes and additions to the Resident Evil franchise, with hopes for Resident Evil Code: Veronica.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new plushies based on the Licker, zombie dog, and HUNK will be released on March 15 for $7.40 USD each.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Resident Evil
   </strong>
  </em>
  has unveiled three new plushies based on two iconic creepy monsters and a long-standing character. The plushies give an amusingly cute overhaul to the iconic
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  designs, turning them into something soft and cuddly instead of terrifying and life-threatening.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  is rapidly approaching its 30th anniversary, and fans are more than ready to see what the future holds for the franchise. Capcom has been readily revisiting the classics in recent years, releasing full remakes for
  <em>
   Resident Evil 2
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   3
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   4
  </em>
  , while also adding new major hits to the series with
  <em>
   Resident Evil 7
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Resident Evil Village
  </em>
  . Gamers are curious to see what - if any - remakes are in the future for the franchise, with hopes for a
  <em>
   Resident Evil Code: Veronica
  </em>
  remake being high on the list. These plushies, however, take some inspiration from the first two games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Capcom has revealed three plushies from
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  , based on the Licker, zombie dog, and HUNK. The three new plushies are part of Capcom's "Capcorom" line, and have a stackable design, with each character depicted as lying flat on their belly. All three character designs have been greatly simplified, but are still plenty recognizable. The dog zombie plush has red stripes showing off gore or exposed flesh, while the Licker has its usual visible brain, and an extended tongue hanging out of its face. Hunk wears tactical gear and has his iconic red-eye gas mask on. The three plushes are set to release on March 15, and will cost 1100 yen, or roughly $7.40 USD.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1136257645" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1136257645" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1136257645" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136257645" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136257645-img" id="article-gallery-1-1136257645">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1136257645" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1628277383">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="resident-evil-and-cute-collide">
  Resident Evil and Cute Collide
 </h2>
 <p>
  With the Licker and zombie dog typically having terrifying character designs, these plushies may strike some fans as odd, if not amusing. However, it's not the first time that
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  has become unexpectedly cute. The series hyped up the release of the
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  remake by launching a short anime series with cute pastel imagery, turning some of the most horrifying moments in the game into funny and cute ones, instead.
 </p>
 <p>
  It seems that some fans of the series enjoy these cute twists, even creating some of their own. One fan got a
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  tattoo, which may not be that surprising, but chose to get an unusual variation of Leon S. Kennedy. The
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  tattoo design turned Leon into a raccoon himself, a play on him being a member of the Raccoon City police, which came to be dubbed "Leon S. Raccoonedy."
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA Sports FC 25: Super Sub Player Items, Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ea-sports-fc-25-super-sub-player-items-explained/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What Are Super Sub Player Items In EA Sports FC 25?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Are EA Sports FC 25’s Super Sub Player Items Worth Using?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    EA Sports FC 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  aims to deliver a comprehensive football experience, allowing players to fine-tune their game strategies with the FC IQ feature. Additionally, they can make substitutions, upgrade players, and adjust other settings to optimize their squad for success in Ultimate Team competitions.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Building on this, the EA Sports team has introduced the new Super Sub Player Items feature, designed to provide a slight in-game boost to help turn the tide in crucial moments. With that in mind, here’s all you need to know about Super Sub Player Items in
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  , including how to use them effectively.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-are-super-sub-player-items-in-ea-sports-fc-25">
  What Are Super Sub Player Items In EA Sports FC 25?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="zidane and bellingham fc 25" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/zidane-and-bellingham-fc-25.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Super Sub items in
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  are players who
  <strong>
   receive full Chemistry
  </strong>
  when
  <strong>
   substituted into a match during the second half or later
  </strong>
  . Additionally, their Role+ level is
  <strong>
   boosted to Role++
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  These upgrades are designed to strengthen your Ultimate Team squad, whether you’re trying to turn around a losing match or secure a late victory, whether to climb the Divisions in Rivals, earn points in Squad Battles, or rack up wins in Champions. However, they’re also useful for more casual, non-competitive modes within Ultimate Team.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-use-super-sub-player-items-in-ea-fc-25">
  How To Use Super Sub Player Items In EA FC 25
 </h3>
 <p>
  To use the Super Sub players effectively in
  <em>
   EA FC 25
  </em>
  , you’ll need to
  <strong>
   substitute them after halftime
  </strong>
  and ensure they are placed in their
  <strong>
   primary or alternate positions
  </strong>
  for the
  <strong>
   Chemistry and Role Familiarity
  </strong>
  effects to activate correctly. The ideal scenarios for using them include
  <strong>
   refreshing your squad
  </strong>
  when the current result isn’t in your favor, securing a late win for better rewards, improving your win total, or simply maximizing your performance in Ultimate Team modes.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Make sure to swap out players with similar on-field performance to maintain your team’s strategy while maximizing the Super Sub player entry.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="are-ea-sports-fc-25-rsquo-s-super-sub-player-items-worth-using">
  Are EA Sports FC 25’s Super Sub Player Items Worth Using?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/ea-sports-fc-25-ultimate-team-tied-match-wins-explained.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since these players are
  <strong>
   most effective in the second half of a match
  </strong>
  — when you have a better understanding of your opponent’s playstyle — Super Sub items can be
  <strong>
   incredibly valuable
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  . Substituting a player who
  <strong>
   strengthens either your attack or defense
  </strong>
  can have a significant impact. Additionally, as most players lose stamina over the course of a match (except those with the Relentless+ PlayStyle, who receive a stamina boost), the strategic substitutions can enhance performance in key areas of the field. Super Subs are particularly useful in this regard, as they receive an
  <strong>
   immediate stat boost
  </strong>
  upon entering the game, allowing them to cover their assigned position more effectively.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
