<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How Dragon Age: The Veilguard May Foreshadow Mass Effect 4's Plans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/dragon-age-the-veilguard-mass-effect-4-no-dlc-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  With BioWare moving on from
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dragon Age: The Veilguard
   </em>
  </strong>
  and setting its sights on its next
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  game, the studio's development, release, and post-launch approach to the former could offer some insight into what to expect for the latter. Despite its predecessor,
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Inquisition
  </em>
  , setting a high standard for post-launch content with its Trespasser
  <em>
  </em>
  DLC in particular setting the stage for
  <em>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </em>
  itself, BioWare's confirmation that it had no similar DLC for its latest game in the series seemed surprising. However, this announcement now makes more sense, given the recent layoffs at BioWare and the studio's uncertain future.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But with BioWare also claiming that it remains committed to its long-since-teased and as-of-yet unnamed
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  , it seems that this next game in its other flagship franchise could determine this future. To add to this reassurance, BioWare's earlier statement during
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  's development that it is refocusing on single-player story-driven experiences following the failure of
  <em>
   Anthem
  </em>
  indicates that the studio is endeavoring to learn from its past. Therefore, looking back on what did and didn't work in
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  could set expectations for
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="choices-made-and-lessons-learned-from-dragon-age-the-veilguard-will-likely-shape-mass-effect-4">
  Choices Made and Lessons Learned From Dragon Age: The Veilguard Will Likely Shape Mass Effect 4
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1745038781" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1745038781" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1745038781" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1745038781" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1745038781-img" id="article-gallery-1-1745038781">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1745038781" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1341257999">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Acknowledging that
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  failed to meet EA's expectations, it was arguably wise for BioWare to move on and scrap any potential plans it had for DLC. However, as
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  joins the likes of
  <em>
   Mass Effect: Andromeda
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Anthem
  </em>
  , BioWare appears to face an uphill struggle as it pushes forward with
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  . With this in mind, the studio will likely review the decisions made during
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  's development and the lessons learned following its launch as BioWare works on its next game.
 </p>
 <p>
  This could mean that
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  will be significantly impacted by
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  , such as potential reworks to its story, characters, setting, and more. For instance,
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  drew criticism for not allowing players to import past saves from
  <em>
   DA: Inquisition
  </em>
  , suggesting the
  <em>
   Dragon Age
  </em>
  game shouldn't have been a sequel. Consequently, despite Liara's cameo in
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  's announcement trailer suggesting it will pick up from where the original trilogy left off, BioWare might want to reconsider this approach after the response it received to
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  as a direct sequel.
 </p>
 <h3 id="mass-effect-4-could-forego-dlc-thanks-to-dragon-age-the-veilguard-and-mass-effect-andromeda">
  Mass Effect 4 Could Forego DLC Thanks to Dragon Age: The Veilguard and Mass Effect: Andromeda
 </h3>
 <p>
  While DLC has played an important role in past BioWare games, such as
  <em>
   Mass Effect 3
  </em>
  's Leviathan
  <em>
  </em>
  and Citadel or
  <em>
   DA: Inquisition
  </em>
  's Trespasser, the fact that
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  didn't receive any appears to fit a trend in the studio's latest games. For example, even though
  <em>
   ME: Andromeda
  </em>
  's ending teased its potential for DLC with a Quarian ark—something that was later addressed in the
  <em>
   Mass Effect: Annihilation
  </em>
  novel—it could be that BioWare is discouraged from pursuing DLC for underperforming games. This could explain why both
  <em>
   ME: Andromeda
  </em>
  and now
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  will not receive any DLC after their mixed receptions.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it could also be that BioWare's previous DLC strategy seemed to set up its future games for failure. For instance, beyond the return of Liara in
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's Lair of the Shadow Broker
  <em>
  </em>
  or new squadmates like Zaeed, Kasumi, or Javik, DLC like Arrival
  <em>
  </em>
  or even
  <em>
   DA: Inquisiton
  </em>
  's Trespasser
  <em>
  </em>
  that directly set up a sequel have not worked out in BioWare's favor. With Arrival's poor reception and
  <em>
   DA: The Veilguard
  </em>
  falling short of expectations set by Trespasser, BioWare might be foregoing DLC with other upcoming games like
  <em>
   Mass Effect 4
  </em>
  to focus on its current games and not its potential sequels.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Warzone Code Gets You Free Calling Card and Double Weapon XP</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-warzone-double-weapon-xp-card-free-calling-card-deal-redeem/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Call of Duty: Warzone players can grab a free Calling Card and one Double Weapon XP Token by redeeming promo code KYHPCVYSNP6HY right now.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Double Weapon XP token can be activated at any time, and lasts for 30 minutes.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Calling Card tied to the promo code celebrates the upcoming return of Verdansk to Call of Duty: Warzone.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A newly shared
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Warzone
   </em>
  </strong>
  promo code grants anyone who uses it a free period of double Weapon XP, together with a themed calling card. This freebie ties into the upcoming return of Verdansk to
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Verdansk is the map that launched with the original, 2020 version of
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  . It was removed from the hit battle royale game in late 2021, when Caldera took its place.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Verdansk now confirmed to be returning to
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  , Activision is looking to celebrate the occasion with a new promo code, granting players a free Calling Card featuring the message that "Verdansk is back" in a graffiti-style font. The code,
  <strong>
   KYHPCVYSNP6HY
  </strong>
  , also comes with an added bonus in the form of a 30-minute double Weapon XP period, which can be activated at any time.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-redeem-new-call-of-duty-warzone-promo-code">
  How To Redeem New Call of Duty: Warzone Promo Code
 </h2>
 <p>
  As per usual, taking advantage of this newly debuted offer is as simple as going to CallOfDuty.com/redeem, logging in, and entering the new promo code before clicking the big "Redeem" button. Doing so will result in both the Verdansk Calling Card and the
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  Double XP Weapon Token being automatically added to one's account. It's generally recommended to redeem the code while the game itself isn't running. Otherwise, a restart might be required for the digital goodies to actually arrive and become usable.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1162931701" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1162931701" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1162931701" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1162931701" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1162931701-img" id="article-gallery-1-1162931701">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1162931701" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-189904138">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's presently unclear how long this newly shared promo code will remain valid. In the past, similar promotions from Activision have lasted anywhere between several days and a few months. This only applies to the actual period during which the promo code itself needs to be redeemed, as the goodies that it brings are afterward free to keep and use whenever.
 </p>
 <p>
  Verdansk returns to
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  on Thursday, April 3. That's also the date when Season 3 is scheduled to kick off. In a rare move, Activision decided to take
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  offline for 24 hours ahead of the new season's release. As compensation, anyone who logs into the game at the start of Season 3 will receive a complimentary Kilo 141 assault rifle. The freebie will also be usable in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , whose Season 3 starts one day earlier, on April 2. Activision didn't clarify how long it intends to keep Verdansk in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , but given its track record, it's likely that the map will eventually be replaced with something else.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sinking City Remastered Announced, And There's Good News for Existing Owners</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-sinking-city-remastered-free-upgrade/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Sinking City Remastered will include enhanced visuals, a new Photo Mode, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      A release date has not been announced, but the remastered title will be available for PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series X/S.
     </li>
     <li>
      Those who already own the original game will receive The Sinking City Remastered for free.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Developer Frogwares has confirmed that
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  will be getting an Unreal Engine 5 upgrade with enhanced visuals, a brand-new Photo Mode, and more with
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City Remastered
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which will be free for owners of the original game. The Lovecraftian action-horror game
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  has developed a cult following since its initial launch, and fans can soon dive back into the terrors of Oakmont when
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  releases for PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series X/S.
 </p>
 <p>
  After
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  was rated in Taiwan in February 2025, many began to speculate when the remaster would be officially announced. Just over a month after guesses started flying, Frogwares has confirmed that
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  is on the way, with the studio also offering some teaser images to showcase the changes that will be found in the UE5 version of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Currently in the middle of developing a sequel to
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  , Frogwares has revealed a first look at
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  , which will include a slew of graphical and performance improvements with Unreal Engine 5. The game originally launched for Switch, PC, PS4, and Xbox One in June 2019, before receiving PS5 and Xbox Series ports in 2021.
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  follows investigator Charles Reed working to uncover the source of a devastating flood in the fictional city of Oakmont. Players are tasked with putting their detective skills to the test while experiencing increasingly bizarre and violent encounters with semi-humanoid inhabitants and aquatic monsters. Despite mixed reviews upon release,
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  has developed a dedicated fandom, and developer Frogwares has used audience feedback to craft some quality-of-life improvements to allow more players to enjoy the game in
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="changes-coming-to-the-sinking-city-remastered">
  Changes Coming to The Sinking City Remastered
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Game fully relit in Unreal Engine 5
  </li>
  <li>
   Enhanced locations with additional levels of detail and objects
  </li>
  <li>
   4K textures and improved reflections
  </li>
  <li>
   Addition of a Photo Mode
  </li>
  <li>
   Support for DLSS, FSR, and TSR upscaling
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Frogwares has noted several major upgrades that will be included in
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  , including reworked lighting, enhanced details, 4K textures, improved reflections, and support for upscaling. The studio also revealed the addition of a brand-new Photo Mode, which will allow players to capture their remastered journey through Oakmont. While a release date was not revealed, Frogwares confirmed that fans who already own
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  on PC, PS5, or Xbox Series X/S will be able to upgrade to
  <em>
   The Sinking City Remastered
  </em>
  free of charge.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1201742571" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1201742571" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1201742571" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1201742571" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1201742571-img" id="article-gallery-1-1201742571">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1201742571" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1897517020">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A number of horror video game remakes and remasters have been met with success in recent years, such as
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  . Audiences are already voicing their support for
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City Remastered
   </em>
  </strong>
  , and interested players can stay tuned for more updates on the game's release date, as well as news regarding
  <em>
   The Sinking City 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: WWE 2K25 Celebrity DLC Characters Leaked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-celebrity-dlc-characters-leak-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      WWE 2K25 will reportedly have celebrity guest DLC characters like KSI, Travis Scott, and NBA players in the lineup.
     </li>
     <li>
      These celebrities have appeared on WWE programming in the past.
     </li>
     <li>
      Plans can change, and WWE 2K25's mystery DLC characters will only be officially revealed at a later date.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s celebrity guest DLC characters may have just been revealed in a new leak. The latest
  <em>
   WWE 2K
  </em>
  video game has one of the biggest rosters to date, sporting a massive mix of current WWE superstars, legends from the past, and new faces alike. Just like with the past few entries,
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  will add more characters throughout 2025, with five DLC packs planned.
 </p>
 <p>
  These packs include classic WWE wrestlers like Mark Henry, Road Dogg and Billy Gunn of the New Age Outlaws, and the Great Khali, newcomers like former AEW luchador and current
  <em>
   Monday Night Raw
  </em>
  sensation Penta, and even a few surprises like TNA alumni Abyss and the late ECW original New Jack. Additionally, the first three
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  DLC waves will include special celebrity guests, though not much is known about who they are aside from June’s Dunk &amp; Destruction Pack containing three famous NBA players.
 </p>
 <p>
  As pointed out by
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  fan and Twitter user WittyWitterson, the names of the DLC celebrity guest characters might have been uncovered in the game’s source files. While this isn’t a guarantee that these figures will be playable in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , the names include famed social media influencer KSI, rap superstar Travis Scott, and NBA players Tyrese Haliburton, Shaquille “Shaq” O'Neal, and Jalen Brunson. These DLC characters were predicted by the WWE2K25Leaks Twitter account earlier this month, around the time that the
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  DLC line-up was first revealed.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="leaked-wwe-2k25-celebrity-dlc-characters">
  Leaked WWE 2K25 Celebrity DLC Characters
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   KSI
  </li>
  <li>
   Travis Scott
  </li>
  <li>
   Tyrese Haliburton
  </li>
  <li>
   Shaq
  </li>
  <li>
   Jalen Brunson
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  All of these celebrities have appeared on WWE programming in the past. Shaq has competed in a few WWE matches, while Tyrese Haliburton and Jalen Brunson confronted each other on the June 28, 2024 episode of
  <em>
   Smackdown
  </em>
  . KSI made a surprise appearance at 2023’s
  <em>
   WrestleMania 39
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  to help Logan Paul in his match against Seth Rollins. The most recent and infamous of these appearances belongs to Travis Scott, who appeared alongside The Rock at this year’s
  <em>
   Elimination Chamber
  </em>
  and took part in a brutal beatdown of current WWE Champion Cody Rhodes – a moment that also saw John Cena turn heel for the first time in over 20 years.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1121776061" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1121776061" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1121776061" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1121776061" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1121776061-img" id="article-gallery-1-1121776061">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1121776061" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1941294606">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This makes their supposed inclusion in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  fitting, but fans should keep in mind that plans can always change and that no one will know for sure who the mystery DLC characters are until they are officially revealed. The first of these guests will be added to
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  as part of the New Wave Pack on May 14.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Theft Auto 6's Unique Marketing Approach Could Set a New Industry Standard</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/grand-theft-auto-6-last-minute-marketing-new-industry-standard-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The reported release window for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Grand Theft Auto 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  is drawing closer, with fans waiting with great anticipation for the next wave of revealed information for the title. There are few other projects in the history of the gaming industry that have possessed the same level of hype as the upcoming Rockstar game, with the industry's other major players seemingly looking at the project's pre-release approach with great interest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Despite the palpable excitement that exists around
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  , Rockstar has been surprisingly quiet regarding direct communication with fans about the title, with over a year having passed since the record-breaking reveal trailer for the game. Rockstar's parent company, Take-Two Interactive, recently made some important clarifications about the unusual marketing strategy for
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  , which will see a lot of the game's pre-release material released very close to the title's launch, and this could set a standard that other big projects follow going forward, if successful.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-6-39-s-burst-of-late-stage-marketing-could-be-a-game-changer-for-the-industry">
  Grand Theft Auto 6's Burst Of Late-Stage Marketing Could Be a Game-Changer For the Industry
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-608693963" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-608693963" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-608693963" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-608693963" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-608693963-img" id="article-gallery-1-608693963">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-608693963" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-455201980">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Analysts are expecting
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  to be one of the most influential gaming releases of all time, with the massive expectations surrounding the title being echoed in the number of eyes that are already on it. Despite the reveal trailer for
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  being controversially leaked before it was officially posted, the trailer still broke multiple world records, including the most amount of views within the first 24 hours of a YouTube video being uploaded, with the trailer currently sitting at just under 250 million views on YouTube alone.
 </p>
 <p>
  With 2013's
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  being the most profitable piece of entertainment media of all time, Rockstar is clearly confident that
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  will be a cultural cornerstone in its own right, with this partially explaining the radio silence that has existed around the title in recent months. Since the release of
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  's trailer in December 2023, essentially no further information has been revealed about the project, with this strangely going against
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  's supposed hopes of a late-2025 launch.
 </p>
 <h3 id="rockstar-is-seemingly-letting-grand-theft-auto-6-39-s-reputation-speak-for-itself-for-the-time-being">
  Rockstar is Seemingly Letting Grand Theft Auto 6's Reputation Speak For Itself For the Time Being
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  released several trailers focusing on the gameplay, protagonists, and major reveals for the title well in advance of its late-2013 launch, and Take-Two Interactive recently confirmed to fans that this same approach should not be expected for
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  . Take-Two's CEO, Strauss Zelnick, recently stated that full pre-release marketing for
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  will start much closer to the game's release, especially compared to past Rockstar titles, with Rockstar seemingly honing in on a rapid burst of major marketing in the immediate run-up to
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  to create an unprecedented explosion of immediate hype.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Grand Theft Auto 5
     </em>
     released five distinct trailers in total prior to its launch, with players perhaps being in store for a similar number of total
     <em>
      GTA 6
     </em>
     trailers in the weeks before the game's launch.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  This could easily place
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  in an even more dominant position at its time of launch compared to a usual pre-release approach, and while other major projects will not possess the same level of inherent hype as
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  , they may opt for a similar brief but intense marketing strategy immediately before their own releases to emulate this potential success. Theories are already circulating that the wider AAA industry may copy
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  's rumored $100+ price tag, meaning a similar poaching of the game's unique marketing approach is not out of the question.
 </p>
 <p>
  While it is a shame that fans will not have more consistent updates regarding
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  in the immediate future, the amount of anticipation that will surely surround the game when this marketing strategy comes into play is already a massively exciting prospect. The longevity, pricing, and offered experience of
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  are already expected to revolutionize the gaming industry, and the recently confirmed marketing approach of the project could be another major example of trends that it will set for other releases going forward.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
