<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Zenless Zone Zero Leak Reveals Interesting Detail about Hugo Vlad in Version 1.6</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/zenless-zone-zero-version-16-leak-hugo-vlad-boss/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A leak claims Hugo Vlad will be an enemy boss in Zenless Zone Zero Version 1.6, using a scythe.
     </li>
     <li>
      The leak suggests Hugo Vlad might become playable later, similar to other characters.
     </li>
     <li>
      Version 1.6 will introduce new characters like Silver Soldier Anby and Trigger.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Zenless Zone Zero
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak reveals that Hugo Vlad will be an enemy boss in Version 1.6. The character has appeared in-game in previous updates, but
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  fans have been hoping he would eventually become playable in future patches.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hugo Vlad appeared for the first time during a cutscene in Lycaon's Agent Story, revealing that both characters used to be close acquaintances. Later on, in
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  Version 1.5, fans met Hugo Vlad in-game during the Bangboo competition event, though he was not formally introduced and was only known as "Blonde Man." Despite having little mention in the game, Hugo Vlad has become a highly-anticipated character among fans. Earlier leaks revealed that Hugo Vlad would join the
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  roster in future updates. Now, a new leak suggests that the character will play an interesting role in Version 1.6.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reliable
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  leaker Donut has reported that Hugo Vlad will be an enemy boss in patch 1.6. The leak includes Hugo Vlad's shadow boss model for Shiyu Defense, but players will also fight his normal model during the update's main story. In his boss form, Hugo Vlad fights with an immense scythe, which has been rumored to be his weapon as a playable character. While developers have shared little information about
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  Version 1.6, Hugo Vlad's boss fight might likely be tied to an unfriendly reunion with Lycaon.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="zenless-zone-zero-leak-reveals-hugo-vlad-boss-fight-in-version-1-6">
  Zenless Zone Zero Leak Reveals Hugo Vlad Boss Fight in Version 1.6
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1443700284" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1443700284" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1443700284" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1443700284" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1443700284-img" id="article-gallery-1-1443700284">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1443700284" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1656227406">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If the leak turns out to be true, Hugo Vlad would not be the first character to be an enemy before becoming playable. In past updates, Jane Doe was an enemy boss before she was released as an S-Rank agent. In a similar manner,
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  confirmed Pulchra's playability for Version 1.6 despite her being a foe in the 1.2 update. Her rarity has not been confirmed yet, but fans speculate that she will be an A-Rank unit.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from Pulchra, Version 1.6 will also debut characters Silver Soldier Anby and Trigger, who are expected to be S-Rank agents. Previous leaks hinted that
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  might give away a free character to players in the next update, but fans will have to wait for an official announcement. It will be interesting to see how Hugo Vlad is involved in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Zenless Zone Zero
   </em>
  </strong>
  's next story chapter, as it has been teased that Version 1.6 will reveal more details about the Obol Squad faction and its members.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Spencer Has Bad News for Gears of War Fans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/gears-of-war-marcus-fenix-collection-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xbox boss Phil Spencer recently unlocked several achievements in Gears of War 2 and 3.
     </li>
     <li>
      This has led some fans to believe that Spencer is preparing for a potential Marcus Fenix Collection.
     </li>
     <li>
      Spencer claims that he was playing the games with a friend, and it remains uncertain if The Coalition is working on an anthology-style release or not.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Gears of War
   </strong>
  </em>
  fans may be let down following Phil Spencer's reasoning for revisiting the original
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  trilogy recently. Following an impressive cinematic reveal trailer
  <em>
  </em>
  during Xbox's June 2024 Summer Game Fest Showcase,
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  has relaunched the popular third-person shooter franchise back into the Xbox zeitgeist. The reveal also fanned the flames of Xbox fans' desire to see a
  <em>
   Halo: The Master Chief Collection
  </em>
  -style anthology release with the original
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  trilogy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Xbox boss Phil Spencer has been known to keep his Xbox profile, P3, viewable to the public so that fans can see his gaming activity on the platform. About a week ago, Xbox fans spotted that Spencer had recently unlocked a number of achievements in
  <em>
   Gears of War 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   3
  </em>
  , leading to a flurry of speculation about Spencer gearing up for a potential Marcus Fenix Collection by revisiting these games. This, combined with
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  's rumored 2025 release window, made a Master Chief-style anthology from The Coalition seem quite viable to fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, in speaking with former IGN member Destin Legarie, Phil Spencer provided some insight into why he recently revisited the original
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  trilogy. Spencer says he was simply playing through the games again in co-op with a friend of his who had never played any of the
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  games. His clarification wasn't in response to a Marcus Fenix Collection query, and he brought it up when talking about the benefits of the Xbox ecosystem, namely, it's seamless save system that allowed him to load up a
  <em>
   Gears of War 3
  </em>
  save from 2011.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="phil-spencer-39-s-gears-of-war-activity-doesn-39-t-confirm-marcus-fenix-collection">
  Phil Spencer's Gears of War Activity Doesn't Confirm Marcus Fenix Collection
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1136650726" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1136650726" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1136650726" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136650726" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136650726-img" id="article-gallery-1-1136650726">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1136650726" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-331178289">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While this may seem like disappointing news for
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  fans, Spencer's clarification about his
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  activity doesn't necessarily mean a Marcus Fenix Collection isn't being planned or worked on. It's possible The Coalition's change to a prequel in
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  could be a move made with Xbox's newfound shift to third-party in mind, potentially providing a fresh start for gamers on PlayStation who might have never played a
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  game before. A Marcus Fenix Collection would be a great way to help get PlayStation gamers up to speed on the original trilogy either before or after
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  releases.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since
  <em>
   Gears of War:
  </em>
  <em>
   E-Day
  </em>
  still seems like a long way off, news about a potential Marcus Fenix Collection may also likely take a while. It's hard to say whether
  <em>
   E-Day
  </em>
  will show up again this upcoming June, but fans of the franchise should still keep an eye on Xbox and The Coalition's social media in case any new tidbits are released.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monopoly GO: How to Play Shutdown</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monopoly-go-how-play-shutdown-target-hack-work/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Play Shutdown in Monopoly GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monopoly GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has a bunch of fun minigames that make things more exciting and help you earn money. One of these minigames is Shutdown.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In Shutdown, you destroy other players’ buildings to slow down their progress. But how do you play the minigame, and can you get back at someone who took down your landmarks? Let’s find out.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-play-shutdown-in-monopoly-go">
  How to Play Shutdown in Monopoly GO
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-f62972eb3f1bab59" id="emaki-video-player-f62972eb3f1bab59">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  First things first, you will need to trigger the Shutdown minigame. To do that, you have to land on any of the four
  <strong>
   Railroads
  </strong>
  on your board. But keep in mind that sometimes you’ll end up in the Bank Heist minigame instead.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you enter Shutdown, the game will take you to your opponent’s city, where you’ll see their buildings. Just click on a building to try and destroy it. But here’s the catch: your friends aren’t completely defenseless. If they have shields equipped, those buildings will be protected, and you won’t be able to take them down. Therefore, we recommend equipping shields on your buildings before going offline.
 </p>
 <p>
  As we said earlier, you earn cash for shutting down your opponent’s buildings. But if your attack gets blocked by a shield, you will get less cash than a successful hit. If a player’s shield is already broken, you’ll see a cloud under their building. So if you see that cloud, go for that building.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to shutdown monopoly go" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/how-to-shutdown-monopoly-go.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Furthermore, shutdowns also give you tournament points in
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  , and as you might have expected, a blocked shutdown grants you fewer points. Usually, you will earn two points for a blocked hit and four points for a successful hit. And yes, the points you earn depend on your active multiplier. So if you have a good amount of dice rolls, you can increase the multiplier before landing on a Railroad tile.
 </p>
 <p>
  If you don’t want to attack your friends or have a specific player in mind for revenge, you have the option to change your target. For this,
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  players will need to hit the
  <strong>
   ‘Switch Opponents’
  </strong>
  button in the shutdown menu. You’ll see two tabs: ‘Friends’ and ‘Revenge.’ But keep in mind that your friends get notified when you destroy their buildings, so they might come after you later.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game also gives you board reports showing who attacked you. If you miss it, you can go to the
  <strong>
   ‘Timeline’
  </strong>
  under the ‘Friends’ tab to see the info.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 12 is Going to Be a Big Day for Overwatch 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/overwatch-2-spotlight-event-date-when-new-heroes-maps-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Overwatch 2 Spotlight event on February 12 will reveal major PvP changes in 2025.
     </li>
     <li>
      This includes a look at new heroes, maps, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans that watch one hour of partner streams on Feb.12 will get Lucio Cyber DJ skin as a Twitch Drop.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Overwatch 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans have good reason to be excited for Wednesday, February 12.
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  dominated the hero shooter genre for years, with competitors failing to match its popularity and many of them fizzling out. That's changed in recent months with the launch of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , a Marvel Comics-themed hero shooter that's taken the gaming industry by storm. With millions flocking to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  is coming out swinging in 2025 with ambitious plans for the new year that will hopefully draw lapsed players back to the game and maybe even convince newcomers to see what all the fuss is about.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  has been making an effort to appeal to lapsed fans through things like 6v6 tests that are attempting to see if a return to the 2 Tank, 2 Damage, and 2 Support format is possible with the changes that have been made to the game. 6v6 is not a permanent part of the
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  experience yet, and it remains to be seen if it will be or if the game will ultimately stick with 5v5. Time will tell on that front, but in the meantime,
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  fans will be getting some concrete answers about the hero shooter's future come February 12.
 </p>
 <p>
  On Wednesday, February 12 at 10am PT, Blizzard will be hosting a special
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  Spotlight livestream. The event promises to reveal "groundbreaking changes" to the
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  PvP experience in 2025 that will "redefine" the game in ways that fans "have never seen before." The spotlight event will explain the changes being made to how
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  is played, while also giving fans a look at new heroes and maps that are coming to the game. Some of the new content will be added to
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  as early as February, though much of it will be added later on.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="when-is-the-overwatch-2-spotlight-event">
  When is the Overwatch 2 Spotlight Event?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-925655964" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-925655964" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-925655964" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-925655964" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-925655964-img" id="article-gallery-1-925655964">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-925655964" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1950871688">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Wednesday, February 12 at 10am PT
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  fans have extra incentive to tune in to the Spotlight event. While it will be available to watch directly from Blizzard, those that decide to watch at least one hour of partner content creators' streams on February 12 will snag the Lucio Cyber DJ legendary skin as a Spotlight exclusive Twitch Drop. While the promise of seeing new
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  heroes and maps was likely enough to get fans to tune in, the Lucio skin is icing on the cake.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="overwatch 2 february 2025" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/overwatch-2-lucio-legendary-skin-twitch-drop.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  is currently in the midst of Season 14, which is scheduled to end on February 18. The big event on February 12 will likely have a great deal of focus on Season 15 since it's right around the corner, so fans should be sure to mark their calendars for Wednesday, February 12 at 10am PT.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God of War Returning to Its Egyptian Plans Now Would Bring About One Extra Challenge</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/god-of-war-egyptian-pantheon-khonshu-moon-knight-marvel-mcu/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In September 2021, about a year before
  <strong>
   <em>
    God of War Ragnarok
   </em>
  </strong>
  's release, Santa Monica's Cory Balrog mentioned in an interview that the team wanted Kratos and Atreus' Norse journey to reach a satisfying conclusion by the end of the saga's second game, believing that any further extensions would dilute the story and character relationships too much.
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  did just that, tying up most of the plot threads set up in
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  2018, while leaving room for the continuation of certain character stories.
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok: Valhalla
  </em>
  then acts as a brief epilogue to Kratos' story, bridging the gap between the Norse saga and whatever comes next.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For years, fans have wanted Kratos to face off against the gods and goddesses of the ancient Egyptian pantheon, and that remains a really strong concept given the pantheon's continued popularity in modern media. But that continued popularity might also put the next
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  in an awkward spot when it comes to the portrayal of one specific Egyptian god.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="god-of-war-39-s-version-of-khonshu-would-have-a-lot-to-live-up-to">
  God of War's Version of Khonshu Would Have a Lot To Live Up To
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1665262217" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1665262217" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1665262217" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1665262217" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1665262217-img" id="article-gallery-1-1665262217">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1665262217" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1865101090">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="marvel-39-s-khonshu-has-become-a-popular-character-in-recent-years">
  Marvel's Khonshu Has Become a Popular Character in Recent Years
 </h3>
 <p>
  The ancient Egyptian god of the moon, Khonshu (also spelled Khonsu or Chonsu) is intrinsically tied to Marvel's Moon Knight character. Making his debut in 1980's
  <em>
   Moon Knight #1
  </em>
  , Khonshu resurrects mercenary Marc Spector, essentially forcing him to become his earthly champion. Though Marc's willingness to be "The Fist of Khonshu" waxes and wanes from comic to comic, like the phases of the moon, at least one of his dissociative identities is usually happy to suit up as Moon Knight and dish out some of Khonshu's "justice."
 </p>
 <p>
  While Khonshu has been an important part of the Marvel universe for over four decades, he didn't become a household name until just a few years ago. Like most Marvel entities, Khonshu entered the mainstream public consciousness due to the Marvel Cinematic Universe. Though it didn't review particularly well, 2022's
  <em>
   Moon Knight
  </em>
  Disney+ miniseries was still incredibly popular, beating out
  <em>
   Hawkeye
  </em>
  's decent viewership numbers.
 </p>
 <p>
  This sudden influx of new Moon Knight fans has led many to check out his extensive back-catalog of comics, which in turn paints an even clearer picture of Khonshu's role in the Marvel universe. The recently released
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  also gives Moon Knight plenty of time in the spotlight, with him arguably being one of the game's best Duelists, and Khonshu gets plenty of mentions during Moon Knight's pre-match dialogue.
 </p>
 <h3 id="god-of-war-39-s-khonshu-would-now-be-compared-to-marvel-39-s">
  God of War's Khonshu Would Now Be Compared to Marvel's
 </h3>
 <p>
  A few years ago,
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  could have presented its own version of Khonshu and many players wouldn't bat an eye. But given Moon Knight's fast rise to fame, any version of Khonshu in other media is bound to draw comparisons with Marvel's version of the Egyptian god of the moon.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     A recent rumor from @DanielRPK claims that Sony is currently casting "Middle Eastern" actors for an upcoming AAA game, which is rumored to be a
     <em>
      God of War
     </em>
     game set in Egypt.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  These comparisons wouldn't necessarily be an issue for the next
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  , but they can lead to some fans having certain expectations of how the character should behave and look. The perfect example of this is
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  's version of Thor. When
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  's Thor design was first revealed, some took issue with how the Norse god looked, with many being used to more traditionally muscular portrayals shown in media like the MCU. Upon playing
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  , many players found its version of Thor to be surprisingly complex and refreshing, and the distinct character design tied in perfectly with the narrative Santa Monica was telling.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  has proven it can overcome comparisons to the MCU, it's still an obstacle that would likely be inevitable if the next game included a version of Khonshu. Of course, an easy fix would be to simply not include him.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
