<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How Persona 6 Could Take School Clubs to New Heights of Immersion</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/persona-6-school-clubs-social-link-events-immersion-rewards/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  It would be great to see
  <em>
   <strong>
    Persona 6
   </strong>
  </em>
  bring back school clubs, but it can go even further with them than previous games did. While
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  's main plot will have to be its main priority, fleshing out the rest of the world in-game will greatly enrich the experience. If the game's going back to a school setting, that will naturally include school clubs and anything associated with them. Letting the protagonist join school clubs is an obvious move. At the same time,
  <em>
   P
  </em>
  <em>
   ersona 6
  </em>
  can go the extra mile and make sure that its clubs offer more than before.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When planning the Social Links of
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  , the developers have a lot of potential routes to go down. For the last three games, one of the biggest sources of Social Links has come through each respective game's school. Since each protagonist since the debut of Social Links has been a student, it only makes sense that they would form connections with some of their classmates. Of course, each game has also included several characters outside of school among their Social Link and Confidant rosters as well. It only makes sense if
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  's school is once again filled with important connections.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="persona-6-39-s-school-clubs-can-be-more-than-social-links">
  Persona 6's School Clubs Can Be More Than Social Links
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-817243733" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-817243733" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-817243733" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-817243733" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-817243733-img" id="article-gallery-1-817243733">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-817243733" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-20003544">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="school-clubs-are-a-common-source-for-persona-39-s-social-links">
  School Clubs Are a Common Source For Persona's Social Links
 </h3>
 <p>
  Several Social Links in the series, such as
  <em>
   Persona 4
  </em>
  's Strength Link, have come about as a result of the protagonist joining school clubs or other functions. Since school clubs are a common part of life for many Japanese students, they're a reasonable source for
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  games to pull from. School clubs can encompass many areas, from sports teams to a theater club to student government. This was especially notable in
  <em>
   Persona 3
  </em>
  , where many of the social links involving other students on both routes were tied to school clubs in some way. Now, it's very likely that
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  will continue this trend.
 </p>
 <h3 id="persona-6-39-s-school-clubs-can-reward-good-attendance">
  Persona 6's School Clubs Can Reward Good Attendance
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  's school clubs can have a bigger impact, especially if
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  shakes up its formula in a notable fashion. Since school clubs are such a big part of school culture,
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  could change to reflect that rather than just having it as another name on the player's list of social links. For example, consistently attending clubs could provide bonuses to the boosts that the protagonist gets from it, because it shows their dedication, while players who only attend occasionally would only get the normal bonuses. It would give players something extra to take into account when scheduling their days.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Since school clubs are a common part of life for many Japanese students, they're a reasonable source for
     <em>
      Persona
     </em>
     games to pull from.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="club-events-can-add-an-extra-kick-to-persona-6">
  Club Events Can Add an Extra Kick to Persona 6
 </h3>
 <p>
  School clubs could also lead to some more unique bonuses for the player. While some of
  <em>
   Persona 4
  </em>
  's Social Links changed depending on the player's club of choice, clubs could have an impact on
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  in another way. Joining certain clubs could lead to a club event being placed on the game's calendar, such as a school play or major athletic meet. Not only that but if the player has been diligent with club meetings and raising the appropriate social stat, they could end up with a reward at the end of the scene. This way,
  <em>
   P
  </em>
  <em>
   ersona 6
  </em>
  's school clubs could have a bigger impact.
 </p>
 <p>
  School clubs have been appearing in
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  's protagonists' lives since Social Links debuted. When it comes to
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  's take on this Social link structure, they could become more of a factor than ever before. Historically, school clubs have done little more than provide the player with another Social Link.
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  can make its school clubs a much more interesting part of its protagonist's life.
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  will have plenty of Social Links, but its school clubs have a chance to stand out from the crowd.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Rene Should Make One Change to The Sims 4's Supernatural Creatures</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sims-4-project-rene-supernatural-creatures-werewolves-vampires-packs/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Though not much is known about the mysterious
  <strong>
   <em>
    Project Rene
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the little information EA and Maxis have revealed about the project promises a lot of changes to
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  franchise. With these significant changes in mind,
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  could distinguish itself from
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  specifically in its approach to occult-type Sims.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are several occult types currently available in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  . Some of these Sims are available in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  base games, like ghosts and PlantSims, but most occult types are only available through DLC. These pay-to-play occult types include aliens (Get to Work Expansion), spellcasters (Realm of Magic Game Pack), mermaids (Island Living Game Pack), vampires (Vampires Game Pack), and werewolves (Werewolves Game Pack). Ghosts were also recently expanded in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  ’s most recent expansion pack, Life and Death, released back in October 2024.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-is-known-about-project-rene">
  What is Known About Project Rene
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1850344479" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1850344479" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1850344479" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1850344479" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1850344479-img" id="article-gallery-1-1850344479">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1850344479" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1318573985">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As mentioned, EA and Maxis have promised quite a bit to players through
  <em>
   Project Ren
  </em>
  e. The new entry into
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  franchise will supposedly be an online multiplayer cross-platform experience. Play tests for the game have tested the game’s multiplayer capabilities, solidifying EA and Maxis’s statements.
 </p>
 <p>
  Datamining and image leaks have also given players an inside scoop on
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  ’s development. While all leaks should be taken with a grain of salt, alleged images of
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  ’s version of Create-A-Sim (CAS) are representative of statements made during the announcement of the game back at the Behind the Sims Summit in 2022.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  ’s CAS will allegedly allow Simmers to adjust the weight and height of their Sims and also layer their clothing. These features have been unavailable in CAS for the franchise’s previous installments. An alleged category for mobility aids, featuring items like wheelchairs, was also uncovered during the datamine. But the most interesting aspect found during this datamining session did not involve humans, but animals.
 </p>
 <p>
  All customizable pets available in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  are paywalled. Animals like cats, dogs, and horses, which have their own version of CAS, can only be obtained by purchasing the Horse Ranch or Cats &amp; Dogs Expansion Packs. This datamine alleges that these pets can be directly edited in
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  ’s base game CAS, suggesting that this gameplay feature that is paywalled in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  will be free-to-play in
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  . If this leak is true, EA and Maxis should take the same approach to occult-type Sims.
 </p>
 <h2 id="project-rene-may-solve-the-sims-39-pay-wall-problem">
  Project Rene May Solve The Sims' Pay Wall Problem
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-713353400" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-713353400" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-713353400" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-713353400" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-713353400-img" id="article-gallery-2-713353400">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-713353400" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1907974927">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The amount of money necessary to purchase all DLC packs currently available in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  is ludicrous. Simmers have been complaining about the franchise’s pay-to-play system practically since DLC was introduced to the franchise. Though EA and Maxis’s approach to paywalls has evolved over the franchise’s twenty-five-year history, players remain disgruntled and disgusted by
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  ’ pricing.
 </p>
 <p>
  But
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  will supposedly be different. EA and Maxis have long touted that the project will be like no
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  game before it and be absolutely filled to the brim with content. If this is the case, occult-type Sims should be available in
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  ’s base game to play from the get-go.
 </p>
 <h3 id="project-rene-will-likely-still-be-monetized">
  Project Rene Will Likely Still Be Monetized
 </h3>
 <p>
  However, EA and Maxis will still want to make money somehow.
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  will likely not be free-to-play on release, as was the case with
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  . Even with the money made on the initial launch, it would not be unlikely for EA and Maxis to search for some other way to monetize
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  . Therefore, the best option for the franchise would not be to sell individual items in the case of
  <em>
   The Sims 3
  </em>
  shop or release restrictive DLC packs like in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , but to turn to releasing more Kits.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Kits have been a divisive DLC feature in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , as they typically feature only CAS items, Build and Buy items, or new gameplay, for $5 per Kit, this specific form of DLC might mesh well with
  <em>
   Project Rene
  </em>
  . Since this new title will be an online multiplayer game, it feels only fair for all players to have access to the same kinds of gameplay. However, selling new furniture and clothing items to Simmers would be a way for EA and Maxis to monetize
  <strong>
   <em>
    Project Rene
   </em>
  </strong>
  , while giving all Simmers the chance to play with features like occult-type Sims.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - I'm On A Boat!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-im-on-a-boat/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player gets bounced upward on a boat in GTA and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization 7 - First Look: Catherine Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/civilization-7-first-look-catherine-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Firaxis and 2K give a first look at Catherine The Great, the newly revealed leader of Russia inside Civilization 7.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Could Hold the Answer to Marvel's Wolverine's Traversal Question</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-insomniac-wolverine-traversal-abilities-leap-wall-run/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  One of the Insomniac
  <em>
   Spider-Man
  </em>
  series' most lauded features is its fluid traversal. The perfect combination of cinematic animations and player-controlled inputs,
  <em>
   Marvel's Spider-Man
  </em>
  's web-swinging is one of the most satisfying traversal systems in video game history, and it goes hand in hand with the series' bustling open-world. But now
  <em>
   <strong>
    Marvel's Wolverine
   </strong>
  </em>
  is expected to reach the same heights.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A core part of Spider-Man's identity in the comics, movies, and any other piece of Marvel media is the hero's agility, acrobatic nature, and unique method of traversal. Wolverine, on the other hand, isn't as closely associated with a specific type of movement. With so much secrecy still surrounding
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  , some fans are wondering just how Insomniac will approach the hero's in-game traversal, and the recently released
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  might be the best indication.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-could-be-setting-the-stage-for-marvel-39-s-wolverine-39-s-traversal">
  Marvel Rivals Could Be Setting The Stage for Marvel's Wolverine's Traversal
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1823056095" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1823056095" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1823056095" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1823056095" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1823056095-img" id="article-gallery-1-1823056095">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1823056095" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1951363758">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="how-wolverine-39-s-movement-works-in-marvel-rivals">
  How Wolverine's Movement Works in Marvel Rivals
 </h3>
 <p>
  Released just over a month ago,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is a new 6v6 hero shooter that lets players take control of some of the most iconic heroes and villains in Marvel's extensive catalog. Wolverine is one such hero, taking the role of a damage-focused Duelist.
 </p>
 <p>
  With hero shooters often revolving around modes that require the player to get back to the objective as fast as possible, many characters tend to have one or two movement abilities. For some characters, these movement abilities double as an attack.
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Wolverine has two such abilities.
 </p>
 <p>
  "Feral Leap" sees Wolverine launch into the air, clearing large distances and grounding any foe that comes into contact with his claws, while "Vicious Rampage" has Wolverine performing a quick dash forward that ends in a claw strike. Though
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Wolverine isn't nearly as agile as heroes like Spider-Man, Iron Fist, or even Moon Knight, his abilities do allow him to enter and leave combat quickly, granting him a much-needed respite from the action.
 </p>
 <p>
  This isn't the first time Marvel fans have seen Wolverine jump across battlefields. Along with leaping across the pages of countless Marvel comics, Wolverine's primary method of traversal in the beloved 2009
  <em>
   X-Men Origins: Wolverine
  </em>
  game is a very satisfying-to-use lunge attack that has the hero leaping between enemies, plunging his claws deep into the chests of each one.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Marvel Rivals
     </em>
     ' Wolverine also has a team-up move with the Hulk that sees the Vanguard launching Wolverine into the air, referencing the "Fastball Special" move he and Colossus have often used in the comics.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="marvel-39-s-wolverine-might-want-to-carry-these-traversal-mechanics-forward">
  Marvel's Wolverine Might Want to Carry These Traversal Mechanics Forward
 </h3>
 <p>
  While Insomniac's
  <em>
   Wolverine
  </em>
  may not be a fully open-world game (nothing has been officially confirmed yet), it might still have open-ended areas, and players will need to be given some way to traverse these stages. A leap ability similar to those found in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   X-Men Origins: Wolverine
  </em>
  would likely be the best option for Insomniac's
  <em>
   Wolverine
  </em>
  , striking the right balance of comic accuracy and player-freedom.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though Insomniac hasn't officially revealed any gameplay details of
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  , leaked early builds of the game suggest players will be able to jump over obstacles, climb surfaces, and run across walls, as well as leap high into the air.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
