<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Interview: Sinking City 2 Dev Discusses New Survival Mechanics, Exploration, and More</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sinking-city-2-interview/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a semi-open world survival horror game, which is a pretty big change from its predecessor. Players will explore the world of Arkham while searching for clues and taking on various monsters inspired by the Cthulhu mythos. There will be a lot of new features for players to enjoy, such as an entirely new and very detailed combat system with a special wound-body feature that allows players to see what kind of damage has been inflicted on an enemy.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In an interview with Game Rant, Frogwares publishing director Sergiy Oganesyan discusses community support around creating
  <em>
   The Sinking City 2,
  </em>
  designing new creatures, the game world and its secrets, and more.
  <strong>
   The following interview has been edited for brevity and clarity.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="taking-the-series-in-a-new-direction">
  Taking The Series In A New Direction
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2077115647" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2077115647" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2077115647" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2077115647" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2077115647-img" id="article-gallery-1-2077115647">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2077115647" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-99283499">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   is going full survival horror as opposed to a detective adventure game. What made you decide to change genres for the sequel?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  We’re an independent studio that, for the past 24 years, has become synonymous with detective games. While that’s been great, it has also somewhat pigeonholed us. The industry and player tastes are evolving, and they will continue to do so as long as people are playing. We want to expand both our abilities and our audience now, ensuring the future of the studio. We want to keep doing this for another 20+ years, and in order to achieve that, we need to take bolder steps.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: The combat and survival mechanics have been reworked for
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   . Can you discuss how they differ from the mechanics in the series’ first installment?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  We’re building our entire combat and survival systems from the ground up for
  <em>
   The Sinking City 2
  </em>
  because they are now some of the key mechanics in the sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  So, if we’re talking about combat specifically, our goal is to make sure it is convincing and satisfying. That includes the usual stuff like punchy recoil, SFX, visual effects that clearly telegraph that you hit your target, enemies reacting in a natural way, getting pushed back or sent flying depending on your weapon, etc. These are the standard things that you expect to see, but when even one element is missing, you’ll surely notice it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Then, we are taking it up a notch by adding a “wound-body” system that clearly shows where and with what kind of punch a weapon hits an enemy. Usually in games, when you shoot an enemy, the impact points get covered with a blood decal or something similar, but in our case, enemies have a detailed second layer of bones and muscle tissue that will show when a bullet penetrates their skin. This second layer covers the entire body, so no matter where you shoot, you will always have those realistic (and gory) impact effects. That adds to that feeling of satisfaction that we are aiming for.
 </p>
 <p>
  We are also hard at work designing enemies that require different strategies to kill. And bosses - Lovecraftian monstrosity, quite fascinating in design.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-368588739" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-368588739" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-368588739" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-368588739" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-368588739-img" id="article-gallery-2-368588739">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-368588739" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-282011445">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On the survival side, we’ve focused a lot of time and iterations on inventory management, crafting, and balancing supplies. Players will need to scavenge and use what they find carefully because the levels won’t be overflowing with items. There’s a fine balance here—you don’t want players to feel like they have nothing but scraps, but it shouldn’t feel like a feast either. And of course, we are going to have multiple difficulty options.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: How do you feel fans of the first
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sinking City
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   will respond to the changes made for
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   ?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  So far, the reaction has been very positive overall. We surely have questions about the role of investigation, but what’s important is that we’re still offering our original fans something that is quintessentially Frogwares — the investigation tools and gameplay. If you don’t care about the combat, you could lower its difficulty and focus on investigation and secret-hunting, much like you did in TSC1. The original game had plenty of combat, it’s just much better in the sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  Investigation in TSC2 is quite fascinating. You can easily have 20, 30, or 40 clues scattered across each map, leading to different mysteries. The key improvement is that most of these clues are optional, meaning you can still solve your cases without having to find all of them. Remember how it was in TSC1? Missing a single clue would get you stuck, unable to progress. Now this problem is solved. You could even come to the right conclusion based on just some of the clues without needing to connect all the dots.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: In just the first day,
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   surpassed its Kickstarter goal. What would you like to say to fans and backers who’ve made this possible?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  Our absolute and heartfelt thanks to every single person who backed us. Honestly, it feels like no words are enough to properly express how incredibly humbled we are. In the back of our minds, we had a feeling we’d meet our goal, especially considering the support we saw on our last Kickstarter project,
  <em>
   Sherlock Holmes: The Awakened
  </em>
  . But reaching our goal so quickly and seeing it continue to grow is nothing short of incredible.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Are there any stretch goals that you are excited about?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  To be honest, I’m personally most excited about the first two stretch goals we’ve already reached. The first goal was to add more missions or content that would allow players to participate in more investigations, while the second goal was to introduce more visual variety to our base enemy type, the Slithers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both of these goals had much of the design and concepts down on paper, but our development team wasn’t sure we’d have the resources to implement them or if there was even a real demand. Now, thanks to the support from our community, we have the green light to move forward with them both.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_21">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Check Out The Sinking City 2's Kickstarter
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="goals-features-and-expanding-cthulhu-mythos-for-the-sinking-city-2">
  Goals, Features, And Expanding Cthulhu Mythos For The Sinking City 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1011820997" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1011820997" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1011820997" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1011820997" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1011820997-img" id="article-gallery-3-1011820997">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1011820997" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1533606551">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   is set to feature new creatures that expand on the Cthulhu Mythos. Can you walk us through the process of turning Cthulhu Mythos into video game creatures?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  Everything starts with narrative design, and the obvious part is to thoroughly collect and follow the canonical descriptions that H.P. Lovecraft made. Narrative is the thing that ties everything together. Our team needs to understand the key elements Lovecraft used to ensure our creatures feel like they genuinely belong in a Lovecraft-inspired world. We try to answer where this new creature can fit into a Lovecraft “monster hierarchy” and also what its role is in the game. For example, some creatures can be used as enemies (in our case it’s the Deep One and the Shoggoth, among others), some can be bosses, while others are characters, etc.
 </p>
 <p>
  Then, our concept artists need to visualize the idea based on the input from the game designers, tech and optimization artists, animators, etc. You have no idea how many guidelines and constraints there can be! We have plenty of metrics that guide us through the development - how wide a room is, how fast the main character is, etc., and each monster has to be designed with those in mind. Once we have all that, we can then create a 3D model, optimized for the game, and send it for test animations. If everything is in order, the model is finalized, and the most difficult part begins, creating gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Likewise, what’s it like working with the Cthulhu Mythos when fleshing out the narrative?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  The Cthulhu Mythos is not just about weird monsters and creepy designs, it represents a deeply philosophical idea of cosmic horror and our place in the universe. It’s also loneliness and isolation, which definitely serve as the foundation for our world-building and level design.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s extremely rewarding because there is so much source material to use as inspiration, but you never feel you are tied down to an overly strict narrative, established characters, etc. Yes, there is a lot of set doom and gloom that you need to stick to, but it’s very open-ended in a lot of ways. So much of what Lovecraft wrote left a lot open to interpretation.
 </p>
 <p>
  Certain creatures are only hinted at or are very vaguely mentioned. If you look online, there are continual debates on people trying to establish a “creature hierarchy,” and while some of it is clear and set, there are many spots where people just simply can’t agree based on written “fact.” There is also a lot of moral gray in the mythos, with some of the creatures not being outright monstrous but they still aren’t anything cute and cuddly either. And this is where we, as a studio, love to write and build stories - where you have this guiding light but the paths you can take are multiple. So long as you respect the source material enough, you can end up creating something that feels different but is also deemed worthy by the super fans who know the Cthulhu Mythos well.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: While
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   isn’t an open-world game, it seems to allow players some degree of freedom. Can you talk about the importance of player freedom in
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   ? How does that factor into the experience?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  I think the biggest feature in terms of player freedom is our optional investigation mechanic, which ties into the semi-open-world design. In
  <em>
   The Sinking City 2
  </em>
  , you can choose to investigate whatever clues you want, and in return, you’ll be rewarded in some way—more lore, supplies, alternate routes, hidden secrets, etc. And so our map is going to have a lot of moments and spots like that. Take the time to dig around, and it will potentially open up something extra for you if you want.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Arkham In The Sinking City 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/arkham-in-the-sinking-city-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: It looks like there are plenty of weapons that you can pick up and use while exploring the ruins of Arkham. How has your approach to weapon design changed this time around?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  It depends on what you consider plenty. I think so far we have around half a dozen weapons, and our MAIN focus compared to the original is on making sure that each gun feels different. We are also adding weapon upgrades in the best traditions of the genre - you will find those when exploring the game and solving cases and puzzles.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   is being made with a different engine than its predecessor. What has the shift to Unreal Engine 5 been like?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  Switching from Unreal 4 to Unreal 5 definitely came with a learning curve, but once you learn the new tools, you can really appreciate how amazing they are. Games take years to make because everything you do requires optimization - it’s often a very manual and long process.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here’s the most basic example. Take a single rock that you will place somewhere in the world. Before Nanite, you had to worry about your polycount, and to optimize your game you would have to create a highly-detailed version of your rock (high-poly), then a second much less detailed copy (low poly), and then transfer the detail from high to low poly through normal maps, which fake the micro detail via shading. Then, you would need to create several LODs (level of detail) for the rock because you don’t want it rendered at the same level of detail up close and a hundred meters away. Repeat that process for every single model that requires that approach, and you can see how exhausting that is.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unreal streamlines many of those optimization processes, and that’s great. Nothing is ever ideal, of course, and there’s an upfront cost associated with those tools, but it’s still more than worth it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Is there anything that you’d like to add about
  </strong>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sinking City 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  <strong>
   ?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   A:
  </strong>
  This is the first time we’re truly embracing community feedback so early in development, and it has already proven invaluable. We know we’re taking a bold step with this game, moving into a genre we’ve only dabbled in before. We’re thrilled to see how many people are supporting us, and it’s exciting to see where our efforts are resonating with fans and where we still need to improve. It’s all part of the process, and we’re excited to continue sharing the journey with our community.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   [END]
  </strong>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones: Kingsroad Now Has 'Mixed' Reviews on Steam</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/game-of-thrones-kingsroad-mixed-reviews-steam-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Game of Thrones: Kingsroad has "Mixed" player reviews on Steam due to aggressive monetization.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite the mixed reviews, as the game is in Early Access, there is potential for improvement in the future.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Netmarble's new action-adventure RPG
  <em>
   <strong>
    Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
   </strong>
  </em>
  has launched to "Mixed" player reviews on Steam. Many of the player complaints are directed at
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  's seemingly aggressive monetization strategy.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  was first announced in November 2024, and immediately generated tons of excitement from fans of the franchise. The trailer for the game indicated that characters from the show would be taking a big role, with the likes of Jon Snow and Jaime Lannister shown in gameplay. While multiple
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  gameplay trailers had continued to build some hype for the game, there was always some concern among the community about the fact that it was releasing on mobile.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, post-launch into Early Access,
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  has already fallen to "Mixed" reviews on Steam, with just 67% being positive. Despite plenty of praise for the core gameplay loop, many players aren't happy that the launch of Game of Thrones:
  <em>
   Kingsroad
  </em>
  is paid, only to then be met with more paywalls when in the game itself. One review from Steam user John the Frightened claims that at "around the 18-20hr mark, the game becomes extremely reliant on timegating and struggles to handles its currencies with any respect for the user's time or balancing," describing it as "pay-to-progress."
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="game-of-thrones-kingsroad-players-aren-39-t-happy-about-monetization">
  Game of Thrones: Kingsroad Players Aren't Happy About Monetization
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1234226268" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1234226268" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1234226268" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1234226268" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1234226268-img" id="article-gallery-1-1234226268">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1234226268" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-215604369">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another review from a user called Viku claims that
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  "is a mobile game through and through," highlighting that the game's energy system "caps your daily activities." They also lament the fact that the game has charm and captures the feeling of being in Westeros, all because "the game is severely held back by the mobile design."
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  isn't coming to consoles, but it will eventually land on iOS and Android in the future. Given the nature of monetization in many mobile games, it will be interesting to see if this is addressed in the future.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's worth noting that
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  is still in Early Access, a title that usually offers games some leeway to fix its errors going forward. There are plenty of games that have made great use of Early Access in the past, so even if there are areas where
  <em>
   Game of Thrones: Kingsroad
  </em>
  can improve, it deserves the chance to fix the issues in those "Mixed" player reviews.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South of Midnight: Release Time and Date</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/south-of-midnight-early-access-release-date-time/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
  </strong>
  has been on many gamers' radars for months now. Its unique storyline combined with an intriguing visual style has captivated players ever since they got their first look at it. Players have been eagerly awaiting the launch of
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  , but they won't have to wait much longer now.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This article tells players what they need to know about
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  's launch date so they can make sure that they're ready to play when the time comes. Additionally, they will also learn more information about the early access release time and how to play it early.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="south-of-midnight-release-date-and-time">
  South of Midnight Release Date and Time
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="south of midnight folklore" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-folklore.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   launches on Tuesday, April 8, 2025, at 12 PM EDT
  </strong>
  . This when it standard version of the game becomes available and also when Game Pass subscribers get access to it. The game will release at the same time across every region, but the exact time depends on the player's timezone.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 8, 9 AM PDT
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 8, 12 PM EDT
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 8, 5 PM UTC
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="south-of-midnight-early-access-launch-date-and-time">
  South of Midnight Early Access Launch Date and Time
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="south of midnight hazel" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-hazel.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gamers who purchase the premium version of
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  or the
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  Premium Upgrade for Game Pass will unlock early access, allowing them to play up to five days earlier.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Early access for
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   begins at April 3 at 12 PM EDT
  </strong>
  . Those who have purchased the game can already pre-load it so that once the time comes, they'll be able to immediately jump into it.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 3, 9 AM PDT
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 3, 12 PM EDT
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    April 3, 5 PM UTC
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Baldur's Gate 3's Dark Urge and Astarion Are Two Sides of the Same Coin</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-dark-urge-astarion-similar-how-story-themes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur’s Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  , both the Dark Urge and Astarion grapple with the legacies of their creators. The Dark Urge, as a Bhaalspawn, was molded by the Lord of Murder himself, while Astarion endured centuries of torment under Cazador, a sadistic vampire lord. Though their origins differ, the psychological control they experience — and their subsequent fight for autonomy — create a striking narrative parallel.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This connection is emphasized through player choices.
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  ’s Dark Urge can succumb to Bhaal's call for bloodshed or resist it, mirroring Astarion’s moral struggle when confronting his former master. The two characters are not merely victims of their pasts — they are opportunities for players to explore how trauma shapes identity. The choices players make determine whether these characters break free from the chains of their creators or become embodiments of the very horrors that defined them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="trauma-and-control-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3-39-s-narrative">
  Trauma and Control in Baldur's Gate 3's Narrative
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-995676110" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-995676110" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-995676110" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-995676110" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-995676110-img" id="article-gallery-1-995676110">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-995676110" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-16836799">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The most overt link between Astarion and the Dark Urge is the concept of control. Cazador’s domination over Astarion was not merely physical; it was psychological. The centuries-long servitude inflicted unimaginable cruelty, conditioning Astarion to act on his master's whims. Even after gaining freedom, Astarion remains haunted, struggling to reclaim his sense of agency. Players witness this internal conflict throughout his Pale Elf quest, where the prospect of revenge and ascension tempts him.
 </p>
 <p>
  Similarly, the Dark Urge is driven by uncontrollable compulsions tied to its murderous lineage. Bhaal’s influence manifests in disturbing episodes of bloodlust, like the infamous scene where Alfira, the tiefling bard, is slain during a long rest. Players are faced with the moral dilemma of accepting responsibility or embracing the Dark Urge’s violent tendencies. This ongoing tension between autonomy and submission mirrors Astarion’s decision to either destroy Cazador or usurp his power through the vampire ascendant ritual.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-baldur-39-s-gate-3-39-s-choices-reflect-their-journeys">
  How Baldur's Gate 3's Choices Reflect Their Journeys
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1325658761" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1325658761" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1325658761" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1325658761" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1325658761-img" id="article-gallery-2-1325658761">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1325658761" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-969708503">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Player agency is at the core of both characters’ arcs. Choosing to help Astarion overthrow Cazador without performing the ascendant ritual showcases his potential for growth. Rejecting the path of unchecked power allows him to forge a new identity, free from his past tormentor's shadow. On the other hand, players who indulge Astarion’s darker desires may witness his transformation into the so-called “Sun King,” a ruthless figure ruling over countless vampire spawn.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Dark Urge offers similarly impactful decisions. Surrendering to Bhaal and becoming his chosen leads to one of the most sinister outcomes in
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  , cementing the protagonist as a true agent of death. Yet resisting the Dark Urge, forging meaningful connections with companions like Astarion, and defying Bhaal’s influence represent a powerful statement of personal agency. A particularly poignant moment occurs if the Dark Urge pursues a romance with Astarion. In one blood-soaked scenario, Astarion attempts to stop the Dark Urge’s violent spiral, reflecting his understanding of what it means to lose control.
 </p>
 <h3 id="thematic-lessons-for-baldur-39-s-gate-39-s-future">
  Thematic Lessons for Baldur's Gate's Future
 </h3>
 <p>
  Both characters serve as reminders of how
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  uses narrative to explore agency, trauma, and redemption. Larian Studios crafted layered character arcs that challenge players to confront difficult choices with lasting consequences. This approach sets a precedent for future installments in the
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate
  </em>
  series, even as Larian steps away from the franchise. Developers could expand on this narrative style by introducing characters with similarly conflicted backgrounds, providing even more opportunities for morally complex storytelling.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, interactions between characters like the Dark Urge and Astarion are a testament to the importance of dynamic companion writing. Astarion’s ability to empathize with the Dark Urge’s struggle — especially when other companions may condemn their actions — creates a bond that feels earned and authentic.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately,
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  uses the Dark Urge and Astarion to pose a fundamental question, that being whether people are bound by their pasts or if they can forge a new destiny. The answer lies in the hands of the player, making their stories two of the most memorable and emotionally resonant in the game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Berserker: Khazan - 8 Hardest Bosses, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-first-berserker-hardest-bosses/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Khazan features brutal boss enemies with unique gimmicks, making each encounter challenging and rewarding.
     </li>
     <li>
      Bosses like Bellerian, Elamein, and Reese test skills with various attacks and phases.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can face difficult bosses like Ozma, Maluca, and Trokka, who require strategy and quick reactions.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In typical Soulslike fashion,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The First Berserker: Khazan
   </em>
  </strong>
  features a ton of brutal boss enemies that players will encounter during their adventure, and while some can be taken down with a few well-timed parries and attacks, not all of them will fall quite as easily. Considering how tight and responsive the core combat feels in this game, each and every one of these encounters an absolute blast to partake in, though overcoming a boss to earn some sweet Gold and Lacrima is far from a walk in the park.
 </p>
 <p>
  Khazan may be fast on his feet, but many of the bosses featured in the game are a lot more mobile than some might be used to in other Soulslike games, and it goes without saying, but they can also be immensely durable. If they also have a unique gimmick up their sleeve, these fights can be even more difficult, but finally beating them can be incredibly rewarding. With that being said, it's time to take a closer look at the
  <strong>
   hardest bosses in
   <em>
    The First Berserker: Khazan
   </em>
  </strong>
  to see what exactly makes them so tough.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="bellerian">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Bellerian
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bellerian-has-plenty-of-tricks-that-can-catch-khazan-off-guard">
  Bellerian Has Plenty Of Tricks That Can Catch Khazan Off Guard
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Bellerian holding a magic crystal in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-09-05-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Hermit Mountains
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  What makes Bellerian such a difficult opponent to beat is the sheer number of powers she can use during a fight. One moment, she will be raising a barrier over herself to protect from incoming damage, while the next, she'll be summoning a swarm of hovering skulls to hunt down Khazan before they deal damage. As a result, it can be easy to get distracted while trying to break through Bellerian's defenses, and with combos being so hard to land because of her agility, Bellerian proves to be a very harsh and demanding boss to take on.
 </p>
 <p>
  Thankfully, like most mages in the game, Bellerian does possess low poise, which gives Khazan a chance to interrupt her spell-casting if he can get close enough. Being able to know when to unleash a Brutal Attack at the right moment is crucially important for being able to chip off some of Bellerian's gigantic health bar during this hectic fight.
 </p>
 <h2 id="corrupted-elamein">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Corrupted Elamein
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="with-a-durable-shield-and-one-heck-of-a-charge-attack-elamein-39-s-corrupted-form-is-tricky-to-take-on">
  With A Durable Shield And One Heck Of A Charge Attack, Elamein's Corrupted Form Is Tricky To Take On
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Corrupted Elamain in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-10-44-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Devoured Village
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Despite acting as an ally to Khazan in the early portions of the game, players will eventually be forced to clash swords with Elamein after she suddenly becomes corrupted by the Chaos. Anyone hoping to button mash their way through this fight will quickly find themselves being shut down, as Elamein loves nothing more than keeping her shield up to protect from powerful slashes and strikes.
 </p>
 <p>
  The best way to try and set up a combo is to catch her off-guard while she's performing an attack, which can be made a lot easier if a Spirit has been called into the fight. However, achieving this is easier said than done, considering Elamein also possesses a lightning-fast extended stab attack and pretty lethal AOE attacks. Bringing along items that can resist being electrocuted is a must, and being able to use the Brink Dodge at just the right time can make dishing out damage a little more manageable.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="princess-ilyna">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Princess Ilyna
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="trying-to-fight-ilyna-from-range-is-never-going-to-end-well">
  Trying To Fight Ilyna From Range Is Never Going To End Well
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Princess Ilyna in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-40-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Strange Melody
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Princess Ilyna is a nightmare to deal with at mid to long range. Because Ilyna has a plethora of spells (some of which are extremely fast, while others have homing properties), she can make quick work of the player's health bar if they don't try and close the gap as quickly as possible. It also doesn't help that most of her attacks can rack up Chaos, limiting Khazan's maximum health for a short period of time in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  While she's more of a ranged fighter, Ilyna still boasts a pretty nasty lunge attack that allows her to rush to the other side of the screen in the blink of an eye if she spots Khazan trying to make a run for it. Her quick blade jab attacks also aren't easy to parry considering how fast she is able to throw them out in succession. Players will need to keep an eye on her attack strings and be prepared to seize any opportunities that arise when taking on the infamous Princess Ilyna.
 </p>
 <h2 id="reese">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Reese
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="avoiding-a-barrage-of-spells-while-also-finding-opportunities-to-throw-out-attacks-is-no-easy-task">
  Avoiding A Barrage Of Spells While Also Finding Opportunities To Throw Out Attacks Is No Easy Task
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Reese in chaos form in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-19-06-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Bloodied Sanctuary
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The beginning of Reese's fight may seem fairly simple, but once she loses a chunk of health, Khazan's childhood friend will go into overdrive, throwing all kinds of deadly spells his way. Not only can Reese set up multiple spells at once; she can also use her wings to throw out quick and sudden pokes and swipes, which can become a real nuisance because of how random they are.
 </p>
 <p>
  The reason this fight ranks so highly, though, is because of the second phase. After becoming completely corrupted by Chaos, Reese will take on a beastial form that grants her new hard-hitting attacks. Reese's swings can also be charged up when she's in this form, so being able to correctly time a parry at the right moment can involve as much luck as it does skill when trying to react to these strikes. Considering she's also able to break out of a combo at a moment's notice and inflict Chaos while doing so, getting into the habit of hit-and-run tactics is the best way to go when encountering Reese.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hismar">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Hismar
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-colossal-dragon-who-possesses-plenty-of-unpredictable-attacks">
  A Colossal Dragon Who Possesses Plenty Of Unpredictable Attacks
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Hismay in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-20-21-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Fall Of The Empire
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players will encounter some pretty large monsters throughout a typical playthrough of
  <em>
   Khazan
  </em>
  , but none are quite as big as the legendary dragon known as Hismar. Despite its size, the beast is surprisingly fast, capable of letting out a flurry of strikes in no more than a few seconds. Players also won't be able to use the classic trick of staying underneath the monster to stop it from attacking either, as Hismar will even use its knees to crush anyone who tries to outmaneuver him. The actual size of Hismar also makes it difficult to focus on him, since many of his attacks can be charged up off-screen, making it hard to predict what's about to come next.
 </p>
 <p>
  Trying to out-survive Hismar is a recipe for disaster, so in order to deal enough damage to avoid getting worn down, it's advised to take aim at his head first. Once Hismar takes to the skies, he can be incredibly difficult to counter, especially when he starts inflicting Chaos, which is why it's worth learning his regular ground attack pattern first. This can make parrying the beast just a little easier.
 </p>
 <h2 id="maluca">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Maluca
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-grizzled-dual-bladed-warrior-is-no-joke-on-the-battlefield">
  The Grizzled Dual-Bladed Warrior Is No Joke On The Battlefield
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Maluca aiming his giant sword in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-08-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Veiled Knives
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Admittedly, Maluca has been nerfed since the game released due to being far too strong, but even after the update, this maniacal swordsman still stands as one of the trickiest bosses in the game. The first phase of his fight may be fairly manageable when keeping pressure on him and avoiding his blade strikes, but the reason so many people have struggled to take him down for good is the second phase.
 </p>
 <p>
  In his second form, Maluca becomes a heck of a lot faster and will even perform flips and leaps at the end of his attacks to avoid being countered. Additionally, some of Maluca's attacks will be so devastating that they can affect the environment itself, with one even whipping up a sandstorm to block visibility. This isn't even mentioning his combo strings, which are so long that being able to parry every attack can feel pretty impossible at times. Rings and Chaos and Resistant Necklaces can help out a lot with this fight, but ultimately, it's the player's combat skills that will be tested the most in this grueling encounter.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="trokka">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Trokka
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="trokka-has-no-shortage-of-deadly-tricks-hidden-up-her-sleeve">
  Trokka Has No Shortage Of Deadly Tricks Hidden Up Her Sleeve
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Trokka in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-30-32-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Witch's Castle
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The main reason Trokka is so downright difficult to beat is because of her variety of attacks. There's simply no telling what this mysterious magician is going to pull out after each spell. Whether it be tossing out a group of dangerous jellyish, firing off a barrage of projectiles, or even throwing down a path of ice, being able to react to Trokka's attack pattern is difficult when she's constantly changing up her fighting style.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is only the tip of the iceberg, though, as the fight will only become more chaotic as it goes on. For example, one of Trokka's most powerful moves sees her flying around the map while shooting a constant stream of projectiles at the player for them to dodge while also placing down numerous jellyfish mines around the arena, giving Khazan barely any room for maneuver. Thankfully, Trokka can be stunned out of a few of her basic moves, but if players don't have their weapons upgraded to a high enough level, they'll be in for a pretty bad time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ozma">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Ozma
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-should-be-prepared-to-pick-up-more-than-a-few-debuffs-when-fighting-the-mighty-ozma">
  Players Should Be Prepared To Pick Up More Than A Few Debuffs When Fighting The Mighty Ozma
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ozma in his Chaos form in The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/screenshot-2025-03-30-at-09-11-39-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mission:
   </strong>
   Master Of Chaos
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While Ozma may seem fairly slow at first, it won't take long until he starts throwing out explosive AOE attacks, which will almost always leave behind a nasty side effect, whether it be Chaos, Flame, or Frost. As a result of this, getting in close can be a risky venture, especially because Ozma's large and deadly slash attacks are also difficult to avoid by simply side-stepping or rolling.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though Ozma tends to use his blade for throwing out attacks, he will also rely on his giant wings to help him out against ranged opponents, just in case he wasn't already difficult enough to overcome. Moving as far away as possible when Ozma begins to generate his purple energy is important, considering that this is one of the deadliest moves in his toolkit, alongside keeping a few potions handy for dealing with his debuffs. With that being said, Ozma's final form is absurdly powerful and deceivingly fast thanks to his tentacle-like wings, with only the most skilled of players being able to take him down once and for all.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
