<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The God Of War TV Series Should Hold On To This Cast Member</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/god-of-war-tv-series-hold-on-to-richard-schiff/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   This article may contain spoilers for the God of War TV show for those who haven't played the games.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_1">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A God of War TV series with production hiccups finds a creative voice in Star Trek producer Donald Moore.
     </li>
     <li>
      Recent game installments focused on emotional storytelling and Kratos' relationship with son Atreus (Loki).
     </li>
     <li>
      Actor Richard Schiff's portrayal of Odin adds nuance to the character, leading to potential for him to reprise his role.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    God of War
   </strong>
  </em>
  TV series is being developed for Amazon Prime Video. The adaptation has experienced some production issues since its announcement. A film was in the works as early as 2005, but it has since morphed into a television series. The project suffered setbacks after a number of scripts were thrown out in favor of a new creative direction. Sony and Amazon finally found that creative voice in
  <em>
   Star Trek
  </em>
  producer Donald Moore.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kratos, the titular god of war himself, has been holding up in the frosty fjords of the Nordic realm for his last two video game outings —
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  (2018) and
  <em>
   God of War: Ragnarök
  </em>
  (2022). With his half-giant son, Atreus (
  <strong>
   a.k.a. Loki
  </strong>
  ), he has torn through the Norse pantheon, laying waste to another set of power-crazed psychopaths. These newer titles took a more emotional approach to Kratos' story, centering the narrative around the loss of his wife, Faye, and the psychological fallout of Odin's cruelty to the nine realms. If the series decides to take inspiration from these recent installments, then the creators should consider holding onto actor
  <strong>
   Richard Schiff,
  </strong>
  who played a significant voice role in those games.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the heart of the story in these two games was Kratos and Atreus' relationship as father and son. Both main titles follow their journey as the two attempt to understand clues left behind by Faye, not just about her burial, but also as to why the giants are virtually extinct and who is to blame for that genocide. It all leads up to an eventful confrontation at the beginning of
  <em>
   God of War: Ragnarök
  </em>
  between the duo and Thor, portrayed in this universe as a violent, towering monster that is built for one purpose: destruction. If Thor is the brawn, the brains of the operation and overarching antagonist of the games, Odin, makes a surprise appearance, voiced by Schiff.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="odin-doesn-39-t-derive-his-power-from-physical-strength">
  Odin Doesn't Derive His Power From Physical Strength
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1441920672" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1441920672" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1441920672" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1441920672" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1441920672-img" id="article-gallery-1-1441920672">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1441920672" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-230330773">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Odin's introduction at the opening of
  <em>
   Ragnarök
  </em>
  was a wise creative decision from Santa Monica Studios. So much mystery and intrigue had been built up around the king of the Norse gods in the first game. Kratos' companion Mimir described him as the worst of the gods: a cruel, merciless, murdering tyrant who brought whole worlds to his heel. With this reputation, it was slightly surprising to see a weedy, thin old man in Odin's first onscreen appearance. It subverted people's expectations, and subtly disarmed players by giving them a quiet, articulate negotiator, rather than the violent terror that had been advertised.
 </p>
 <p>
  In an interesting parallel to Kratos and Atreus, gamers got to see the emotional and psychological control Odin had over Thor. It lent the antagonist greater authority in the scene. Thor could have crushed him at any moment, but was clearly afraid of Odin's abilities. Odin then proceeded to present, in his eyes, a good-faith truce. But for any player worth their salt, it was an obvious attempt to pour poison in Kratos' ear. The All-Father met his match with the stalwart and resilient Kratos, but it demonstrated to the audience that Odin's reflexive form of attack is manipulation. As the story continued, Odin appeared in various negotiations, influenced by shifting alliances and feuds, all in an attempt to assume absolute control.
 </p>
 <p>
  This interpretation reflected a key part of the gods' description in Norse mythology. In the MCU, a huge part of what was missing from Odin's character was his cunning and persona as a trickster. Antony Hopkins did a fine job portraying a strong, imposing, and wise leader, but this only gave audiences a small glimpse into the All-Father's personality. In
  <em>
   God of War,
  </em>
  his charismatic and power-obsessed qualities are portrayed brilliantly. Admittedly, this is a more evil, menacing interpretation that deviates from Norse legend to fit in with the themes of the
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  universe. However, it conveys some of the most essential aspects of Odin's identity: his thirst for knowledge, his inability to lose, his lust for power, and at all times, the execution of his master plan.
 </p>
 <h2 id="don-39-t-let-richard-schiff-out-of-your-sight">
  Don't Let Richard Schiff Out Of Your Sight
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1103150959" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1103150959" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1103150959" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1103150959" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1103150959-img" id="article-gallery-2-1103150959">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1103150959" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1682472217">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In so many ways, Richard Schiff was perfect voice casting to play Odin in the
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  series. The actor is most known for his Emmy-award-winning role as Toby Ziegler on
  <em>
   The
  </em>
  <em>
   West Wing.
  </em>
  In the series, Schiff is the White House's Communications Director, and portrays an intelligent, master political negotiator. Odin is of a similar breed, taking Atreus into his household and switching from the role of villain to misunderstood mentor. The All-Father attempts to warp the young Loki's (
  <strong>
   Atreus
  </strong>
  ) mind towards his purposes, trying to convince him that the Asgardians' bloody history is misrepresented, and his actions are all for a good cause.
 </p>
 <p>
  Schiff also brings a great deal of nuance to the part, slowly weening out Odin's paranoia and putting his thirst for knowledge front and center. There was one thing that Odin failed to master in the games, and that was his knowledge of what happens to gods when they die. He agonizes over it for the whole story, refusing to believe that the gods simply disappear when they die. He manipulates Atreus into helping him discover the secret. Schiff masterfully portrayed this, bringing a whole new dynamic to the All-Father.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since Schiff is already an established onscreen presence, Amazon would be remiss not to allow Schiff to reprise his role on the series. Prime Video will be considering a range of people to cast in their show. Finn Wolfhard recently expressed a desire to play Atreus in an adaptation. It's not too much of a stretch to see him as a live-action version of Sunny Suljic's Atreus. But considering that Suljic is a fairly well-established screen actor, there would be a strong argument for keeping him in the part. The
  <strong>
   <em>
    God of War
   </em>
  </strong>
  TV series doesn't need to look too far to find their casting for a retelling of the Norse Saga. Some actors in the video game cast, like Schiff, are already perfect.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Indie Game Gives Breath of the Wild Vibes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/upcoming-indie-game-gives-breath-of-the-wild-vibes-the-knightling/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Legend of Zelda series inspired many adventure games like it. Breath of the Wild specifically led to many titles with the same vibe. The upcoming game, The Knightling, seems to be doing the club.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Rift - Official Reveal Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/lost-rift-official-reveal-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Lost Rift is a first-person survival shooter developed by People Can Fly. See the official reveal trailer here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 Finally Fixes Its Most Annoying Issue</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-new-game-main-menu-removed/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Warhorse Studios removes the New Game option from the in-game pause menu in Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      Its removal is to prevent accidental overwrites of existing playlines after countless complaints from players.
     </li>
     <li>
      The official patch notes state that a "more robust" solution will be implemented in a future update.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new update for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  has removed the option to start a new game from the pause menu, something that has been highly requested by fans ever since the game's launch back in early February. While the latest
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  update isn't nearly as big as its 1.2 patch that was released earlier this month, fans are pleased to see the annoying placement of the New Game option finally removed.
 </p>
 <p>
  After a hugely successful launch with rave reviews from both players and critics, developer Warhorse Studios released the first major content update for
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  on March 13. Alongside a ton of bug fixes and improvements, players were also treated to official modding support on PC and a new barber feature. After updating to version 1.2, players can visit one of the two new barbers in either Trosky or Kuttenberg and give Henry a brand-new look with a fresh hairstyle and beard. Customizing Henry's appearance will also grant a temporary "Freshly Trimmed" buff, which increases the player's Charisma by 2.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2-removes-new-game-option-from-pause-menu">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 Removes New Game Option From Pause Menu
 </h2>
 <p>
  On March 20, Warhorse Studios released yet another update for
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  ​​​​​​. While the patch wasn't quite as substantial as its predecessor, it did finally remove the New Game option from the pause menu, something fans have wanted to see changed for weeks now. According to the patch notes for update 1.2.2, Warhorse Studios has removed the New Game option from the in-game pause menu "to prevent accidental overwrites of existing playlines." While fans seem incredibly pleased by the change, it looks like its removal may only be temporary, as the patch notes state that a "more robust" solution will be implemented in a future update.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1081298889" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1081298889" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1081298889" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1081298889" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1081298889-img" id="article-gallery-1-1081298889">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1081298889" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1698822298">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Shortly after the game's launch, players quickly took issue with the placement of the New Game option when in the pause menu. Unlike many other games, New Game was the very first option that appeared when pausing the game, which quickly resulted in complaints from players due to accidentally starting a whole new game when most expected Resume to be the first available option. While
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  received rave reviews, this is one issue that players were eager to see fixed. Fans have already taken to Reddit to praise the update, with many exclaiming "finally."
 </p>
 <p>
  It's unclear when Warhorse Studios intends to release the game's next update, but there is plenty of new content in the works for the smash hit sequel. According to the post-launch roadmap for
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  , fans can still expect to see two more content updates released in the Spring. The next update is expected to include the highly anticipated Hardcore Mode, followed by another update with a new horse racing feature. There will also be three paid expansions released throughout the rest of 2025, the first of which will launch in the Summer, followed by a second DLC in the Autumn and a third in the Winter.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomfall: Release Time &amp; Date</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/atomfall-release-time-launch-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Standard Atomfall Release Date &amp; Time
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Atomfall Advanced Access Release Date &amp; Time
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rebellion's latest game,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Atomfall
   </em>
  </strong>
  ​​​​​​, is right around the corner – but players who are excited to get into this post-apocalyptic U.K. setting can start playing the game a few days ahead of the
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  standard release date by purchasing certain special editions.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Because the game will be released at the same time across the world, depending on where you live, the exact
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  release time and date may vary. This guide explains when the Standard Edition
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  release date is across several major time zones, the advanced access
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  launch time, and how to play
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  early in the first place.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="standard-atomfall-release-date-amp-time">
  Standard Atomfall Release Date &amp; Time
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Atomfall Release Date Wyndham Village Green" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wyndham-village-green.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  is set to
  <strong>
   release on March 27, 2025
  </strong>
  across all available platforms, including
  <strong>
   PlayStation 4 and 5, Xbox One and Series X|S, and PC
  </strong>
  . The game will
  <strong>
   not launch on the Nintendo Switch
  </strong>
  , and it is not known whether the game will come to the Switch 2 when it launches later in 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, depending on where you are located in the world, the exact
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  release time may change. The
  <strong>
   game is set to launch at 10 a.m. EST (US) on March 27
  </strong>
  , but if you live in a far-eastern time zone such as Australia or New Zealand,
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  will not become available until the wee hours of the morning on March 28.
 </p>
 <h3 id="atomfall-advanced-access-global-release-times-chart">
  Atomfall Advanced Access Global Release Times Chart
 </h3>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Time Zone
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Console EA Launch Time
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       PST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       7:00 a.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       EST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       10:00 a.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       GMT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       2:00 p.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       CET
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       3:00 p.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       SGT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       10 p.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       JST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       11 p.m. (March 27)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       AEDT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       1 a.m. (March 28)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       NZDT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       3 a.m. (March 28)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="atomfall-advanced-access-release-date-amp-time">
  Atomfall Advanced Access Release Date &amp; Time
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Atomfall Release Date Wicker Man" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/atomfall-release-date-wicker-man.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though the
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  release date is set for March 27, 2025 across all time zones, players
  <strong>
   can play the game up to three days early if they pre-purchase the Deluxe or Quarantine editions
  </strong>
  of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Atomfall
   </em>
   Advanced Access release date is March 24, 2025
  </strong>
  . However, just like the standard edition, depending on where you live in the world, you may not be able to play
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  until the next day because this is a concurrent global release.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though we have listed common time zones below, if you convert 10 a.m. EST (U.S.) to your local time, you will find out what time
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  launches in your time zone.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-atomfall-early-access">
  How To Get Atomfall Early Access
 </h3>
 <p>
  To
  <strong>
   play
   <em>
    Atomfall
   </em>
   early, you must purchase either the Deluxe Edition or Quarantine Edition of
   <em>
    Atomfall
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The Deluxe Edition is available for $69.99 and includes a variety of bonus items and access to the Story Expansion Pack, while the Quarantine Edition costs $89.99 and comes with a T-Shirt and a variety of extra bonuses, in addition to everything contained in the Deluxe Edition.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both the Deluxe Edition and Quarantine Edition grant
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  Advanced Access on March 24, 2025.
 </p>
 <h3 id="atomfall-advanced-access-global-release-times-chart">
  Atomfall Advanced Access Global Release Times Chart
 </h3>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Time Zone
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Console EA Launch Time
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       PST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       7:00 a.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       EST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       10:00 a.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       GMT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       2:00 p.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       CET
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       3:00 p.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       SGT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       10 p.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       JST
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       11 p.m. (March 24)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       AEDT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       1 a.m. (March 25)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       NZDT
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       3 a.m. (March 25)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
