<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How Cyberpunk 2077's NCPD Could Become More Frightening in a Sequel</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cyberpunk-2077-ncpd-police-presence-improvement-sequel-aggressive-corrupt/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Cyberpunk 2077
   </em>
  </strong>
  's sequel, currently known only as
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , is interesting to speculate about for several reasons, not the least of which being the wellspring of potential left behind by the former. Something that CD Projekt Red honed in on toward the tail end of its
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  redemption project is the NCPD, making them a more integral part of the gameplay experience through
  <em>
   GTA
  </em>
  -esque pursuit mechanics that many would have expected to be included from the jump.
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  can take this concept even further.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The NCPD is defined by corruption. There are certainly some "good eggs," so to speak, like Regina Jones, who seem to be trying their best to make their way through the complex web of Night City's criminal world without getting stained, but any notion of the police force at large being for the people is mostly a farce. Just a year before
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's narrative kicks off, the NCPD was privatized in an effort to cut costs, turning it into a quasi-military force with close ties to the privatized prison system. In other words, the NCPD is basically just another corp in
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's twisted capitalist nightmare, and this nightmare can become more florid in the next game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_2">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     All of this is to say nothing of MaxTac, a "law enforcement" brigade composed of chromed-out, deadly combat specialists.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="project-orion-can-make-the-ncpd-more-intimidating-and-impactful">
  Project Orion Can Make the NCPD More Intimidating and Impactful
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-417863654" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-417863654" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-417863654" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-417863654" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-417863654-img" id="article-gallery-1-417863654">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-417863654" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1280156830">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="honing-in-on-corruption-could-make-the-ncpd-a-greater-threat-in-project-orion">
  Honing In On Corruption Could Make the NCPD a Greater Threat in Project Orion
 </h3>
 <p>
  It shouldn't come as a surprise that the NCPD is rife with corruption, with most officers either being bullies or tending toward greed rather than the pursuit of justice. With little to no oversight, and the profit-driven philosophy of private industry, there's almost no chance for the police force to be a positive entity in Night City.
 </p>
 <p>
  Perhaps players could engage with more of these corrupt cops in
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , gaining greater insight into just how dangerous unchecked power and desperation can be. Maybe the game could feature a character similar to
  <em>
   GTA San Andreas
  </em>
  ' Frank Tenpenny: a power-hungry sociopath with a desire to leverage their power to cause greater strife and violence in the city they are meant to protect and serve. Such an archetype would be naturally elevated in a
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  sequel, as its setting and narrative context would mean even less recourse for those affected by law enforcement's misdeeds. Offering a window into the unfettered depravity facilitated by privatized law enforcement is certainly one way to make the NCPD a more intimidating and disturbing presence.
 </p>
 <h3 id="project-orion-could-make-cops-scarier-on-the-gameplay-front-as-well">
  Project Orion Could Make Cops Scarier On the Gameplay Front as Well
 </h3>
 <p>
  At launch,
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  didn't have a fully fleshed-out police system, but post-launch updates have improved matters. In its current state,
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  features cops that will, at the very least, pursue V once they get into a car, ramping up their presence in accordance to the player's wanted level. It's not as immersive or deep as something like
  <em>
   GTA
  </em>
  's police system, but it's a major improvement from launch, making the NCPD something to actually worry about in the overworld.
 </p>
 <p>
  Naturally, making this system more multifaceted and relentless would go a long way toward making the NCPD more intimidating in
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  . Maybe police officers could employ more diverse methods for apprehending the player, making use of more advanced technology like EMPs or quickhacks. After all, the world of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  offers several unique options for bloody conflict, but the NCPD, in its current state, doesn't make much use of them. Perhaps, with its struggle to slow the climbing crime rates in the first game, the NCPD could significantly increase its budget and further decrease its ethical qualms in
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Mafia 2 Mod Adds New Missions and Working Metro System</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/mafia-2-final-cut-mod-2025-update-new-missions-working-metro/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mafia 2's Final Cut mod update for 2025 will introduce new content, including a fully functional metro system and additional missions.
     </li>
     <li>
      The trailer released by the modders suggests the potential addition of an alternative ending for Mafia 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      Initially released in 2023, the Final Cut mod has since added new cut dialogues, new locations, and various design changes.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A team of modders has released a new update for its massive
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mafia 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  mod titled “Final Cut,” which expands the game with a wealth of new content, including additional plots and missions, a fully functional metro system, and more.
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  ’s Final Cut mod introduces numerous enhancements to sound, textures, and graphics, with its next update slated for release in 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  was a successful sequel that built upon the foundation of its predecessor. The story follows a war veteran who finds himself drawn into organized crime to pay off his debts. In 2020,
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  received a remastered version for PS4, Xbox One, and PC, featuring enhanced graphics and all previously released DLC. Later, in 2023, a team of modders released the original version of the Final Cut mod, expanding and refining several aspects of the game. Now, the modders are gearing up to release the next update, introducing even more content to the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  ’s “Final Cut” update 1.3 is expected to launch in 2025. Known as Night Wolves, the team of modders has released a two-minute trailer showcasing the new content. Among the notable additions to
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  ’s gangster world, players will now be able to use a fully functional metro system, allowing them to travel throughout the city. Additionally, the update introduces new scenes and gameplay moments for various characters, and the trailer suggests that the opening mission has been expanded. Finally, the trailer hints at a potential alternative ending, which only seasoned players of
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  are likely to notice.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="mafia-2-final-cut-mod-update-1-3-trailer-revealed">
  Mafia 2 Final Cut Mod Update 1.3 Trailer Revealed
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-7dbb7f4aa6dde88e" id="emaki-video-player-7dbb7f4aa6dde88e">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  Final Cut mod first launched in 2023 and has since added several new features to the game. In its latest update, the mod introduced cut dialogues and cutscenes, as well as various features such as the ability to sit in bars and homes, which enhance the immersion of
  <em>
   Mafia 2
  </em>
  ’s story and gameplay. It also added new locations like the Maxwell Supermarket and a car dealership. The Final Cut mod further included graphic and design changes, such as a complete overhaul of the game’s map and newspapers, along with new shooting sounds.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-945212999" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-945212999" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-945212999" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-945212999" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-945212999-img" id="article-gallery-1-945212999">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-945212999" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1471613646">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The installation process for the mod is straightforward but varies depending on whether users have any DLC installed. Players can find detailed instructions for installing the Final Cut mod on Night Wolves’ NexusMods page. For fans of this classic entry in the
  <em>
   Mafia
  </em>
  franchise, the Final Cut mod is a noteworthy addition.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Pokedex Entries Were Literal (Volume 58)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/if-pokedex-entries-were-literal-volume-58/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Some pokemon shouldn't join their owners at the restaurant table.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper Light Breaker's Core Gameplay Loop Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hyper-light-breakers-gameplay-interview/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Releasing to Steam Early Access on January 14,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
  </strong>
  is the long-awaited sequel to 2016's
  <em>
   Hyper Light Drifter
  </em>
  and transitions the series from its iconic 2D pixel art style to an equally vibrant 3D world.
  <em>
   Hyper Light Breaker
  </em>
  players take on the role of a Breaker, tasked with venturing into procedurally-generated biomes in order to defeat enemies and collect new gear on their way to confronting the Abyss King. The ambitious roguelike from developer Heart Machine has already showcased plenty of impressive-looking footage of alpha gameplay.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Game Rant sat down with Lead Producer Michael Clark and Senior Designer Ben Strickland to discuss
  <em>
   Hyper Light Breaker gameplay
  </em>
  in more detail. They broke down some of the game's core mechanics, the inspiration behind it, and the build variety on offer.
  <strong>
   This interview has been edited for clarity and brevity
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-hyper-light-breaker-caters-to-a-wide-audience">
  How Hyper Light Breaker Caters to a Wide Audience
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1602919283" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1602919283" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1602919283" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1602919283" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1602919283-img" id="article-gallery-1-1602919283">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1602919283" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1616645708">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   is introducing multiplayer gameplay. How do you balance cooperative elements with the original solo experience to ensure a cohesive experience?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  We have difficulty scaling systems that dynamically scale things based on the number of players. You’ll see tankier, harder-hitting bosses, more enemies per enemy group, harder enemies in a group appearing earlier, harder extractions, etc. It’s important to us to treat difficulty scaling as something more than just stat-tuning - while sometimes stats are the right thing to be changing in order to change difficulty, these other elements create a better multiplayer experience that can’t be attained with just scaling damage numbers. Our process starts by finding something that feels right for solo players, and then using these tools to scale the difficulty up for multiplayer.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Overall, how would you summarize
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   ’s gameplay loop?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strickland:
  </strong>
  The game is broken up into cycles and runs. In every cycle, we roll a new map and populate it with monsters and treasure. The player’s goal for the cycle is to defeat the three Crowns (Bosses) and open the way to the Abyss King. Players can take multiple runs at the map, collecting gear and building themselves up until they either get strong enough to tackle the Crowns or die trying. At the end of a cycle, win or lose, we reset the map, but the player comes away with the means to buff themselves and improve their chances for the next cycle.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-hyper-light-breaker-combines-open-world-and-roguelike-genres">
  How Hyper Light Breaker Combines Open-World and Roguelike Genres
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-545442230" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-545442230" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-545442230" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-545442230" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-545442230-img" id="article-gallery-2-545442230">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-545442230" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1741832796">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   is described as the first “open-world roguelike.” Can you talk about how you combined these two genres and what challenges(and successes) came from this hybridization?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  We started with an “impossible problem” - a term for contradictory features in a game - open world games are about retreading spaces, learning them and becoming familiar, and approaching things at your own pace. Roguelikes are about fast action and disposing of everything and starting fresh.
 </p>
 <p>
  Early on, we had a classic roguelike formula and found that even with a too-small world that captured none of the things we wanted from an open world - we still had too much game. One of the attractions of the roguelike genre is that runs are fast enough that you can do “just one more run” and not commit hours of your life to it. Speed running those early versions still took an hour+ to complete, and it never felt like an open world - again, in an open world, you are learning the space and recognizing features as you come back- all of that was absent.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the fall of 2023, we decided we needed to make some radical changes. We wanted you to spend hours with each procedurally generated world, but we wanted a run to be short enough that you could do a few in an hour. Alx and I were chatting about this one night and I mentioned that whenever you die in an extraction game it feels similar to dying in a roguelike, and we started talking through how extraction could be the way to both capture the feeling an open world game and the highs and lows of a roguelike game. With that allowing us to decouple the scale of the world from the time it takes to complete a run, the team built a bespoke world that we experimented with until we had figured out what we wanted from a procedural open world. We wanted three things:
 </p>
 <p>
  Space - the biggest frustration with our old model was the world was too small and too dense, it felt like you were Godzilla stomping through Disneyland - you’d frequently aggro several different enemy groups while fighting one. We made the worlds larger, giving us space between each element, allowing us to build bigger structures, etc.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unique, memorable terrain - our early versions were built with multiple islands, and while each biome is vibrant and radically different in aesthetic, there just wasn’t enough space on those islands for big mountains, long beaches, etc.
 </p>
 <p>
  Terrain that matters - this was the most important element. In early versions, we had undulating terrain, but you could always beeline your way over any terrain. It rendered all the world useless - you didn’t have anything to learn or remember or notice. You had no surprises. To accomplish this, our procedural generation team had to completely rethink and rebuild how we generate worlds. We built a new process that starts by laying out the key locations that players must always be able to reach - Crown Arenas and Prisms. We connect these key locations with paths. Then we generate our terrain, with mountains and cliffs and rivers. Finally, we take those paths and we use those to identify where we need to add a bridge, carve a switchback into a mountainside, or add some jump pads to give you a fast way up a sheer cliff face - if you can find them.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hyper-light-breaker-39-s-inspiration-and-approach-to-hub-world">
  Hyper Light Breaker's Inspiration and Approach to Hub World
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Were there any titles you looked to for inspiration when combining the two above genres?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strickland:
  </strong>
  If I recall correctly,
  <em>
   Risk of Rain 2
  </em>
  drove a lot of early conversations since it featured a lot of open environments. Over time, we started looking at several extraction-y games (
  <em>
   Call of Duty: DMZ
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Witchfire
  </em>
  ).
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/hyper-light-breakers-game-rant-advance-npc-pherus-bit.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: What can you tell us about the hub city that players will be exploring in between runs? Does it also feature elements of random generation or is it more static and constant? What kind of features/characters can be experienced there?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strickland:
  </strong>
  The Cursed Outpost is the one part of the game that isn't constantly changing - it’s a fixed point in a world that is always reshaping itself. Sure, there are things to unlock and critters who want to sell you things, but it’s a calm, vibe-y place to return to after the chaos of a run.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: How did you approach roguelite concepts like meta-progression? How much did you want players to lose or keep between runs?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strickland:
  </strong>
  This is something we’ve gone back and forth on quite a bit. We’ve always had a concept of players building up their Sycoms (read: character classes) and unlocking permanent upgrades between cycles - pretty standard stuff - but on a more granular level, there was always a question as to how we should treat the weapons and mods the players were picking up on every run, the more modular stuff. Earlier in the project, the game was very punishing; players would lose almost everything at the end of a run, or we would melt everything down at the end of a cycle...which can be discouraging! Eventually, we started folding in some elements that would allow gear and mods to persist for longer - introducing the concept of gear durability or the ability to stash gear in a vault.
 </p>
 <h3 id="hyper-light-breaker-39-s-biomes-and-traversal-explained">
  Hyper Light Breaker's Biomes and Traversal Explained
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: How large can each of
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   ’s different biomes be? Do these change between runs?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  Each world is roughly the same size - they’ll take a while to cross from one end to the other even on your hoverboard. Each world is comprised of 3 (of a total of 4 at early access launch) biomes, which are also roughly the same size, but all of our worlds have a lot of natural features that add a lot of wiggle room. You’ll do multiple runs in the same world per Cycle, but each Cycle comes with a whole new world, with new terrain and biomes and structures and everything. There are a few things that change right now at launch from run to run, but over the course of Early Access we’re looking to add a lot more dynamic changes to each run.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1489010373" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1489010373" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1489010373" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1489010373" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1489010373-img" id="article-gallery-3-1489010373">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1489010373" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1099032652">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Can you talk about all the possible traversal features, like the hoverboard, and their overall role in the game?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strickland:
  </strong>
  Our maps are large, have a lot of verticality, AND we give the player a lot of freedom with the order in which they tackle their missions. There’s a lot of ground to cover! A lot of our traversal features are low-key quality-of-life improvements. There’s loot at the bottom of that cliff? Pull out your glider and float down. You’ve opened the way to a Crown’s arena? Get on your hoverboard and go. There’s plenty of space to admire the world and vibe out, but if you’re getting down to business, we’ve given you the toolkit to do it efficiently.
 </p>
 <h3 id="hyper-light-breaker-39-s-approach-to-progression-and-build-variety">
  Hyper Light Breaker's Approach to Progression and Build Variety
 </h3>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Can you discuss how progression systems and character/skill customization work in
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   ?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  There are four major progression systems that will have you powering up over time - your vault, which is the gear you’re collecting - you’ll lose gear when you die, but amassing a vault of gear will keep you going into the next run with the power you need to succeed. You’ll find gear everywhere in Breaker - killing enemies, finding secrets, buying them from vendors, and looting chests. The second system is your SyComs - each character has multiple SyComs, which provide unique abilities and stats, and those stats are upgradeable - want more health or want to hit harder with your Rail? That’s how you’ll do that. You upgrade your SyComs by spending Cores - rare items that are found throughout the world.
 </p>
 <p>
  Next up are Player .EXEs - these are permanent upgrades that add new functionality to your Breaker - making your starting gear more powerful, letting you reflect projectiles with a parry, carry medkits, etc. These are unlocked with Golden Rations. Finally, you can also gift those Golden Rations to the various vendors and build your relationship with them - this will unlock deals, weapon upgrades, and other abilities with the vendors.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-825563177" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-825563177" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-825563177" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-825563177" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-825563177-img" id="article-gallery-4-825563177">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-825563177" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-583266635">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Can you talk about how you approached build variety in
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   ? How much might two players' playstyles differ? Were you looking to fill specific roles or archetypes?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  We started designing our gear by envisioning a large number of specific archetype builds - tank, summoner, sniper, etc. The gear supporting these builds formed an initial pool, but this approach generates a lot of narrow-use gear that doesn’t mix and match well - so once we have that pool, we start changing things up to make things more flexible. From there, it’s mostly a matter of playing a lot and asking “what do I want to find next to make this cooler? Is that in the game?” Ultimately it comes down to playing the game a LOT, and trying a lot of different combinations.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   [END]
  </strong>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Marvel Rivals Banning Mods is a Necessary Evil</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-ban-modes-free-to-play-cosmetics-revenue-good-bad/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Marvel Rivals
   </strong>
  </em>
  is off to a huge start and the game hasn’t even hit its first official season yet. With more than 20 million active players in the three short weeks since its launch, NetEase has an incredible amount of forward momentum to make the comic book-themed hero shooter one of the next big players in the live service ecosystem. There’s a huge and active fan community for the game, though it comes with its own set of pros and cons.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When a game reaches the massive popularity that a title like
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is currently enjoying, there’s almost inevitably going to be a vibrant and thriving modding community that crops up around it. Normally, this is a great thing; mods keep fans engaged with a game over time, and it’s a great expression of a community’s creativity. But in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' unique case, banning users from accessing mods might be better for the overall health of the game in the long run.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-marvel-rivals-needs-to-crack-down-on-mods">
  Why Marvel Rivals Needs to Crack Down On Mods
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1762189136" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1762189136" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1762189136" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1762189136" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1762189136-img" id="article-gallery-1-1762189136">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1762189136" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-608991280">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="client-side-cosmetic-mods-decrease-marvel-rivals-39-ability-to-effectively-monetize">
  Client-Side Cosmetic Mods Decrease Marvel Rivals' Ability to Effectively Monetize
 </h3>
 <p>
  When it comes to mods, there’s one type that everyone will agree should be banned wholesale and it’s mods that give the player an otherwise unfair advantage over their opponents. No one in their right mind would ever argue against NetEase using whatever means it can to prevent cheaters from ruining the experience for others. But unfortunately, it’s not just these types of mods that NetEase is going to have to bring down the hammer on.
 </p>
 <p>
  A big part of what’s made
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  so successful is the fact that it’s free-to-play. It’s heavily accessible to just about anyone with a PC or console able to run it, with the entirety of the game’s business coming from transactions made in the in-game store. Like
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  , the lifeblood of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  comes from these largely cosmetic purchases.
 </p>
 <p>
  Simple client-side mods that change the appearance of a character seem pretty harmless on the surface, but these will eventually impact NetEase’s ability to keep the game running over the next few years. A mod that gives Captain America his outfit from
  <em>
   Avengers: Infinity War
  </em>
  is just a matter of the gamer's personal preferences. That is until NetEase releases its version of that skin and loses money from players with the mod already installed.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s an unfortunate situation, but it’s a necessary decision for the developers that will help support the game far into the future.
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is one of the most promising hero shooters the industry has seen in a number of years, and with a full back catalog of Marvel heroes and villains to add, there’s potential for it to expand and surpass any of its competitors in just a few short years' time. It would be tragic if the game had to shutter its doors early because it wasn’t generating enough revenue due to unofficial fan-made mods.
 </p>
 <h3 id="on-the-bright-side-of-the-marvel-rivals-modding-situation">
  On the Bright Side of the Marvel Rivals Modding Situation
 </h3>
 <p>
  It’s not all gloom and doom, though. Yes, the free-to-play nature of the game means that NetEase will have to crack down on cosmetic mods. But on the flip side of that, it means that fans will soon be getting a whole host of cosmetic options to satiate their desire for new content/skins.
 </p>
 <p>
  If cosmetics are the lifeblood of a free-to-play game like
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , then there will certainly be a glut of them coming down the pipeline for the same reason NetEase will have to eventually take a hardline against mods: they need to keep the lights on somehow. And with each character in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  coming complete with decades of alternate costumes and looks from the comics, movies, and television shows, players will be eating very well when it comes to their cosmetic options for their favorite heroes.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
