<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>'83 - Official Re-Announcement Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/83-official-re-announcement-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  '83, a spiritual successor to Rising Storm 2 Vietnam, has been re-announced, with the developers working on an early-access release. Watch the official trailer here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Player Discovers Handy Trick for New Season 2 Map</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-lifeline-map-alternative-route-trick/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 player discovers a sneaky flanking route on Lifeline.
     </li>
     <li>
      The player discovered an out-of-bounds trick that allows players to pop up behind the enemy spawn point.
     </li>
     <li>
      Lifeline is one of the three new maps added to Black Ops 6 with Season 2.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  player has discovered a handy traversal trick for the new Season 2 map, Lifeline, allowing them to appear behind the enemy spawn point without being seen. Lifeline was just one of three new maps added to
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  with the game's Season 2 update and is set onboard a luxury yacht similar to Hijacked, which was a popular multiplayer map during the days of
  <em>
   Black Ops 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  After one of the longest seasons in
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  history,
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  ​​​​'s highly-anticipated Season 2 update was finally released on January 28. The patch brought with it a fresh Battle Pass filled with new weapons, operator skins, Double XP tokens, and various other cosmetic items. While
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  players were also treated to new maps and modes,
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  players had less content to check out as Activision confirmed it would be prioritizing gameplay tuning, bug fixes, and quality-of-life improvements for Season 2. The decision comes after multiple weeks of complaints from players, as many believe
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  is
  <em>
  </em>
  in its worst state to date.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="call-of-duty-black-ops-6-player-discovers-alternative-route-on-lifeline">
  Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Player Discovers Alternative Route on Lifeline
 </h2>
 <p>
  With the game's Season 2 update, developer Treyarch Studios released three new maps for
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , with two more still to come during the mid-season update. One of the most highly-anticipated maps to arrive with Season 2 was Lifeline, with fans instantly comparing it to Hijacked from 2012's
  <em>
   Black Ops 2
  </em>
  ​​​​​​. The map can be played on either 6v6 modes, such as Team Deathmatch, or on the popular Gunfight mode, which is 2v2. With the map being so small, one player has discovered a handy traversal trick to quickly get behind the enemy spawn point and rack up plenty of kills in quick succession.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the short clip, the user shows how it is possible to dive off the side of the yacht in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  's Lifeline map and swim to the back end of the ship. With less than a second left before being eliminated for being out of bounds, the player springs up behind the enemy team and racks up plenty of eliminations. As diving into the water is not technically part of the map, players only have three seconds to pull off this trick before they are eliminated, so it might take a few attempts.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-623457363" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-623457363" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-623457363" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-623457363" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-623457363-img" id="article-gallery-1-623457363">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-623457363" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-86244236">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This isn't the first time that a player has discovered an out-of-bounds trick on one of the game's maps. Not long after its release,
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  players discovered a similar traversal trick on Stakeout, one of the game's most popular maps. On one side of the map is a hallway with a set of stairs; while these stairs are blocked by a small rope that indicates an out-of-bounds area, players quickly realized that they can still venture up the stairs and jump from the top floor back into the center of the map. Again, with only three seconds on the clock, it requires some quick and precise movements to pull off successfully.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect from Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap Post-Release</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/orcs-must-die-deathtrap-post-launch-plans-maps-characters/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Four years since its last entry, the
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die!
  </em>
  series is back with the release of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The game introduces a four-player co-op, roguelite mechanics, and six new War Mages to the saga, while maintaining classic
  <em>
   OMD!
  </em>
  features like third-person view and fantasy elements.
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap
  </em>
  also brings back the fan-favorite Mage Max as a playable character and Gabriella as an NPC in the lobby.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Earlier in September, developer Robot Entertainment confirmed that Gabriella would eventually join the
  <em>
   OMD! Deathtrap
  </em>
  playable roster sometime after the game's release. Like previous
  <em>
   OMD!
  </em>
  titles,
  <em>
   Deathtrap
  </em>
  is expected to receive periodic updates after launch. In a recent interview with Game Rant, game director Kyle Snyder shared details about what's next in store for
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap
  </em>
  throughout its first year.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-orcs-must-die-deathtrap-fans-can-look-forward-to-after-launch">
  What Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap Fans Can Look Forward to After Launch
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1065415741" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1065415741" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1065415741" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1065415741" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1065415741-img" id="article-gallery-1-1065415741">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1065415741" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1653582591">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="omd-deathtrap-39-s-closest-post-launch-content">
  OMD! Deathtrap's Closest Post-Launch Content
 </h3>
 <p>
  Snyder revealed that Gabriella will become playable sooner rather than later, and she will not be debuting alone. A new map, called Resort Canal, will be added in upcoming updates. According to Snyder, the development team is already "hard at work on a lot of exciting additions" and more traps, characters, and enemies are coming to
  <em>
   OMD! Deathtrap
  </em>
  's first and later years.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "Gabriella and a new map, Resort Canal, will be coming not too long after launch, in addition to a few other little surprises. And then, throughout the year and beyond, we’ll be adding more traps, War Mages, enemies, modes, and maps."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Snyder did not elaborate much on the availability of these additions, but he stated that "all maps will be free for all players" so fans can rest assured that some free content is in the works. He added that the team is still also looking into integrating player feedback in future features. Player input was a big part of the development of
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die! Deathtrap
  </em>
  , with Robot Entertainment holding multiple playtests ahead of launch to refine aspects like barricades and multiplayer balance. Snyder intends to carry the practice of involving players in decisions forward, especially as more players try out
  <em>
   OMD! Deathtrap
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="gabriella-39-s-kit-and-more-new-mages">
  Gabriella's Kit and More New Mages
 </h3>
 <p>
  Along with Max, Gabriella is one of the popular characters from the
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die!
  </em>
  series. She debuted in
  <em>
   OMD! 2
  </em>
  and consistently remained part of the roster in the following titles. Unlike Max, she wasn't available in
  <em>
   Deathtrap
  </em>
  on day one, but Snyder revealed that Gabriella's kit will introduce "a new and improved arcane magic and status effect," features that are deliberately absent from the base game. This likely follows
  <em>
   Deathtrap
  </em>
  's goal of giving each Mage their own unique abilities. Finally, Snyder shared that Gabriella is getting a new battle outfit and the game director is confident that her design will appeal to fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  But Gabriella won't be the last War Mage in the works for
  <em>
   OMD! Deathtrap
  </em>
  . The base game presents Kalos and Sophie, two anthropomorphic Mages with bear and cat-like features, respectively. The last entry in the
  <em>
   Orcs Must Die!
  </em>
  series with animal characters was
  <em>
   OMD! Unchained,
  </em>
  so Snyder was excited to reintroduce this type of War Mages in
  <em>
   Deathtrap
  </em>
  . He revealed that Sophie was his favorite character in the game so far, and she proved to be popular among fans during playtests as well. Snyder admitted that there are plenty of fantasy races to choose from for character design, and added that more anthropomorphic Mages are very likely to join the
  <em>
   OMD! Deathtrap
  </em>
  roster.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "I don’t expect us to stop at bears and cats, so definitely expect even more variety in the future."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Snyder mentioned that "other little surprises" are coming soon, so hopefully fans won't wait too long to see what developers have prepared for them.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds - Go Wild Together Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/monster-hunter-wilds-go-wild-together-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Check out this official Go Wild Together trailer for Monster Hunter Wilds, which shows off the game's co-op play. The game is set to be released on February 28, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why March 2025 Is the Perfect Time to Finally Jump Into Fallout 76</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-76-march-25-start-playing-why-season-20/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  After its infamously rough launch,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 76
   </em>
  </strong>
  has grown immensely from what the game once was. Throughout the past six years, tons of new content updates and countless gameplay improvements have flipped the narrative for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , redeeming the game from its troubled past. With the game in a better place than it ever was and a bright future ahead of it, the upcoming March 2025 update will be a great chance to finally jump into the game for any players who haven’t been convinced by
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s comeback story so far.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While every new update for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  is typically the new best time to finally jump into the game, the upcoming Season 20 and playable Ghoul update will be a special moment for the franchise that players won’t want to miss. With plenty of returning players anticipated to make a fresh start when
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s playable Ghoul character arrives, this could be the perfect opportunity for new players to tag along and join in on the fun.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fallout-76-has-come-a-long-way-since-its-rough-launch">
  Fallout 76 Has Come a Long Way Since Its Rough Launch
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2117410618" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2117410618" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2117410618" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2117410618" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2117410618-img" id="article-gallery-1-2117410618">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2117410618" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1048614152">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It’s no secret that
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  got off to a rough start, but players who have written off the game in the past may be surprised to see how much the game has evolved after its initial release in 2018. Since then, numerous free content updates have continued to shape the game into the best version of itself. In the past year alone,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  reached record player counts, partly due to the success of the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  show putting the spotlight on the franchise, but still to the credit of the game’s ongoing support.
 </p>
 <p>
  The numerous updates
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  has received have reshaped the game in major ways, notably improving the new-player experience, introducing new questlines, as well as new endgame activities, overall touching on and improving just about every aspect of the game. Considering all these recent improvements that new players will have the benefit of naturally experiencing, the upcoming Season 20 update is shaping up to be a great chance for new players to finally jump into
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  . Not to mention, there’s still plenty more in store for the game in the near future, with no end in sight for
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s ongoing support just yet.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     ’s Season 20 and playable Ghoul update still doesn’t have an exact release date, though this update is expected to arrive immediately after
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     ’s Season 19 ends in early March 2025.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="fallout-76-rsquo-s-playable-ghoul-character-will-be-a-milestone-moment-for-the-franchise">
  Fallout 76’s Playable Ghoul Character Will Be a Milestone Moment for the Franchise
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1865283346" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1865283346" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1865283346" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1865283346" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1865283346-img" id="article-gallery-2-1865283346">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1865283346" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1885772710">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The main attraction of
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s Season 20 update is the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  franchise’s first-ever playable Ghoul character, offering a completely new way to experience the game with new buildcrafting tools and unique world interactions. Whether or not new players are enticed by the upcoming Ghoul playable character, this update will still be a great opportunity to start a fresh journey in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , nonetheless.
 </p>
 <p>
  While some players will be transforming their existing characters into a Ghoul, many longtime players will likely be creating a fresh character in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  to experience the unique features that are exclusive to the upcoming playable Ghoul character. Consequently, there are expected to be tons of players engaging with the early-game content in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , meaning newer players won’t have to take on the early-game difficulty curve alone.
 </p>
 <p>
  Considering how much the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  franchise’s community has grown recently, the new playable Ghoul character coming to
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  will surely be a special moment for the franchise. Even if players would rather play as the original Vault-dweller character, the game has come a surprisingly long way since its initial launch with countless improvements and new content to experience. With plenty of other players populating the Appalachian wasteland at this point,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s upcoming Season 20 update will arguably be the perfect opportunity to finally join in on the fun.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
