<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Haunted Chocolatier Could Double Dip on Stardew Valley's Most Iconic Feature</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/haunted-chocolatier-stardew-valley-pelican-town-second-location-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Though the game is still early in development, players are already excited about indie developer ConcernedApe’s next title,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Haunted Chocolatier
   </em>
  </strong>
  . While the game comes from the same developer as
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , players should not expect
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  to be yet another simulation game. Rather,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  will be an action-adventure RPG featuring high-stakes combat with simulation elements. Combat represents the first half of the game’s title, whereas the simulation elements represent its second half, as the central focus of
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  is running a confectionery.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  may not be a simulation game, but that doesn’t mean it won’t borrow, be inspired by, or even feature the same gameplay as
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . After all, since both games were developed by ConcernedApe, there’s bound to be some sort of overlap. Based on images and a gameplay trailer released by ConcernedApe,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  shares the same art style as
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . Additionally, this content confirms that NPCs will be present in the new indie game, with a few of these characters likely being romanceable.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  ’s romanceable NPCs are certainly one of its most popular gameplay features, but one central mechanic should be implemented in
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  in some way.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-39-s-pelican-town-is-the-heart-and-soul-of-the-game">
  Stardew Valley's Pelican Town is the Heart and Soul of the Game
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1796659178" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1796659178" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1796659178" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1796659178" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1796659178-img" id="article-gallery-1-1796659178">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1796659178" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1708926824">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Pelican Town is the central location of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  outside the player’s farm. As the hub for meeting NPCs, selling wares, fishing, and many other tasks, it’s impossible to play
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  in its entirety without stepping into Pelican Town at least once. The game features a few other locations, mostly by passing mention, but players can eventually unlock another farm on Ginger Island.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nevertheless, when gamers think of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , they tend to also think of Pelican Town. The game’s rich setting is host to some of the most iconic parts of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . But with ConcernedApe dedicated to making
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  grand in both size and detail, it would make sense for
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s version of Pelican Town to be expanded in some way. This unique opportunity could lead to not just one central town in
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  , but maybe two.
 </p>
 <h2 id="two-locations-could-be-better-than-one-for-haunted-chocolatier">
  Two Locations Could Be Better Than One for Haunted Chocolatier
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1557998310" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1557998310" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1557998310" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1557998310" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1557998310-img" id="article-gallery-2-1557998310">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1557998310" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1212473610">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  could easily justify two locations. While implementing more settings would obviously lead to a longer development stage, two central locations could easily fit into the game’s story. As mentioned, while players will get to fight ghosts and ghouls, running a chocolate shop is
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s main form of gameplay. Running deliveries from the store to two separate towns could easily lead to players bumping into creatures that they have to fight off, leading to combat encounters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Part of
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s confectionery making involves hunting down various ingredients. With a second town, certain ingredients could be made native only to that specific region. This could unlock new flavor profiles and new sweets, leading to a recipe collection that players can eventually complete. A second town could also mean a second location, like
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  ’s Ginger Island farm. Different towns could prefer specific kinds of sweets, with NPCs also having their own particular tastes. Of course, with another town comes a whole new set of NPCs for players to grow attached to and eventually romance. Perhaps these hypothetical towns have a rivalry, which could further
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s lore. After all, the game is an RPG despite its simulation elements.
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s story will likely be integral to its gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  ’s central town still unnamed, it will likely be a while before further details about the game’s location are revealed by ConcernedApe. Despite this, it’s still fun to speculate and imagine how certain elements of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  could be included or expanded upon in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Haunted Chocolatier
   </em>
  </strong>
  , especially its location.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Testing New Rewards Feature</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-rewards-go-pass-april-2025-testing/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO introduces the GO Pass, offering free rewards for completing tasks and leveling up.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can upgrade to the Deluxe version for premium rewards like Lucky Trinkets and Candy XL.
     </li>
     <li>
      The feature is only available in some regions, with a global launch expected in the future.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has announced the GO Pass, which will be available for trainers in select regions starting on April 1. Working to offer
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players additional ways to get items and critters to add to their collections, the new feature comes on a trial basis.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although new, this isn't the first time players have seen something like this in the game. After all, in anticipation of this year's GO Tour, which focused on the Unova region,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  introduced the Tour Pass. This type of battle pass gave players rewards, improving their experience during the annual event of Niantic's augmented reality game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  has unveiled the GO Pass: April, which will be available starting on Tuesday, April 1, at 10 am until Tuesday, May 6, at 10 am local time. With this feature, similar to the Unova pass, players in specific countries will receive a free pass, completing tasks to collect points and leveling up to unlock more rewards. Like in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  events, the rewards will expire after a while. Therefore, they must be claimed by Tuesday, April 8, at 10 am local time. In addition,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  will launch the paid version of the GO Pass on April 1, which will include both premium and free pass rewards. It is important to note that the announcement indicates plans to potentially launch the pass globally sometime in the future.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-details-go-pass-testing">
  Pokemon GO Details GO Pass Testing
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1950318835" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1950318835" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1950318835" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1950318835" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1950318835-img" id="article-gallery-1-1950318835">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1950318835" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1701294640">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GO Pass (Free)
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Availability: Tuesday, April 1, at 10 am to Tuesday, May 6, at 10 am local time
    </li>
    <li>
     Players from selected regions will receive it automatically.
    </li>
    <li>
     Rewards are obtained by completing tasks and earning points to level up the pass.
    </li>
    <li>
     Rewards expire on Thursday, May 8, at 10 am local time.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GO Pass (Deluxe)
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Availability: Tuesday, April 1, at 10 am to Tuesday, May 6, at 10 am local time
    </li>
    <li>
     Players can purchase (price not announced at time of writing)
    </li>
    <li>
     Rewards are obtained by completing tasks and earning points to level up the pass.
    </li>
    <li>
     Rewards expire on Thursday, May 8, at 10 am local time.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Rewards obtained by completing tasks and leveling up the GO Pass
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Encounters with Xerneas and other Pokemon
    </li>
    <li>
     Stardust
    </li>
    <li>
     XP
    </li>
    <li>
     Poke Balls
    </li>
    <li>
     Candy
    </li>
    <li>
     And more
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Rewards obtained by completing tasks and leveling up the GO Pass Deluxe
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Lucky Trinket
    </li>
    <li>
     Premium Battle Passes
    </li>
    <li>
     Incense
    </li>
    <li>
     Lucky Egg
    </li>
    <li>
     Incubator
    </li>
    <li>
     Lure Modules
    </li>
    <li>
     Candy XL
    </li>
    <li>
     Additional encounters
    </li>
    <li>
     And more
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Rewards for reaching milestones
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Tier 1:
     <ul>
      <li>
       2× Daily Adventure Incense duration
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Tier 2:
     <ul>
      <li>
       Increased XP and Stardust from Research Breakthrough rewards
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Tier 3:
     <ul>
      <li>
       Increased Stardust and XP from hatching Eggs.
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Trainers who complete the pass tasks will earn rewards like XP, Stardust, and encounters with pocket monsters such as Xerneas, the Gen 6 Legendary Pokemon. Those who upgrade from the free pass to the paid one will earn Premium Battle Passes, Candy XL, and Lucky Trinket, an item that makes a Friend into a Lucky Friend temporarily, turning the next trade into a Lucky Pokemon. Reaching major milestones will give players even more goodies: double the duration of the Daily Adventure Incense (Tier 1), extra XP and Stardust from Research Breakthrough rewards (Tier 2), and extra Stardust and XP from hatching Eggs (Tier 3).
 </p>
 <p>
  Also in April, the Spring to Spring event will take place, adding Gossifleur and Eldegoss to
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . From April 9 to 14, players will find critters like shiny Fletchling, shiny Remoraid, and other wild spawns like Growlithe, and Exeggutor's regional forms. The April Fool's Day event is another confirmed activity, and on April 1, the game will scatter Poke Balls across the map. Interacting with them will give trainers a chance to catch normal and regional forms of Voltorb and Electrode, Foongus, Amoongus, or Galarian Stunfisk.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Player Confused By Random Item Falling From the Sky</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-item-falling-from-sky/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley players are puzzled by odd moments, like random seed drops, that surprise and amuse the community.
     </li>
     <li>
      Most in-game items can be picked up accidentally, but odd occurrences keep players entertained.
     </li>
     <li>
      Community speculates on the origins of the mysterious mossy seed, with possible explanations ranging from squirrels to divine gifts.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  player was left confused when they suddenly had a mossy seed drop onto their head, seemingly from the open sky. The odd moment is one that some other
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players have reportedly experienced, amusing and puzzling the community at large.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  items can be left on the ground as physical objects that are added to the player's inventory if they're touched, or if a player simply gets close enough with a magnet ring equipped. Picking up random objects by accident is a common occurrence in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , but this moment is a bit more odd.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  player Lemay_7 shared a gameplay video of their odd experience of having a mossy seed drop onto their head from out of nowhere. Their
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  farmer was riding a horse home towards their farm when they got about halfway down the neighboring path. As they pass through, the seed can be seen dropping from the top of the screen directly onto the player. The strange moment took them so much by surprise that the player stops at the end of the video and turns around, staring in confusion at the place where it had just happened.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-players-ponder-mossy-seed-39-s-origins">
  Stardew Valley Players Ponder Mossy Seed's Origins
 </h2>
 <p>
  Outside just sharing their bemusement at the video,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players have been trying to come up with reasons for the seed's sudden appearance. One of the more comical responses has suggested that Yoba gifted the seed to the player for some good they'd done previously. However, some fans have proposed more reasonable causes for this to happen. The leading suggestion is that the mossy seed was shaken out of a tree by a squirrel climbing it closer to the bus stop, above where the player was running through. Instead of the seed simply falling to the ground, some have noted that they've seen them fall down across the screen. If this is the case, it could have put it close enough to the player for their basic magnet ring to have kicked in and guided the mossy seed the rest of the way to their character.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-164941652" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-164941652" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-164941652" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-164941652" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-164941652-img" id="article-gallery-1-164941652">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-164941652" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-794905665">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Whatever the reason for this odd little moment, it's just one of the many examples of how
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  keeps players surprised and amused even after spending hundreds or thousands of hours in the game. Sometimes these moments are inspired by Easter eggs added to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  by developer ConcernedApe, while others are just completely random gameplay moments that delight fans. Chances are
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  will keep finding ways to impress and surprise its players for many years to come.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InZOI Players Are Loving How Romance Plays Out in the Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/inzoi-romance-options-good-player-stories/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players enjoy InZOI's hyperrealistic avatars and detailed romance features.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game's unpredictability attracts players, with some experiencing dark or funny romantic encounters.
     </li>
     <li>
      InZOI surpassed The Sims 4 in player count, peaking at 72,000 players on Steam.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An
  <strong>
   <em>
    InZOI
   </em>
  </strong>
  player shared their Zoi's heartwarming romantic date, and other fans reacted with their own experiences with the game's romance features. It has been less than a week since InZOI released its early access, but the game has quickly become a massive hit.
 </p>
 <p>
  Krafton's latest life simulation title,
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  , has taken the genre by storm since it became available for PC on March 28. In its first 24 hours,
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  surpassed
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , its main competitor, and peaked at over 72,000 concurrent players on Steam. One of the game's main appeals is the hyperrealistic design of its avatars, also known as Zois. Moreover, similar to most life sims,
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  lets players have their characters socialize with other Zois at jobs, social events, and even dates. The latter is related to
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  's romance functions, which players have been loving so far as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  characters can fall in love and even get married if their dating lives are successful enough. One
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  player named freshcinnabon shared how their Zoi's date had brought flowers to her apartment and found the interaction very romantic. According to the fan, the Zois had three more encounters, each with a new bouquet involved. They also pointed out that the male date would only visit the female Zoi after her working hours, which shows the level of detail in the game's romance features.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="inzoi-players-share-their-zois-39-unique-romantic-experiences">
  InZOI Players Share Their Zois' Unique Romantic Experiences
 </h2>
 <p>
  Under the post, while some players also considered the interaction adorable, others revealed that their Zois weren't as lucky in love. One user shared that their Zoi received a rock as a gift from their date. Another player's Zoi was already married when their companion began cheating on them. A third player's character suffered a darker fate when their fiancé unexpectedly died from slipping days before the wedding. Although some of these anecdotes are surprising,
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  's unpredictability has become one of its main assets for attracting players.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-449057181" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-449057181" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-449057181" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-449057181" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-449057181-img" id="article-gallery-1-449057181">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-449057181" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-360981597">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Krafton's life sim has received positive reviews overall, but its early access launch hasn't been free of problems.
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  's director recently released an apology regarding reports of crashes or lack of content and promised that the development team would address these issues in due time.
  <strong>
   <em>
    InZOI
   </em>
  </strong>
  does not have a release date for PS5 and Xbox Series X/S yet, but a first DLC is already planned for August 2025. The game is still in its early days and will likely draw in more players as it adds more content.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Pokemon Leak Reveals New Details About Gen 10</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-leak-gen-10-nintendo-switch-2-gaia/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon series shifting to Nintendo Switch 2 after Pokemon Legends: Z-A launch.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans concerned about issues like in Pokemon Scarlet and Violet with future games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Generation 10 game, codenamed Gaia, to be exclusive to Nintendo Switch 2.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  leak indicates that the core series will be moving on entirely to the Nintendo Switch 2 following the release of
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . This may surprise
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans, as the information differs from prior
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  leaks.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  series has seen ups and downs on the Nintendo Switch. Titles like
  <em>
   Pokemon: Let's Go Pikachu
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Eevee
  </em>
  , as well as
  <em>
   Pokemon Sword and Shield
  </em>
  received a positive response, but
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  suffered from a number of issues at launch. While fans were excited for a
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  game with a more open world that would let them explore and challenge gyms however they saw fit, the technical problems with the game marred the experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, a new leak from Centro Leaks indicates that no further core series
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  games will be released for the original Nintendo Switch after
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  launches. Instead, the next generation of the franchise, Gen 10, will be moving to the Nintendo Switch 2 exclusively. The first
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  Gen 10 game in the franchise is reportedly codenamed Gaia, which was also referred to in prior leaks. However, prior leaks indicated that Gaia would be produced for the Nintendo Switch, and "Super Gaia" would be for the Nintendo Switch 2. It now seems that the plan to release two versions, or possibly a backwards-compatible game with improvements on the Nintendo Switch 2, have been scrapped in favor of focusing entirely on the new console.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fans-react-to-gen-10-leak">
  Pokemon Fans React to Gen 10 Leak
 </h2>
 <p>
  Pokemon trainers responding to the news have had mixed opinions, though many seem hopeful that moving to more powerful hardware will reduce the risk of seeing
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  's mistakes again. However, it's still not known what the specs of the Nintendo Switch 2 will actually be. Leaks have teased possible upgrades, but more details will be known for certain following the upcoming Nintendo Switch 2 Direct slated for April 2. However, fans shouldn't necessarily expect to hear more about Gen 10 there, as The Pokemon Company likely won't want to take any focus away from
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1459657700" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1459657700" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1459657700" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1459657700" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1459657700-img" id="article-gallery-1-1459657700">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1459657700" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1483578327">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  New generations of
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  games are always exciting for fans. Gen 10 may be even more exciting since
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  is shaking up the traditional
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  game formula. Players may be hoping to see more innovations and unique twists in a future mainline
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  game. For now, though, fans will just have to be patient and see what the future holds for both
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  and Nintendo.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
