<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered Could Be Getting a Physical Release</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tomb-raider-4-6-remastered-physical-release-teaser/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Publisher Aspyr is teasing a physical release for the upcoming Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered compilation.
     </li>
     <li>
      Brand Manager Matthew Ray suggested there are "more details to come" about a physical remake for the classic trio of games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Tomb Raider has experienced a major resurgence throughout recent years, between remasters and new Netflix and Amazon shows.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The highly-anticipated remaster compilation of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Tomb Raider 4-6
   </em>
  </strong>
  could potentially be receiving a physical release in the future, as teased by an executive from the publisher. The adventures of Lara Croft have long been one of gaming's most iconic properties since the earliest days of the franchise's roots on the original PlayStation. The
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  franchise has seen numerous reboots and remasters, ranging from the Crystal Dynamics reboot of the franchise to the return of the original trilogy with
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 1-3 Remastered
  </em>
  . Now, even more of Lara Croft's classic adventures are set to make their return.
 </p>
 <p>
  Following the success of last year's
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 1-3 Remastered
  </em>
  , publisher Aspyr confirmed its intent to continue the franchise with even more remasters.
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  will feature a trio of games from the franchise's glory days, with
  <em>
   Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Tomb Raider: Chronicles
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Tomb Raider: Angel of Darkness
  </em>
  all featured on the compilation. The
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  trilogy will even feature some previously cut content, restoring some axed dialogue from
  <em>
   Angel of Darkness
  </em>
  . Now, fans of
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  may have even more exciting news on the way.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="tomb-raider-4-6-remastered-teases-physical-release">
  Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered Teases Physical Release
 </h2>
 <p>
  As reported by NintendoLife, Aspyr may be considering a physical release for
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  . When asked about the potential for a physical release, Aspyr brand manager Matthew Ray suggested that "more details will be shared soon" for
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  . Ray also suggested that Aspyr understands the "importance of physical media to nostalgic gaming" in regard to the compilation, potentially hinting at more to come from
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  is scheduled to launch later this week on February 14.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-588032841" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-588032841" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-588032841" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-588032841" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-588032841-img" id="article-gallery-1-588032841">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-588032841" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-778038626">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A physical release for
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  would likely look to follow in the footsteps of its predecessors with plenty of exclusive goodies. The physical version of
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 1-3 Remastered
  </em>
  offered both a Standard and Collector's Edition release, with the latter boasting collectibles like trading cards, figures, and posters. The premium version of
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 1-3 Remastered
  </em>
  even came with replicas of Lara Croft's iconic pistols, encased in a shadowbox as a display piece.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  comes as the franchise has seen a major resurgence throughout the last year. Alongside the release of
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 1-3 Remastered
  </em>
  , Netflix released its own animated series based on the franchise, with
  <em>
   Tomb Raider: The Legend of Lara Croft
  </em>
  receiving a nomination for "Best Adaptation" at the 2024 Game Awards. Amazon has also been working on its own series based on the franchise, with a live-action
  <em>
   Tomb Raider
  </em>
  show currently in development for Prime Video.
  <em>
   Tomb Raider 4-6 Remastered
  </em>
  is set to be another fond return to some of Lara Croft's most well-known adventures.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur’s Gate 3: The Argument For and Against Character Problems Like Gale’s in BG4</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-gale-artifacts-hunger-problem-eat-magic-items-bg4/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Larian Studios’
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur’s Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  introduced a cast of deeply flawed, yet compelling, characters, with Gale standing out as one of the most interesting. His insatiable hunger for magic items adds a mechanical and narrative layer that makes his story both engaging and frustrating. This duality—where an interesting character quirk also becomes a potential annoyance—raises an important question for
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  : Should the next entry continue this trend of personal burdens affecting gameplay, or should it refine how these elements are integrated?
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With Larian moving on to its own IPs, a potential
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  would be in the hands of a different studio. The next developers will need to balance staying true to the framework left behind, while also pushing the franchise forward. One way to do this is by leaning into party tension more aggressively than
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  , making companions feel less like unwavering allies and more like real individuals with their own agendas, opinions, and conflicts.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-rsquo-s-gate-3-rsquo-s-gale-created-genuine-party-tension">
  Baldur’s Gate 3’s Gale Created Genuine Party Tension
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-156936831" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-156936831" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-156936831" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-156936831" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-156936831-img" id="article-gallery-1-156936831">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-156936831" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-830176330">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Companion characters in RPGs tend to be supportive of the protagonist, only objecting in extreme moral circumstances. However,
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  made strides in adding personal stakes to companion dynamics. Gale exemplifies this with his Netherese Orb predicament, which forces the player into difficult decisions about sacrificing magical artifacts to sustain him. This choice makes his journey feel personal, but it also highlights an area where
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  could go further: party tension could be more of a constant and less of an occasional interruption.
 </p>
 <p>
  A moment that showcases this well is Gale’s reaction if the player describes their first night together as “fine.” His response isn’t just disappointment, it’s bitterness, reminding the player of the explosive situation (quite literally) in his chest. This moment is uncomfortable, but it also makes
  <em>
   BG3’s
  </em>
  Gale feel real. His flaws are on full display, and he reacts in a way that isn’t always palatable.
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  could benefit from more moments like this. Moments where companion relationships aren’t just about external conflicts, they are also personal, sometimes messy, dynamics between characters and the player.
 </p>
 <h3 id="baldur-rsquo-s-gate-3-and-its-polarizing-character-arcs">
  Baldur’s Gate 3 and Its Polarizing Character Arcs
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of the most fascinating aspects of
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  is how it presents its characters with pivotal choices that define their arcs. Each of the origin companions has a storyline rooted in breaking free from, or succumbing to, a powerful external force. Shadowheart must choose between rejecting or embracing Shar. Lae’zel has to decide between loyalty to Vlaakith or forging her own path. Astarion can take Cazador’s place or reject his cycle of abuse. Wyll’s destiny is shaped by whether he breaks his pact or remains bound by it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gale, however, has a unique twist: his “good” ending is framed as returning to Mystra, his former lover and a god who both mistreated and manipulated him. The alternative, where he pursues the Crown of Karsus, is arguably depicted as a descent into megalomania rather than a rejection of his past in favor of self-determination. This portrayal is unusual compared to the other companions, as it subtly suggests that accepting Mystra’s control is preferable to breaking away, despite the perceived power imbalance in their relationship. It raises the question of whether
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  should continue this model of companion arcs or explore different ways of presenting complex character choices.
 </p>
 <h3 id="baldur-rsquo-s-gate-4-should-push-conflict-further">
  Baldur’s Gate 4 Should Push Conflict Further
 </h3>
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  builds on Larian’s foundation, one of the best ways it can evolve is by amplifying player-driven conflict. Many RPGs offer choices, but few force players into situations where a companion’s demands directly clash with personal interests. One way to enhance this is by implementing more binary choices that impact the party dynamic—similar to
  <em>
   Mass Effect’s
  </em>
  Virmire mission, where players must make an irreversible decision about which companion survives.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, a future character could have a conflict where their loyalty is tied to specific player actions, forcing the protagonist to take a side. Imagine a scenario where a mage companion demands exclusive access to certain magical resources and denying them weakens their abilities, or even pushes them to leave the party. This could create natural friction, making relationships feel more organic rather than solely based on approval ratings.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gale’s story, despite its inconsistencies, sets a precedent for characters who have baggage that actively affects gameplay. If
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 4
  </em>
  introduces more characters with similarly demanding conditions, it could make party interactions more engaging and unpredictable. Rather than simply managing approval ratings, players would have to navigate the consequences of their actions in a way that directly impacts their journey.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization 7: How to Counter Spy</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/civilization-vii-civ-7-how-prevent-espionage-counter-spy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Prevent Espionage in Civilization 7
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Unlock Counter Spy in Civilization 7
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Civilization 7
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the Civics Tree gives players access to tons of useful Diplomatic Actions that gamers can use to improve or worsen their relationships with other players in the game. While some Civics unlock friendly Endeavors, others give players access to unpleasant Sanctions and Espionage options.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It's important to know how to counter espionage in
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  , as opponents will use it to steal Technologies, give them advantages during Wars, and reveal precious information that can make it easier to win the game. This guide shows gamers how to Counter Spy in
  <em>
   Civ 7
  </em>
  so they can protect themselves against shady enemies.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-prevent-espionage-in-civilization-7">
  How to Prevent Espionage in Civilization 7
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="civ 7 espionage detected-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/civ-7-espionage-detected-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  , players can spend Influence to send spies to gather or steal information from other Civilizations. However, when they do this, the Reveal Chances are often quite high, but if they don't protect themselves, they will only become aware that they were targeted after they've suffered an espionage attack. Thankfully, there are measures that players can take to prevent espionage from happening.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   To prevent espionage in
   <em>
    Civ 7
   </em>
   , gamers must study the Counter Spy Technology and issue a Diplomatic Counter Spy Action against the Leader they find most likely to send spies to infiltrate their Settlements
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-unlock-counter-spy-in-civilization-7">
  How to Unlock Counter Spy in Civilization 7
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1649262198" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1649262198" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1649262198" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1649262198" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1649262198-img" id="article-gallery-1-1649262198">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1649262198" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1775679813">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Counter Spy is a Diplomatic Action option that can be studied in the Exploration Age Civics Tree.
  <strong>
   To unlock the Counter Spy ability in
   <em>
    Civ 7
   </em>
   , players must study the Authority Civic
  </strong>
  , which becomes available after the Piety Civic is unlocked.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once Authority is obtained, gamers can start protecting themselves against potential spies. To Counter Spy in
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  , players must first open the Radial Menu and select a Leader. Then,
  <strong>
   in the Espionage section, they will notice the "Counter Spy" option
  </strong>
  , which they can select to begin running this Action.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <tbody>
   <ul class="column-to-list">
    <li>
     <td>
      <div class="body-img landscape">
       <div class="responsive-img img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
        <figure>
         <picture>
          <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
          <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
          <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
          <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
          <img alt="single instance actions civ 7" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/single-instance-actions-civ-7.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
         </picture>
        </figure>
       </div>
      </div>
     </td>
    </li>
    <li>
     <td>
      <p>
       Counter spying lasts 20 turns, and it costs 80 Influence in the Exploration Age and 120 Influence in the Modern Age.
       <strong>
        Players can only issue a Counter Spy Action against one player at a time
       </strong>
       , so they must think long and hard about who is most likely to target them.
      </p>
     </td>
    </li>
   </ul>
  </tbody>
 </div>
 <p>
  If a player runs a Counter Spy Action against another Leader, it will triple the amount of time it takes to complete an espionage action, increase how the cost of Influence per turn, make it more likely for it to be revealed, and decrease the success rate of the mission.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best PlayStation Plus Games (February 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/playstation-ps-plus-premium-best-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  On June 13, 2022, Sony launched its new
  <strong>
   PlayStation Plus
  </strong>
  in North America. Split into three tiers, this model combines the previous version of PS Plus with PS Now; depending on which level someone subscribes to, they will gain access to certain services and games.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Essential ($9.99/month):
   </strong>
   This tier is the equivalent of the old PS Plus. A subscription includes online access, monthly free games, and discounts.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Extra ($14.99/month):
   </strong>
   Along with the Essential tier benefits, Extra provides access to hundreds of PS4 and PS5 games.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Premium ($17.99/month):
   </strong>
   Along with the Essential and Extra tier benefits, Premium includes a library of classic games (PS3, PS2, PSP, and PS1), trials, and cloud streaming in certain regions.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   PS Plus Premium
  </strong>
  has over 700 games covering more than two decades of PlayStation history. Such a huge collection can be overwhelming, and the PS Plus app does not make it very easy to browse through the library; as such, it can be useful to know this tier's highlights before investing in a subscription. Each month, Sony adds a handful of new games. While most of these are PS5 and PS4 releases, they are occasionally accompanied by a few classic titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Let's take a look at some of the
  <strong>
   best PlayStation Plus games
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on February 9, 2025, by Mark Sammut
   </strong>
   : PlayStation Plus Essential's February 2025 lineup does not contain any must-play games. Fortunately, PS Plus already has plenty of titles that qualify.
  </em>
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The rankings are not based solely on a game's quality; they also take into account things like their PS Plus addition date. For instance, new
     <strong>
      PS Plus games
     </strong>
     will be temporarily placed in the top spots for visibility, and PS Plus Essential games will also be highlighted first if they are mentioned.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-stanley-parable-ultra-deluxe-january-2025-ps-plus-essential">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   God Of War Ragnarok
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="kratos-39-norse-mythology-saga-comes-to-an-epic-end">
  Kratos' Norse Mythology Saga Comes To An Epic End
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1303062025" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1303062025" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1303062025" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1303062025" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1303062025-img" id="article-gallery-1-1303062025">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1303062025" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1250332604">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Now, this is how to get a year started on the right note. Sure, PS Plus Essential's January 2025 selection was nothing to write home about, but Sony made up for it with a fairly stacked Extra and Premium lineup.
  <em>
   Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Atlas Fallen
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   MediEvil 2
  </em>
  are all big deals in their own right, but they exist entirely in the shadow of one game:
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  A direct sequel to 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  brings the franchise's Norse saga to an end, or at least that seems to be the case. As suggested by the title, the story revolves around the pending onset of Ragnarok, an end-of-the-world event said to coincide with the destruction of the realms and the gods. Kratos wants to stop that, but he is also on the cusp of war with Odin; in the meantime, the All-Father is trying to bring Atreus to his side.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gameplay-wise,
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  plays similar to 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  , albeit with a few tweaks and the introduction of a new weapon. The combat is still crunchy, satisfying, and intense; that said, if someone hated the system in the previous game, they likely will not get too much out of the sequel. While Atreus is still the main companion, Kratos is also aided by a few other characters, all of whom have unique abilities that are fun to use in battles. The campaign is fairly long and generally ambitious, blending character-driven moments with an epic sense of scale.
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  also comes with Valhalla, an epilogue mode that is just all-around brilliant.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-last-of-us-part-1">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   The Last Of Us Part 1
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-remake-of-a-ps3-masterpiece">
  A Remake Of A PS3 Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1820414849" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1820414849" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1820414849" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1820414849" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1820414849-img" id="article-gallery-2-1820414849">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1820414849" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1629750489">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Naughty Dog's
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  brought the PS3 era to an end on the strongest possible note, producing a genre and, arguably, an industry-defining game that has gone on to produce a big sequel and a highly-regarded TV adaptation. While the original release is not on PS Plus Premium, subscribers can check out the PS4 remaster, which is the definitive version. PS5 owners can also play
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 1
  </em>
  , a 2022 remake that gives the classic release a pretty thorough make-over. Honestly, if someone has already played through the original or remastered versions, they might not get too much out of the remake since the best part, the story, is unchanged. However, newcomers can just jump into this iteration.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  follows Joel and Ellie as they go on a harrowing journey through post-apocalyptic United States, all in the hopes of finding a group that might be able to create a cure using the latter's immunity to a fungus that has eradicated most humanity. Blending stealth, melee combat, and exploration, the gameplay sections are intense, visceral, and relatively challenging. More importantly, the story and characters are phenomenal, comfortably among the best in PlayStation history.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="citizen-sleeper">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-gripping-sci-fi-rpg-inspired-by-tabletop-gaming">
  A Gripping Sci-Fi RPG Inspired By Tabletop Gaming
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1483668831" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1483668831" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1483668831" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1483668831" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1483668831-img" id="article-gallery-3-1483668831">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1483668831" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-493059850">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  is somewhat difficult to describe in a way that fully reflects its magic. Jump Over the Age's sci-fi RPG is undeniably inspired by tabletop gaming, to the point that dice rolls play a significant part in determining the outcome of events. Also, similar to tabletop RPGs,
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  is very much driven by player choice, and that goes beyond just big fork-in-the-road decisions found in many other narratives.
 </p>
 <p>
  A Sleeper on the run from the corporation that owns them, players must try to settle down on the Eye, a space station that houses many folks who are just trying to survive. Once there, players enter the daily grind, which means working to earn some cash, interacting with NPCs, buying resources, and trying to stay ahead of bounty hunters who are trying to collect.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  's brilliance lies in its immersion, dropping players into a fully-formed ecosystem filled with characters with rich histories and engaging stories to tell. In a single playthrough, decisions will need to be made that promote specific relationships and hinder others, and players are mostly free to go down whichever direction they want. While not part of the survival genre, the game incorporates some aspects from that blueprint, mainly in the form of a few meters that determine the player's health.
 </p>
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="return-to-los-santos">
  Return To Los Santos
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-306254835" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-306254835" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-306254835" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-306254835" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-306254835-img" id="article-gallery-4-306254835">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-306254835" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-860999251">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Removed from PS Plus Extra in June 2024,
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  only stayed away for a couple of months, returning as part of the November 2024 lineup. Obviously, Rockstar's game is among the most popular projects of all time, so it is a big deal in a vacuum. That said, some of that excitement is hurt by its "leave and bring back" cycle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still,
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  is great, and there is nothing really that can change that. The story campaign has likely been experienced by most people at this point, but the PS4 and PS5 versions available on PS Plus could be worth trying if somebody only played the original PS3 release.
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  is the ultimate time sink too.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-wild-hunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-top-contender-for-the-best-rpg-of-all-time">
  A Top-Contender For The Best RPG Of All Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1034474352" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1034474352" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1034474352" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1034474352" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1034474352-img" id="article-gallery-5-1034474352">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1034474352" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-46088221">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For most months, picking the biggest new PS Plus Extra game is just a matter of personal taste; however, August 2024 was not one of those months. That's not meant as a criticism of games like
  <em>
   Wild Hearts
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Watch Dogs 2
  </em>
  , but rather a celebration of CD Projekt Red's RPG masterpiece.
  <em>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </em>
  was a landmark release for the genre, establishing a new era that emphasized storytelling, secondary content, and world-building more than ever before. While not flawless, the 2015 game is arguably timeless, at least up to this point. Hard as it is to believe,
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  has been out for nearly a decade, and its shadow continues to loom large over RPGs and even CD Projekt Red specifically.
 </p>
 <p>
  Due to its popularity and relative accessibility,
  <em>
   Wild Hunt
  </em>
  is probably not a new game for most PS Plus subscribers. Certain projects are so big that they stop being exciting additions to subscription services, simply since most people would already own them. Still, there must be a few exceptions who have never loaded up Geralt's final (full) chapter, and they can now experience the best console iteration since PS Plus Extra has both the PS5 and PS4 versions. They will find an ambitious and (at times) overwhelming open-world RPG with fully realized characters, immersive exploration, rich side quests, and a unique combat system.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cult-of-the-lamb">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Cult Of The Lamb
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="make-friends-defeat-non-believers-and-resurrect-a-god">
  Make Friends, Defeat Non-Believers, And Resurrect A God
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1946696712" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1946696712" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1946696712" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1946696712" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1946696712-img" id="article-gallery-6-1946696712">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1946696712" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1355241971">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Is this the cutest cult simulator of all time?
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  is an unapologetically dark roguelite that follows a Lamb as they diligently work to set the stage for their god's return, a process that involves defeating four bishops, recruiting plenty of followers, and the occasional sacrifice. Roguelikes are a dime-a-dozen nowadays, and the genre can be automatically written off if someone does not see the appeal of endlessly replaying the same loop.
 </p>
 <p>
  In cases like this, roguelites can act as a fun middle-ground between the replayable nature of roguelikes and more story-driven adventures, and
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  walks this line expertly. While, for the most part, players will revisit the same four (randomly generated) dungeons to try and clear them out and take out their bosses, they will constantly be recruiting new characters for their town/cult, which will further unlock new mechanics and upgrades.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most importantly,
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  is just an absolute sinister delight that revels in macabre imagery and ideas. Along with just being very dark, the humor frequently hits the mark as it constantly pushes the envelope. Furthermore, the gameplay is rock-solid as well, be it the dungeon runs or the town-management aspect. The latter is arguably the best part of the game, as the followers have a ton of personality and evolve alongside the Lamb and cult.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="timesplitters-2-and-future-perfect">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   TimeSplitters 2 And Future Perfect
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="two-all-time-classic-fps-games-that-are-great-solo-or-with-a-friend">
  Two All-Time Classic FPS Games That Are Great Solo Or With A Friend
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1617655368" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1617655368" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1617655368" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1617655368" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1617655368-img" id="article-gallery-7-1617655368">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1617655368" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1311871072">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list specs">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  was the biggest PS Plus game of August 2024, an argument could be made that it was not the most exciting. In a move that was a long time coming, Free Radical Design's
  <em>
   TimeSplitters
  </em>
  trilogy finally made its way to modern systems, with all three PS2 games landing on the PS4 and PS5. These are mostly straight ports of the original versions, and they do show their age in a few ways. However, they are still fantastic console shooters that represent the genre at its early best, especially
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Both entries are great, and they also shine in somewhat different areas. In terms of pure gunplay,
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  is arguably the superior of the two games, and it still sits among the best shooters of all time. Although containing something resembling a plot, the story mode is mostly just a series of extraction-style maps, all of which are well-designed and a blast to master. As the franchise's title suggests, players travel through time, ensuring the stages have quite a bit of variety to them. Co-op is supported as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  has a far more robust and prominent story that creates a cohesive adventure rather than a loosely connected jumble of maps. While not high art, the campaign is fun in the way that a blockbuster can be. The gameplay is quite good, although it is notably less intense and frantic than
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  . Nothing wrong with that, but
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  feels a touch less special in this area.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_53">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The first
     <em>
      TimeSplitters
     </em>
     has charm as well, but it is rightfully overshadowed by both of its sequels. To be clear, the 2000 release is worth a playthrough, as long as newcomers prepare themselves for a somewhat rough experience. Also, its gameplay is not that similar to
     <em>
      TimeSplitters 2
     </em>
     or
     <em>
      Future Perfect
     </em>
     , so do not ignore the latter if the former fails to strike a chord.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="bloodborne">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Bloodborne
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fromsoftware-39-s-lovecraftian-ps4-soulslike">
  FromSoftware's Lovecraftian PS4 Soulslike
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1201139850" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1201139850" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1201139850" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1201139850" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1201139850-img" id="article-gallery-8-1201139850">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1201139850" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-110155920">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  FromSoftware has cornered the hard-hitting action RPG genre through its immaculate
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  trilogy, and that looks set to continue with
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . Out of all the studio's many great games,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  might just be FromSoftware's magnum opus.
 </p>
 <p>
  Boasting a Gothic aesthetic and reflex-based combat that demands aggression from players,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  delivers a kinetic experience that delights on a visual, auditory, and gameplay level. Naturally,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  is not an easy game, but it is one of the most rewarding PS4 exclusives. Consequently, it is easily among the best games on PS Plus.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_60">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Both versions of
     <em>
      Demon's Souls
     </em>
     are also on PS Plus.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="celeste">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Celeste
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="story-driven-2d-platformer-with-high-skill-ceiling">
  Story-Driven 2D Platformer With High Skill Ceiling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-2079341395" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-2079341395" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-2079341395" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-2079341395" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-2079341395-img" id="article-gallery-9-2079341395">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-2079341395" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-380059303">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Celeste
  </em>
  is a highly regarded side-scrolling indie game with a steep learning curve and an absorbing narrative. As Madeline, players climb the Celeste mountain, taking on seemingly impossible challenges and dangerous foes in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Celeste
  </em>
  's campaign guides the character and players on an emotional journey of self-discovery. This voyage is not meant to be easy, and the game makes sure that it is not. The unforgettable story is accompanied by precise gameplay and a soundtrack that ranks among the most memorable of the late 2010s.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dave-the-diver">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Dave The Diver
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="genre-blend-done-really-well">
  Genre Blend Done Really Well
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1171164578" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1171164578" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1171164578" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1171164578" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1171164578-img" id="article-gallery-10-1171164578">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1171164578" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1250593536">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not unheard of, Day 1 PS Plus arrivals are rare, with most months not featuring this type of release. Consequently, whenever an exception materializes, it is always a cause for celebration; more importantly,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  is an exceptional exception. Technically, Mintrocket's indie darling has been around since 2023, but it had to wait until April 16, 2024, to make its PlayStation debut, so it still counts as a Day 1 addition. When this year comes to an end,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  will almost certainly be remembered as one of the best PS Plus newcomers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combining restaurant management with fishing, Mintrocket created a package that feels oddly unique, despite sharing similarities with many other projects. As Dave, players have two general responsibilities: catch and serve fish. The former takes up the protagonist's days, forcing him to constantly make trips into an evolving ocean in search of materials that can be used to create sushi at his restaurant. Naturally, the nights are spent running the establishment, making sure that customers are satisfied. While the management aspect is not as deep as some other titles on the market,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  gives players more than enough control to make these segments engaging. However, the fishing element is the game's highlight and adds the most replay value.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="animal-well">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Animal Well
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="atmospheric-metroidvania-with-great-puzzles">
  Atmospheric Metroidvania With Great Puzzles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-869399482" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-869399482" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-869399482" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-869399482" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-869399482-img" id="article-gallery-11-869399482">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-869399482" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1557883035">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the
  <strong>
   best PlayStation Plus games
  </strong>
  to launch on Day 1,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  is an inspired Metroidvania with simple but effective controls. For the most part, the game sticks very close to the genre's standard formula of unbound exploration, puzzles, platforming, and the gradual reveal of new items that provide access to different areas; however, Shared Memory succeeded in stitching these well-worn pieces together to create something that feels at least somewhat fresh. A big part of this comes down to
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  's haunting aesthetic and ambient music, which combine to create a campaign oozing in atmosphere and style, making up for a lack of a conventional story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although fun, the platforming sections are quite easy, with most of the jumps providing players with plenty of room for error. However,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  is still pretty darn difficult due to its puzzles, very open nature, and clever boss fights. The game's brainteasers often require lateral thinking (and clever use of a slink), while the latter could cause players to feel lost on occasion. That said, the in-game map is detailed and useful.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ratchet-amp-clank-rift-apart">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dependable-playstation-ip-39-s-ps5-debut">
  A Dependable PlayStation IP's PS5 Debut
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1100386194" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1100386194" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1100386194" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1100386194" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1100386194-img" id="article-gallery-12-1100386194">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1100386194" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-310789891">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
  </em>
  is among the most high-profile PS5 games available on PS Plus Extra. As a console exclusive, this reveal seemed destined to transpire sooner or later, although almost two years from the game's debut had to pass for this moment to arrive.
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  might very well still be the most beautiful PS5 title on the market, a testament to Insomniac's mastery of technology and talent for creating vibrant and stunning worlds that would not look out of place in a Pixar movie.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  backs up its good looks with fantastic gameplay and an enjoyable story that allows its lovable characters to shine. Although Ratchet and his robotic companion take center stage, they are accompanied by a new playable Lombax in the form of Rivet, who also comes with her own partner. In combat, the characters largely control the same; however, the game does a great job of establishing Rivet's own identity through her personality.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately,
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  lives and dies on the strength of its gameplay, and
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  is right up there with the franchise's best efforts. Ratchet and Rivet have access to a wide assortment of fun weapons, all of which serve a purpose within the campaign.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost-of-tsushima-director-39-s-cut">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost Of Tsushima: Director's Cut
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="gorgeous-open-world-with-unique-historical-japanese-setting">
  Gorgeous Open-World With Unique Historical Japanese Setting
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-309448762" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-309448762" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-309448762" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-309448762" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-309448762-img" id="article-gallery-13-309448762">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-309448762" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1241483332">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Insomniac's
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  ended the PS4's life as Sony's main console on a high, and the
  <em>
   Director's Cut
  </em>
  is just a better version of that already great game. Taking place during the Mongolian invasion of Japan, This samurai epic tells a tale of revenge as Jin Sakai seeks to protect Tsushima Island.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  might be the most beautiful game on PS Plus Premium, and it is not just a looker. The hack and slash combat is a great deal of fun, managing to be deep and also cinematic. Narratively, the title does not do anything too out of the ordinary, but the unique setting helps set
  <em>
   GOT
  </em>
  apart from the many other open-world games on the market.
 </p>
 <h2 id="returnal">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Returnal
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="challenging-roguelike-with-incredible-action">
  Challenging Roguelike With Incredible Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1663732734" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1663732734" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1663732734" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1663732734" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1663732734-img" id="article-gallery-14-1663732734">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1663732734" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-2099193658">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not quite as recognizable as Naughty Dog or Insomniac, Housemarque has been producing PlayStation gold for more than a decade, and the studio was even picked up by Sony in 2021.
  <em>
   Resogun
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Alienation
  </em>
  are fantastic and easy recommendations for anyone who enjoys shoot 'em ups or top-down shooters, respectively; however, Housemarque's portfolio seemed to be all leading to one particular project:
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  . Among the first titles to truly showcase the next-generation hardware, the 2021 release is still comfortably among the best PS5 games, even if it comes with a fairly steep learning curve.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  is a roguelike third-person shooter set on a strange alien planet. As Selene, players will have to make their way through six biomes, all of which are reasonably large, filled with secrets, feature unique enemies, and culminate in spectacular boss fights. Death means returning to the start or the mid-point, depending on how far someone managed to get. As with most roguelikes, players need to find and upgrade their weapons and stats during each run, and things like parasites and artifacts add extra nuance.
 </p>
 <p>
  While overwhelming at first,
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  's gameplay will eventually feel second nature, transforming players into powerful entities capable of destroying most enemies without breaking a sweat. When this moment strikes, the game becomes even more special.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="undertale">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Undertale
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-definitive-indie-rpg">
  The Definitive Indie RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1266168342" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1266168342" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1266168342" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1266168342" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1266168342-img" id="article-gallery-15-1266168342">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1266168342" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1143752653">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The 2010s was the decade of indie games, so much so that it is near impossible to select the independent scene's crowning achievement for that period. That said,
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  is undoubtedly one of the top contenders. Inspired by the
  <em>
   Mother
  </em>
  series, Toby Fox's RPG follows a child as they explore the Underground, a seemingly typical monster-filled setting for the genre. Obviously, players can decide to adhere to RPG tradition and massacre everything that moves, but they do not have to do that.
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  does not force anyone to play a certain way, and players can follow a few different routes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Blending meta-commentary with nuanced world-building and a strong narrative,
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  is the full package. Anyone remotely interested in RPGs or just gaming in general should give this seminal project a try, and the game's player-driven structure means multiple playthroughs are encouraged.
 </p>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-rise">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="capcom-39-s-most-accessible-monster-hunter-that-is-still-great-for-veterans">
  Capcom's Most Accessible Monster Hunter (That Is Still Great For Veterans)
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1912784868" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1912784868" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1912784868" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1912784868" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1912784868-img" id="article-gallery-16-1912784868">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1912784868" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1783880791">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While no longer exclusive to PlayStation consoles,
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  will always be associated with Sony's brand to an extent. In recent years, Capcom has tried to lower the barrier of entry for the franchise, crafting projects that are more accessible in their opening hours, all the while retaining most of the earlier entries' depth.
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  is the most beginner-friendly project in the series, and it comes with a short "campaign" that should teach the basics in roughly 10 hours. Just to be clear to people not familiar with
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  , finishing
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  's village quests and rolling the credits only means they have completed the tutorial. Now, they can focus on working through the Gathering Hub missions as they collect resources to craft better equipment, allowing them to take on harder quests that will reward higher-tier resources. Repeat the cycle until the end of time (or until it becomes dull).
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  has a fairly simple formula, but it is expected to perfection. Lasting less than an hour at most (and usually considerably shorter), quests drop players in open but not massive maps which will have a few major monsters, including that mission's specific target. Players will then have to track down the enemy and slowly whack away at their health, all the while utilizing the tools at their disposal. Eventually, the fun comes in the preparation for each hunt, crafting a loadout designed to fully target a monster's weaknesses while elevating the hunter's strengths.
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  has a robust selection of weapon types as well, and they all control differently.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="remnant-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Remnant 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="co-op-soulslike-shooter-with-high-replay-value">
  Co-Op Soulslike Shooter With High Replay Value
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-527365636" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-527365636" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-527365636" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-527365636" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-527365636-img" id="article-gallery-17-527365636">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-527365636" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-975967237">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  PS Plus has more than a few Soulslike games, reflecting the genre's explosion in popularity over the last couple of years. In most cases, people's first exposure will be a FromSoftware project, be it
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , or
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  . These are all great places to start, but if the introductory game fails to hit the mark with a new player, they might conclude that Soulslikes are just not for them and ignore any releases by other developers. While most titles take heavy inspiration from the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  games, the genre has enough variety to offer genuine alternatives that do their own thing. Gunfire's
  <em>
   Remnant
  </em>
  games serve as prime examples of Soulslikes with unique identities that set them apart from their contemporaries. The first game is not available on PS Plus, but Sony's subscription service has the (arguably) superior sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  Starting with the most "obvious" distinction,
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  is predominantly a third-person shooter, although melee weapons are available as secondary options. Players steadily gain access to a respectable selection of hand and long guns, with the latter generally acting as a loadout's main option. While most guns are purchased rather than looted, enemies regularly drop mods and mutators that can be used to modify builds on the fly, providing customization without flooding the inventory.
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  's class system is also fantastic.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  is at its best when played in 3-player co-op, to the point that many of the archetypes (classes) and bosses feel tailor-made for parties rather than solo runners. The latter can pick a class that includes a dog companion, so they have an option; however, they might find the campaign to be quite difficult, even on the lowest challenge level. Still, the gameplay is fun, the build variety is solid, and the world-hopping structure is pretty awesome. The bosses are also awesome, including a few that have an impressive sense of scale.
 </p>
 <h2 id="pistol-whip">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Pistol Whip
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-virtual-reality-showcase-that-is-also-among-the-best-games-on-ps-plus-in-general">
  A Virtual Reality Showcase That Is Also Among The Best Games On PS Plus In General
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-903137939" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-903137939" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-903137939" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-903137939" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-903137939-img" id="article-gallery-18-903137939">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-903137939" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-130940038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  80% of PS Plus Premium subscribers will ignore
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  , and they might have no choice since it requires a PS VR2 headset. Consequently, one of the
  <strong>
   best PS Plus games
  </strong>
  will only be experienced by a very small group of players; however, anyone who has the required hardware should download Cloudhead's project ASAP. Sony has been steadily adding virtual reality games to the service since June 2024, and
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  is currently the top pick in this niche bracket.
 </p>
 <p>
  So, what is
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  ? Well, it is basically a modern take on the traditional on-rails shooter format, albeit with a beat thrown in for good measure. Across a series of stages, players will work their way through creative and fairly abstract levels filled with enemies that need to be shot down, all while a song plays in the background. While they don't have to shoot with the rhythm, players earn more points for doing so, and it is just satisfying to pull off.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although not necessarily the deepest game ever,
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  is simply fun and a great showcase of virtual reality's appeal and capabilities.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="wolfenstein-2-the-new-colossus">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Wolfenstein 2: The New Colossus
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="great-over-the-top-alternate-history-fps-with-stealth">
  Great, Over-The-Top Alternate History FPS With Stealth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1893077653" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1893077653" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1893077653" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1893077653" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1893077653-img" id="article-gallery-19-1893077653">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1893077653" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-653878981">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  PS Plus Extra has all four modern
  <em>
   Wolfenstein
  </em>
  games, and the best one is arguably
  <em>
   The New Colossus
  </em>
  ​​​​​​. Building nicely on
  <em>
   The New Order
  </em>
  's strong foundations, the sequel is bigger and generally better. Featuring an all-time great villain and an appreciation for scale and spectacle,
  <em>
   The New Colossus
  </em>
  is an action-packed blockbuster that looks, controls, and sounds great.
 </p>
 <p>
  PS Plus does not have an overabundance of brilliant first-person shooters, but MachineGames' mainline
  <em>
   Wolfenstein
  </em>
  trilogy is now available in its entirety to Extra and Premium subscribers. When taken as a whole, these games are arguably the genre's best representatives on the service. William "B.J." Blazkowicz's journey is one filled with visceral action, gore, stealth kills, satisfying weapons, and glorious set pieces that put many Hollywood productions to shame. For the most part, these games tell entertaining stories that usually have just the right amount of cheese without coming across as try-hard.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rogue-legacy-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Rogue Legacy 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="addictive-roguelike-with-interesting-structure">
  Addictive Roguelike With Interesting Structure
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-494654050" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-494654050" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-494654050" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-494654050" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-494654050-img" id="article-gallery-20-494654050">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-494654050" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-458614928">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Roguelikes have grown exponentially in popularity over the last few years, and
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy
  </em>
  played a role in amplifying the genre's exposure. The sequel builds nicely on its predecessor's ideas, offering a more fine-tuned experience while not deviating too far from the beaten path.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy 2
  </em>
  follows a knight as they try to power through an array of dungeons in pursuit of treasure. Naturally, they will eventually die, forcing players to start from scratch. The twist is that, rather than playing with the same character, players jump to the next generation, a process that is repeated whenever death comes knocking.
  <em>
   Rogue Legacy 2
  </em>
  also slips into roguelite territory by incorporating permeant upgrades and abilities, so a new run is not a completely fresh start. While perhaps not the absolute biggest addition, this addictive roguelike was among the
  <strong>
   best PS Plus games
  </strong>
  of 2023.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - Where To Get &amp; Repair Shoes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-where-get-repair-shoes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Repair Shoes In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Where To Get New Shoes In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  All your armor, clothing, and weapons in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  will have their durability go down as they are used, lowering their overall effectiveness. While replacing items that are breaking is almost never worthwhile, your best bet is to repair everything you can, though that isn't done in one central place.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Out of all your gear, you'll end up going through the durability of shoes the fastest, even with higher-quality ones. Especially early into the game, it's not clear how to repair shoes or where to get new ones aside from off dead bodies; here's where you need to go.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-repair-shoes-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  How To Repair Shoes In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-604681185" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-604681185" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-604681185" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-604681185" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-604681185-img" id="article-gallery-1-604681185">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-604681185" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1850409091">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are two types of merchants that can repair shoes for you,
  <strong>
   Cobblers and Saddlers
  </strong>
  as they both work with leather. The first option you can find is the Saddler in Samine, found in the southwestern corner of the town. Boots and shoes aren't incredibly high quality, so repairing them even from a very low durability won't take much more than a few Groschen.
 </p>
 <p>
  You can also
  <strong>
   repair shoes yourself using a
  </strong>
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3411845" style="; ;">
   <span>
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/02/cobblers-kit-utility-item-kcd2-wiki-guide.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
    Cobbler's Kit
   </span>
  </span>
  , which is a very worthwhile repair kit to carry with you considering how quickly shoes run out of durability. While shoes are easily repaired once you know where to go, it's usually worthwhile to have a second pair stored on your person or your horse before going on a longer adventure, especially if you don't have a Cobbler's Kit on hand.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Saddlers are also great places to buy new equipment for your horse.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="where-to-get-new-shoes-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  Where To Get New Shoes In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1274476357" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1274476357" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1274476357" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1274476357" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1274476357-img" id="article-gallery-2-1274476357">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1274476357" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-107847777">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  New shoes can be purchased from the same stores you can repair them at, though buying shoes is not recommended at least in the early sections of the game. Shoes are
  <strong>
   the most common drop from a killed person in the game
  </strong>
  , with every bandit and ruffian having a pair on them. It will be much cheaper overall to find a camp of enemies, kill them, and take their shoes, before taking those shoes to get repaired.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   biggest effects that are noteworthy of shoes are your Charisma and Conspicuousness
  </strong>
  , as fancier shoes will give a boost in Charisma but also make you more noticeable. If those are two stats you're not worried about, simple
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3409253" style="; ;">
   <span>
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/02/soft_shoes_8_legs_armor_kcd2_wiki_guide_64px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
    Soft Shoes
   </span>
  </span>
  or any boots will more than get you around the world without costing too much to get or maintain.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
