<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25: How to Get Five Star Matches</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-how-get-five-star-matches-increase-rating/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    WWE 2K25
   </em>
  </strong>
  , like previous titles, is all about entertaining the fans with exciting matches and interesting stories. It’s not just about winning; it’s about telling a story in the ring that leaves the audience wanting more.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  That being said, achieving the highest possible match rating in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  becomes the ultimate measure of your skills. A five-star match rating shows that you've truly understood the essence of WWE entertainment. This guide breaks down how you can get a five star matches in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  and leave your fans with an unforgettable performance.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-increase-match-rating-in-wwe-2k25">
  How To Increase Match Rating in WWE 2K25
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-795577981" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-795577981" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-795577981" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-795577981" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-795577981-img" id="article-gallery-1-795577981">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-795577981" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-100735799">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you want to get a five-star match rating in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , you need to deliver a show that leaves a lasting impression on the virtual crowd. This means creating moments that feel genuinely unpredictable and exciting.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here are a few factors that can give you a better match rating in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Defensive Prowess
  </li>
  <li>
   Memorable Moments
  </li>
  <li>
   Heightened Drama
  </li>
  <li>
   Signature Offense
  </li>
  <li>
   Varied Offense
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Think of it like this: to get a good rating in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , you need to show you can do a bit of everything. That means blocking and dodging attacks, using your character's special moves, making the match exciting with close calls and big moments, and having a variety of different ways to attack in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  . You don't have to be perfect at everything, but being good at all of them is better than just doing one or two really flashy moves.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-a-five-star-match-rating-in-wwe-2k25">
  How To Get A Five-Star Match Rating in WWE 2K25
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="How to Expose the Turnbuckle in WWE 2K25" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg" decoding="async" height="1250" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-expose-the-turnbuckle-in-wwe-2k25.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2500"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  , a five-star match is all about being able to perform consistently. However, if you truly want to hook your audience, you need to master the art of drama. To get that five-star rating, make sure your match is engaging and memorable. If your match delivers consistent drama and memorable moments, you're well on your way to earning a five-star rating.
 </p>
 <p>
  There is nothing that builds excitement like a spot-on near fall, where tension lingers until the very last second. Apart from this, you need to showcase a dynamic and unpredictable offense. Don't fall into predictable patterns and surprise your opponent (and the crowd) with unexpected moves and creative combinations.
 </p>
 <p>
  You can also use the ring posts, barricades, and any available weapons in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  to create impactful moments. A well-placed table spot or a dramatic throw into the steel steps can also increase your rating.
 </p>
 <p>
  Make sure to connect with the crowd through taunts and gestures. While you’re at it, delivering one final signature move can be the difference between a good rating and a great one.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Xbox Update Will Make Freeing Up Storage Space Easier</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-console-storage-optimization-update/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The next Xbox Insider update helps gamers optimize storage.
     </li>
     <li>
      Xbox Insider program provides early access to updates but may cause issues.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Microsoft has recently unveiled a new Xbox Insider update, which promises to help gamers optimize storage space on their
  <strong>
   Xbox
  </strong>
  . With the Xbox Insider program, Xbox
  <strong>
  </strong>
  owners can get early access to new, experimental features, and this one seems very helpful for players who constantly struggle with not having enough storage space to install new games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Released by Microsoft in 2020, the Xbox Series X/S consoles have sold around 30 million globally. Since their release, the consoles have received periodic updates, and the Xbox Insider program allows some gamers to gain access to them ahead of time. By playtesting these features early, the Xbox Insiders program helps to ship them in a more stable state to the rest of the user base.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, Microsoft has unveiled a new Xbox Insider feature, which promises to help gamers free up space on the console. After the update, rather than simply displaying leftover add-ons and shrinkable games to users, the console will also include recommendations such as removing duplicate copies of games, or files from titles that are no longer accessible by the console owner. While this does not automatically mean players will have more free HDD space, it may help them to manage their old data. Apart from this new feature, the update also fixes an issue where some users would see “odd” text across their console in some languages.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="new-xbox-insider-update-can-help-gamers-to-optimize-storage-space">
  New Xbox Insider Update Can Help Gamers to Optimize Storage Space
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-31122387" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-31122387" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-31122387" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-31122387" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-31122387-img" id="article-gallery-1-31122387">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-31122387" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1234752504">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Xbox Insider program often pushes out some very useful updates. Last year, for example, the program released an Xbox Insider update that made downloading game updates easier and quicker to manage.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unfortunately, the experimental nature of the program also means that gamers may face a few issues while trying out new updates. For example, earlier this month, gamers had their Xbox consoles reset to factory settings after an Xbox Insider update. This happened with multiple individuals, who were very annoyed by this issue.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from pushing regular updates for the Xbox Series X/S, Microsoft is already working on its successor. Recent rumors indicate that Microsoft could be planning two different projects for the Xbox successors: a handheld and a TV-friendly PC. According to reports, the next Xbox console will be like a PC, in essence, with a TV-friendly shell, which can greatly help during game development by simplifying the process.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Absolutely Devastating' Xbox 360 Gamer Gets Bad News After Nearly 18 Years</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-360-red-ring-of-death-rrod-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xbox 360 Red Ring of Death issue plagued many consoles.
     </li>
     <li>
      Recent reports show long-lasting Xbox 360 systems also failing.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An
  <strong>
   Xbox 360
  </strong>
  gamer's console has finally been hit with the Red Ring of Death after nearly 18 years of playing the console. Microsoft's Xbox 360 is one of the best-selling video game consoles of all time, earning significantly higher sales than its predecessor and giving the PS3 a run for its money. Many gamers have fond memories of playing the Xbox 360, but the console was also notorious for its serious technical problems.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the early years of the Xbox 360's life, the system suffered from catastrophic failure, marked by the dreaded Red Ring of Death. It's been estimated that at least half of the early Xbox 360 consoles eventually suffered from the Red Ring of Death, though the issue was thankfully fixed by later hardware revisions.
 </p>
 <p>
  While many Xbox 360 gamers suffered from the Red Ring of Death within the first couple of years of the system's life, there are those who managed to keep their early console in working order. Unfortunately, there have been reports in recent years of these long-lasting Xbox 360s also succumbing to RROD, with the latest example provided by Reddit user TheRealTacoBellMan. They revealed that their console of nearly 18 years was finally hit with the Red Ring of Death. "Absolutely devastating," they said. Prior to the RROD, they said their console only had a disc tray problem where it wouldn't open without a disc already being inside.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="xbox-360-console-gets-red-ring-of-death-after-nearly-18-years">
  Xbox 360 Console Gets Red Ring of Death After Nearly 18 Years
 </h2>
 <p>
  Some users commented on the latest Xbox 360 RROD post and suggested that the console may still be saved. The theory that it's really the Xbox 360's power brick that's the problem and not the console itself was floated, but it's unclear if that possibility was tested or not. In any case, the Reddit user currently plays games on Xbox Series X, and was primarily using their 360 to play
  <em>
   Guitar Hero
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  It's possible a new
  <em>
   Guitar Hero
  </em>
  game will be made or that the games will eventually be added to the backward compatibility lineup. After all, Microsoft has acquired Activision Blizzard, and so it now owns the rights to the
  <em>
   Guitar Hero
  </em>
  IP. Licensing issues may make that impossible, though, meaning fans may have to stick with older hardware when it comes to playing
  <em>
   Guitar Hero
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-367499582" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-367499582" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-367499582" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-367499582" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-367499582-img" id="article-gallery-1-367499582">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-367499582" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-867481280">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Due to issues like the Red Ring of Death and people throwing out old consoles, the original line of Xbox 360 models is at risk of one day becoming extinct. The Xbox 360 consoles with the blades dashboard are especially at risk, as connecting old 360s to the internet wipes out the blades and replaces them with the newer UI.
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition Release Time</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/when-does-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition-come-out-release-time/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Definitive Edition of 2015's underrated Wii U gem,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X
   </strong>
  </em>
  , is merely days away from launching on the Nintendo Switch, giving it a chance to finally have its moment in the sun. With an immensely bigger audience this time around,
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is primed to probably have the most players it's ever seen in the past decade.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Not only that, but some major changes are being made to the game, like several quality-of-life improvements, a cleaned-up UI, new characters, and even new post-game content. If you're wondering exactly
  <strong>
   when
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
   </em>
   launches on the Switch eShop
  </strong>
  , we have the answer for you here.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="xenoblade-chronicles-x-release-time-on-nintendo-switch">
  Xenoblade Chronicles X Release Time on Nintendo Switch
 </h2>
 <h3 id="when-can-you-play-it">
  When Can You Play It?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-622557654" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-622557654" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-622557654" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-622557654" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-622557654-img" id="article-gallery-1-622557654">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-622557654" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1040348896">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike other big video game companies, Nintendo refuses to share information on its social media accounts regarding the official launch times of its published titles. However, that doesn't mean that the info isn't out there.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like other first-party Nintendo Switch games,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
   </em>
   is expected to digitally launch on Wednesday, March 19, 2025, at 9 PM PT
  </strong>
  . This means that if you're on the East Coast of the States, the
  <strong>
   game should unlock around midnight (ET) on March 20
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     This information comes directly from the Nintendo support page for new eShop titles. Also, these release times are typically spot-on, so there should be no delays.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  For other time zones, refer to the chart below.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   March 19 at 10 PM MT (Denver)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 19 at 11 PM CT (Chicago)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 12 AM ET (New York)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 5 AM GMT (London)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 6 AM CET (Berlin)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 1 PM CST (Beijing)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 2 PM JST (Tokyo)
  </li>
  <li>
   March 20 at 4 PM AEDT (Melbourne)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="do-i-need-to-play-other-xenoblade-games-before-playing-xenoblade-chronicles-x">
  Do I Need to Play Other Xenoblade Games Before Playing Xenoblade Chronicles X?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-595623016" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-595623016" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-595623016" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-595623016" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-595623016-img" id="article-gallery-2-595623016">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-595623016" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-501575310">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fortunately,
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  is a standalone story that is very loosely related to the
  <em>
   Xeno
  </em>
  series. Players can jump into this title for the first time and won't completely feel lost about the storyline and lore.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="">
 </h2>
 <h2 id="how-big-is-the-file-size-for-xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition">
  How Big Is the File Size for Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition?
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-d1be99bccb51ef80" id="emaki-video-player-d1be99bccb51ef80">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  According to the eShop,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
   </em>
   will take up about 13.5 gigabytes of storage
  </strong>
  .
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   Interestingly enough
   <em>
    , Xenoblade Chronicles 3
   </em>
   takes up 14.4 gigs; the second takes up 13.2, and the first
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles
   </em>
   takes up about 13.7 gigs.
  </span>
 </p>
 <h2>
  FAQ
 </h2>
 <h3>
  Q: What's the release time for Xenoblade Chronicles X?
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  on Switch will be released digitally at 9 PM Pacific time on March 19, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undertale: How Long to Beat</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/undertale-how-long-to-beat/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How Long Is Undertale?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How Long To 100% Complete Undertale?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The cult favorite indie game
  <strong>
   <em>
    Undertale
   </em>
  </strong>
  has remained an incredibly popular RPG, still drawing in new players after many years. There are many new locations to visit, bosses to spare or defeat, and puzzles to solve. While the story of
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  is compelling and rich, the game itself is not incredibly long to finish.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  revolves around a young human who has fallen into a world of monsters underground and must survive in this new and unfamiliar place. Players are working towards finding away out of the underworld, or risking staying there forever. Completing the game can take different amounts of time, depending on your playstyle.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-long-is-undertale">
  How Long Is Undertale?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1433240630" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1433240630" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1433240630" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1433240630" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1433240630-img" id="article-gallery-1-1433240630">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1433240630" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1336389911">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A lot of what determines how long
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  will take for you depends on your own playstyle, and how much you want to discover in the game. Some prefer to only focus on the main story, while others might want to check out some side content, or complete the game 100%.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a few different worlds that players will come across in the game, including
  <strong>
   Ruins, Snowdin, Waterfall, Hotland, New Home, and The Core
  </strong>
  . Within these worlds, there are many different locations that you can visit, such as Papyrus and Sans's house, Toriel's home, MTT Resort, and much more. These six different worlds essentially represent how many chapters are in the game. Within these areas, there are additional side contents that you can check out.
 </p>
 <p>
  If you are looking to focus on the main story, these are the times you can expect to complete
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Main Story: 7 Hours
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Main + Extra: 11-12 Hours
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="how-long-to-100-complete-undertale">
  How Long To 100% Complete Undertale?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Undertale (3)" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/undertale-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Some players prefer to check out all the game has to offer, including hidden locations, secrets, and more. Players can even find hidden lore and items if they search through every location in the game thoroughly, and unlock more content.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's a lot of side content and hidden items to discover in
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  , which will take around
  <strong>
   20 1/2 hours
  </strong>
  for a full 100% completion. Players will need to make sure they have completed at least one True Pacifist route first before they can begin working towards 100% completion, however. After doing so, there are a few additional parameters that will need to be met, including completing a Genocide route, another True Pacifist route where you spare enemies and mini-bosses with particular methods, pick up every item available in the game, and much more.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
