<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How One Palworld Pal Has Become the Community's Most Hated</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/palworld-gobfins-most-hated-pal-why-annoying-aggressive/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The islands of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Palworld
   </em>
  </strong>
  are full of many interesting creatures, all of which have unique qualities and traits that make them either desired or disliked by players. But whether people like them or not, there's no denying that they're beneficial when used right, as many Pals can be considered best for combat, base work, traveling, etc. But there is one that, despite how useful it can be if it were to be a party member, has proven to be quite an annoyance, mainly due to what it does as an enemy.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Those who decide to explore the islands of
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  will eventually end up in a location called the Gobfin Turf. There, one can encounter the titular monster, and it has become a Pal that has drawn the attention of many, but for the wrong reasons. Although no longer a threat to seasoned veterans, those starting their journey will likely be caught off-guard by how aggressive Gobfins are and how they attack even when unprovoked. While other Pals can be just as aggressive, this one in particular is more hated than the rest because of certain aspects that emphasize how much of a nuisance it can be.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-players-dislike-palworld-rsquo-s-gobfins">
  Why Players Dislike Palworld’s Gobfins
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2018023755" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2018023755" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2018023755" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018023755" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018023755-img" id="article-gallery-1-2018023755">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2018023755" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2129519602">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the Gobfins of
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  aren't exactly the scariest things to encounter in the game, they're definitely one of the most annoying. Other than the Pal being very aggressive, there are a few other things that make it one of the most disliked monsters in the game:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   They usually come in large groups, meaning that players can easily be hounded by more than 5 at once if they aren't aware of their surroundings
  </li>
  <li>
   They are one of the best ways for players to farm Pal Fluids, but having them constantly come in large numbers can make it feel like a chore
  </li>
  <li>
   The area they're situated in has other valuable resources to acquire, but their constantly unprovoked attacks during the mining or gathering process can make the Pal feel extremely annoying
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This particular Pal proves that sometimes, the worst enemies aren't the ones who are strong, but rather those that can make the gameplay experience less enjoyable. If one chooses to enter the Goblin Turf, that person will likely immediately understand why the titular monster of the area is widely disliked by the game's fans.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-palworld-rsquo-s-gobfins-can-also-be-seen-as-a-good-thing-for-the-game">
  How Palworld’s Gobfins Can Also Be Seen as a Good Thing for the Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  Even if the Gobfin is disliked and can be seen as one of the worst Pals in
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  because of what it does, one can say that the ire it has received is actually a good thing. It has managed to grab the community's attention and have its people talk about it, meaning that the monster has played a role in keeping it alive and active. Also, having the Gobfins constantly attack players means that gathering resources within their area is never boring, ensuring that players are always engaged. So, while the Pal is disliked or even hated by players, there's no doubt that it has contributed to livening up
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  , even if not in the way people would have liked.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gobfins may be infamous due to their numbers and in-game behavior, but they play a role that makes the Pal more than just any other aggressive monster. So, if there's one additional thing to put on the players' list of expectations for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Palworld
   </em>
  </strong>
  in 2025, then perhaps it's more such creatures to make the game more engaging.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Fallout 76's Bobbleheads</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-76-bobbleheads-buffs-defense-good-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 76
   </em>
  </strong>
  being a multiplayer game in an otherwise exclusively single-player franchise naturally means that it varies from past games in the franchise in several ways. One such difference between
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  and its predecessors is the potency of certain buildcrafting tools, like
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s perk cards, as well as minor, temporary buffs via consumable items. With past
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games often being criticized for letting players achieve omnipotent builds that trivialize the game’s RPG elements, the limits
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  places on players' builds are arguably necessary for the sake of a balanced multiplayer experience, despite being initially considered a downgrade.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A prime example of how
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  limits players' builds is the potency of buffs from Vault-Tec bobbleheads. In
  <em>
   Fallout 3
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  , bobblehead consumables provide permanent buffs to players, incentivizing players to collect every bobblehead in the game to upgrade their builds. In
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , bobbleheads aren’t permanent and only one bobblehead buff can be utilized at once. However, despite being much less potent,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s bobbleheads have a few unique advantages over bobbleheads from previous
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games, ultimately making them a happy middle-ground.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fallout-76-rsquo-s-bobblehead-buffs-have-unique-advantages-over-past-games">
  Fallout 76’s Bobblehead Buffs Have Unique Advantages Over Past Games
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-543359610" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-543359610" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-543359610" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-543359610" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-543359610-img" id="article-gallery-1-543359610">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-543359610" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-929378615">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="fallout-76-rsquo-s-bobbleheads-have-become-a-new-trading-currency">
  Fallout 76’s Bobbleheads Have Become a New Trading Currency
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of the biggest advantages of
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s version of bobbleheads is that they respawn often, they can be purchased from select vendors and even earned as a reward for completing certain activities, allowing players to stock up on bobbleheads and use them as a trading currency. Similar to past
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games, Caps are the main currency in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  . However, unlike past games,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  imposes a maximum limit of 40,000 Caps for all players, making additional currencies a necessity.
 </p>
 <p>
  Outside of Caps,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  players generally use leader bobbleheads, skill magazines, berry mentats, and bobby pins, among other collectible items, as trading currencies. As long as players have the inventory and stash space to collect them, using other collectibles as a currency allows players to make exchanges that potentially exceed the value of 40,000 Caps, which is often necessary when trading for some of the rarest items in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , such as rare apparel items or God-roll legendary weapons.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     When trading for highly valuable items, players should consider enlisting the services of a courier in
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     , who will act as a third-party mediator to prevent trading scams.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="fallout-76-rsquo-s-bobblehead-buffs-help-combat-controversial-omnipotent-builds">
  Fallout 76’s Bobblehead Buffs Help Combat Controversial Omnipotent Builds
 </h3>
 <p>
  In general,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s version of bobblehead buffs are much weaker than those from past
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games because the buffs are only temporary, and players can only use one at a time. While this is admittedly a downgrade compared to how
  <em>
   Fallout 3
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  let players permanently stack every bobblehead buff together, this is a necessary step toward combating the overpowered builds in
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games that often undermine the RPG elements.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Equipping the Curator Luck Perk Card in
     <em>
      Fallout 76
     </em>
     will extend the duration of bobbleheads and magazine buffs from 30 minutes to 60 minutes.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Instead of having a one-size-fits-all build in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  , players are encouraged to make separate builds that specialize in a limited variety of weapons and SPECIAL skills. Otherwise, players will generally have to sacrifice parts of their builds in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  to achieve a well-rounded endgame build.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately, while the potency of their buffs may not be as powerful as those in past
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  games,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s bobbleheads still have some redeeming qualities that arguably make up for this. Especially considering that balancing is a much more delicate matter in online multiplayer games,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  ’s bobbleheads are a happy middle-ground that has turned into a valuable currency despite not being as powerful as buildcrafting tools.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Co-Op Games On Steam (January 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-coop-multiplayer-games-pc-steam/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Thanks to the
  <strong>
   Steam
  </strong>
  platform, there are tons of amazing games for PC players to purchase, download, and enjoy. The Steam Greenlight program is even helping indie developers push their products, giving players even more choices, with tons of games released on the service each month. Steam also makes it incredibly easy for players to join one another in games, thanks to the handy friends list and invite features.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This makes the platform the perfect place for players to hop online and enjoy cooperative adventures together. There are tons of great co-op games on Steam to choose from, ranging from AAA releases to Indie darlings. To better point out some of the memorable cooperative adventures floating around the service, here's a look at some of the
  <strong>
   best co-op games on Steam
  </strong>
  and what players can expect from them.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     As local co-op has its own discussion, online co-op will take center stage for this article.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated January 18, 2025 by Mark Sammut:
   </strong>
   <strong>
    PC co-op games
   </strong>
   are always debuting, and a few major titles have been confirmed for 2025. Click below to read about a few upcoming titles.
  </em>
 </p>
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Exciting Upcoming Co-Op Games On Steam
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals">
  Marvel Rivals
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-81">
  Steam User Rating: 81%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1729005863" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1729005863" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1729005863" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1729005863" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1729005863-img" id="article-gallery-1-1729005863">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1729005863" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1463042361">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  OK, multiplayer games are generally thrown into a different category than co-op projects, and rightfully so. That said,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is such a hot property that it warrants a mention, at least for the time being.
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  is still around and a big name in the free-to-play scene, but the hero shooter has been crying out for another notable contender for a long time. Enter
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , a game that takes plenty of lessons from Blizzard's original
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  , albeit enhanced by the presence of one of the most recognizable and lucrative IPs on the market. Honestly, and this is not meant to be a criticism,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' greatest asset is the fact that it features the likes of Spider-Man, Hulk, and Black Widow. The gameplay is otherwise fairly typical for the genre, holding little surprises beyond abilities tweaked to suit the licensed characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Focusing on 6v6 matches,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  launched with four modes: Convoy, Domination, Convergence, and Conquest. They are all fairly traditional for the genre, and they all require teamwork to different degrees, with Conquest focusing the least on co-op-style action. Players can pick from more than 30 heroes, and they should take into account team synergy when selecting their preferred character. Team-up abilities are a big deal in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , and going solo is unlikely to yield results against even a moderately coordinated squad.
 </p>
 <h2 id="warhammer-40-000-space-marine-2">
  Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-80">
  Steam User Rating: 80%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-807239227" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-807239227" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-807239227" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-807239227" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-807239227-img" id="article-gallery-2-807239227">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-807239227" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1283378847">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It took more than a decade to materialize, but
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  is now a reality. So, was it worth the wait? Well, the answer is mostly yes, even if some aspects could use some tweaking. Putting aside Operations, the PvE mode designed for players to replay the same missions and grind XP, the main campaign supports online co-op, and it is by far the best way to experience this story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sure, co-op improves nearly everything, but
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  is very much designed around a three-person squad; consequently, solo players will be saddled with two AI partners who are not always the sharpest knives in the shed. Just to be clear, the campaign is still a blast in single-player as it is always satisfying to tear armies of Tyranids to shreds. Co-op just lessens some of the occasional frustration.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_18">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Operations can be fun too, but it is a grind and its mileage may vary from player to player. That said, the mode is worth a try since it will greatly extend
     <em>
      Space Marine 2
     </em>
     's life cycle.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="satisfactory">
  Satisfactory
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-57563312" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-57563312" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-57563312" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-57563312" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-57563312-img" id="article-gallery-3-57563312">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-57563312" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-641390405">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After roughly 5 years in early access,
  <em>
   Satisfactory
  </em>
  finally made its full debut on September 10, 2024. Unsurprisingly, the full game is fantastic, delivering an addictive sandbox-style experience that allows players to create the factories of their dreams. Obviously, this type of game is fairly niche, but if someone wants to get lost in creating elaborate metal jungles that turn an alien planet into the ultimate resource farm, they will struggle to find something quite as deep as
  <em>
   Satisfactory
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Four players can jump into the same world, and they can mostly decide how much they want to interact. Like the rest of the game, co-op is not for everyone, and player compatibility is important to reduce irritation. That said, with the right group, this function can improve what is already a brilliant experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="helldivers-2">
  Helldivers 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-85">
  Steam User Rating: 85%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1819518843" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1819518843" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1819518843" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1819518843" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1819518843-img" id="article-gallery-4-1819518843">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1819518843" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-736094527">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_30">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Helldivers 2
     </em>
     currently has server issues which are predicted to take a while to fix. This can make things difficult to get out of queues and into matches. Arrowhead's CEO even recommended that players tight on cash hold off on purchasing
     <em>
      Helldivers 2
     </em>
     at the moment since they might not get a seamless experience.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  When February 2024 started, few people would have predicted that the month's big game would be
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  rather than
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Skull and Bones
  </em>
  . The latter two titles both support co-op, although only Rocksteady's superhero project is on Steam. While not devoid of positives,
  <em>
   Suicide Squad
  </em>
  is the definition of a mixed bag, although it is better when played with a couple of friends. However,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  is on a whole other level, delivering one of the best multiplayer experiences of recent years. The original
  <em>
   Helldivers
  </em>
  is a great co-op game, but it operates on a far smaller scale than its successor, which significantly expands on the same general blueprint.
 </p>
 <p>
  Boasting a tongue-in-cheek narrative and presentation,
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  casts players as soldiers who are liberating the galaxy, one planet at a time. The community takes on this (not so) righteous battle as a unit, so it genuinely feels like a joint effort. Players can join randoms or play with friends, and while the latter generally leads to a superior experience, the former is also fine for the most part.
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  handles co-op beautifully, but that would not matter if the actual gameplay was not addictive and fun. As it so happens, Arrowhead also crafted a brilliant third-person shooter that is both satisfying and challenging.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chained-together">
  Chained Together
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-89">
  Steam User Rating: 89%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1056165949" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1056165949" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1056165949" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1056165949" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1056165949-img" id="article-gallery-5-1056165949">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1056165949" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-386927649">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Chained Together
  </em>
  is the definition of an acquired taste. Designed to be frustrating to an extent, Anegar's project fits into a peculiar platforming/puzzle subgenre that challenges players to climb up a collection of assets, all the while living with the knowledge that a restart could be just a single mistake away.
  <em>
   Chained Together
  </em>
  has a few things that set it apart from releases like
  <em>
   Only Up!
  </em>
  ; for one, the game is set in hell, with the "story" revolving around escape attempts. While not sounding like a big deal, this element gives the title a clearer identity than most of its contemporaries.
 </p>
 <p>
  More significantly,
  <em>
   Chained Together
  </em>
  is designed with up to 4-player co-op in mind. Solo runs are viable, but going down this route eliminates the game's freshest ingredient, resulting in an experience that might be too infuriating to take on without the presence of a Twitch audience. Co-op adds far more replayability, turning the frustration into potential hilarity. That said, it could also result in fights.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lethal-company">
  Lethal Company
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1927964575" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1927964575" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1927964575" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1927964575" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1927964575-img" id="article-gallery-6-1927964575">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1927964575" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-866832123">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Every month, Steam seems to produce a couple of early-access games that take the world by storm, and
  <em>
   Lethal Company
  </em>
  won this lottery in October 2023. Supporting four-player co-op, the first-person horror game revolves around visiting moons that happen to have a few wayward creatures running around. The goal is to explore the area, collect loot to satisfy the company's quota, and make it out alive. Basically, the concept is very similar to an extraction shooter, albeit without the shooter part.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even though solo runs are possible,
  <em>
   Lethal Company
  </em>
  really emphasizes teamwork, to the point that someone can stay on the ship to monitor the moon and guide the rest of the group to safety. While still a work in progress,
  <em>
   Lethal Company
  </em>
  already executes its premise well, and the progressively growing quota provides replay value. The game can also be genuinely intense and terrifying.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  Baldur's Gate 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-428265760" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-428265760" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-428265760" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-428265760" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-428265760-img" id="article-gallery-7-428265760">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-428265760" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1172917659">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A belated sequel to an all-time beloved RPG franchise created by a different developer who opted to change the core gameplay in a new direction,
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  needed to be near-perfect to avoid backlash. Somehow, Larian accomplished just that. After spending a few years in early access,
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  was finally released on Steam in August 2023, and it was everything most people could potentially want in a CRPG. For one, the game's character creator is deep and impacts the rest of the campaign, meaning the first few decisions players make have consequences. This foreshadows the rest of the experience since player choice is a huge part of this
  <em>
   Dungeons and Dragons
  </em>
  adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  went down as one of the best single-player RPGs of 2023, and the same can be said for co-op. Friends can jump into each other's campaigns, and they are largely left to their own devices in how they interact with the world. While groups can decide to do everything as a unit, they can also spend considerable time apart as they focus on different things.
 </p>
 <h2 id="palworld">
  Palworld
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-93">
  Steam User Rating: 93%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1901623782" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1901623782" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1901623782" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1901623782" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1901623782-img" id="article-gallery-8-1901623782">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1901623782" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1420592269">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Launching into early access on January 19, 2024,
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  instantly took the gaming world by storm, cracking the million-player count on Steam. It is safe to say that Pocket Pair's open-world survival game with monster-collection and shooter elements is a resounding success, and the project is still a work in progress. While the latter fact might discourage some folks from taking the plunge, the current version is hardly lacking in content, although some aspects are rough around the edges and mechanics could change as the weeks and months roll by.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still,
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  is an impressive achievement by any metric, and it manages to cover various genres and concepts without buckling under the weight of its ambition. While not especially punishing, the game's survival elements are handled fairly well, especially the building and crafting. The gunplay is not that big of a focus and takes a while to open up, but the action is exciting whenever it takes center stage. The monster-taming element attracted the most attention before
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  's debut, and the project succeeds in taking ideas from staples like
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  while still carving out a unique identity.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game is largely presented as a solo experience, and anyone who decides to stick to their own worlds will not feel like they are missing out on a large part of the overall package. However,
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  also supports multiplayer in the form of 4-player co-op, along with servers that allow for 32 players at a time. While showcasing the game's early access status due to its somewhat uneven implementation, this component nevertheless adds another dimension, permitting players to work together to craft bases and head out on exploitative adventures as a unit.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ready-or-not">
  Ready Or Not
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-88">
  Steam User Rating: 88%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-801004156" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-801004156" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-801004156" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-801004156" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-801004156-img" id="article-gallery-9-801004156">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-801004156" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-669208378">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Void Interactive’s
  <em>
   Ready or Not
  </em>
  spent roughly two years in early access before officially launching in December 2023, and that time was not wasted. As members of a SWAT unit, players can tackle more than 15 maps, each of which is well-designed and fairly large for this type of shooter. While the gunplay is great,
  <em>
   Ready or Not
  </em>
  is very much intended to be tactical rather than a twitch shooter, and the game encourages teams to coordinate their movements to ensure maximum success (and a great score). The enemy AI can be quite aggressive and intelligent too, so just going in guns blazing with no thought will result in poor returns.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ready or Not
  </em>
  features a single-player option that teams players up with AI characters, but this exchange robs the gameplay of its sophistication. As such, this release is only worth recommending to people who plan to play online multiplayer with friends. For those who are struggling to piece together a full squad, they should try reaching out to the community through Discord or Reddit. The game has a relatively big playerbase, so it should not be impossible to find a few people to play with.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rabbit-and-steal">
  Rabbit And Steal
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-19505458" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-19505458" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-19505458" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-19505458" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-19505458-img" id="article-gallery-10-19505458">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-19505458" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1821791584">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A fairly small release compared to
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Rabbit and Steel
  </em>
  is nevertheless a noteworthy co-op option that provides a pretty unique adventure that not many other projects can deliver. Inspired by MMO raids, the game challenges players to pick a class and then progress through chapters that contain mostly boss-style encounters that utilize bullet hell gameplay. The combat revolves around skills with cooldowns, adding a strategic element as players have to decide when it is best to use, for example, their dodge maneuver.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Rabbit and Steel
  </em>
  knows what it is trying to be and succeeds in bringing that experience to life. That said, it is designed with a very specific audience in mind, and it is much better when played with a few friends (after all, it is based on MMOs, a genre driven entirely by multiplayer). Due to its specialized combat, new players should try out the Steam demo before picking up the full game, just to make sure it is their speed.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sons-of-the-forest">
  Sons Of The Forest
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-86">
  Steam User Rating: 86%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-2033744570" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-2033744570" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-2033744570" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-2033744570" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-2033744570-img" id="article-gallery-11-2033744570">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-2033744570" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-2007871028">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Endnight Games introduced its wildly popular horror survival game,
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  , back in 2014. Now, almost ten years later, the studio is back with a new adventure in
  <em>
   Sons of the Forest
  </em>
  . This sequel features all the same gameplay elements that fans enjoyed in the first release with a handful of surprises thrown throughout. The title is currently in Early Access, but developers are adamant about adding tons of new content over the coming months, with countdown timers that outline subsequent patches and releases.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although
  <em>
   Sons of the Forest
  </em>
  can be played solo, it's an absolute blast to play with friends. Similar to the original game, players can build their own bases, traps, and defenses, and explore areas with friends.
  <em>
   Sons of the Forest
  </em>
  's horror element is diluted in co-op, resulting in a less tense and (obviously) isolating experience than in single-player; consequently, the feature might be better left for a second playthrough.
 </p>
 <h2 id="borderlands-3">
  Borderlands 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-85">
  Steam User Rating: 85%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1018671526" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1018671526" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1018671526" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1018671526" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1018671526-img" id="article-gallery-12-1018671526">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1018671526" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1918173910">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  All the
  <em>
   Borderlands
  </em>
  games revolve around co-op, even if they are still perfectly playable solo. Now, personal preference might promote some of the other entries to the top position, especially
  <em>
   Borderlands 2
  </em>
  for its great story and main villain; however,
  <em>
   Borderlands 3
  </em>
  has pretty comfortably the best gameplay in the series, which is arguably more important for a co-op run.
  <em>
   Tiny Tina's Wonderlands
  </em>
  is a fine
  <em>
   D&amp;D
  </em>
  -twist on the formula, but it is not quite as replayable as the main entries.
  <em>
   Borderlands
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Borderlands 2
  </em>
  are still worth playing, as long as new players go in with realistic expectations as their gunplay is outdated by this point.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite its polarizing narrative and characters,
  <em>
   Borderlands 3
  </em>
  's gameplay, progression, vault hunter builds, and visuals are all best-in-class, delivering the most enjoyable overall experience if players mainly want to shoot and loot. Seamlessly implemented and encouraged, the game not only implements co-op well but also minimizes any hassle to access it.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-outlast-trials">
  The Outlast Trials
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-93">
  Steam User Rating: 93%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-2042817887" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-2042817887" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-2042817887" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-2042817887" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-2042817887-img" id="article-gallery-13-2042817887">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-2042817887" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1740763073">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Red Barrels'
  <em>
   Outlast
  </em>
  is well-cemented as a modern horror staple, even if the games can be divisive. Taking a single-player franchise in a multiplayer direction will always attract doubt from the fanbase as it comes with a significant risk of undermining the IP's core appeal. Although not without issues,
  <em>
   The Outlast Trials
  </em>
  serves as an admirable example of how to execute this shift without gutting everything that came before.
 </p>
 <p>
  Playable solo but designed with 4-player co-op in mind,
  <em>
   The Outlast Trials
  </em>
  challenges players with completing experiments within self-contained maps. The latter zones are structured similarly to the classic areas in the previous
  <em>
   Outlast
  </em>
  games, albeit with the objectives being generalized rather than story-driven. Just to be clear, the game still has a story and adds important lore to the franchise as a whole; however, the runs themselves are fairly light in this area. The maps are all atmospheric, creepy, and well-designed, and they are littered with horrifying monstrosities that live up to
  <em>
   Outlast
  </em>
  's horror reputation.
 </p>
 <h2 id="stardew-valley">
  Stardew Valley
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1184161431" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1184161431" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1184161431" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1184161431" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1184161431-img" id="article-gallery-14-1184161431">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1184161431" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-895926126">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the best Indie releases ever made,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  actually has a pretty fun and robust cooperative mode. Up to four players can band together to build their own farm, though it is important to note that one player will be the "owner" and the others will work as farmhands.
 </p>
 <p>
  This means that players will be forced to wait for the owner to be online in order to continue their journey and their characters will be saved to that player's specific world. Still, there are many unique features in multiplayer, like the ability for each player to marry their own NPC and the ability to build additional player housing (via cabins) onto the farm property. Players can even track and complete quests on their own.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="for-the-king">
  For The King
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-88">
  Steam User Rating: 88%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1050614505" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1050614505" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1050614505" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1050614505" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1050614505-img" id="article-gallery-15-1050614505">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1050614505" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-664211020">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Turn-based RPGs are a ton of fun, but they're even more entertaining with friends as proven by
  <em>
   For the King
  </em>
  . This multiplayer cooperative (up to 3 players at the same time) story-driven adventure sees players choosing a class and then setting out to battle enemies, make decisions, and uncover lore.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are tons of areas to explore and battles to engage in, with each player taking their own turn in both the Overworld and during a fight. Players can unlock new abilities by swapping weapons and will have to make a series of dice-roll decisions that can strengthen or weaken their character over time.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_104">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      For the King 2
     </em>
     's launch has been a bit of a mixed bag, but the sequel is also on Steam and, obviously, supports co-op.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="remnant-2">
  Remnant 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-84">
  Steam User Rating: 84%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-166750102" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-166750102" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-166750102" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-166750102" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-166750102-img" id="article-gallery-16-166750102">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-166750102" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-473119860">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gunfire Games has sought to bless the world with third-person shooter Soulslikes. While not the only developer to accept this worthy challenge, Gunfire is the most notable, with both
  <em>
   Remnant: From the Ashes
  </em>
  and its sequel garnering predominantly praise. Released in 2019, the former was a great proof of concept, but
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  is bigger and better. The 2023 release offers way more (unlockable) classes and build options, superior and more nuanced combat, and far more diverse locations, all the while still incorporating procedurally generated elements like its predecessor.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both games support 3-player co-op, and this is undoubtedly the best way to experience
  <em>
   Remnant
  </em>
  . Players are encouraged to create balanced teams from the available archetypes, all of which have unique strengths and weaknesses that allow them to slip into specific roles. While playable solo, the dungeons are designed to be tackled by a group of players, and they will need to work together well if they want to survive the game's challenges, particularly on its highest difficulties.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-world-or-rise">
  Monster Hunter World Or Rise
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-88-world-amp-81-rise">
  Steam User Rating: 88% (World) &amp; 81% (Rise)
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1877826498" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1877826498" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1877826498" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1877826498" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1877826498-img" id="article-gallery-17-1877826498">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1877826498" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-171117837">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list specs">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Monster Hunter World
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  both support online co-op, and there is not a huge difference in quality between them. Consequently, newcomers should just go with their gut instinct and pick the game that looks the most enticing to them, although they should try to pick up a version that includes each title's respective expansion, both of which are better than the base content. Despite being the newer release,
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  looks somewhat worse than
  <em>
   World
  </em>
  since it originally launched on the Nintendo Switch, and its maps are generally smaller than its predecessor's offerings. Nevertheless,
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  is well-rounded and awesome, all the while being the most accessible entry in Capcom's franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both games allow up to four players to go on hunts together, and their combat loops are fundamentally identical. However,
  <em>
   World
  </em>
  's co-op implementation is slightly more peculiar since it requires the host player to summon hunters during quests, resulting in a process that is not as seamless as the version in
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  . That said, it is not complicated, just unnecessary. During the harder hunts, co-op makes a notable difference in battle, and the feature should extend the game's replayability since it helps reduce the grind's exhaustion.
 </p>
 <h2 id="overcooked-2">
  Overcooked! 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-90">
  Steam User Rating: 90%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1862137796" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1862137796" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1862137796" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1862137796" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1862137796-img" id="article-gallery-18-1862137796">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1862137796" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-639291243">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players looking for a puzzle, strategy, and skill-based challenge should definitely check out
  <em>
   Overcooked! 2
  </em>
  . What starts out as a deceptively simple cooking game soon devolves into madness, and it takes quite a bit of teamwork to do well in the later levels. Players will need to work together, tossing each other ingredients and ensuring they use the right cooking stations in order to get meals out to hungry customers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Each level has a star-based system and players can earn more stars by performing better. It can be quite challenging and is a ton of fun, featuring up to four players racing around a wide variety of strange kitchen settings.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="content-warning">
  Content Warning
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-93">
  Steam User Rating: 93%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-350156859" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-350156859" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-350156859" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-350156859" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-350156859-img" id="article-gallery-19-350156859">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-350156859" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-1574710802">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Released on April's Fools,
  <em>
   Content Warning
  </em>
  exploded onto Steam thanks to an inspired premise that is (literally) made for streaming. While performing OK on Valve's store, Landfall's release will probably not have the same shelf-life as other recent successful
  <strong>
   co-op Steam games
  </strong>
  like
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Lethal Company
  </em>
  ; conversely, the fact
  <em>
   Content Warning
  </em>
  has not been forgotten completely yet serves as a testament to its quality. Still, people interested in giving this a go should probably not wait too long.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Content Warning
  </em>
  challenges players with filming "scary" videos, and then airing them on an in-universe platform to earn cash. This concept is so obvious that it seems like it should have been done already, and Landfall presents a charming interpretation of this idea. Armed with items and gadgets, players head out into the Old World's facilities in search of monsters, and survival is not guaranteed.
 </p>
 <h2 id="grounded">
  Grounded
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-89">
  Steam User Rating: 89%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-1882592008" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-1882592008" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-1882592008" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-1882592008" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-1882592008-img" id="article-gallery-20-1882592008">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-1882592008" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-1676433789">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Obsidian's
  <em>
   Grounded
  </em>
  is a charming take on the survival genre that is perfect for both solo players and groups. After being shrunk down to ant size, four children find themselves trapped in a backyard that has its own ecosystem ruled by different insect societies. While reversing their stature is important, the characters have more pressing matters to attend to, including setting up a base that will hopefully be able to keep them safe from the many threats that exist in this familiar but creative world.
 </p>
 <p>
  In theory, the survival genre seems like a better fit for single-player projects since the lack of support heightens the challenge; however,
  <em>
   Grounded
  </em>
  serves as a prime example that adding a few companions can reveal a new dimension to the overall package. Unsurprisingly, the writing is consistently witty and endearing, even though the game does not emphasize its main story all that much. The gameplay and mechanics are relatively typical for the survival genre, but they are executed well and regularly expanded upon.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="phasmophobia">
  Phasmophobia
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-96">
  Steam User Rating: 96%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-21-1438099197" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-21-1438099197" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-21-1438099197" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-21-1438099197" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-21-1438099197-img" id="article-gallery-21-1438099197">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-21-1438099197" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-21">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-21-slides-container-1758575023">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Those looking for something that will really scare their socks off should consider trying out
  <em>
   Phasmophobia
  </em>
  . In this Indie release, players must enter locations and gather paranormal evidence using a variety of tools. What starts out as a seemingly routine exploration soon turns to chaos as players realize that the spirits they are investigating are hostile.
  <em>
   Phasmophobia
  </em>
  is dark, gritty, and can be downright terrifying, especially when played in VR.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can bring friends along to help cut through the fear and tension and many of the game mechanics offer up a great opportunity for cooperative play as players will need to work together and communicate to make it out of each location alive. In terms of the horror genre,
  <em>
   Phasmophobia
  </em>
  is comfortably among the
  <strong>
   best Steam co-op games
  </strong>
  ​​​​​​.
 </p>
 <h2 id="it-takes-two">
  It Takes Two
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-95">
  Steam User Rating: 95%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-22-884392490" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-22-884392490" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-22-884392490" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-22-884392490" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-22-884392490-img" id="article-gallery-22-884392490">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-22-884392490" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-22">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-22-slides-container-1526356738">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Anyone looking for a fun and engrossing cooperative experience needs to put
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  at the top of their list. This release, from the same studio that created
  <em>
   A Way Out
  </em>
  , is a masterpiece of cooperative gaming. Not only is the story engrossing, but the art style is also fantastic, and the gameplay is addictive. Players will have to support one another on their journey through
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  's action-and-puzzle-filled chapters.
 </p>
 <p>
  No matter which character they pick, players will constantly switch back and forth between a leadership and support role, spending time in the limelight before helping to accentuate and elevate their partner. It's a beautifully balanced release that shows how incredible a good cooperative multiplayer experience can be.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="crab-champions">
  Crab Champions
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-23-2124400662" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-23-2124400662" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-23-2124400662" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-23-2124400662" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-23-2124400662-img" id="article-gallery-23-2124400662">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-23-2124400662" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-23">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-23-slides-container-189577546">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Crab Champions
  </em>
  is a third-person shooter featuring crabs. This description might make it sound like a joke game, but that would be a disservice to the quality on display here. In early access, Noisestorm has been updating the base game at a fairly consistent rate, releasing patches that either add new content or improve things like balancing. Consequently,
  <em>
   Crab Champions
  </em>
  will continue to improve over the following months and possibly years, which is exciting since the current version is already great.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Crab Champions
  </em>
  absolutely nails its movement; in fact, an argument could be made that it is one of the most smooth and fluid third-person shooters on the market. While the gameplay loop gets repetitive after a while, the core mechanics are so enjoyable that they can carry the load. The game is a blast as a solo experience, and it is only enhanced when a few friends are brought along for the ride.
 </p>
 <h2 id="terraria">
  Terraria
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-24-1017875450" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-24-1017875450" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-24-1017875450" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-24-1017875450" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-24-1017875450-img" id="article-gallery-24-1017875450">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-24-1017875450" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-24">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-24-slides-container-1327033582">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although many would consider
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  as the defacto building, crafting, and survival game, there are some who would argue that
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  is just as, if not more, engaging. This release ditches the 3D blocky aesthetic in favor of a pixelated, 2D side-scrolling adventure. Like
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  's worlds are procedurally generated, so no two playthroughs will ever feel the same. Those craving something a bit more difficult than a traditional
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  session can turn to
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  for a much more in-depth combat system, as well as an array of difficult bosses that will have the player fighting, grinding, and exploring for better gear.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  can be a blast alone, but it's even better with friends. Players are free to tackle the entirety of Terraria as a coop pair or even in a group.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="left-4-dead-2">
  Left 4 Dead 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-25-531383477" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-25-531383477" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-25-531383477" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-25-531383477" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-25-531383477-img" id="article-gallery-25-531383477">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-25-531383477" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-25">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-25-slides-container-1682514134">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although Turtle Rock Studios recently released
  <em>
   Back 4 Blood
  </em>
  , a game influenced by its original Left 4 Dead release, there are still many players flocking to
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  to get their zombie-fighting fix. This is because
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  has been a phenomenal part of the cooperative scene ever since it hit store shelves back in 2009. It's a bit of an upgrade from the original release while still maintaining all the core gameplay elements that made it such a fantastic experience. The end result is a sequel that is engaging, fast-paced, hectic, and immensely fun.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  can be experienced alone with AI partners, but it's much more fun via cooperative play. With so much mod support and even custom campaigns, players who are just hopping into
  <em>
   Left 4 Dead 2
  </em>
  will find tons of content to explore with their friends.
 </p>
 <h2 id="valheim">
  Valheim
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-95">
  Steam User Rating: 95%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-26-779686256" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-26-779686256" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-26-779686256" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-26-779686256" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-26-779686256-img" id="article-gallery-26-779686256">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-26-779686256" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-26">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-26-slides-container-691493700">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another difficult-yet-rewarding release,
  <em>
   Valheim
  </em>
  is an Indie smash-hit that has players taking over the role of a Viking. To survive, new adventurers will need to construct shelter, craft weapons, and collect materials to fasten armor and other tools. Similar to
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  and its sequel, players will find themselves weak and helpless at the start, as they're forced to avoid or tangle with some pretty difficult enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Valheim
  </em>
  is a bit more "
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  -like" in its combat approach, and players will need to learn enemy attack patterns and behaviors in order to defeat most of them. There are even some imposing bosses to take down. The best part is that players can bring a friend along, to make the journey a bit easier.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="don-39-t-starve-together">
  Don't Starve Together
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-95">
  Steam User Rating: 95%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-27-132410320" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-27-132410320" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-27-132410320" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-27-132410320" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-27-132410320-img" id="article-gallery-27-132410320">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-27-132410320" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-27">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-27-slides-container-1101862464">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Don't Starve
  </em>
  was another Indie release that took the gaming world by storm, quickly developing a cult following thanks to its punishing game world, seemingly unfair mechanics, and alluring storybook-like art style. Played from a top-down perspective, players will have to survive by foraging for food and other items while building shelters and avoiding an array of deadly monsters found in each procedurally generated playthrough.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  lets players experience all the struggles found in the original release with a group, helping one another to survive by picking from a series of interesting characters, each with their own abilities and stats.
 </p>
 <h2 id="payday-2">
  Payday 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-89">
  Steam User Rating: 89%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-28-845982690" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-28-845982690" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-28-845982690" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-28-845982690" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-28-845982690-img" id="article-gallery-28-845982690">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-28-845982690" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-28">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-28-slides-container-139654151">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Those who enjoy heisting their way through
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  will find a lot to love with
  <em>
   Payday 2
  </em>
  . This release takes the heist concept and crafts an entire release around it, giving groups of players access to an array of missions, bank jobs, and other types of heists to complete. Players will need to keep a level head as they attempt to avoid guards, disable security cameras, take hostages, and perform other heist tasks while avoiding capture.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes
  <em>
   Payday 2
  </em>
  so engaging is that players can complete missions in a variety of ways. Sometimes they'll need to attack things from a stealthy perspective, and sometimes they can run in guns blazing. There are also an array of character types and special abilities that players can unlock as they play.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="killing-floor-2">
  Killing Floor 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-89">
  Steam User Rating: 89%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-29-2105513214" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-29-2105513214" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-29-2105513214" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-29-2105513214" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-29-2105513214-img" id="article-gallery-29-2105513214">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-29-2105513214" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-29">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-29-slides-container-566861120">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Tripwire's
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  has had a longer-than-most shelf life. While not quite as popular as Valve's own zombie co-op shooter, the game has maintained a decent playerbase on Steam, and it is frequently on sale for dirt cheap. Technically,
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  can be played solo, but it is not recommended nor particularly enjoyable; as such, this is one title that should be played alongside a few other people. Wave-based levels are not unusual for the genre, but it is a tried and tested structure and formula that can provide accessible and constant thrills when executed well.
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  proves as much, and the game has more to offer than just an enjoyable loop.
 </p>
 <p>
  The title's classes are arguably the game's highlight, as the Perks all bring something fresh to the plate. Testing different team configurations adds a great deal of replayability, and each class can be leveled up to expand its abilities.
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  implements these light RPG elements well, and their inclusion elevates what could have otherwise been a fun but forgettable shooter.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sea-of-thieves">
  Sea Of Thieves
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-90">
  Steam User Rating: 90%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-30-738605301" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-30-738605301" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-30-738605301" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-30-738605301" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-30-738605301-img" id="article-gallery-30-738605301">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-30-738605301" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-30">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-30-slides-container-978261875">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When it set sail in 2018, Rare's high-seas project hit immediate rough waters; however, the game managed to weather that storm to come out on the other side. Now, more than 5 years later,
  <em>
   Sea of Thieves
  </em>
  is firmly established as a cornerstone of the online scene that can satisfy both co-op and PvP fans, along with the occasional lone pirate. While not devoid of direction, Rare designed the game to encourage players to seek out their own adventures, which is generally easier to do when part of a crew.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if it is not narratively dense,
  <em>
   Sea of Thieves
  </em>
  is still stuffed with content and objectives. There are missions, tall tales, factions, treasure hunts, and timed events to keep players engaged; more importantly, a crew can simply spend their days exploring the sandbox and embracing whatever comes their way, be it a Kraken or another pirate ship.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="one-piece-pirate-warriors-4">
  One Piece: Pirate Warriors 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-92">
  Steam User Rating: 92%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-31-211636554" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-31-211636554" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-31-211636554" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-31-211636554" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-31-211636554-img" id="article-gallery-31-211636554">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-31-211636554" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-31">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-31-slides-container-1858985785">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_202">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      One Piece: Pirate Warriors 4
     </em>
     is a stand-in for all viable
     <em>
      Warriors
     </em>
     games, many of which support co-op.
     <em>
      Dynasty Warriors 8: Xtreme Legends Complete Edition
     </em>
     has a co-op story, while
     <em>
      Samurai Warriors 5
     </em>
     is also a good option.
     <em>
      Pirate Warriors 4
     </em>
     was picked solely due to personal preference.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Koei's Musou games tend to be polarizing. Either they are action-packed romps with cathartic gameplay or repetitive wastes of time with combat that gets old within seconds. There does not seem to be much of a middle ground. Despite being the definition of niche,
  <em>
   Warriors,
  </em>
  as a franchise, is somehow popular enough to warrant a billion sequels and spin-offs. And, sometimes, nothing hits the spot like blowing away thousands of enemies with a single swing as a one-person wrecking crew. Sure, the combat might not be deep, but it is flashy and fun.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   One Piece: Pirate Warriors 4
  </em>
  is packed with fanservice that should thrill people who have spent the last two decades reading Eiichiro Oda's manga, and they are frankly the only people who should consider picking up this title. Along with cliffsnotes versions of past arcs, the campaign also tells a non-canon storyline that is fun enough to keep things interesting for 20 or so hours. The playable character roster is absolutely massive, containing more than 40 options in just the base game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, co-op comes with a few limitations, and it needs to be unlocked for story missions. However,
  <em>
   Pirate Warriors 4
  </em>
  has a couple of modes that allow up to 4 players to join in on the mayhem, and the co-op is entertaining whenever the connection is smooth.
 </p>
 <h2 id="barotrauma">
  Barotrauma
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-93">
  Steam User Rating: 93%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-32-1846236065" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-32-1846236065" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-32-1846236065" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-32-1846236065" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-32-1846236065-img" id="article-gallery-32-1846236065">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-32-1846236065" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-32">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-32-slides-container-260254685">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Barotrauma
  </em>
  drops players in a submarine that is exploring the depths of an alien ocean, one crawling with entities far scarier than a Great White Shark. Along with a campaign catering to solo players,
  <em>
   Barotrauma
  </em>
  has two modes designed specifically with co-op in mind, and they arguably showcase the game at its peak.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the latter options,
  <em>
   Barotrauma
  </em>
  players take charge of individual roles in the submarine, each of which has a crucial part to play in a mission's success and the crew's general survival. Even when surrounded by friends, the game manages to still be excruciatingly stressful, in the best possible way.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rotwood">
  Rotwood
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-72">
  Steam User Rating: 72%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-33-1933305822" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-33-1933305822" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-33-1933305822" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-33-1933305822" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-33-1933305822-img" id="article-gallery-33-1933305822">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-33-1933305822" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-33">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-33-slides-container-878099089">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Klei Entertainment created one of the
  <strong>
   best co-op Steam games
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  , and while it would be a tall order to surpass that masterpiece,
  <em>
   Rotwood
  </em>
  is a viable alternative. To be clear, the early access project is a wildly different beast than that survival title and focuses way more on combat. A beat 'em up that follows a roguelite structure,
  <em>
   Rotwood
  </em>
  has an over-the-top cartoony animation style that lends itself brilliantly to the flashy and fairly challenging action.
 </p>
 <p>
  While accessible enough at a glance, the gameplay focuses on combos, which does bring an element of challenge. With multiple weapon types to master and a decent range of biomes and bosses, the current version is already a respectable package. Solo runners will likely have a decent time with
  <em>
   Rotwood
  </em>
  , but the game shines far brighter when played with a couple of friends.
 </p>
 <h2 id="portal-2">
  Portal 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-98">
  Steam User Rating: 98%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-34-440321030" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-34-440321030" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-34-440321030" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-34-440321030" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-34-440321030-img" id="article-gallery-34-440321030">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-34-440321030" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-34">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-34-slides-container-237884939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Pairs of players looking for a great puzzle game should put
  <em>
   Portal 2
  </em>
  at the top of their list. Although this release has a great single-player campaign, it also features a robust cooperative storyline that stands as its own adventure. Players will control one of two bots and be subject to a variety of GLaDOS' seemingly sinister portal-based tests. This is a fantastic puzzle game and a great use of Portal's unique gameplay mechanics. The cooperative play is well-thought-out and will force players to work together to escape each room.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Portal 2
  </em>
  is a game that all players should check out at least once and the cooperative experience makes it even better.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="deep-rock-galactic">
  Deep Rock Galactic
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-97">
  Steam User Rating: 97%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-35-1688421265" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-35-1688421265" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-35-1688421265" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-35-1688421265" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-35-1688421265-img" id="article-gallery-35-1688421265">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-35-1688421265" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-35">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-35-slides-container-975922022">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Deep Rock Galactic
  </em>
  puts players in the shoes of a resource collection team as they're sent off on an array of missions to collect minerals and other valuable items. In this futuristic and campy first-person shooter, players will need to band together as one of four different classes in order to ensure that each mission goes off without a hitch, checking certain tasks off their to-do list like collecting a specific amount of resources, defending a specific area, or subduing certain threats.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Deep Rock Galactic
  </em>
  is a great FPS, offering a challenge at higher levels while simultaneously promoting a fun and funny environment.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dead-island-2">
  Dead Island 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-64">
  Steam User Rating: 64%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-36-354920515" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-36-354920515" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-36-354920515" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-36-354920515" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-36-354920515-img" id="article-gallery-36-354920515">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-36-354920515" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-36">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-36-slides-container-14371086">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After spending a year as an Epic Games Store exclusive,
  <em>
   Dead Island 2
  </em>
  finally made its Steam debut in April 2024, garnering a mixed reception due to issues not related to the game's quality. While these criticisms should not be ignored, this section will focus solely on
  <em>
   Dead Island 2
  </em>
  's co-op gameplay, which is awesome enough to warrant a spotlight.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like the original
  <em>
   Dead Island
  </em>
  , the sequel is primarily concerned with providing accessible first-person action with a
  <em>
   lot
  </em>
  of gore.
  <em>
   Dead Island 2
  </em>
  does not tell a complex narrative or feature particularly memorable characters, and it is fine without them. After a short intro section, players will unlock co-op, allowing them to join forces with two other slayers. From that point, the campaign descends into glorious madness as players get to rampage through a post-apocalyptic Los Angeles. The combat is simple but satisfying, and it is complemented by decent progression and customization systems.
  <em>
   Dead Island 2
  </em>
  's post-game is also quite robust, ensuring the fun does not stop just because there are no story missions left.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="call-of-duty-black-ops-6-zombies">
  Call Of Duty: Black Ops 6 (Zombies)
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-54">
  Steam User Rating: 54%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-37-1811911826" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-37-1811911826" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-37-1811911826" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-37-1811911826" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-37-1811911826-img" id="article-gallery-37-1811911826">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-37-1811911826" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-37">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-37-slides-container-442234976">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  is kind of difficult to recommend on Steam, mostly due to the game being available through Game Pass. If somebody has access to Steam, that means they can also jump into the PC Game Pass version, and if they are on the fence about trying Activision's latest entry in the series, they should go with the latter.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, removing that component from the equation,
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  is a good return to form following the disappointing
  <em>
   Modern Warfare 3
  </em>
  . The single-player campaign is one of the best in the franchise's history, specifically when it comes to gameplay. It has variety, intensity, and even a few surprises. At eight hours, the story is relatively long too, although it does not support co-op. The PvP modes are fairly standard for
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  For this particular discussion, those elements do not matter, and everything comes down to
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  's Zombies. Nowadays, this mode is firmly established as a
  <em>
   COD
  </em>
  staple, with each iteration allowing four players to come together as they mow down undead hordes, upgrade/buy weapons, and occasionally unlock a few buffs. After
  <em>
   MW3
  </em>
  took a bit of risk with Zombies,
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  opted to play things safe and return to
  <em>
   Black Ops Cold War
  </em>
  's formula, with storylines following a rounds-based structure that constantly pushes teams to unlock new areas.
 </p>
 <h2 id="starship-troopers-extermination">
  Starship Troopers: Extermination
 </h2>
 <h3 id="steam-user-rating-84">
  Steam User Rating: 84%
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-38-1916159758" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-38-1916159758" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-38-1916159758" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-38-1916159758" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-38-1916159758-img" id="article-gallery-38-1916159758">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-38-1916159758" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-38">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-38-slides-container-1106264336">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After spending roughly a year in early access,
  <em>
   Starship Troopers: Extermination
  </em>
  made its full debut in October 2024, and it is a fun but messy time. Despite reaching that 1.0 milestone, the game still has plenty of bugs, and not the type that you are meant to blast in the face. Still, there is a lot to enjoy here, largely thanks to strong gunplay, an impressive sense of scale thanks to the expansive maps, and the well-implemented co-op.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although containing something akin to a single-player campaign,
  <em>
   Starship Troopers: Extermination
  </em>
  is unquestionably meant to be experienced in multiplayer, one designed to continue endlessly as players wage an exhausting war with a fun assortment of alien bugs. Fittingly, considering the original movie inspired
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Extermination
  </em>
  provides a somewhat similar multiplayer structure as Arrowhead's project, although the gameplay is fairly different. Besides the focus on first-person combat, missions incorporate base building, along with just feeling like larger-scale wars.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="exciting-upcoming-co-op-games-on-steam">
  Exciting Upcoming Co-Op Games On Steam
 </h2>
 <h3 id="monster-hunter-hazelight-studios-and-elden-ring">
  Monster Hunter, Hazelight Studios, and Elden Ring
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-39-1184587427" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-39-1184587427" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-39-1184587427" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-39-1184587427" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-39-1184587427-img" id="article-gallery-39-1184587427">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-39-1184587427" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-39">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-39-slides-container-1633966530">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list specs">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Even if new games were to stop coming out today, Steam's seemingly endless library of co-op options could keep players busy for, essentially, ever. However, the gaming industry never sleeps, especially on PC. Every month, week, and day includes a couple of new titles. Sure, a lot of these releases go unnoticed, but exciting projects are pretty much always just around the corner.
 </p>
 <p>
  While still in its infancy, 2025's gaming calendar is already starting to take shape, particularly for its first quarter. An array of huge co-op games have been confirmed for the year, and two of them will debut quite soon.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Split Fiction
   </em>
   – Created by Hazelight Studios,
   <em>
    Split Fiction
   </em>
   has to follow up
   <em>
    A Way Out
   </em>
   and
   <em>
    It Takes Two
   </em>
   , which are among the greatest co-op games of all time. Similar to those projects, the upcoming title will likely not support a solo mode, especially since the story revolves around two characters who have to work together. The campaign follows two writers who are dragged into their own creations, and they have to combine their minds to escape. Going by the available footage,
   <em>
    Split Fiction
   </em>
   seems to be an action-driven adventure game, more so than the company's previous releases.
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </em>
   – At this point, most people should know what to expect from
   <em>
    Monster Hunter
   </em>
   , and
   <em>
    Wilds
   </em>
   does not appear to be too different from the norm. While solo play is certainly viable, Capcom's franchise shines in multiplayer, allowing hunters to work together to take down increasingly bigger and harder beasts.
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    Elden Ring Nightreign
   </em>
   – Well, this announcement came out of nowhere. FromSoftware is returning to The Lands Between for a multiplayer-driven adventure, one that is a standalone package and not an expansion.
   <em>
    Nightreign
   </em>
   will drop teams onto a map for three (in-game) days, challenging them to survive and triumph en route to facing a boss at the end of the cycle.
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales Of Graces F Remastered: How To Unlock The Bonus Content</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tales-of-graces-f-remastered-how-unlock-bonus-content/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Unlock Bonuses And DLC In Tales Of Graces F
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Unlockable Content In Tales Of Graces F Remastered
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The standard and deluxe versions of
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f
  </em>
  have packs of DLC content that can be claimed and used in the game. However, it can be difficult to find the menus where you can claim these items. You can also unlock other game-changing extras like EXP, SP, and HP boosts in the same menu thanks to the Grade Shop feature. The bonus menu also allows you to access the level-up add-on packs you can purchase from the Steam, PlayStation, and Xbox Stores. This guide will show you how to access all of your extra content in
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-unlock-bonuses-and-dlc-in-tales-of-graces-f">
  How To Unlock Bonuses And DLC In Tales Of Graces F
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Tales of Graces f - claiming items from the bonus menu" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-items-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Deluxe Edition DLC, Level Up Add-Ons, the Grade Shop, and preorder bonuses are accessible from the same menu screen in
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f Remastered.
  </em>
  Longtime
  <em>
   Tales
  </em>
  fans will be familiar with the method for claiming the bonuses and extras, but it may not be immediately obvious to new players. Use the following steps to unlock your DLC and more:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   During gameplay, open your menu screen.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select the
   <strong>
    Items
   </strong>
   tab.
  </li>
  <li>
   Navigate to the
   <strong>
    circular icon
   </strong>
   on the far right, just after the treasure chest menu.
  </li>
  <li>
   From there, you can access and claim your bonus content and skits further down the menu.
  </li>
  <li>
   After unlocking your content, it will be greyed out on the menu screen.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="unlockable-content-in-tales-of-graces-f-remastered">
  Unlockable Content In Tales Of Graces F Remastered
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Tales of Graces f - claiming costumes from the bonus menu" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-costumes-from-the-bonus-menu.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  You can access preorder and deluxe edition DLC for Tales of Graces, as well as paid Level Up bonuses. Here is a list of content you unlock in the bonus menu:
 </p>
 <h3 id="pre-order-content">
  Pre-Order Content
 </h3>
 <p>
  If you preorder
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f Remastered,
  </em>
  you'll get the
  <strong>
   Super Adventuring Asstance Set
  </strong>
  , which is unlocked in the bonus menu and includes items you can use in and out of combat in
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Apple Gel x 10
  </li>
  <li>
   Grape Gel x 10
  </li>
  <li>
   Life Bottle x 10
  </li>
  <li>
   Panacea Bottle x 10
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="deluxe-edition-content">
  Deluxe Edition Content
 </h3>
 <p>
  In addition to Battle BGM packs and the digital soundtrack, you'll also get the
  <strong>
   Super Growth Support Herb Set
  </strong>
  , which includes:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Red Chamomile × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Lavender × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Rosemary × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Savory × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Saffron × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Sage × 15
  </li>
  <li>
   Red Verbena × 15
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="grade-shop-extras">
  Grade Shop Extras
 </h3>
 <p>
  In older versions of
  <em>
   Tales of Graces,
  </em>
  you had to earn Grade Points so you could unlock bonuses ready for your New Game Plus mode. In the 2025 remaster, you can unlock these bonuses from the start, providing a lot of quality-of-life extras, Gel sets, costumes, and more.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Tales of Graces f - claiming grade shop items" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tales-of-graces-f-claiming-grade-shop-items.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Double Experience
  </li>
  <li>
   5 x Experience
  </li>
  <li>
   Double Item Drops
  </li>
  <li>
   Expand Inventory
  </li>
  <li>
   Double SP
  </li>
  <li>
   Triple SP
  </li>
  <li>
   Chain Capacity + 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Chain Capacity + 2
  </li>
  <li>
   Unlock Qualities
  </li>
  <li>
   Maximum Eleth + 500
  </li>
  <li>
   Upgrade Eleth Mixer
  </li>
  <li>
   Double Gald
  </li>
  <li>
   Halved Shop Prices
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="add-on-dlc-packs">
  Add-On DLC Packs
 </h3>
 <p>
  If the Grade Shop bonuses aren't enough, you can always purchase level-up boost packs that increase your character's level by 5 or 10.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Level Up+5
  </li>
  <li>
   Level Up+10
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_22">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     If you have activated the Experience and SP boosts in the Grade Shop, there is little point in spending real money and purchasing Level Up bonuses.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  That's everything that can be unlocked and can be claimed in the bonus DLC menu for
  <em>
   Tales of Graces f.
  </em>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geralt's Role in The Witcher 4 Already Seems Clear</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/witcher-4-geralt-role-mentor-vesemir/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Witcher 4
   </em>
  </strong>
  has put Ciri in the spotlight, and while she is primed to be a strong protagonist to carry the torch, there are naturally questions about Geralt's role in the story. Geralt has led the franchise until now, and although the story of
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  is unclear, there has at least been confirmation that he will be featured in the game in some capacity. His role may seem uncertain, but there is one route that feels like a given.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As Geralt's adoptive daughter, Ciri has learned many of her survival skills from him, and that mentor-mentee relationship seems bound to continue.
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  is likely a long time away, but when it comes to the evolving relationship of Ciri and Geralt, it feels highly probable that the latter will take on the same role that Vesemir did in
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="geralt-and-ciri-are-primed-to-have-a-similar-relationship-to-him-and-vesemir">
  Geralt and Ciri are Primed to Have a Similar Relationship to Him and Vesemir
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-656896769" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-656896769" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-656896769" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-656896769" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-656896769-img" id="article-gallery-1-656896769">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-656896769" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2138652715">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="vesemir-39-s-role-in-the-witcher-3-needs-to-be-filled">
  Vesemir's Role in The Witcher 3 Needs to be Filled
 </h3>
 <p>
  Unfortunately, Vesemir's death in
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  is an unavoidable tragedy that sets the stage for Geralt to take his place. His hero's death is the result of protecting Ciri, which makes it even more poetic that she is now serving as the game's lead. Vesemir sacrificing himself in order to protect her makes Geralt potentially stepping into his shoes an emotional transition, as well as a natural progression.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     During the events of
     <em>
      The Witcher 3
     </em>
     , Vesemir is the oldest living witcher.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="geralt-serving-as-a-mentor-isn-39-t-surprising">
  Geralt Serving as a Mentor Isn't Surprising
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  focused largely on Geralt and his role as a father figure as he searches for Ciri. Since Vesemir was Geralt's father figure, it makes perfect sense for Geralt to continue to be Ciri's mentor, as that has been his ongoing role in her life. While the evolution of these characters' relationships with one another may seem obvious to many who have played the game, it has yet to be confirmed. The lack of confirmation could make some fans feel uneasy and lead to speculation that Geralt may not be important to the game. Vesemir may not have played a starring role, but he was still quite important overall, which is a likely route for Geralt.
 </p>
 <p>
  So far, CD Projekt Red has been understandably secretive about how important Geralt will be to the story. In an interview with PC Gamer, game director Sebastian Kalemba coyly stated, "I can't tell you more, but I think the promise is enough" when discussing Geralt in
  <em>
   The WItcher 4
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     There is no official release window for
     <em>
      The Witcher 4
     </em>
     . Between this and
     <em>
      Cyberpunk 2077
     </em>
     's sequel, CD Projekt Red has its hands full.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="even-if-geralt-39-s-role-is-minimal-it-could-have-a-big-impact">
  Even If Geralt's Role is Minimal, It Could Have a Big Impact
 </h3>
 <p>
  Of course, some longtime fans may be sad to see Geralt take a backseat in the story, but his role will likely be essential, even if it's smaller. His advice and care for Ciri is bound to create some emotional moments that can bring a combination of nostalgia and excitement for the future. Ciri now leading the story is introducing a new era for
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  franchise, and it's exciting to think of what lies ahead.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_14">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     I can't tell you more, but I think the promise is enough.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  It could be years before
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  is released to the masses, so until then, the game remains a fertile field for speculation to grow. As more details about
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  are brought forth, it will be compelling to see how it differs from its successful predecessor. Having Ciri take Geralt's place as the new protagonist may be a big change, but it's also a strong way to demonstrate how far the relationship between these two characters has come.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
