<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Square Enix Requests Life is Strange Feedback Following Poor Sales</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/life-is-strange-double-exposure-poor-sales-square-enix-feedback-survey/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Square Enix is surveying Life is Strange fans after the latest entry in the series, Life is Strange: Double Exposure, wasn't received well.
     </li>
     <li>
      The survey quizzes fans about some key aspects of Life is Strange: Double Exposure, even asking them whether they felt the game was worth purchasing.
     </li>
     <li>
      Future Life is Strange games may be influenced by the community feedback Square Enix gathers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The disappointing commercial performance of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Life Is Strange: Double Exposure
   </strong>
  </em>
  has prompted publisher Square Enix to investigate what went wrong with the game by way of a survey. Accumulating fan feedback may help future Life is Strange games avoid the same pitfalls
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  found itself in.
 </p>
 <p>
  Released in October 2024,
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  had a lot going for it as a continuation of the story of Max Caulfield, the fan-favorite protagonist of 2015's original
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  . However, the return of Max Caulfield didn't do much for the newest entry in the episodic narrative-driven series.
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  garnered lukewarm reviews at launch, with its PS5 version currently standing at a 73 critic score and 4.2 user score on Metacritic. Many attribute this underwhelming reception to some of the major story decisions taken in
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Things took a turn for the worse when
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  developer Deck Nine Studios announced layoffs in December 2024. Determined to learn from the game's numerous missteps, Square Enix recently issued a wave of emails with a
  <strong>
   15-minute questionnaire to gather feedback from
   <em>
    Life is Strange
   </em>
   fans
  </strong>
  . The survey quizzes participants about key aspects of
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  , like its narrative, gameplay mechanics, technical performance, etc. It also asks fans if they thought
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  was worth purchasing and whether their experience has affected their interest in future series entries.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="square-enix-wants-to-know-why-life-is-strange-double-exposure-flopped">
  Square Enix Wants to Know Why Life is Strange: Double Exposure Flopped
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-345218079" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-345218079" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-345218079" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-345218079" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-345218079-img" id="article-gallery-1-345218079">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-345218079" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1055780450">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's clear that Square Enix expected a much more favorable reception to
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  , and so the questionnaire's findings may be very important for the company to assess where exactly the game stumbled. Deck Nine’s previous effort,
  <em>
   Life Is Strange: True Colors
  </em>
  , was widely praised for its storytelling and emotional depth.
  <em>
   Life is Strange: True Colors
  </em>
  protagonist Alex Chen also managed to captivate players in ways
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  's cast of characters could not.
 </p>
 <p>
  As for what the future of the
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  series holds,
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  did tease some plot points that can be explored by new entries down the line. However, the community feedback being amassed by Square Enix could very well influence the storylines of future
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  games. While there's a discussion to be had about where the line should be drawn when it comes to fan service, only time will tell how much (if at all) the next
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  game will cater to players.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smite 2 - Aladdin Gameplay Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/smite-2-aladdin-gameplay-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Check out this official gameplay trailer to see Aladdin in action in Smite 2. The iconic character will be available on January 13th, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuthering Waves: How to Unlock Nightmare Crownless</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wuthering-waves-wuwa-how-unlock-nightmare-crownless-ruins-where-shadows-roam/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Ruins Where Shadows Roam Quest Guide
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Unlock Nightmare Crownless in WuWa
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Nightmare Crownless is one of the new Nightmare versions of Overlord-class Echoes in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Wuthering Waves
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Unlike its regular counterpart, this one offers bonus Havoc DMG and Basic Attack DMG, making it an excellent pick for certain characters.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Much like other Nightmare Echoes in
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  , Nightmare Crownless can be farmed from its overworld spawn point. However, before you can tussle with this shiny spear user, you'll first need to
  <strong>
   complete the Ruins Where Shadows Roam quest and one extra step after that
  </strong>
  . Here's what you need to do to unlock Nightmare Crownless.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="ruins-where-shadows-roam-quest-guide">
  Ruins Where Shadows Roam Quest Guide
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-564295461" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-564295461" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-564295461" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-564295461" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-564295461-img" id="article-gallery-1-564295461">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-564295461" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1796027378">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This isn't your typical
  <em>
   WuWa
  </em>
  quest. Instead of being given by an NPC or by an interactable object in the world, Ruins Where Shadows Roam is found in the
  <strong>
   Exploration Progress menu for the Penitent's End region in Rinascita
  </strong>
  . You can get here by opening your map and clicking on the compass icon on the upper-left side, right next to the name of your current location.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ruins Where Shadows Roam goes hand-in-hand with
  <strong>
   Quest of Faith
  </strong>
  , an optional quest that involves defeating four enemies in specific areas of the Penitent's End region. To begin, go to the Resonance Beacon across the broken bridge in Wailing Ascent, then interact with the prompt that appears near the circular arena next to the beacon. This will start a fight against a Questless Knight similar to the ones in the Silver Moon? Crimson Moon? quest in
  <em>
   WuWa
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  To defeat the knights, you need to lure them into standing near a lit Macabre Torch in the arena. Torches can be reignited by baiting Fae Ignis enemies into hitting them. Be careful not to cast any hard-hitting skills near the torches, as you might end up extinguishing them.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-unlock-nightmare-crownless-in-wuwa">
  How to Unlock Nightmare Crownless in WuWa
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Dream Patrols in Penitent's End in WuWa" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wuthering-waves-penitent-s-end-dream-patrols.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After completing Ruins Where Shadows Roam and Quest of Faith, you'll then need to
  <strong>
   find all four Dream Patrols in Penitent's End
  </strong>
  . You don't need to complete any of these challenge, but if you want to get more resources and Monnaie in
  <em>
   WuWa
  </em>
  , you'll want to complete them all regardless. The locations of these Dream Patrols are on the image above. Once you find all the patrols, Nightmare Crownless will become visible on the map. You can find it in the ruins north of Penitent's End.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's worth noting that Nightmare Echoes use Enhanced Absorption charges, which significantly increase the drop rate of Echoes. Players only get 15 of these charges per week, so try not to spend all of them in one place if you're planning on building multiple characters.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palworld's Feybreak Update May Be the Game's Darkest Yet</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/palworld-feybreak-update-dark-splatterina-nitemary-dazzi-noct/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The monster-capturing and survival game hybrid,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Palworld
   </em>
  </strong>
  , has recently been given one of its biggest patches that has changed it for the better. The major Feybreak update has introduced a variety of new things, such as a bigger island, more Pals, resources, and more. Everything that it has brought to the game has improved the player's experience in ways that many appreciate, and it's a good sign for things to come if this is what Pocketpair expects to dish out more of in the future. But as great as it is, the latest update can also be seen as the darkest compared to the previous ones, as some of its additions have tapped into the macabre side of the in-game world.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  's Feybreak update has introduced a lot of interesting content, and the ones that have caught the eye of certain individuals come in the form of Pals. The patch has introduced 24 new monsters to battle or capture, giving people more reason to keep playing to see what they can offer to the game. Though the Pals are finely designed, their Paldeck entries have caused a number of players to raise their eyebrows. Though most contain normal descriptions, some enter into darker territory, making the Feybreak update feel more sinister when compared to something like the Sakurajima patch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-terrifying-paldeck-entries-that-make-the-feybreak-update-scarier-than-it-rsquo-s-supposed-to-be">
  The Terrifying Paldeck Entries That Make the Feybreak Update Scarier Than It’s Supposed to Be
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-343959848" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-343959848" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-343959848" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-343959848" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-343959848-img" id="article-gallery-1-343959848">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-343959848" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-862551210">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Feybreak Island of
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  may contain many beautiful environments, but it also hosts the Pals who look great in terms of design, but are extremely frightening based on what they could potentially do. Out of all the new monsters introduced, there are three in particular who have the darkest entries:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Nitemary's entry says that it forcibly extracts the soul of whoever it falls in love with and merges it with its own, ensuring a terrible fate for whoever the monster happens to fall for.
  </li>
  <li>
   Splatterina's description states that it has an uncontrollable urge to tear its prey and that each one has its own unique process of dismemberment, making it a creature that someone would rather not run into.
  </li>
  <li>
   While Dazzi Noct's Paldeck entry states that it ends up making friends with lonely Pals, its initial intentions show that it could have been a vile creature as it has the desire to lure others into a false sense of security before killing them.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The three can be seen as Feybreak update's way of showing that not everything in the game is full of wonder and excitement, emphasizing the dangers the world's inhabitants must face to survive. Because of what they're capable of aside from their combat strength, they may just be some of the scariest Pals in
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="why-it-rsquo-s-a-good-thing-that-the-feybreak-update-introduced-pals-with-darker-entries">
  Why It’s a Good Thing That the Feybreak Update Introduced Pals With Darker Entries
 </h3>
 <p>
  While not exactly playing a direct role in the big success of the Feybreak update, the darker entries help give the major patch more value. Having them shows that Pocketpair has not forgotten that the game is taking a more mature approach when compared to others of its kind, as that's one of the appeals it has that has made it popular and successful. Hopefully, the developer will consider adding more of such Pals in future updates, as tapping more into the darker side could attract even more people into playing
  <em>
   Palworld
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The Feybreak update's new Pals and their Paldeck entries help make the in-game world darker than before, and many fans likely appreciate it. While there's no telling what to expect from
  <em>
   <strong>
   </strong>
   Palworld
  </em>
  in 2025, there is hope that Pocketpair continues to provide more patches that show the darker side of what people are playing, as doing so can open up opportunities for even more interesting content.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New EA Sports UFC 5 Update Adds Undefeated Fighter</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ea-sports-ufc-5-new-update-january-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      EA Sports UFC 5 releases new update for January 9, available at 1 PM ET for PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S.
     </li>
     <li>
      Patch 1.18 for EA Sports UFC 5 adds undefeated fighter Azamat Murzakanov and makes numerous bug fixes.
     </li>
     <li>
      Xbox Game Pass Ultimate subscribers can play EA Sports UFC 5 via EA Play from January 14.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    EA Sports UFC 5
   </strong>
  </em>
  developer EA Vancouver is set to release a new update for the popular mixed martial arts fighting game on January 9, adding a new undefeated fighter to the roster and making a handful of bug fixes and improvements. Patch 1.18 for
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  will be available for PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S users on January 9 at 1 PM ET, with no downtime expected for the update.
 </p>
 <p>
  While rumors continue to circulate around a new
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC
  </em>
  game, EA Vancouver appears to remain dedicated to the latest installment. When
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  was first released back in October 2023, many die-hard
  <em>
   UFC
  </em>
  players were left disappointed by the game's fighter roster. In response to the backlash, EA Vancouver announced it would be working to bring more and more ranked fighters from various weight classes to the game. Since the announcement,
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  has reached 98% parity with the current UFC top ten rankings thanks to a steady stream of new content updates.
 </p>
 <p>
  EA Vancouver has kicked off
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  's second year with a brand-new update, which will be released at 1 PM ET on January 9. The latest update adds Azamat Murzakanov to the game's Light Heavyweight division, with an undefeated record and some impressive stats. The Russian mixed martial artist joins
  <em>
   UFC 5
  </em>
  with a power punch rating of 97, 95 accuracy, and 94 ground striking. Although there is only one new fighter included in today's update, EA Vancouver has also revealed that three new alter egos will be coming to
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  with the update but did not reveal which fighters they would be for.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1148793865" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1148793865" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1148793865" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1148793865" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1148793865-img" id="article-gallery-1-1148793865">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1148793865" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1142272303">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Aside from the addition of a new fighter and three new alter egos,
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  's new update also includes a few minor bug fixes and one gameplay adjustment. According to the official patch notes, which can be viewed in full further down this article, patch 1.18 reduces the stamina cost of the muscle modifier from x3.125 to 2.5. In terms of bug fixes, an incorrect translation for some languages has been rectified, as well as an issue with Stand and Bang in Ranked, and more.
 </p>
 <p>
  The latest update comes after Microsoft announced that
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  would be joining Xbox Game Pass on January 14. Although the upcoming game drop will feature the likes of
  <em>
   Road 96
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Lightyear Frontier
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   My Time at Sandrock
  </em>
  , and more for Xbox Game Pass' Standard tier,
  <em>
   EA Sports UFC 5
  </em>
  will only be available on the subscription service's Ultimate tier as it will be joining Xbox Game Pass via EA Play.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="ea-sports-ufc-5-patch-notes-for-january-9-update">
  EA Sports UFC 5 Patch Notes for January 9 Update
 </h2>
 <h3 id="general">
  General
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   New Fighters
   <ul>
    <li>
     Azamat Murzakanov
    </li>
    <li>
     Three new Alter Egos
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   More Offers Store - Sort by Release Series (ie Pride, Prime, Champion, etc)
  </li>
  <li>
   New assorted vanity rewards added
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="gameplay">
  Gameplay
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Reduced the stamina cost of the muscle modifier from x 3.125 to 2.5.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="bugs">
  Bugs
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed incorrect translations in some languages
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where the match result method (KO/TKO, etc) wouldn’t appear in Ranked Championship: Stand and Bang
  </li>
  <li>
   Updated AE UFC 309 Stipe and Jones portraits to match their glove update
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
