<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>My Night Job - Official Nintendo Switch Release Date Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/my-night-job-official-nintendo-switch-release-date-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Take a look at the official Nintendo Switch release date trailer for My Night Job, which is set to be released on Nintendo Switch on February 27, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - All Bathhouses (&amp; How They Work)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-all-bathhouses-how-they-work-trosky-kuttenberg/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What Are Bathhouses For in Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Bathhouse Locations in KCD2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The semi-realism of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  doesn't stop at basic survival needs. Apart from eating and sleeping to avoid health-related penalties, players will also want to keep themselves clean if they don't want to give themselves away in moments that count.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Cleanliness should be on the mind of every new
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  player. Washing yourself at a trough will only get you so far, and if you find yourself walking away from a grueling fight, you're better off going to a bathhouse. In this guide, we'll show you what you can expect from these fine establishments as well as the locations of the most conveniently-placed bathhouses across the game's two regions.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-are-bathhouses-for-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  What Are Bathhouses For in Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Bath options in KCD2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-21_184304454.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unsurprisingly, bathhouses are for taking baths for a small fee. Compared to simply washing yourself in a trough, a full bath will clean you more thoroughly, increasing the time it takes before you become notably dirty again. More importantly, bath services also include an option to fully wash dirt off all your clothes and armor, something you'd otherwise only be able to do at laundry sites with soap in
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  <em>
   .
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Most (if not all) bathhouses also offer special services, which involve a quick, one-hour romance with one of the bathmaids. This option costs more, but you'll end up completely clean and with the
  <strong>
   Time Well Spent
  </strong>
  buff, which temporarily increases your Strength, Agility, and Vitality by 1.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bathhouse-locations-in-kcd2">
  Bathhouse Locations in KCD2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-783127507" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-783127507" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-783127507" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-783127507" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-783127507-img" id="article-gallery-1-783127507">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-783127507" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-473781075">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are numerous bathhouses spread through both the Trosky and Kuttenberg regions, with the latter having significantly more of everything, with it being a large city and all. The prices for bathhouse services will remain more or less the same, however, and if you know how to make money fast in
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  , this shouldn't be an issue.
 </p>
 <p>
  Bathhouses are represented by either
  <strong>
   perfume bottle or bathtub icons
  </strong>
  on your map and compass. If you want to see the entirety of both world maps without having to run around everywhere, get the Explorer perk under Scholarship. Be warned, though, as this might ruin the experience for you if you like exploring and finding different things the old-fashioned way.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th colspan="2" scope="col">
      <p>
       KCD2 Bathhouse Locations
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Trosky
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Kuttenberg
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Zhelejov - Bathmaid Dorothy
       </li>
       <li>
        Trosky Castle - Near Osina's smithy
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Kuttenberg - Kingfisher Bathhouse
       </li>
       <li>
        Kuttenberg - City Bathhouse
       </li>
       <li>
        Maleshov Baths
       </li>
       <li>
        Devil's Den Baths
       </li>
       <li>
        Sigismund's Camp Baths
       </li>
       <li>
        Pschitoky Baths
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     You can travel between regions by taking a carriage. Also, some areas may be inaccessible during or after certain points of the main story.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars: KOTOR's Development Problems Can't Be for Nothing</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/star-wars-kotor-remake-problems-quality-release-influence/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Development issues with the KOTOR Remake need to end on a strong note to ensure success.
     </li>
     <li>
      Relying solely on nostalgia can alienate new players and disappoint veterans.
     </li>
     <li>
      The KOTOR Remake must be as thorough as the original, balancing innovation and respect for the past.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the most prominent pieces of news in the gaming industry revolves around the highly anticipated but increasingly skeptical
  <strong>
   <em>
    Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
   </em>
  </strong>
  remake. This constant news is largely due to the game's developmental issues, which are now more common knowledge than even the game's own features. Initially, Aspyr Media was heading up the development of the remake, but the project shifted to Saber Interactive in August 2022 after some significant changes were made to Aspyr's development team. Things then got even more complicated last February, when Embracer Group announced plans to sell Saber Interactive.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite these massive upheavals, Saber Interactive's CEO, Matthew Karch, stated in April 2024 that the
  <em>
   Star Wars: KOTOR
  </em>
  remake remained "alive and well," reaffirming the company's commitment to the project. Nevertheless, there is still no official release date for the game, nor has there been any more noteworthy news on the state of its development. All of these problems ultimately create one considerable issue that the
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  remake will need to overcome: it can't be all for nothing. In other words, the
  <em>
   Star Wars: KOTOR
  </em>
  remake can't just rely on nostalgia to succeed, and should instead move on to carry the torch of its namesake as one of the most influential RPGs ever made.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-kotor-remake-39-s-development-problems-need-to-end-on-a-strong-note">
  The KOTOR Remake's Development Problems Need to End on a Strong Note
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-680845424" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-680845424" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-680845424" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-680845424" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-680845424-img" id="article-gallery-1-680845424">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-680845424" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1741661055">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-kotor-remake-can-39-t-rely-on-nostalgia-to-succeed">
  The KOTOR Remake Can't Rely on Nostalgia to Succeed
 </h3>
 <p>
  It's no secret that BioWare's
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  is one of the most influential RPGs ever made, as many modern RPGs today still look to it for guidance when it comes to choice and morality systems, character development, storytelling, and world design. Given the impact that
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  had and still has on the gaming industry, Saber's remake might be tempted to think nostalgia alone will be enough to carry it forward to success. Unfortunately, nostalgia has never been effective at ensuring the long-term success of anything, much less a video game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most notably, video game remakes that rely too much on nostalgia often alienate new players who lack emotional attachment to the original. Without modern quality-of-life improvements, gameplay, and storytelling, these remakes end up feeling too antiquated for new audiences to get into, resulting in a cold reception. On the flip side, video game remakes that reinvent things too much alienate the original game's veterans, as they may believe that the remake is out of touch with the original. It's a remake's ability to strike a balance between innovation and respect that leads to its success, as games like
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake
  </em>
  and its sequel,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  , have proven.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-kotor-remake-needs-to-be-as-influential-as-the-original">
  The KOTOR Remake Needs to Be as Influential as the Original
 </h3>
 <p>
  If the
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  remake ends up going through all of these developmental problems, only to come out on the other side as an irrelevant, redundant, nostalgia-fueled product, that would undoubtedly lead to its demise. New fans that it could have captivated would therefore be disregarded, and veteran fans will ultimately be let down by the short-term appeal of the game after the nostalgia has worn off. This puts the
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  remake in a unique position, and one that reflects the status of its namesake.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     It's no secret that BioWare's
     <em>
      Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
     </em>
     is one of the most influential RPGs ever made, as many modern RPGs today still look to it for guidance when it comes to choice and morality systems, character development, storytelling, and world design.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  In short, the
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  remake has just as much of an opportunity to reinvent the RPG landscape as its predecessor did, but it will need to ensure it's not simply relying on nostalgia to capture the success of the original. Instead, all the development problems the
  <em>
   Star Wars: KOTOR
  </em>
  remake has endured will need to pay off in an inventive and innovative way that still manages to honor the legacy of the original game. Then, perhaps it might be able to be the next big influential RPG of its own time, showing that every issue it faced during its development was worth it in the end.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farming Simulator 25 Releases New Update for February 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/farming-simulator-25-update-february-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Farming Simulator 25's free content update adds new machines like tractors and front loaders for players.
     </li>
     <li>
      The update includes quality-of-life improvements like a ModHub "update all" button and graphics settings menu.
     </li>
     <li>
      The community also plays a role in expanding the game with mods, while the developer continues to support modders.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Farming Simulator 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  has released its first free content update, adding new machines alongside various quality-of-life improvements and bug fixes. This free
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  content update gives players even more options to take care of their crops and enjoy their farms.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ever since its release in November 2024,
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  has quickly established itself as a staple for farm-simulation enthusiasts.
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  allows players to build and manage their own farms. The game features realistic machinery like tractors and front loaders that players operate to cultivate crops across various landscapes, from European farmlands to East Asian rice paddies and classic American farmhouses.
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  sold 2 million copies in its first week, ranking it among the top 20 best-selling Xbox games of 2024.
 </p>
 <p>
  Giants Software released the first free content update for
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  , introducing several new machines and vehicles for free alongside quality-of-life improvements and bug fixes. Players can claim two new tractors for free, the CLAAS ARION (550–530) and John Deere 6R Series (230–250). This free update also brings two new front loaders, the CLAAS FL 140 and John Deere 683R. Last but not least, players can get a free Albutt f155A Bale Grab at the dealership. These new machines add more vehicle variety to
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  , which already boasts over 100 machines and dedicated mods to add even more options.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="farming-simulator-25-releases-adds-free-machines">
  Farming Simulator 25 Releases Adds Free Machines
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-8338850e665b4283" id="emaki-video-player-8338850e665b4283">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Beyond new machinery, this free
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  update brought a variety of gameplay improvements and bug fixes. Giants Software added a ModHub "update all" button, a saving notification icon in multiplayer, smaller engine configurations on DEUTZ-FAHR Series 6C and SAME Virtus RVShift, as well as the ability to access the graphics settings menu while already in a game for those who would like to get enhanced graphics in
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  . Some minor balancing changes address issues with AI fieldwork helpers and animals. Additionally, various bugs were fixed to further improve the overall gameplay experience.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-267119096" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-267119096" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-267119096" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-267119096" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-267119096-img" id="article-gallery-1-267119096">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-267119096" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2094104436">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While official updates continue to add new content, the
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  community also plays a key role in expanding the game. Players frequently develop mods that introduce new features, such as graphics enhancements for improved visuals, custom vehicle mods that add new tractors and machinery, and crop mods that adjust growth mechanics in
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  . Giants Software continues to support the modding community by adding new options for modders in
  <em>
   Farming Simulator 25
  </em>
  , although the developer warned that the new update could require updating some mods to work properly.
 </p>
 <h2 id="farming-simulator-free-content-update-patch-notes">
  Farming Simulator Free Content Update Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <h3 id="free-content">
  Free Content
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Albutt f155A Bale Grab
  </li>
  <li>
   CLAAS ARION (550–530) Tractor
  </li>
  <li>
   CLAAS FL 140 Frontloader
  </li>
  <li>
   John Deere 6R Series (230–250) Tractor
  </li>
  <li>
   John Deere 683R Frontloader
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="new-additions-amp-functionality">
  New Additions &amp; Functionality
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   ModHub "update all" button
  </li>
  <li>
   Saving notification icon in multiplayer
  </li>
  <li>
   Smaller engine configurations on DEUTZ-FAHR Series 6C and SAME Virtus RVShift
  </li>
  <li>
   Graphics settings menu within the active gameplay
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="changes-amp-improvements">
  Changes &amp; Improvements
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Various technical changes to improve performance
  </li>
  <li>
   Various stability improvements to prevent crashes
  </li>
  <li>
   Various text / translation adjustments
  </li>
  <li>
   Various visual adjustments on several models
  </li>
  <li>
   Changed custom pasture calculations allowing for more chicken, pigs, and sheep in the same area as before
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed AI fieldwork helper ignoring user preferences
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed animal health and productivity calculation
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed animal productivity bar showing global productivity state instead of combined productivity (globalProductivity*foodProductivity)
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed belt position while unloading bales on the New Holland Pro-Belt 165
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed display of cow barn capacities
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed export of farmland area and price for game stats on dedicated servers
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed grass eating cows
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed International CV Box configuration wetness
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed missing beetroot filltype on Bergmann RRW 500
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed missing silage additive on Pöttinger BOSS ALPIN 251
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed ModHub checkmark on newly downloaded mods
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed shop display cutting off filltypes on some machines
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed shop display when all used machines are bought
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed spinach not withering
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed train hotspot stuttering when far away
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed UI scaling not being applied correctly on some UI elements
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed UI sound when opening the license plate menu or color picker
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed wrong or no player names displayed when selecting vehicle on map
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved offroad driving speed and behavior of Go To helper
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved performance of periodic game stats saving on dedicated servers avoiding lag spikes
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved shop display of long machine names
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="modding">
  Modding
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added support for continuous motion in uvScrollShader using z and w values in 'offsetUV' parameter
  </li>
  <li>
   Added warning of env map directory if not properly setup for maps
  </li>
  <li>
   Added rearLight84 &amp; rearLight85
  </li>
  <li>
   Adjusted light of rearLight30
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed custom placeable names using 'nameL10nKey' attribute not being synchronized to clients
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed Lua breakpoints in Studio not working if they were added before connecting the game instance to Studio
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite Is Crossing Over With Cowboy Bebop</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-cowboy-bebop-crossover/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fortnite will crossover with Cowboy Bebop on February 28, featuring Spike and Faye skins.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans can earn a free Cowboy Bebop wrap and loading screen through quests.
     </li>
     <li>
      Future collaborations are rumored to include Demon Slayer and Like a Dragon.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Epic Games has announced that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  will be crossing over with the hit anime
  <em>
   Cowboy Bebop,
  </em>
  beginning on February 28.
  <em>
   Cowboy Bebop
  </em>
  was originally released in Japan in 1998 and aired for 26 episodes before making its way to the United States in 2001. Many fans have been clamoring to see the show's classic characters come to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  for quite some time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Epic Games recently released Chapter 6 Season 2 of
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , which will likely come with numerous collaborations as the months roll on. Given that Sub-Zero from
  <em>
   Mortal Kombat
  </em>
  is included in the battle pass, a lot of players think it's likely that Scorpion and other fighters could be just around the corner. An official video shared on social media also documented a fake rap beef between
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  's Big Dill and T-Pain, leading many to believe the Grammy-winning artist could be coming to the island soon.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  's patch notes have revealed that it will soon feature a crossover with the popular anime
  <em>
   Cowboy Bebop
  </em>
  . Epic Games stated that fans can expect to see skins for the characters Spike Spiegel and Faye Valentine in their classic outfits arrive in the Item Shop on February 28. Meanwhile, players will also be able to complete quests in order to earn a free wrap and loading screen based on the hit show. Gamers will have to act fast, as the challenges are set to end on March 18.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="cowboy-bebop-cosmetics-coming-to-fortnite">
  Cowboy Bebop Cosmetics Coming to Fortnite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-440930525" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-440930525" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-440930525" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-440930525" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-440930525-img" id="article-gallery-1-440930525">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-440930525" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1650910452">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Spike Spiegel - Skin
  </li>
  <li>
   Faye Valentine - Skin
  </li>
  <li>
   COWBOY BEBOP - Wrap
  </li>
  <li>
   BEBOP Legends - Loading Screen
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  could also feature a crossover with the anime
  <em>
   Demon Slayer
  </em>
  , which many fans wanted to see during Chapter 6 Season 1. While some players are still hopeful that the two could combine forces, others believe that Epic Games was actually teasing its official collaboration with
  <em>
   Kaiju No. 8
  </em>
  . Leakers have remained adamant that
  <em>
   Demon Slayer
  </em>
  is still on the way to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , but such unconfirmed information could always prove to be unreliable.
 </p>
 <p>
  It has also been rumored that a collaboration may be happening between
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  , which many fans have expressed excitement about. A large portion of the community seems to feel the crossover would be perfectly timed, as Chapter 6 Season 2 features organized crime as a prominent theme. While unconfirmed, leakers have claimed that the potential collaboration would involve Kazuma Kiryu and Goro Majima making their way to the island. With a fresh season to explore and even more content on the horizon, many fans are feeling optimistic about the future of
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
