<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Fashion Week Event is Coming Back for 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-fashion-week-event-january-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO's Fashion Week event returns with new costumed Pokemon and rewards on January 10.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can earn double Stardust, encounter costumed shiny Pokemon in the wild, and participate in Fashion Week raids.
     </li>
     <li>
      Paid Timed Research will be available for $5, offering XP, Stardust, and encounters with featured Pokemon.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon GO
   </strong>
  </em>
  developer Niantic confirmed that the limited-time Fashion Week event is coming back as one of the game's first events of 2025. During Fashion Week,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players can encounter new costumed Pokemon and earn additional rewards, thanks to several event bonuses and Field Research tasks.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  recently celebrated New Year's Day 2025 with a limited-time event to hype fans up for another year of updates and events to come. In January,
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  will host a Mega Gallade Raid Day event, the next Community Day event, and a limited-time collaboration with McDonald's, just to name a few. Fashion Week has been added to the slate of events for January, giving players another opportunity to earn some enticing rewards.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Fashion Week returns on Friday, January 10 at 10:00 a.m. local time, and the event will last until Sunday, January 19, 2025, at 8:00 p.m. local time. During the event, players will earn double Stardust for catching Pokemon, and players level 31 and up are twice as likely to receive Candy XL in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . There's an increased chance to encounter a costumed shiny Kirlia in the wild, along with costumed Diglett and Blitzle. Costumed Butterfree, Dragonite, Minccino, and Cinccino will also appear in the wild after completing Fashion Week Field Research tasks, with the chance to encounter a shiny variant. Skitty, Buneary, Furfrou, and Bruxish will appear more frequently in the wild as well.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-fashion-week-details">
  Pokemon GO Fashion Week Details
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1813464354" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1813464354" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1813464354" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1813464354" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1813464354-img" id="article-gallery-1-1813464354">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1813464354" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-456680338">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
   Fashion Week will be live from January 10 at 10:00 a.m. to January 19 at 8:00 p.m. local time.
  </li>
  <li>
   Players can earn double Stardust and Candy XL by participating in Fashion Week.
  </li>
  <li>
   There's an increased chance of encountering the following Pokemon in the wild and in raids:
   <ul>
    <li>
     Costumed Butterfree
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Dragonite
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Minccino
    </li>
    <li>
     Furfrou
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Cinccino
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Diglett
    </li>
    <li>
     Skitty
    </li>
    <li>
     Buneary
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Blitzle
    </li>
    <li>
     Bruxish
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Kirlia
    </li>
    <li>
     Costumed Shinx
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Completing Fashion Week Field Research and Paid Timed Research tasks grants additional encounters and rewards.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Fashion Week one-star and three-star raids will be held, giving players a better chance to encounter some of the event's new costumed Pokemon, including a costumed Shinx.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO's
  </em>
  Remote Raid Passes may be used to enter the raid from a distance. Players wanting to earn more XP and Stardust after completing Field Research tasks may purchase the new Fashion Week Paid Timed Research for $5. Timed Research rewards include 3,500 XP, 3,500 Stardust, a new event-themed pose, and additional encounters with Fashion Week's featured Pokemon. It's worth noting that Timed Research rewards must be claimed before Fashion Week ends.
 </p>
 <p>
  The in-game
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  shop will also get new Plaid Top and Plaid Pants avatar items, which will continue to be available for purchase after Fashion Week ends. Like past
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  events, players can enter their newly acquired Pokemon in PokeStop Showcases to receive rewards during Fashion Week. Lastly, Niantic confirmed that a Fashion Week-themed Collection Challenge will be available, and completing the challenge grants more XP and a guaranteed encounter with a costumed Shinx.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master Chief's Return to Fortnite Should Only Be The First Step of Many</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-master-chief-collaboration-characters-cortana-arbiter/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Over
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s seven-year-long lifespan, a wide cast of varied characters from all mediums of pop culture have appeared in the game as outfits for gamers to play as in Battle Royale and other game types. From the Marvel Cinematic Universe’s Mad Titan Thanos to the critically acclaimed American singer and songwriter Mariah Carey, gamers have been able to play as almost every popular icon within
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In 2024’s late holiday season, gamers were once again able to purchase and play as
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s Master Chief before being vaulted before the new year. While Master Chief didn’t return for long, his popularity among longtime
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  fans should encourage Epic Games and Halo Studios to introduce more
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  characters to the game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fortnite-rsquo-s-master-chief-explained">
  Fortnite’s Master Chief Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-661606082" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-661606082" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-661606082" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-661606082" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-661606082-img" id="article-gallery-1-661606082">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-661606082" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1794974524">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While Master Chief wasn’t the first video game character to appear in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , he was one of the most surprising to appear in the game since the Spartan is the mascot of Xbox’s flagship exclusive franchise,
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  . In late 2020, 343 Industries and Epic Games chose to release Master Chief as the next Gaming Legend for
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ’s Chapter 2: Season 5 in coordination with
  <em>
   Halo Infinite
  </em>
  ’s initial release date of November 2020. Master Chief’s addition to the game additionally coincided with the release of
  <em>
   Red vs. Blue: Zero
  </em>
  , the 18th season of
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s long-running Rooster Teeth machinima series in December 2020, as characters, such as Sarge and Grif, from the series appeared in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  marketing for the Spartan’s arrival.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  players weren't just able to purchase Master Chief as an outfit, however. Players who purchased the Master Chief Bundle were additionally able to equip the Battle Legend Back Bling based on
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s Legendary Difficulty symbol, a Gravity Hammer Pickaxe, a UNSC Pelican Glider, and a Lil' Warthog emote. Gamers who were able to play
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  on an Xbox Series X/S console or through the Xbox Cloud Gaming service would have further unlocked a Matte Black alternate style of Master Chief’s GEN3 armor. In 2020, players were further able to relive
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s glory days in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  by playing Slayer-esque matches in the remake of
  <em>
   Halo: Combat Evolved
  </em>
  ’s classic map Blood Gulch via
  <em>
   Fortnite Creative
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Master Chief was first vaulted in
     <em>
      Fortnite
     </em>
     in December 2020 but returned in March 2021, August 2021, September 2021, May 2022, June 2022, and December 2024.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="other-potential-halo-characters-to-arrive-in-fortnite">
  Other Potential Halo Characters to Arrive in Fortnite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1852118859" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1852118859" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1852118859" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1852118859" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1852118859-img" id="article-gallery-2-1852118859">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1852118859" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1896046232">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Based on Master Chief's recurring popularity in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and his ability to have numerous
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  fans flock to the battle royale game, Epic Games and Halo Studio should consider adding more
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  characters to continue spiking player interest. Several other iconic video game series have had multiple characters cross over into
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  such as
  <em>
   Destiny
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  , so it would make sense for Halo Studios to want to equalize
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s playing field in the battle royale game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     With a new
     <em>
      Halo
     </em>
     game possibly being announced sometime in 2025, and given that 2026 will be the franchise's 25th anniversary, Epic Games and Halo Studios could coordinate to bring back Master Chief alongside other
     <em>
      Halo
     </em>
     characters to coincide with this new game’s announcement.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Two of the most probable
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  characters to join Master Chief in Fortnite would be Cortana and the Arbiter. All three characters make up
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s core trio from the series’ original trilogy and are some of the most iconic protagonists in the entire franchise. Cortana could be released with three distinct styles, one based on her original, purple
  <em>
   Combat Evolved
  </em>
  appearance, another based on her evil
  <em>
   Halo 5: Guardians
  </em>
  appearance, and another based on The Weapon from
  <em>
   Halo Infinite
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Meanwhile, the Arbiter could have two styles: one based on his
  <em>
   Halo 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   3
  </em>
  appearance and another based on his
  <em>
   Halo 5
  </em>
  appearance. The Arbiter could also come with an Energy Sword Pickaxe and Banshee Glider, while Cortana could come with a Guardian Glider and Index Pickaxe.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-potential-halo-villain-brought-to-fortnite">
  A Potential Halo Villain Brought to Fortnite
 </h3>
 <p>
  First introduced in 2016’s
  <em>
   Halo Wars 2
  </em>
  , Atriox has quickly become one of the most popular antagonists in the
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  franchise, with his Banished faction becoming the main opponents seen in
  <em>
   Halo Infinite
  </em>
  . With Atriox possibly set to return in
  <em>
   Halo 7
  </em>
  , he could make for an exciting addition to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  , especially if his red Energy Mace Chainbreaker is made as a Pickaxe skin. While
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  ’s future is currently uncertain, these additions could spike interest in the franchise as it nears its 25th anniversary.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Quest Headsets Get a 10% Discount, But There's a Catch</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/meta-quest-headset-10-percent-discount-catch/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Meta is offering a 10% discount on Quest headsets to students and educators through their official website.
     </li>
     <li>
      The discount can save buyers up to $49.99 on models like the Quest 3, making the high-end devices more affordable.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite recent technical issues with Quest headsets, Meta dominates the wireless VR market, likely without competition soon.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  VR enthusiasts who are interested in the
  <strong>
   Meta Quest
  </strong>
  headsets may be excited to learn that there's an available 10% discount. However, this Meta Quest discount is only available to select buyers, namely those who are in school or are teachers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Currently, the Meta Quest 3 and 3S are on store shelves, with Meta Quest Pro and Meta Quest 2 no longer being produced. The Meta Quest 3 is currently Meta's best headset available with a higher price point, while the 3S sacrifices certain features in order to make the cost more affordable. However, with the base Meta Quest 3S model starting at $299.99, some interested buyers may still be hopeful for a price cut.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, Meta is offering a 10% discount to students and educators. In order to get it, all gamers need to do is to go to Meta's official website and enter a valid email address ending in the .EDU extension. Meta will send a link to the email address which will enable the 10% discount, which can be applied to Meta Quest headsets, Ray-Ban Meta Glasses, and some accessories for the devices. This discount will shave a nice $29.99 off the base model of the Meta Quest 3S, and $49.99 off the Meta Quest 3.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1204349909" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1204349909" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1204349909" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1204349909" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1204349909-img" id="article-gallery-1-1204349909">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1204349909" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1941923046">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="meta-quest-3-and-3s-get-10-education-discount">
  Meta Quest 3 and 3S Get 10% Education Discount
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Meta Quest 3S 128GB: Originally $299.99, $270 after $29.99 discount
  </li>
  <li>
   Meta Quest 3S 256GB: Originally $399.99, $360 after $39.99 discount
  </li>
  <li>
   Meta Quest 3 512GB: Originally $499.99, $450 after $49.99 discount
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Meta Quest line of headsets is experiencing something of a rough patch right now, as a recently-launched update apparently bricked numerous Meta Quest units, including the Meta Quest 2, 3, and 3S headsets. The company has since pushed updates that have reportedly fixed the issue for a number of owners, but for those who are still having problems, the company is offering a way to get a replacement Meta Quest headset. While it's an unfortunate development, it's good to see that the company stands behind its products.
 </p>
 <p>
  Depsite this recent mishap, Meta remains largely unchallenged in the realm of wireless VR headsets. While there have been rumors of a new VR headset from Valve, nothing official has surfaced. Meta tends to offer discounts for its headsets or bundles that include additional games or accessories during holidays, but for those who want a discount now, this may be the best offer for a while.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaphor: ReFantazio's Summoner Archetype Could Inspire a Knockout Feature for Persona 6</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/metaphor-refantazio-summoner-archetype-persona-6-boss-shadow-summons/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_0">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     Spoilers ahead for Metaphor: ReFantazio.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For years, Atlus has mostly been known for its two pillar JRPG franchises:
  <em>
   Shin Megami Tensei
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  , the latter of which spun off of
  <em>
   SMT
  </em>
  to begin with. In 2024, however,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Metaphor: ReFantazio
   </strong>
  </em>
  changed that, beginning a new Atlus franchise and racking up critical acclaim, including several wins at The Game Awards 2024.
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  shares a ton of DNA with
  <em>
   SMT
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  , especially in borrowing
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  's social sim elements and how party members awaken to magical power through the power of their heart. In exchange, the inevitable
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  might borrow some ideas from
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  , and if so, it should draw on the Summoner Archetype in particular.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Summoner belongs to a long tradition of JRPG characters, classes, and jobs that revolve around conjuring up a powerful monster to attack enemies. Many incarnations of Summoners have special requirements for unlocking new abilities, and
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  is no different, asking fans to craft vessels to get new Summoner skills.
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  already has extensive themes of "summoning" thanks to the titular Personas, but it still has room for a more traditional summoning mechanic inspired by the Summoner Archetype in
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  . Just like how the Archetype references classic monsters from Atlus history like Jack Frost,
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  could celebrate the franchise's history and spotlight its own major encounters with the power of summoning.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="a-metaphor-refantazio-style-summoning-mechanic-could-be-persona-6-39-s-version-of-theurgy">
  A Metaphor: ReFantazio-Style Summoning Mechanic Could Be Persona 6's Version of Theurgy
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-962209590" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-962209590" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-962209590" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-962209590" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-962209590-img" id="article-gallery-1-962209590">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-962209590" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1893116537">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The broad strokes of
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  seem fairly obvious -- turn-based combat, dungeon crawling, and a calendar-based social system are all but guaranteed to return. However, after games like
  <em>
   Persona 5 Royal
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </em>
  introduced mechanics like Hold Ups, Showtimes, and Theurgy to increase their depth of strategy, Atlus has put some pressure on itself to build some special combat tricks into
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  to set it apart. One way to do that could be by combining Theurgy from
  <em>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </em>
  with the Summoner Archetype.
 </p>
 <p>
  Theurgy attacks revolve around
  <em>
   Persona 3 Reload
  </em>
  's party members turbo-charging their Personas to use a special technique. Rather than focusing on Personas,
  <em>
   Persona 6 Reload
  </em>
  could allow players to charge up an attack that allows them to summon a powerful Shadow to attack the enemy.
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  features a variety of Persona-user antagonists that make use of Shadows to advance their own interests, whether by directly manipulating them or simply scheming around them, so it's entirely within the realm of possibility that
  <em>
   P6
  </em>
  's party could figure out a way to do it too, especially if
  <em>
   P6
  </em>
  retains
  <em>
   Persona 5
  </em>
  's
  <em>
   SMT
  </em>
  -inspired intelligent Shadows.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a wide variety of ways that
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  players might unlock Shadow summons:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Persona 6
   </em>
   could feature a highly traditional Summoner mechanic where fans have to battle tough optional bosses in order to earn the right to summon that boss in battle later.
  </li>
  <li>
   The protagonist might unlock a Persona-based summon when they fuse that Persona in the Velvet Room, which would encourage players to fill out the compendium (and play off
   <em>
    P3R
   </em>
   's unlockable Theurgies for the protagonist)
  </li>
  <li>
   Completing non-party Social Links in
   <em>
    Persona 6
   </em>
   could reward players with a special summon inspired by that character -- essentially conjuring a Shadow version of their unawakened Persona in battle without physically bringing that character into the Shadow world
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The
     <em>
      Persona 3 Reload
     </em>
     protagonist's Theurgy skills are actually a little similar to the Summoner Archetype already, in that he calls for help from Personas he used in the past, who don't have to be in the player's current inventory of Personas to be used in a Theurgy.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Perhaps the biggest question for a Shadow summon mechanic would be whether the whole party could use it. It certainly seems like a trait that might be unique to
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  's Wild Card protagonists, since it's so unorthodox, but that would be disappointingly restricted, especially compared to Theurgy. Given how little precedent there is for a feature like this, Atlus could certainly find a narrative reason to open it up to the whole party. Eupha's role as the source of
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  's Summoner Archetype is deeply connected to her life as a priestess and mustari culture, but thanks to the broader Archetype lore, it's still perfectly justified that her fellow party members can use the power of a Summoner. Similarly,
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  could make Shadow summoning a technique that starts out exclusively in the Wild Card's hands during a tutorial battle to play into its own lore conventions, but then quickly have the protagonist teach the technique to their allies.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  is already so rich with summoning that a more classical Summoner mechanic only seems like a logical progression.
  <em>
   Shin Megami Tensei
  </em>
  and its spin-offs already deal heavily with mortals who team up with Shadows or Demons, so it'd hardly be out of place for
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  to equip players with their own Shadow allies and minions. Nothing is guaranteed about
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  for now, but given its monumental success, it would be wise to draw on stand-out features of
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </em>
  like the Summoner Archetype.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Quest 11: Lost Lovers Quest Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/dragon-quest-11-dq11-lost-lovers-quest-guide-echoes-of-an-elusive-age/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Where To Find Erdwin's Bracelet In Dragon Quest 11
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Rewards For Lost Lovers Side Quest In Dragon Quest 11
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dragon Quest 11: Echoes Of An Elusive Age
   </strong>
  </em>
  has many side quests that will continue to be unlocked as you complete the game. Many of these side quests offer basic rewards such as items or gold, while some offer much better permanent buffs.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The side quest Lost Lovers can be started in Havens Above and is said to boost the Luminary's sword abilities if you're able to find Erdwin's Bracelet and reunite it with Serenica's bracelet which is already on the statue. Here's where to find Erdwin's Bracelet and complete the quest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-erdwin-39-s-bracelet-in-dragon-quest-11">
  Where To Find Erdwin's Bracelet In Dragon Quest 11
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-763076527" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-763076527" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-763076527" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-763076527" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-763076527-img" id="article-gallery-1-763076527">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-763076527" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-5098547">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To find Erdwin's Bracelet, use
  <strong>
   Zoom to travel to Drustan's Labyrinth - Trial Isle
  </strong>
  and head inside to the various saplings that take you to the trials of the Luminary. Interact with the Sapling on the right altar to enter The Disciple's Trial. Once inside, head south through the linear path until you reach the first area where you're presented with three routes forward.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Using Holy Protection or a Holy Water can let you get Erdwin's Bracelet without having to fight any monsters if you're high enough in level.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Take the middle path
  </strong>
  , which will break beneath your feet and take you to the second floor of the trial. In the lower section, head into the main room full of all the slot-machine monsters and head to the hallway along the back right. Turn the corner to find a chest, with Erdwin's Bracelet being inside. From here you can use Zoom to immediately go back to Havens Above if you have already completed the trial or wish to do so later after completing the quest.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rewards-for-lost-lovers-side-quest-in-dragon-quest-11">
  Rewards For Lost Lovers Side Quest In Dragon Quest 11
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Player Talking To The Watcher" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/dragon-quest-xi_-echoes-of-an-elusive-age_20241231215557.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Erdwin's Bracelet is an Important Item and not something that can be equipped for a boost in stats. Give it to the Watcher to complete the quest and you'll get a boost in the damage for the Luminary's Sword abilities, which are:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Earthsplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Earth damage.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Skysplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Wind damage.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Seasplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Ice damage.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Flamesplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Fire damage.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Brightsplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Light damage.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Blightsplitter
   </strong>
   - Deals Dark damage.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   MP cost for all of these skills will permanently be increased
  </strong>
  along with the boost in damage, and this can't be undone once completed. That being said the boost in damage is well worth the cost of MP, especially since this bonus is applied so late in the game when MP management won't be nearly as big of an issue.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
