<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Great Games Where Your Decisions Truly Matter</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-video-game-decisions-matter/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Choices in video games can matter, with decisions altering storylines and character relationships significantly.
     </li>
     <li>
      Popular RPG games like Fable 2 and Mass Effect 2 emphasize strategic choices impacting outcomes.
     </li>
     <li>
      Content-heavy games like Detroit: Become Human and Life is Strange 2 are home to diverse narrative paths.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the factors that separates gaming from other popular forms of entertainment like film is that gaming, generally speaking, puts players in the shoes of the main character. Today, many games expand upon the idea of the player truly being in control of the protagonist by giving them a vast range of choices and decisions to make that will alter the direction of the story. This certainly isn't a new feature of gaming, as it was the key selling point of numerous 80s and 90s graphic adventures.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it's fair to say that the choices in many games today are far more expansive than ever before, and the popularity of
  <strong>
   games where the player's choices matter
  </strong>
  has led to significantly more games being available to choose from. Unfortunately, the popularity of
  <strong>
   decision-based games
  </strong>
  has meant that many developers and publishers have tried to shoehorn decision-making into their games despite the choices having little to no impact on the direction of the story. Thankfully, there are numerous games where decision-making isn't just a gimmick but a key, in-depth feature.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated February 22, 2025, by Mara Cowley:
   </em>
   Choice-based games
  </strong>
  remain a popular option among gamers, especially those who are fans of RPGs or point-and-click adventures. These games allow players to feel as though they have true player agency within the game and its world, directly interacting with it, and influencing the coutcome. While there are many games where players' decisions don't have too much sway, there are plenty of
  <strong>
   decision-based games
  </strong>
  that provide players with ways to change how the story unfolds. This article already included some of the
  <strong>
   best choice-based games
  </strong>
  out there, but there are still many more that deserve to be hailed as such.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="saw">
  <span class="item-num">
   40
  </span>
  <span>
   Saw
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="tapp-39-s-final-test-is-a-choice">
  Tapp's Final Test is a Choice
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1793226607" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1793226607" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1793226607" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1793226607" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1793226607-img" id="article-gallery-1-1793226607">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1793226607" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-872884907">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Even those who aren't fans of horror know the movie series called
  <strong>
   <em>
    Saw
   </em>
  </strong>
  , and its killer Jigsaw, who places victims in deadly traps that require sacrifice to escape from. As with any popular movie,
  <em>
   Saw
  </em>
  received a video game adaptation, and one that was pretty good at the time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players control Tapp after the events of the first movie, as the detective is saved and kidnapped, and placed in an asylum where Tapp will face a cornucopia of different and grisly trials, saving other victims on his way. At the game's end, players are given a choice that will greatly affect the ending they receive: escape the traps with the others, or pursue the killer, both with drastically different outcomes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="king-39-s-quest-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   39
  </span>
  <span>
   King's Quest 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-key-decision-can-make-the-game-unwinnable">
  One Key Decision Can Make the Game Unwinnable
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-186339027" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-186339027" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-186339027" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-186339027" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-186339027-img" id="article-gallery-2-186339027">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-186339027" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1080586219">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The game developers at Sierra are responsible for many great point-and-click adventure games, such as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Gabriel Knight
   </em>
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   <em>
    King's Quest
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The fifth entry into the latter series introduces players to protagonist Graham after his castle is engulfed by a magically conjured whirlwind before it vanishes. Only King Graham is the one left behind, as he was outside the castle when it occurred. He sets off on a quest to find the wizard responsible and return the castle and all his family.
 </p>
 <p>
  While exploring the world, players might encounter a cat hunting a mouse. Unless the player has the foresight to intervene, the game becomes unwinnable. This is an excellent example of the players' actions — or lack thereof — having the most impact on the game, as it may see the game end prematurely.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="batman-the-enemy-within">
  <span class="item-num">
   38
  </span>
  <span>
   Batman: The Enemy Within
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-player-has-a-direct-impact-on-the-joker-39-s-character">
  The Player has a Direct Impact on The Joker's Character
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2115076108" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2115076108" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2115076108" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2115076108" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2115076108-img" id="article-gallery-3-2115076108">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2115076108" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1960361646">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Telltale Games prides themselves on choice-driven games. They confront players with decisions they must make quickly, as well as providing dialogue choices to allow them to address other characters as they wish.
  <strong>
   <em>
    Batman: The Enemy Within
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one such game, letting players control the Caped Crusader as he does what Batman does best: protecting the people of Gotham.
 </p>
 <p>
  Many famous villains make their appearance in this game, but the dark stars of this show are Joker and Harley. Their relationship is inverted so that Harley is the manipulative mastermind, and Joker is the one manipulated. But the player can also have a hand in shaping the Joker's character. Depending on how they choose to treat him, the player either makes him become a vigilante, or turns him into a villain.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-age-the-veilguard">
  <span class="item-num">
   37
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="minor-choices-echo-throughout-the-game">
  Minor Choices Echo Throughout The Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-926673096" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-926673096" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-926673096" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-926673096" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-926673096-img" id="article-gallery-4-926673096">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-926673096" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-674815662">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the role of Rook, it is up to the player to stop the Gods from enacting their plans to spread the Blight over the world, which would end all life as it is known. On their quest to do so, they will travel to many different locations, meet many different people, and, of course, be met with different choices, such as decided the fate NPCs, and how they speak to them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Decisions made, such as the fate of the Mayor in D'Meta's Crossing, will have consequences that players won't know about until they are further in the game. Smaller choices, such as which dialogue options they pick, will even have influences on future dialogue with that same character. The result is a game where players truly feel that their choices are being taken into account.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chrono-trigger">
  <span class="item-num">
   36
  </span>
  <span>
   Chrono Trigger
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="choices-made-throughout-various-eras-will-influence-the-narrative">
  Choices Made Throughout Various Eras Will Influence the Narrative
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2010778535" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2010778535" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2010778535" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2010778535" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2010778535-img" id="article-gallery-5-2010778535">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2010778535" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1751776993">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Even back in the mid 90s, developers such as Square Enix allowed players to have a hand in how their game plays out by presenting choices that could have a major impact on the story. This is no more true than with one of their most beloved RPGs of all time,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Chrono Trigger
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The game's story will take players and their companions through several different eras on their quest to save the world as they know it. And with time travel stories, there are always consequences for meddling with the timeline. Choices that the player makes can change how the narrative unfolds , which is an impressive amount of freedom considering the game's age.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fable-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   35
  </span>
  <span>
   Fable 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-final-decision-determines-the-player-character-39-s-fate">
  The Final Decision Determines The Player Character's Fate
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-795332356" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-795332356" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-795332356" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-795332356" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-795332356-img" id="article-gallery-6-795332356">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-795332356" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-377384675">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fable 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  was perhaps the most heralded title in the series, and it is clear to see why. It oozed charisma, character, and took players on a whirlwind story in order to save the lands from the evil powers of Lucien, the man who killed their older sister when they were both poor orphans living on the streets.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will be presented with choices throughout
  <em>
   Fable 2
  </em>
  , and the well-implemented morality system gives their decisions weight and can alter how their character looks. There are three possible endings to Sparrow's adventure, and what choice the player makes will determine what ending they receive. It certainly isn't an easy choice to make, and most players will go through multiple playthroughs just so they can experience everything
  <em>
   Fable 2
  </em>
  has to offer.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="i-was-a-teenage-exocolonist">
  <span class="item-num">
   34
  </span>
  <span>
   I Was A Teenage Exocolonist
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-character-39-s-life-hinges-on-certain-decisions-that-can-be-made">
  The Character's Life Hinges On Certain Decisions That Can Be Made
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-592484339" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-592484339" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-592484339" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-592484339" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-592484339-img" id="article-gallery-7-592484339">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-592484339" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1463004293">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In a game that perhaps rings a bit too true to reality, the Earth has become unlivable, leading to a group of colonists taking a spaceship through a wormhole to colonize a habitable planet. The player character falls into a coma and awakens to see their new home on Vertumna 4.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    I Was A Teenage Exocolonist
   </strong>
  </em>
  players have great agency with their character; they are able to customize them, select their childhood friend, and pick traits that can have an impact on their game. As the plot spans multiple years of the protagonist's life, the player chooses what activities they partake in as time passes, and some of these activities can even spell death for their colonists. The choices in this game are not to be underestimated, as they can have some of the biggest impacts seen in choice-based games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="vampyr">
  <span class="item-num">
   33
  </span>
  <span>
   Vampyr
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-fate-of-london-and-its-inhabitants-rest-in-the-bloody-hands-of-dr-reid">
  The Fate Of London And Its Inhabitants Rest In The Bloody Hands Of Dr. Reid
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1869293336" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1869293336" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1869293336" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1869293336" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1869293336-img" id="article-gallery-8-1869293336">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1869293336" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-2059946511">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Army medic Jonathan Reid returns to his home in London after his time in the war, only to be welcomed back into the arms of death. He awakens in a mound of corpses and must learn to temper his thirst as he upholds the hippocratic oath even in death.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it is up to the players if they want to resist the hunger for blood. There are many humans that players are free to feed on to grow more powerful, but this choice will have consequences. If enough humans are drained, the district becomes dangerous, and Jonathan Reid loses just a little of himself, which is reflected in the ending. Alternatively,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Vampyr
   </em>
  </strong>
  players can ignore the beast inside and choose to remain an ally and protector of the people.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="frostpunk">
  <span class="item-num">
   32
  </span>
  <span>
   Frostpunk
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-choices-during-construction-can-impact-the-lives-of-inhabitants">
  Players Choices During Construction Can Impact The Lives Of Inhabitants
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1551433522" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1551433522" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1551433522" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1551433522" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1551433522-img" id="article-gallery-9-1551433522">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1551433522" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-525452697">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One might think that a city builder game such as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Frostpunk
   </em>
  </strong>
  couldn't qualify as a choice-based game, but they would be wrong. Along with the gameplay of creating cities, constructions, and advancing technology to protect habitations and inhabitants from the bitter cold, smart choices and resource-managing all play a big part in this game and require smart thinking on the player's side.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will also be challenged to certain moral choices throughout the game that can have serious consequences for their settlements. Making the wrong choice could cost several lives, but what makes these choices even more impactful is the fact none of them are easy. Players might even be forced to make a few suffer for the betterment of many.
 </p>
 <h2 id="road-96">
  <span class="item-num">
   31
  </span>
  <span>
   Road 96
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-decisions-alter-the-entire-story-and-the-setting">
  Players Decisions Alter The Entire Story And The Setting
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-837602351" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-837602351" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-837602351" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-837602351" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-837602351-img" id="article-gallery-10-837602351">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-837602351" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1611744714">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Road 96
   </strong>
  </em>
  takes players on a tour through the fictional nation known as Petria, an authoritarian place nearing a new election that could shake the political landscape. A group of hitchhiking teenagers are attempting to escape across the border without being caught by border patrol. Each failure results in the player taking control of one of the other teens, with the decisions made during their subsequent run referenced in this new one.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are more decisions to be made outside a player's escape attempts, such as interacting with various NPCs and engaging in mini-games to learn more about them and the world at large. One's choices in
  <em>
   Road 96
  </em>
  have the potential to shape the future of an entire nation.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-quarry">
  <span class="item-num">
   30
  </span>
  <span>
   The Quarry
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="decisions-must-be-made-quickly-and-they-have-the-potential-to-lead-to-death">
  Decisions Must Be Made Quickly, And They Have The Potential To Lead To Death
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1665018786" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1665018786" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1665018786" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1665018786" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1665018786-img" id="article-gallery-11-1665018786">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1665018786" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-215945710">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Quarry
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a strong entry in Supermassive's library of horror games, taking clear inspiration from classic horror titles such as
  <em>
   Friday the 13th
  </em>
  with its summer camp setting and roster of counselors who are more interested in throwing parties than following the rules.
 </p>
 <p>
  Before long, they learn that their extra night at camp has led to disastrous consequences, as werewolves prowl these woods and will tear apart any person they come face to face with. Players will not only be challenged with QTEs but also with decisions that must be made quickly. These decisions can lead to the deaths of characters, which makes the timer placed on the player even more stressful.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tyranny">
  <span class="item-num">
   29
  </span>
  <span>
   Tyranny
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="player-choices-can-lead-to-the-eradication-of-locations">
  Player Choices Can Lead To The Eradication Of Locations
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-720065553" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-720065553" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-720065553" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-720065553" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-720065553-img" id="article-gallery-12-720065553">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-720065553" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-822743677">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Set in a fantasy world with its own unique technology,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Tyranny
   </em>
  </strong>
  puts the player in the shoes of the Fatebinder, tasked with the onerous mission to quell the rebellion rising due to the infighting of two major factions or die along with everyone else.
 </p>
 <p>
  With stakes this high, it makes sense there are many sensitive choices the player must make that can have drastic consequences. Depending on what choices players follow, some game locations may not even exist, dramatically altering the narrative path.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="disco-elysium">
  <span class="item-num">
   28
  </span>
  <span>
   Disco Elysium
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-player-39-s-build-can-alter-what-information-they-are-privy-to">
  The Player's Build Can Alter What Information They Are Privy To
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-379925746" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-379925746" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-379925746" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-379925746" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-379925746-img" id="article-gallery-13-379925746">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-379925746" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1648590534">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Disco Elysium
   </em>
  </strong>
  is an ambitious RPG that impressed gamers with its unique dialogue system and well-crafted characters. The game features very little combat, focusing more on plot, dialogue, and player agency.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like most RPGs, players are able to put points into skills to create a unique build for their character, and even this choice is one to be made with care. Depending one's builds and background, the player may be privy to unique tidbits of information and lore they wouldn't know otherwise, which they can then use to their advantage during some conversations with certain NPCs.
 </p>
 <h2 id="oxenfree">
  <span class="item-num">
   27
  </span>
  <span>
   Oxenfree
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dialogue-choices-play-a-big-role-in-the-player-39-s-relationship-with-characters">
  Dialogue Choices Play A Big Role In The Player's Relationship With Characters
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-900267724" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-900267724" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-900267724" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-900267724" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-900267724-img" id="article-gallery-14-900267724">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-900267724" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-102200925">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This charming graphic 2.5D adventure game sees players controlling Alex, a teenager who unwittingly frees a dangerous paranormal power that they must now find and put a stop to.
 </p>
 <p>
  As they are trying to save the island, players can stop and chat with the various other characters in a unique way, as they are still free to move around during conversations.
  <strong>
   <em>
    Oxenfree
   </em>
  </strong>
  players will be offered multiple dialogue choices, with each one having the possibility to affect the relationship with the character in a positive or negative way. If the player cares for particular characters, they need to be mindful of how they talk to them.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="divinity-original-sin-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   26
  </span>
  <span>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="side-quests-can-be-failed-causing-npcs-to-never-return-or-die">
  Side Quests Can Be Failed, Causing NPCs To Never Return Or Die
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-513969670" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-513969670" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-513969670" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-513969670" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-513969670-img" id="article-gallery-15-513969670">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-513969670" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-144251328">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3,
  </em>
  there was
  <strong>
   <em>
    Divinity: Original Sin 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Larian's unique RPG set in original lore with pages of lore for players to sink their teeth into. Players could choose to play as one of the Origin characters or create their own Sourcerer to set upon the world and stop the Voidwoken.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from the main quest, there are various side quests players can embark on, with choices that can result in the quest failing, causing the associated character to leave or even die. Players are given agency to approach missions how they wish, which they might encounter the consequences of later down the line.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-outer-worlds">
  <span class="item-num">
   25
  </span>
  <span>
   The Outer Worlds
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-player-39-s-morality-reflected-through-dialogue-options-directly-influence-the-game-39-s-ending">
  The Player's Morality Reflected Through Dialogue Options Directly Influence The Game's Ending
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-7169060" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-7169060" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-7169060" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-7169060" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-7169060-img" id="article-gallery-16-7169060">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-7169060" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1923153533">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following on from the major success of
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  , gamers were clamoring for another RPG game in the same vein as Obsidian, and they delivered with
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Outer Worlds
   </strong>
  </em>
  . This game changed the course of history by having Roosevelt never succeed McKinley, and megacorporations soon took over the earth, which had moved their ambitions to space, colonizing planets. They successfully do so, transforming many planets in the Halcyon system into new homes for citizens of Earth.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are many choices players will be confronted with while space-faring in
  <em>
   The Outer Worlds
  </em>
  , both big and small, with some influencing the attitudes of other characters towards the player. These choices should not be made lightly, as players may come to regret it later.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="as-dusk-falls">
  <span class="item-num">
   24
  </span>
  <span>
   As Dusk Falls
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-player-39-s-actions-at-pivotal-moments-can-change-the-trajectory-of-the-plot">
  The Player's Actions At Pivotal Moments Can Change The Trajectory Of The Plot
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1425163869" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1425163869" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1425163869" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1425163869" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1425163869-img" id="article-gallery-17-1425163869">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1425163869" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-2124328009">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This narrative-driven adventure drama game spins the tale of two families who find themselves crossing paths with one another in the Arizona desert after a robbery goes horribly wrong. In a similar vein to games more like
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  and less like
  <em>
   Dragon Age
  </em>
  , it requires plenty of choice-oriented input from the players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Split across two 'books,'
  <em>
   <strong>
    As Dusk Falls
   </strong>
  </em>
  plays like an interactive movie, with the players interjecting their choices into pivotal moments in the game and directly influencing the trajectory of the plot. It even has a co-op mode for players to have a friend join them, much like the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dark Pictures
   </strong>
  </em>
  anthology series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="assassin-39-s-creed-odyssey">
  <span class="item-num">
   23
  </span>
  <span>
   Assassin's Creed Odyssey
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="how-players-choose-to-navigate-certain-missions-impacts-the-ending">
  How Players Choose To Navigate Certain Missions Impacts The Ending
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-2011408339" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-2011408339" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-2011408339" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-2011408339" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-2011408339-img" id="article-gallery-18-2011408339">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-2011408339" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-284225704">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Assassin's Creed
   </strong>
  </em>
  franchise has taken players far and wide, from Renaissance Italy to Victorian London.
  <strong>
   <em>
    Odyssey
   </em>
  </strong>
  takes them back to the times of Ancient Greece, in which they take control of either Alexios or Kassandra as they fight as a Spartan in a war between Athens and Sparta. In comparison to earlier titles,
  <em>
   Odyssey
  </em>
  takes on more RPG elements, focusing less on stealth and more on combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  It also features multiple endings, with the outcome depending directly on the player's choice. With a total of nine endings that players can get, they must make sure to make wise choices on certain missions if they want the best outcome.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="catherine-full-body">
  <span class="item-num">
   22
  </span>
  <span>
   Catherine: Full Body
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-game-poses-a-moral-question-each-night-with-every-answer-influencing-the-ending">
  The Game Poses A Moral Question Each Night, With Every Answer Influencing The Ending
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1142377877" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1142377877" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1142377877" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1142377877" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1142377877-img" id="article-gallery-19-1142377877">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1142377877" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-860068984">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Catherine: Full Body
   </strong>
  </em>
  falls into the same category as
  <em>
   <strong>
    P4 Golden
   </strong>
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   <strong>
    P5 Royal
   </strong>
  </em>
  : It's not quite a remaster; it's more of a rework with added content. The new content found in
  <em>
   Catherine
  </em>
  mostly centers around newcomer Rin, who becomes the new neighbor of Vincent and one of the new possible romance routes that players can pursue. Suffering a bout of amnesia other than a certain piano melody Rin often plays, it is up to the players to help Rin uncover those buried memories.
 </p>
 <p>
  Choices play a major part in this game, with the players given a question after every nightmare stage they pass. They will be confronted by a moral dilemma and given two answers to choose from. While some questions are obvious as to which will put them on the good or bad path, these become less obvious as the game progresses, and depending on how that morality meter looks like at the end of the game, Vincent's fate can be affected.
 </p>
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   21
  </span>
  <span>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="every-decision-proposed-to-players-during-missions-will-ripple-throughout-the-entire-campaign">
  Every Decision Proposed To Players During Missions Will Ripple Throughout The Entire Campaign
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-421039467" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-421039467" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-421039467" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-421039467" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-421039467-img" id="article-gallery-20-421039467">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-421039467" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-1714998060">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Larian's epic
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dungeons and Dragons
   </strong>
  </em>
  -themed RPG has captured the hearts of millions of gamers, bringing them and their characters into the world of Faerun as they travel far and wide in search of one with the skills to cure them of their recently acquired passenger. The quest to rid themselves of the Illithid passengers will bring them to multiple locations and multiple people, giving them the freedom to choose who they trust and ally themselves with.
 </p>
 <p>
  These choices aren't ones to be made on a whim, as their ripples will be felt throughout the campaign. Siding with the wrong (or right) person can close players off from certain missions and companions.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Action RPGs for Players Who Love Customization</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-action-rpgs-for-players-who-love-customization/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      RPGs like Black Desert Online offer extensive character customization for unique playstyles.
     </li>
     <li>
      Path of Exile 2 showcases advanced build customization for unique character experiences.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like Skyrim provide revolutionary build mechanics for engaging RPG experiences.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Whether as a warrior, archer, mage, or cleric, playing video games is often closely with experiencing different lives in a completely new world. Since the early days, the ability for players to customize their own character has been a feature that stands out as something particularly unique to the medium of gaming.
 </p>
 <p>
  This characteristic is especially important for RPGs, or Role-Playing Games, whose very name describes the experience as the act of embodying another life or role. In this context, some titles stand out for their extensive customization options, ranging from altering the character's appearance to changing gameplay by selecting new abilities to face challenges in a completely new way.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="black-desert-online">
  Black Desert Online
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-can-create-unique-characters-with-freedom">
  Players Can Create Unique Characters With Freedom
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1699998000" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1699998000" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1699998000" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1699998000" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1699998000-img" id="article-gallery-1-1699998000">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1699998000" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-536179103">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Black Desert Online
  </em>
  is an action RPG and open-world MMO that drew a lot of attention upon its announcement, specifically for its impressive character customization. The variety of facial features that can be adjusted and the vast number of unique characters players can create drew thousands to try the Korean game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, as a great MMORPG, the game offers various builds and classes that can be tailored to different gameplay styles, changing how it’s played, allowing players to experiment with different options as they venture through it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="path-of-exile-2">
  Path Of Exile 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-best-games-for-build-customization">
  One Of Best Games For Build Customization
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1733927306" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1733927306" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1733927306" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1733927306" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1733927306-img" id="article-gallery-2-1733927306">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1733927306" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1473038514">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At its launch,
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  went viral through videos of players reacting for the first time to the game's build creation system. Even the most experienced players were taken by surprise, as the new title from Grinding Gear Games offers advanced customization, allowing each character to be truly unique with an incredible variety of skills and playstyles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Inspired by classics like
  <em>
   Diablo
  </em>
  , this action RPG lacks an appearance customization mechanic but, at the same time, stands out as one of the games with the most extensive build variety in the genre. It’s a must-play for players who want the freedom to create different characters, customizing abilities or even the weapons obtained through enemy loot.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-age-inquisition">
  Dragon Age: Inquisition
 </h2>
 <h3 id="it-39-s-possible-to-customize-different-builds-in-this-action-rpg">
  It's Possible To Customize Different Builds In This Action RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1867232141" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1867232141" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1867232141" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1867232141" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1867232141-img" id="article-gallery-3-1867232141">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1867232141" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1687575613">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Aiming to balance between the mechanics of the first two games in the franchise,
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Inquisition
  </em>
  introduced a distinct combat system, blending some of the tactical depth from
  <em>
   Origins
  </em>
  while maintaining the action-oriented approach of
  <em>
   Dragon Age 2
  </em>
  . To make this experience even more distinct, the game provided players with a wide variety of classes and abilities to use throughout their journey.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, another standout aspect of
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Inquisition
  </em>
  at launch was the advancements in appearance customization brought by the Frostbite 3 engine, which, at the time, impressed by allowing players to modify intricate facial details for each character. This made it possible to create truly unique Inquisitors as they ventured through Thedas.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-4">
  Fallout 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-can-build-aggressive-or-diplomatic-characters">
  Players Can Build Aggressive Or Diplomatic Characters
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2142036968" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2142036968" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2142036968" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2142036968" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2142036968-img" id="article-gallery-4-2142036968">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2142036968" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-149517883">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  is one of the standout titles in one of the most famous RPG franchises of all time. The game is set in a post-apocalyptic future where players must survive in a world ravaged by nuclear war, filled with chaos and hostility. Like other great RPGs, it offers a deeply immersive experience, allowing players to create their own character and customize it how they want to.
 </p>
 <p>
  So, their main character can focus on a more aggressive gameplay style, solving problems through violence, or take on a more diplomatic approach, relying on wit and charisma to achieve their goals. Additionally, the game also offers a great customization options, allowing players to craft their own weapons or even experiment with different builds through its unique perk system.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="diablo-4">
  Diablo 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="each-class-offers-a-different-and-customizable-playstyle-in-this-action-rpg">
  Each Class Offers A Different and Customizable Playstyle In This Action RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2018734681" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2018734681" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2018734681" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2018734681" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2018734681-img" id="article-gallery-5-2018734681">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2018734681" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-124003108">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the major appeals of the
  <em>
   Diablo
  </em>
  franchise is the variety of playstyles and characters players can create, and
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  is no exception. Blizzard's character creator allows players to design necromancers, druids, barbarians, mages, warriors, and more.
 </p>
 <p>
  Set in a world overrun by demonic forces, players can face their enemies in various ways, switching between different classes and playstyles, each with unique weapons and visuals. In fact, each available character feels truly distinct, thanks to the variety of abilities they possess, allowing for builds that shape each experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  Elden Ring
 </h2>
 <h3 id="endless-builds-for-ultimate-versatility">
  Endless Builds For Ultimate Versatility
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-234790844" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-234790844" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-234790844" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-234790844" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-234790844-img" id="article-gallery-6-234790844">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-234790844" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1065092774">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  is renowned for its exceptional gameplay, challenging difficulty, and a world created in collaboration between Hidetaka Miyazaki and writer George R.R. Martin. However, one of the key features in any
  <em>
   FromSoftware
  </em>
  game, also strongly present here, is character customization.
 </p>
 <p>
  The character creator, while still not one of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  's strongest aspects, allows for better-looking faces compared to the developer's previous
  <em>
   soulslike
  </em>
  titles. However, the real highlight of the game lies in its versatility in gameplay customization. Weapons, skills, armor, and magic provide countless combinations of powers, allowing players to overcome enemies in a variety of ways.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-world">
  Monster Hunter World
 </h2>
 <h3 id="weapons-define-entire-gameplay-experience">
  Weapons Define Entire Gameplay Experience
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1998897946" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1998897946" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1998897946" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1998897946" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1998897946-img" id="article-gallery-7-1998897946">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1998897946" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-2055966287">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Monster Hunter: World
  </em>
  is a especially unique game, because character customization mainly focuses on the weapon the player chooses to wield. Switching weapons in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  is almost equivalent to playing a game with entirely different mechanics, each offering unique strategies and approaches for dealing with various creatures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, at more advanced levels, players gain access to a wide range of options through buffs that can be incorporated into their builds, allowing for high-level customization tailored to enhance their hunting experience. Mastering these combinations is essential, as some endgame challenges can be quite punishing for players who are not adequately prepared.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077">
  Cyberpunk 2077
 </h2>
 <h3 id="modify-characters-physically-and-mechanically">
  Modify Characters Physically And Mechanically
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1804705960" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1804705960" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1804705960" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1804705960" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1804705960-img" id="article-gallery-8-1804705960">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1804705960" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1814377193">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since its release,
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  has been a significant promise for fans of tabletop role-playing games. Inspired by Mike Pondsmith's classic in the dystopian sci-fi genre, the game preserves some of its key features, emphasizing extensive character customization in both aesthetics and mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Set in a world teeming with implants and body modifications, this
  <em>
   Action RPG
  </em>
  provides extensive character customization. Players can modify appearance, build, and even the cybernetic implants of each version of V, allowing the gameplay experience to change entirely based on individual playstyle preferences.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-rsquo-s-dogma-2">
  Dragon’s Dogma 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="customization-that-exceeds-expectations">
  Customization That Exceeds Expectations
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-549758517" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-549758517" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-549758517" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-549758517" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-549758517-img" id="article-gallery-9-549758517">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-549758517" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1418838587">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon’s Dogma 2
  </em>
  follows in the footsteps of its predecessor by offering players a unique
  <em>
   Action RPG
  </em>
  experience with a level of freedom uncommon in other games of the genre. The game features an impressive
  <em>
   Character Creator
  </em>
  that allows players to design unique faces for their protagonist or even recreate the appearance of popular characters from other games.
 </p>
 <p>
  However,
  <em>
   Dragon’s Dogma 2
  </em>
  stands out not only for its detailed character appearance customization but also for the hundreds of build possibilities through skill and vocations combinations, as each option provides a distinct gameplay experience. This allows players to experiment with different choices to tackle bosses and other enemies throughout the game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="skyrim">
  Skyrim
 </h2>
 <h3 id="revolutionary-builds-mechanics-keep-players-engaged-in-this-action-rpg">
  Revolutionary Builds Mechanics Keep Players Engaged In this Action RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-2015425480" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-2015425480" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-2015425480" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-2015425480" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-2015425480-img" id="article-gallery-10-2015425480">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-2015425480" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1701247302">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  is widely regarded as one of the greatest RPGs ever made, largely due to the immense freedom it offers - something that was impressive at launch and remains so to this day. Another key reason behind this acclaim is the level of customization players have when creating or developing a character throughout their adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Bethesda’s developers brought years of RPG experience to craft a game where each player can create a truly unique character. Skills are unlocked through use, allowing for versatile builds that combine traits from various classes, enabling players to shape their journey in their own way.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Open-World Games With No Or Limited Map Markers</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-open-world-games-no-map-markers/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      <em>
       Elden Ring
      </em>
      emphasizes natural exploration sans map markers, setting a benchmark for seamless open-world exploration.
     </li>
     <li>
      <em>
       Sunless Skies
      </em>
      offers organic exploration and storytelling in a vast, improved sandbox setting.
     </li>
     <li>
      <em>
       Kenshi
      </em>
      drops players in a dangerous wasteland with no objectives, requiring self-discovery and survival skills.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Some of the
  <strong>
   best open-world games
  </strong>
  players can get their hands on understand how frustrating it is to get lost while exploring a massive sandbox. However, map markers and waypoints are a clumsy solution that can take away from the magic of exploration that these games try to sell.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is why open-world games need to figure out the best way to make exploration feel both organic and seamless. The best titles in this genre have nailed this balance finding ways to include
  <strong>
   no—or at least limited—map markers,
  </strong>
  and they are worth checking out for fans of quality open-world games.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Elden Ring
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fromsoftware-39-s-world-design-makes-exploration-more-organic">
  FromSoftware's World Design Makes Exploration More Organic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-875159867" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-875159867" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-875159867" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-875159867" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-875159867-img" id="article-gallery-1-875159867">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-875159867" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-531186370">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The beauty of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring
   </em>
  </strong>
  stems from how natural its exploration feels. This game took a page out of
  <em>
   Breath of the Wild's
  </em>
  playbook, blending its open-world design with FromSoftware's action RPG expertise to make for a tantalizing combination.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's made clear where players need to go without using map markers, which is a major achievement. The fact that an update that added a few minor map markers for NPC locations elicited such a polarizing response from players shows just how seamless exploration is in
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="sunless-skies">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Sunless Skies
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-immersive-game-with-a-focus-on-exploration-and-storytelling">
  An Immersive Game With A Focus On Exploration And Storytelling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-6623623" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-6623623" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-6623623" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-6623623" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-6623623-img" id="article-gallery-2-6623623">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-6623623" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1565398567">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sunless Skies
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a massive improvement over its predecessor, shifting the setting from the seas to the skies and turning combat into a tense real-time affair. The slow exploration of the first game was addressed, with players enjoying a decent speed from the get-go while traveling from one area to another.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes
  <em>
   Sunless Skies
  </em>
  such a brilliant title stems from its organic exploration and excellent storytelling. Players will head to a place to make the most of some profitable trade deals, only to be immersed in the story of a settlement as the mysterious horrors of this title rear their ugly heads.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kenshi">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Kenshi
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="drops-players-into-the-world-with-no-objectives">
  Drops Players Into The World With No Objectives
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-905415849" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-905415849" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-905415849" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-905415849" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-905415849-img" id="article-gallery-3-905415849">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-905415849" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-212048015">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike most other open-world games,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kenshi
   </em>
  </strong>
  has no objectives to speak of. All players need to do is pick a background, following which they're unceremoniously dumped into a wasteland full of dangers that can tear them apart in no time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players must figure out how to amass a fortune, improve their skills, gather a party of explorers, and uncover all the content this game has to offer. As one would suspect, there are no map markers to speak of, and players must rely on their gut to make a decision that they'll explore after leaving the safety of a settlement.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-matchless-kungfu">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   The Matchless Kungfu
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-make-progress-on-their-own-and-decide-how-the-open-world-expands">
  Players Make Progress On Their Own And Decide How The Open World Expands
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-162951610" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-162951610" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-162951610" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-162951610" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-162951610-img" id="article-gallery-4-162951610">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-162951610" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-282529525">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platform:
   </strong>
   PC
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Release Date:
   </strong>
   November 6, 2024
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer:
   </strong>
   HuanMos Game
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A unique indie game with a ton of potential,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Matchless Kungfu
   </em>
  </strong>
  is essentially a wuxia version of
  <em>
   Kenshi
  </em>
  with turn-based melee combat and an excellent progression system. From the moment players start their playthrough, the informational overload will make their heads spin.
 </p>
 <p>
  Eventually, they'll grasp the basics and make enough progress to set more blocks that help increase the size of the open world. This makes for a unique gameplay loop where anything and everything can happen. As one would expect, players can't rely on map markers to guide them on any step of their journey.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="outer-wilds">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Outer Wilds
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="exploring-the-galaxy-is-driven-by-player-curiosity">
  Exploring The Galaxy Is Driven By Player Curiosity
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-353370422" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-353370422" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-353370422" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-353370422" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-353370422-img" id="article-gallery-5-353370422">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-353370422" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-2007937380">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The freeform design and unique knowledge-based exploration of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Outer Wilds
   </em>
  </strong>
  make it one of the best indie open-world games players can get their hands on. Players need to pay attention to the information they acquire on every step of their journey, since these tidbits contain valuable hints that help players make meaningful progress, and there are no other indicators to guide them to the next step.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's a simple and tantalizing way to guide players in the right direction without overloading the game world with map markers.
  <em>
   Outer Wilds
  </em>
  can take a while to grow on players, but those who get invested in its mystery will find it hard to tear themselves away when there are so many leads to pursue.
 </p>
 <h2 id="gothic">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Gothic
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-nameless-stranger-starts-from-nothing-and-must-struggle-to-make-a-name-for-themself">
  The Nameless Stranger Starts From Nothing And Must Struggle To Make A Name For Themself
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-660217527" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-660217527" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-660217527" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-660217527" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-660217527-img" id="article-gallery-6-660217527">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-660217527" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2051808550">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Piranha Bytes is one of the most unique open-world RPG developers around, integrating tough combat systems and open-ended gameplay in their titles as players are unceremoniously dropped into unfamiliar worlds.
  <strong>
   <em>
    Gothic
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a great example of the same.
 </p>
 <p>
  The landscape is fraught with horrors that can take out the Nameless Hero in a single hit. Players must figure out on their own that their experience can be cashed in to learn new combat moves, giving them the means to survive in a brutal, glorified prison where anything and everything is out to kill them.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-elder-scrolls-3-morrowind">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   The Elder Scrolls 3: Morrowind
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-old-school-open-world-rpg-where-players-must-follow-directions-and-read-the-map">
  An Old-School Open-World RPG Where Players Must Follow Directions And Read The Map
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-117014183" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-117014183" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-117014183" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-117014183" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-117014183-img" id="article-gallery-7-117014183">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-117014183" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-323046386">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  An old-school open-world RPG that fans will love, there's something about
  <em>
   <strong>
    Morrowind
   </strong>
  </em>
  that makes it deeply tantalizing even after all the time that's passed since it launched. Modern gaming trends have made later
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  games easier to get into, but
  <em>
   Morrowind
  </em>
  's retro gameplay has its undeniable charms that most people will find hard to resist.
 </p>
 <p>
  Instead of staring at markers on a map, players must listen to directions and follow them while looking at a simple, unmarked map from time to time. This organic method of exploration makes every discovery rewarding as players make headway in their journey at their own pace, seeking to fulfill the prophecy and become the Nerevarine.
 </p>
 <h2 id="caves-of-qud">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Caves Of Qud
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-roguelike-open-world-game-with-numerous-opportunities-to-explore">
  A Roguelike Open-World Game With Numerous Opportunities To Explore
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1947174851" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1947174851" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1947174851" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1947174851" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1947174851-img" id="article-gallery-8-1947174851">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1947174851" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-2002264377">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players who want to check out a roguelike that emulates old-school gameplay and lets players explore a massive procedurally generated open world will love what
  <em>
   <strong>
    Caves of Qud
   </strong>
  </em>
  brings to the table. The title is punishing for beginners, who will likely die over and over again before figuring out what they must do to make meaningful progress in each run.
 </p>
 <p>
  After these basics are cleared up, players will be introduced to the faction system and the various avenues of interest that they can check out. All of this combines to make
  <em>
   Caves of Qud
  </em>
  a rewarding open-world game where the simple visuals don't do justice to its incredibly complicated combat mechanics. As one would expect, players won't be drip-fed map markers in this title. Instead, how and where they want to explore is completely up to them.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Microsoft May Be Preparing for Digital-Only Generation</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/rumor-microsoft-digital-only-next-generation-console-xbox/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xbox may end Series X sales in Brazil, hinting at a shift to digital focus globally.
     </li>
     <li>
      Microsoft is emphasizing Xbox's digital ecosystem over dominating hardware sales.
     </li>
     <li>
      Rumors suggest Xbox is moving towards an all-digital gaming future like Sega.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Rumors have surfaced that point to
  <strong>
   Xbox
  </strong>
  ceasing Series X sales in Brazil, compounding an existing scarcity for the system in some regions. Gamers have expressed concern that this is an indicator of a grim future for the Xbox brand altogether, but it's unclear whether these changes will remain specific to their region, or if they're a sign of the strategies Xbox will be implementing globally.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's apparent that Xbox is focused on evolving, as execs like Phil Spencer have expressed recently. Seemingly no longer intent on dominating the hardware market altogether, there's been plenty of energy directed at driving attention toward Xbox's digital ecosystem using systems like the Series S in combination with their hugely popular Game Pass service. Rumors point to more movement in this direction for Xbox.
 </p>
 <p>
  According to rumors from IconEra, Xbox is reducing its sales of the Series X console in Brazil, ultimately readying to cease shipments of the system in the region altogether. Others have corroborated the information, stating that Xbox is no longer restocking the series X in Brazil. Microsoft has reportedly pointed to Xbox Cloud Gaming and Game Pass as valid alternatives for players, insisting that these platforms will largely be the future of their services in this region.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-series-x-may-stop-sales-in-brazil">
  The Series X May Stop Sales in Brazil
 </h2>
 <p>
  These rumors also seem to echo behavior from Xbox in Saudi Arabia and several European countries, with some feeling surprised at how hard it's become to find an Xbox Series X in their respective location. Although plenty of Xbox fans enjoy their Series S systems and a focus on digital gaming, many other fans are concerned that this could be another signal of Xbox bowing out of the Console race altogether. Although Phil Spencer and Xbox representatives have insisted on first-party support on the gaming end, dedicated Xbox players fear that the brand is shifting its tune about hardware.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1708603749" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1708603749" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1708603749" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1708603749" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1708603749-img" id="article-gallery-1-1708603749">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1708603749" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2049891862">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Much of this information appears to indicate that Microsoft is attempting a clean break from physical gaming to push ahead into an all-digital future. Some have cited the "This is an Xbox" ad campaign as further evidence that this is the case, feeling as if the brand hasn't inspired much confidence in its existing hardware lately. For some, this seems like a natural step, believing that Xbox is mirroring how Sega behaved before its exit from the console market. Whether this instance is an isolated event or an indicator of the future of Xbox is yet to be seen.
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur's Gate 3: 12 Mods That Add New Armors</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-bg3-best-armor-mods/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Patch 7 in Baldur's Gate 3 introduced Toolkit Data for mod creation, expanding player customization options.
     </li>
     <li>
      Armor mods like Avernus Warhound and Hexblade Armor enhance character customization and gameplay variety.
     </li>
     <li>
      Mods like The Treasure Trove and GraphicFade Equipment provide themed equipment for specific classes, enriching gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Thanks to the arrival of patch 7 in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  , players have gained access to the Toolkit Data, which enhances the freedom to create mods in the game. Through this tool, users have more liberty to modify the game, allowing them to create new options that further complement the gameplay of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  In this way, new classes or even races are being added to the game, giving players more options to customize their characters throughout their journey. However, another very exciting addition in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  is the armor mods, which add new possibilities for character attire, whether focused solely on appearance or for those seeking even more powerful options.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated February 21, 2025, by Eduardo Ariedo:
   </strong>
   After some time since Baldur's Gate 3 received official mod support, the community has been able to create various equipment and other amazing customizations for the game. One of the main highlights is the armor mods for BG3, which add new gear for characters to use and become even stronger. These items are perfect for players who also want to keep their gameplay experience fresh.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="avernus-warhound">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Avernus Warhound
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-armor-mod-with-dieselpunk-design">
  An Armor Mod With Dieselpunk Design
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Warhound Harness, a durable 16 AC heavy armor, showcases infernal design in this Baldur's Gate 3 armor mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/warhound-harness-a-durable-16-ac-heavy-armor-showcases-infernal-design-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   58posrattrooper
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Despite being a setting highly inspired by medieval fantasy, the universe of Faerûn, where the entire
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  saga takes place, has areas where the ambiance shifts slightly. One such area is Avernus, which players have the opportunity to explore briefly during the third act.
 </p>
 <p>
  Drawing from these inspirations, this armor mod in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  adds a new armor to the game inspired by the Dieselpunk aesthetic. Despite deviating somewhat from the game's more traditional designs, it remains a beautiful piece of equipment. Additionally, the author created different versions of the entire set, allowing it to be purchased and used by players throughout all three acts of the game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lotr-fellowship-weapons">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   LoTR Fellowship Weapons
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-collection-of-tolkien-inspired-equipment">
  A Collection Of Tolkien-Inspired Equipment
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Boromir's Shield, offering +3 AC and missile deflection, is a standout item in this Baldur's Gate 3 armor mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/boromir-s-shield-offering-3-ac-and-missile-deflection-is-a-standout-item-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   rosprey
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  is one of the universes that established many pillars of medieval fantasy and served as inspiration for numerous subsequent works, including
  <em>
   Dungeons &amp; Dragons
  </em>
  , which shares many similar concepts. This armor mod in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , released on the Mod Manager, brings a bit of that magic to Larian's game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although the mod is more focused on the weapons used by the characters of the Fellowship of the Ring, players can still access Boromir's shield, which is an excellent option for tank characters. Besides the defense bonuses, the item also helps players defend against damage caused by projectiles and some other ranged attacks in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-mantle-of-the-true-war-priest">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   The Mantle Of The True War Priest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-powerful-armor-mod-for-war-domain-clerics-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  A Powerful Armor Mod For War Domain Clerics In Baldur's Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Deathstalker Mantle, a rare cloak restoring attack charges, enhances gameplay in this Baldur's Gate 3 armor mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-deathstalker-mantle-a-rare-cloak-restoring-attack-charges-enhances-gameplay-in-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   deimozzzsecondone
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Whether for Shadowheart, who has been respecced with Withers, or for a character designed to be a War Domain cleric, this armor mod in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  adds one of the best cloak options for those who chose this domain in the game. Besides being a stylish garment, the item also has a passive ability that brings significant offensive power to characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  When equipped with this cloak and defeating an enemy, the extra attack from the War Priest passive, which allows clerics to make an extra attack per turn using a bonus action, is recharged, enabling another strike. However, players interested in wearing this mantle need to stay alert, as it is available for purchase only in Act 1 or Act 3, so it's necessary to be attentive not to miss the opportunity.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hexblade-armor">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Hexblade Armor
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-excellent-armor-mod-for-spellswords-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  An Excellent Armor Mod For Spellswords In Baldur's Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Adamantine Scale Mail offers radiant resistance and 17 AC, perfectly designed for this Baldur's Gate 3 armor mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/adamantine-scale-mail-offers-radiant-resistance-and-17-ac-perfectly-designed-for-this-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   nezenth
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While the game allows characters capable of wielding a sword and casting spells, their defense options are not usually varied. However, this armor mod for
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  aims to correct that, especially for players who also use another modification that adds Hexblade to the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Thus, players can have medium armor tailored to the various requirements of the class. Although it doesn't introduce anything entirely new, using the Adamantine Scale Mail already present in the game as a base, the equipment has undergone several changes to facilitate the lives of warlocks focused on melee combat, making it an excellent option for the endgame of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="additional-class-styled-armors">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Additional Class-Styled Armors
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="specific-armor-mods-for-all-classes">
  Specific Armor Mods For All Classes
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Plate of Devotion, with 18 AC and devotion boosts, exemplifies rare heavy armor in this armor mod for Baldur's Gate 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/the-plate-of-devotion-with-18-ac-and-devotion-boosts-exemplifies-rare-heavy-armor-in-this-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   literallytape
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This armor mod, currently in development, offers
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  players an opportunity to further personalize their characters. Focusing on the Monk, Paladin, Rogue, and Barbarian classes, it adds exclusive equipment that allows players to feel more unique, reflecting the combat style and personality of each class.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although the mod is a work in progress and the statistics are not final, it's already possible to equip the armors and explore patch 7 of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  with more variety. The items are being adjusted to ensure that each class benefits optimally from each piece of equipment, making them even more useful in combat.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-treasure-trove">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   The Treasure Trove
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="armor-mod-adding-equipment-for-various-classes-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  Armor Mod Adding Equipment For Various Classes In Baldur's Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Angelic Justice Armor, providing 20 AC and Moonlight Blessing, shines in this unique armor mod for Baldur's Gate 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/angelic-justice-armor-providing-20-ac-and-moonlight-blessing-shines-in-this-unique-armor-mod-for-baldur-s-gate-3.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   horizon-vp
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Treasure Trove mod brings a collection of armors for various classes in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , offering abilities and spells without the need for spell slots for the characters. While this can make certain characters extremely powerful, weapon damages remain balanced, and the armor does not offer significant boosts to the Armor Class of those who use them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even so, these armors allow players to explore build combinations that can maximize their characters' potential, especially in patch 7 of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  . For those still undecided about their character's class, it's possible to download this modification and have custom-tailored equipment ready.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Gauntlets of Storm Giant Strength
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="devastating-power-in-the-hands-of-melee-characters">
  Devastating Power In The Hands Of Melee Characters
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Gauntlets of Storm Giant Strength boost lightning damage and strength in this powerful Baldur's Gate 3 armor mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/gauntlets-of-storm-giant-strength-boost-lightning-damage-and-strength-in-this-powerful-baldur-s-gate-3-armor-mod.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   rosprey
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Gauntlets of Storm Giant Strength are perfect for players who wish to combine brute strength and elemental powers in their
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  builds. Equipped with these, melee attacks receive bonus electrical damage, turning any enemy into a victim of nature's force. Additionally, they offer complete immunity to lightning damage, ideal for facing enemies with electrical attacks.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most impressively, these gauntlets increase the user's Strength to 29, ensuring a devastating impact in combats and most physical attacks. Perfect for classes that depend on strength, the Gauntlets of Storm Giant Strength provide a significant advantage in any melee combat, maintaining balance without detracting from the fun and challenge.
 </p>
 <h2 id="armor-of-effri">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Armor_of_Effri
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="adds-a-new-armor-for-lae-39-zel-to-wear-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  Adds A New Armor For Lae'zel To Wear In Baldur's Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Lae'zel with a new starting armor in Baldur's Gate 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2024/09/lae-zel-with-a-new-starting-armor-in-baldur-s-gate-3.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   modiouser2075409
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  As an option to tweak the beginning of the game, the Half Plate Armour +1 is the armor with which Lae'zel starts in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , serving as an excellent choice for players in new saves. The armor's robust and attractive design makes it an essential piece at the start of the journey, although it can be challenging to acquire in later stages without using cheats.
 </p>
 <p>
  In terms of stats, it has an Armor Class of 16, is capable of reducing all received damage by 2, and prevents critical hits against the user. Additionally, it offers resistance to piercing damage and sets the character's Constitution to 15, providing consistent protection in the early challenges of the campaign.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="selune-armory">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Selune Armory
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-thematic-selune-armor-mod-for-baldur-rsquo-s-gate-3">
  A Thematic Selune Armor Mod For Baldur’s Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Shadowheart in silver and gold Selune-themed armor poses near a cart in Baldur’s Gate 3 Selune Armory mod" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-in-silver-and-gold-selune-themed-armor-poses-near-a-cart-in-baldur-s-gate-3-selune-armory-mod.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   WaterWitch83
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Even though they are items that can be used by all companions in the game, these pieces from this
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  mod form a fine combination for equipping Shadowheart. Not because they connect to the character’s lore and can be found in places referencing the goddess Selune, but because some of them match the character well.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, these equipments are not exclusively made for her, and there are varied choices for other characters that align with different builds. Besides adding several interesting items to the game, this mod also places them around the map, so players can find them while exploring different regions of
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="eilistraee-39-s-armory">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Eilistraee's Armory
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-mod-that-adds-a-thematic-armor-in-baldur-rsquo-s-gate-3">
  A Mod That Adds A Thematic Armor In Baldur’s Gate 3
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Wyll in blue robes and a winged drow stand in Baldur’s Gate 3 wearing Eilistraee’s Armory mod gear" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/wyll-in-blue-robes-and-a-winged-drow-stand-in-baldur-s-gate-3-wearing-eilistraee-s-armory-mod-gear.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   minic00pers
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Designed for those seeking dexterity-focused builds, this mod includes a set of gear themed around the goddess Eilistraee, who is briefly mentioned in
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  through related items and books. For those wanting deeper roleplay and, above all, a complete set to pair with Phalar Aluve, this ranks among the best mods in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Her related items can be found in the tutorial chest for players who want quick access, but they are also hidden in the Underdark for those who choose to explore. It is possible to upgrade the pieces in this set by locating the necessary resources in specific places throughout
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="draconic-elf-armor-set">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Draconic Elf Armor Set
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-nice-set-of-new-gears-for-players">
  A Nice Set Of New Gears For Players
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A warrior in blue and gold Draconic Elf Armor Set poses with a mage in red in Baldur’s Gate 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/a-warrior-in-blue-and-gold-draconic-elf-armor-set-poses-with-a-mage-in-red-in-baldur-s-gate-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   PurpleWalri
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This RPG features various armors throughout the game, appealing not only for their benefits but also for their detailed visuals. However, for anyone seeking something new, this mod adds extra equipment to
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  inspired by elven culture, offering complete sets to players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether for equipping a companion or for an elf-centered roleplay in
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  , the Draconic Elf Armor Set provides crafted pieces that fit the style of the game. They appear in the tutorial chest, which might make them strong early on, but their bonuses and effects become more practical in the late game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="graphicfade-equipment-mods">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   GraphicFade Equipment Mods
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-series-of-thematic-gear-for-baldur-rsquo-s-gate-3-classes">
  A Series Of Thematic Gear For Baldur’s Gate 3 Classes
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Shadowheart and Gale wearing gears from a armor mod in BG3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/shadowheart-and-gale-wearing-gears-from-a-armor-mod-in-bg3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mod Link
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Mod Creator:
   </strong>
   GraphicFade
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This Baldur’s Gate 3 armor mod is not just one modification adding new armors, but a set of smaller submods designed for each class. It lets players install only what fits a specific run. Also, with Fade’s Equipment Distribution, these items can spawn around the map, ready to be found during exploration.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although some pieces from this mod use textures from gear already in the game, the new effects, focused on each class’s strengths, make them valuable to many players. For those who want to customize characters with new equipments and have more variety, this mod is an excellent option.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
