<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Throne and Liberty Giving Away Free Items</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/throne-and-liberty-free-items-january-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Throne and Liberty compensates players with valuable in-game rewards for extended downtime due to update issues.
     </li>
     <li>
      Compensation includes Ornate Coins, Trait Unlockstones, Star Crystals, and Rare Rune Chests.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite technical setbacks, players can re-immerse themselves in the game's world after fixes.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Throne and Liberty
   </strong>
  </em>
  will receive an array of free items as compensation for prolonged downtime caused by the Lunar Celebration updates, which began on January 22. The free-to-play MMORPG by Amazon Games and NCSoft was released to much fanfare in the latter half of last year.
  <em>
   Throne and Liberty
  </em>
  enjoyed a solid start, posting strong player numbers and garnering mostly positive reviews before the full release. However, the game has been hit by a string of technical issues since its global launch.
 </p>
 <p>
  The first major issue surfaced on day one, when
  <em>
   Throne and Liberty
  </em>
  faced server problems due to an overwhelming influx of new players. Since then, the game has been plagued by smaller bugs and glitches, a common challenge for new releases. Despite these setbacks, it continues to draw plenty of players, with most of the negative criticisms leveled at the technical issues rather than the game's content.
 </p>
 <p>
  As announced by Throne and Liberty Game Status via Twitter, compensation is being provided for the extended downtime needed to address two issues caused by the planned update v1.13.0. The post apologizes for the inconvenience and highlights the main problems: player disconnections and combat power displaying lower than intended. It also outlines the specific compensation players will receive, which will be delivered through in-game mail. The downtime reparations offered to players include a suite of valuable gifts, such as
  <em>
   Throne and Liberty
  </em>
  Ornate Coins, which players can use to buy a variety of prized items.
 </p>
 <div style="margin-left:8px">
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="throne-and-liberty-free-compensation-items">
  Throne and Liberty Free Compensation Items
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   2500 Ornate Coins
  </li>
  <li>
   200 Trait Unlockstones
  </li>
  <li>
   1200 Star Crystals
  </li>
  <li>
   250 Rare Rune Chests
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  In addition to an impressive number of Ornate Coins, players will get Trait Unlockstones as compensation for the downtime. The power to unlock
  <em>
   Throne and Liberty
  </em>
  traits is highly valuable in the game, as it’s the main tool used to build and customize the player's character. From improving health and mana to reducing cooldowns to increasing the odds of hitting enemies, it's central to conquering the endgame.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-634595305" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-634595305" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-634595305" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-634595305" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-634595305-img" id="article-gallery-1-634595305">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-634595305" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1131406400">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For players, also in the mix of free items are
  <em>
   Throne and Liberty
  </em>
  Star Crystals, which are one of the game's premium currencies. Star Crystals can be used to purchase a bunch of goodies players will want to get their hands on. While the downtime caused headaches and disrupted gameplay, the compensation offered will help ease some of that irritation by providing a bevy of valuable rewards.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game is now back up and running, with all major issues being fixed. So, players can re-enter the vast world of Solisium to battle the evil Kazar, without the risk of being kicked out, and with a welcome boost to item stocks.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Playable Character In Ninja Gaiden 2 Black, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/every-best-worst-playable-character-ninja-gaiden-2-black-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Rachel has an uneven character build with a slow hammer but a powerful machine gun.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ayane is fast and ninja-like, armed with twin swords and a decent Ninpo spell.
     </li>
     <li>
      Momiji stands out with the Heavenly Dragon Nagita as one of the best weapons in the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
   </em>
  </strong>
  starts players off with Ryu, the main character of the series. Ryu has been fighting fellow ninjas and monsters since the 80s when his franchise debuted in arcades in 1988. In 2004, the series was reborn on the original Xbox and it was Koei Tecmo’s and Team Ninja’s decision to meld this world with
  <em>
   Dead or Alive
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  That’s why Ryu has appeared as a guest fighter in those games and why characters from
  <em>
   Dead or Alive
  </em>
  have appeared in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  games. This is all to say that altogether there are four playable characters in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  some of which are from the acclaimed fighting game series. How do they all play? Here's a ranking of them based on their weapons and strengths.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="rachel">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Rachel
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="it-rsquo-s-hammer-time">
  It’s Hammer Time
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Rachel in Ninja Gaiden 2 Black" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rachel-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Appearance: Chapter 8
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Rachel is the returning femme fatale from the first
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  reboot in 2004. She’s the second guest character in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  and is equipped with a big hammer, a machine gun, and one Ninpo spell. The hammer is slow, making it easy for the smaller and faster monsters to swarm Rachel. Savvy players familiar with the countering and evasion system can make this hammer sing though. Her Ninpo spell can summon thorny vines to surround her which is not a bad defensive move.
 </p>
 <p>
  Compared to other Ninpo spells in the game though, it’s not as versatile as players have to wait for enemies to get close. Rachel’s best attribute is her machine gun with the catchy name Type 666 Heavy Machine Gun. The stopping power isn’t much to brag about but consistent bullets will stop enemies in their tracks long enough for players to finish them off with the hammer. Overall, Rachel has an uneven character build. She’s a tank with the hammer but the rest of her gear doesn’t reflect that type of classic RPG build.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ayane">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Ayane
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-purple-blur">
  The Purple Blur
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ayane in Ninja Gaiden 2 Black" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ayane-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Appearance: Chapter 11
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Next to Ryu, Ayane is probably the most recognizable character in this game and overall series. Ayane was in the very first
  <em>
   Dead or Alive
  </em>
  game, as a ninja, so it made sense to bring her into
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  when it was decided the two series would share a world. Origins aside, Ayane is the last guest character players can control in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  . She’s armed with two small swords, explosive kunai, and a pretty decent Ninpo spell that can damage enemies around her. The explosive kunai replaces a typical ranged weapon like a gun or bow, but that’s okay as the power is decent for stunning enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ayane’s best gear is her twin swords, the Fuma Kodachi, which make her incredibly fast. Of the four playable characters in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  , Ayane acts the most ninja-like thanks to her swiftness. Ayane sticks out as much as Naruto does in his anime series thanks to her bright blue color and giant pink bow but at least she’s quick on her feet. Like Sonic the Hedgehog, Ayane will leave blurs of her image behind as she slices and dices her way through opponents. While not the strongest physically, Ayane is a classic character who should honestly get her own
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  -style adventure instead of a volleyball one.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="momiji">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Momiji
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-shrine-maiden-with-bite">
  A Shrine Maiden With Bite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Momiji in Ninja Gaiden 2 Black" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/momiji-in-ninja-gaiden-2-black.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Appearance: Chapter 5
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Momiji is the first guest character players can get into and they may not want to return to Ryu afterward. She has an incredible main weapon, the Heavenly Dragon Nagita, which is essentially a heavy spear with a sword-like blade attached. The nagita is a traditional Japanese weapon that players have probably seen before in games like
  <em>
   Bushido Blade
  </em>
  . It’s not as heavy as Rachel’s hammer, but not as swift as Ryu’s Lunar Staff. The Heavenly Dragon Nagita fits somewhere in the middle but regardless it’s a lot of fun to use especially when impaling enemies on it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Her bow is faster than Ryu’s but not as strong. Her fire-based Ninpo spell, The Art of the Crimson Lotus, is stronger than Ryu’s starter though. Overall, the Heavenly Dragon Nagita is why Momiji is fun to play which shows this shrine maiden is not playing around. It’s one of the best weapons in the game and it’s a shame Ryu can’t use it or that Momiji doesn’t appear in more levels.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ryu">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Ryu
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="who-could-have-guessed">
  Who Could Have Guessed?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-320765757" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-320765757" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-320765757" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-320765757" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-320765757-img" id="article-gallery-1-320765757">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-320765757" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-216971077">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It would be weird if the main character in any game was not the best one to play. Ryu definitely earns the title of the Dragon Ninja by the end of
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  . He’s the best character simply because players get to upgrade him, unlike the guest characters. Players can find a large array of weapons from his starting katana to the aforementioned Lunar Staff which is THE best weapon in the game. Ryu can equip two ranged weapons as well, a bow and a cannon, and he can throw kunai to stun enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are four Ninpo spells to collect. Two are fire-based, one is wind-based, and the fourth one uses darkness. Of those four, The Art of the Flame Phoenix is the best one which will summon fiery birds to surround Ryu defensively and they will ignite enemies if they get too close. Players can find a bunch of moves too like the ability to run on walls or one that will piledrive enemies into dirt. If Ryu has one poor quality, it’s that he controls like a tank sometimes but that’s more a problem with the camera angles than anything else. Ryu is a classic video game ninja which is why fans are so excited to see him return with this remaster and the upcoming
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 4
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Handheld Castlevania Games That Still Hold Up</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-handheld-castlevania-games-that-still-hold-up/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There have been several collections of the Gothic Konami action hit
  <strong>
   <em>
    Castlevania
   </em>
  </strong>
  in recent years, which has fans overjoyed. First, there was the large bundle of classics,
  <em>
   Castlevania Anniversary Collection,
  </em>
  followed by
  <em>
   Castlevania Advance Collection
  </em>
  . More recently, the bundle of unique DS games, Castlevania Dominus Collection has capped things off, reminding fans of how well this franchise can play on handheld.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Konami may not be making new
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  games, but fans can rest assured most of the classics are (or likely will be) available in some fashion — and in better form than ever. A 3D collection is high on the list of things at least some diehards and series newbies want to see next. Some games naturally hold up better than others, so in celebration of
  <em>
   Castlevania Dominus Collection
  </em>
  , this list will highlight the portable entries that hold up the best; whether still trapped on handheld gadgets, or now able to thrive further on PC/home console.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated January 25, 2025 by Stephen LaGioia:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   While new Castlevania games remain scarce, the series lives on through other means — between the spiritual successor Bloodstained, Netflix series, and of course, alluring bundles that feature the 2D action series at its peak. After consuming this dark, thrilling, and imaginative content, gamers will likely wish to venture back in time and revisit (or encounter for the
   <strong>
    first
   </strong>
   time) the classic Castlevania games. And in an era where handheld gaming is on the rise (via mobile, Switch, and Steamdeck), many will specifically want to seek out handheld renditions of the franchise, which are still fun to play. Luckily, there are plenty to choose from.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="castlevania-lords-of-shadow---mirror-of-fate">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Lords Of Shadow - Mirror Of Fate
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fine-blend-of-old-and-new-castlevania">
  A Fine Blend Of Old And New Castlevania
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-599067607" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-599067607" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-599067607" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-599067607" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-599067607-img" id="article-gallery-1-599067607">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-599067607" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1912472689">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following the journeys of the 11th-century knight and Brotherhood of Light member Gabriel Belmont, the
  <em>
   Lords of Shadow
  </em>
  trilogy is a self-contained reboot and spinoff of
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  . While it's not as esteemed as many classic entries in the franchise, the action romp filled a niche in the Xbox 360 and PS3's libraries — but especially the Nintendo 3DS.
 </p>
 <p>
  Specifically,
  <em>
   Mirror of Fate
  </em>
  , the second of this trilogy, found its way to 3DS in 2013, and received generally good reviews from fans and critics alike. This underrated entry is regarded for its nice blend of more traditional
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  action and Metroidvania progression and exploration. The 2.5D aesthetic works well here; allowing for a classic style while giving a more modern visual flair, and engrossing gamers deeper into the Gothic atmosphere, further amplified by a terrific soundtrack.
 </p>
 <p>
  Action is dialed back a bit in this one, but this is made up for by the great presentation, solid mechanics, and a slew of fun, unique weapons (as well as characters) to play with. This version also takes advantage of the dual-screen feature, displaying an easily digestible map system that helps when it comes to backtracking — and the sprinkling of Metroidvania traits in general.
 </p>
 <h2 id="castlevania-2-belmont-39-s-revenge">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania 2: Belmont's Revenge
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-surprisingly-ambitious-effort-on-game-boy">
  A Surprisingly Ambitious Effort On Game Boy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-347666205" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-347666205" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-347666205" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-347666205" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-347666205-img" id="article-gallery-2-347666205">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-347666205" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2140822560">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While it's easy to view much of the green and yellow, brick Game Boy's material as being rather dated — and this partly includes the
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  debut on the handheld — this isn't quite the case for this sequel. The game draws upon the strengths of its predecessor, and the series at large, while expanding
  <strong>
   just
  </strong>
  enough to craft a more compelling experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unlike the first Game Boy entry, this follow-up utilizes sub-weapons by way of holy water and axes, adding a bit of depth and more of that
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  feel. While just a handful of stages exist, each proves surprisingly dense, with distinct biome themes (plant, crystal, and earth, to name a few), and can be tackled in any order a la
  <em>
   Mega Man
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The game also just plain looks and plays sharper than the '89 debut. The satisfying action and rewarding progression are still here, but the game also brings a sense of freedom and nuance rarely seen in early Game Boy games.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kid-dracula-game-boy">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Kid Dracula (Game Boy)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="alucard-goes-on-a-whimsical-adventure">
  Alucard Goes On A Whimsical Adventure
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1169897303" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1169897303" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1169897303" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1169897303" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1169897303-img" id="article-gallery-3-1169897303">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1169897303" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-365727270">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Kid Dracula is a sequel/remake port to the NES game of the same name. It literally stars Dracula’s son, Alucard, but as a more mischievous child compared to the more adult version found in
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s a 2D action platformer with Alucard having the innate ability to throw fireballs at enemies. It’s not as intricate as some other portable
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  experiences, but it's still a blast to play thanks to the jolly music, cute aesthetics, and tight controls.
 </p>
 <p>
  While it may seem a bit silly and whimsical for
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  , this distinct motif works on the more humble hardware of the Game Boy. It also makes for an amusing novelty in the
  <em>
   Castlevania Anniversary Collection
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="castlevania-circle-of-the-moon">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Circle Of The Moon
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-gba-rsquo-s-first-metroidvania">
  The GBA’s First Metroidvania
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-886751154" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-886751154" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-886751154" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-886751154" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-886751154-img" id="article-gallery-4-886751154">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-886751154" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-945972280">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Circle of the Moon
  </em>
  is the first (and one of the best) 2D Metroidvanias to follow
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night
  </em>
  . Fans of the previous game had to wait from 1997 until 2001 to experience this spiritual sequel. Instead of Alucard, players controlled Nathan who inherited the whip-cracking abilities of the Belmont clan.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players could still level up and equip Nathan with gear like in
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night
  </em>
  , but Nathan’s only weapon was that whip — unlike Alucard who could equip
  <strong>
   many
  </strong>
  varied weapons. Players could collect cards from monsters that could then be infused into their whip. For example, one could give the whip thorns in
  <em>
   Castlevania: Circle of the Moon
  </em>
  . Nathan’s movements quite literally start slow, but after acquiring boots, players can run around more easily — thus making the game more playable.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="castlevania-harmony-of-dissonance">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Harmony Of Dissonance
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-belmonts-are-back-in-style">
  The Belmonts Are Back In Style
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1888896162" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1888896162" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1888896162" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1888896162" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1888896162-img" id="article-gallery-5-1888896162">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1888896162" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-292415421">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance
  </em>
  returns the Belmont clan to prominence with Juste. Like Nathan, he could only infuse his whip with abilities taken from monsters. From fire powers to the ability to spin the whip around, players could find various uses for the whip.
 </p>
 <p>
  Leveling up and equipment gathering returned as well and Juste overall had more of a speed and cadence akin to Alucard and
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night
  </em>
  . It was a big upgrade over
  <em>
   Castlevania: Circle of the Moon
  </em>
  especially since players at the time complained that the GBA’s screen did not light that game well.
  <em>
   Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance
  </em>
  perhaps course corrected too much and made the game garishly vibrant at times which helps it stand out at least.
 </p>
 <h2 id="castlevania-aria-of-sorrow">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Aria Of Sorrow
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-futuristic-setting-taking-on-old-horrors">
  A Futuristic Setting Taking On Old Horrors
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1532880944" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1532880944" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1532880944" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1532880944" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1532880944-img" id="article-gallery-6-1532880944">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1532880944" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1617503753">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow
  </em>
  was the final entry in the series on the GBA. It was, and still is, the most distinct game because it takes place in the future, and has a quasi-sci-fi feel. Soma, a student, happens upon Dracula’s Castle reappearing in Japan and is then tasked with trying to solve its mysteries.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow
  </em>
  gave players the ability to once again equip several weapons from deadly swords to long spears — like Alucard could in
  <em>
   Castlevania: Symphony of the Night
  </em>
  . Soma can also learn abilities from monsters for sub-attacks, like throwing bones from a skeleton. It was a high note to end with the GBA, so much so that it helped summon a direct sequel.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="castlevania-dawn-of-sorrow">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Dawn Of Sorrow
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rare-direct-sequel">
  A Rare Direct Sequel
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-514977514" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-514977514" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-514977514" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-514977514" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-514977514-img" id="article-gallery-7-514977514">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-514977514" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-85626510">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There aren’t many direct sequels in the
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  series. The franchise tends to jump around timelines much like
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda
  </em>
  series.
  <em>
   Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow
  </em>
  is a rare sequel directly following
  <em>
   Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow
  </em>
  , and sees the return of Soma.
 </p>
 <p>
  It was the first entry on the DS and was ultimately a refresh of ideas from the previous game — but enhanced thanks to DS' dual screens and touch controls. Soma could collect weapons and monster abilities again with the neat concept of upgrading gear via monster souls. It also used touch controls a bit to open doors or seal bosses away, for example. Back to back, these two Soma games rank among the top-tier entries for fans.
 </p>
 <h2 id="castlevania-portrait-of-ruin">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Portrait Of Ruin
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="two-vampire-hunters-are-better-than-one">
  Two Vampire Hunters Are Better Than One
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1952071464" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1952071464" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1952071464" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1952071464" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1952071464-img" id="article-gallery-8-1952071464">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1952071464" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-431178923">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin
  </em>
  was the second game in the series released on the DS, and brought forth some interesting ideas. Instead of one hero, players could control
  <strong>
   two
  </strong>
  via Jonathan and Charlotte. They could swap between them on the fly or summon both to fight side by side, adding some depth and strategy to the formula.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players could also command one character to stay still while another character moves to solve a puzzle, adding a unique dynamic to map progression. Both played differently, with Jonathan using a whip and sub-weapons like throwing knives, while Charlotte used books and monster magic. Gamers could hop around levels using paintings on the walls, giving the locations a fresh coat of paint frequently.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="castlevania-order-of-ecclesia">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Castlevania: Order Of Ecclesia
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-last-true-2d-metroidvania-in-the-series">
  The Last True 2D Metroidvania In The Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1294389771" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1294389771" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1294389771" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1294389771" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1294389771-img" id="article-gallery-9-1294389771">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1294389771" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1256207592">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This epic
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  stars Shanoa, a gifted warrior facing the many forces of evil. She can absorb various Glyphs from monsters. Glyphs grant her abilities like a magnetic pole that can launch her around the screen. In essence, Glyphs are how players can obtain weapons and this entry allows players to equip two weapons at once so that they can create some fast combos. Some weapons, of course, pair better than others.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Castlevania: Order of Ecclesia
  </em>
  was the last 2D
  <em>
   Castlevania
  </em>
  game of the Koji Igarashi era of Konami, who was the longtime Castlevania series producer. The term 'Igavania' is closely associated with these portable entries, and occupies the same line of thought as the Metroidvania term. Igarashi went on to Kickstart the spiritual successor series,
  <em>
   Bloodstained
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Atmospheric Strategy Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-most-atmospheric-strategy-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Indie games excel in atmosphere, offering unique experiences.
     </li>
     <li>
      Strategic games like Duskers and Dune: Spice Wars provide immersive atmospheres.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like Darkest Dungeon create gripping atmospheres with style and narration.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Strategy games aren't typically known for their atmosphere, instead relying on deeply mechanical gameplay to draw in players. While it's true that games such as
  <em>
   StarCraft 2
  </em>
  are able to offer a well-crafted atmosphere via a strong art style and a fitting soundtrack, the gameplay is often too fast-paced to appreciate it.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, many strategy games excel with their immersive atmospheres, which often elevate solid game designs. From
  <em>
   Dune: Spice Wars
  </em>
  and its slow pace and thematic mechanics to
  <em>
   Balatro
  </em>
  and its casino-style and entrancing atmosphere, there's an abundance of strategic titles to get immersed in.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="balatro">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Balatro
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-entrancing-casino-atmosphere">
  An Entrancing Casino Atmosphere
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1769766627" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1769766627" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1769766627" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1769766627" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1769766627-img" id="article-gallery-1-1769766627">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1769766627" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-963464400">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Balatro
  </em>
  is a tremendously accessible roguelike deck-builder thanks to its familiar mechanics, which are heavily based around Poker. In keeping with its casino-game influences,
  <em>
   Balatro's
  </em>
  aesthetic and overall tone resembles that of a slot machine, or maybe digital Solitaire.
 </p>
 <p>
  The charming, quirky pixel art and entrancing soundtrack help to support this hypnotizing atmosphere, further elevated by crunchy sound effects and tactile controls. It may not immerse players in any particular location, but
  <em>
   Balatro's
  </em>
  casino atmosphere can be spellbinding.
 </p>
 <h2 id="duskers">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Duskers
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-eerily-quiet-slow-burning-strategy-game">
  An Eerily Quiet Slow-Burning Strategy Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-253981160" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-253981160" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-253981160" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-253981160" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-253981160-img" id="article-gallery-2-253981160">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-253981160" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-751364932">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Duskers
  </em>
  tasks players with controlling a group of hardy robotic drones through derelict spaceships, salvaging what they can while avoiding hidden horrors. This slow-burning gameplay is supported by a tense, eerie atmosphere that manages to be immersive despite minimalist visuals.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Duskers
  </em>
  , players must control their drones from afar, viewing their surroundings through unstable cameras. This, along with the tinny audio provided by the in-game remote microphone, provides a palpable, quiet atmosphere that balances tension with moments of reprieve.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cataclismo">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Cataclismo
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-subdued-cartoon-style-amp-melancholic-tone">
  A Subdued Cartoon Style &amp; Melancholic Tone
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-853688924" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-853688924" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-853688924" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-853688924" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-853688924-img" id="article-gallery-3-853688924">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-853688924" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1614752825">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This horde-survival strategy game follows a fairly standard base defense structure, but it stands out with its modular building system and gloomy atmosphere. The subdued art style and melancholic tone provide a dreary ambiance, counterbalanced by a cartoonish edge.
 </p>
 <p>
  Base-building with the modular system is perhaps
  <em>
   Cataclismo's
  </em>
  greatest strength, but its well-crafted atmosphere elevates the moment-to-moment gameplay quite a bit. This is especially so thanks to the ability to pause the game at any time, allowing players to enjoy the ambiance while they think about their next moves or overall strategy.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dune-spice-wars">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Dune: Spice Wars
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="atmospheric-sound-design-amp-thematic-gameplay">
  Atmospheric Sound Design &amp; Thematic Gameplay
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1439614594" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1439614594" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1439614594" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1439614594" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1439614594-img" id="article-gallery-4-1439614594">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1439614594" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1698610232">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With rich source material to draw from in Frank Herbert's
  <em>
   Dune
  </em>
  and the accompanying films,
  <em>
   Dune: Spice Wars
  </em>
  uses thematic mechanics and stylish presentation to create an immersive atmosphere. The gameplay mechanics and underlying systems of
  <em>
   Dune: Spice Wars
  </em>
  are among the biggest reasons to play, but the subtle ambiance of the iconic planet Arrakis provides a suitably exotic atmosphere.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fitting soundtrack, packed with strange melodies and atmospheric sounds, is just one element of this title's expert presentation. Appropriate and wholly satisfying sound design and the aforementioned thematic mechanics provide an almost relaxing environment that's both foreign and striking, sure to satisfy any fans of the
  <em>
   Dune
  </em>
  franchise or fans of real-time strategy games.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dungeon-of-the-endless">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Dungeon Of The Endless
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="gritty-pixel-art-amp-a-consistent-tone">
  Gritty Pixel Art &amp; A Consistent Tone
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1180843785" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1180843785" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1180843785" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1180843785" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1180843785-img" id="article-gallery-5-1180843785">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1180843785" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-564439856">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dungeon Of The Endless
  </em>
  is a unique title that combines elements of tower defense, resource management, and real-time strategy. In the game, players work their way through a variety of gritty sci-fi dungeons with a small party of heroes while defending an all-important crystal.
 </p>
 <p>
  The moment-to-moment gameplay is tremendously strategic and often intense, but it can get repetitive. Thankfully,
  <em>
   Dungeon Of The Endless
  </em>
  is supported by a well-crafted atmosphere that combines gritty visuals with an ambient soundtrack designed to draw players into its immersive gameplay loop.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cobalt-core">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Cobalt Core
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-wholly-relaxing-tone-with-a-charming-aesthetic">
  A Wholly Relaxing Tone With A Charming Aesthetic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1781353240" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1781353240" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1781353240" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1781353240" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1781353240-img" id="article-gallery-6-1781353240">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1781353240" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1909769947">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Cobalt Core
  </em>
  is a roguelike deck-builder with a tactical twist that has players duking it out in turn-based space battles. The game's combination of turn-based tactics and deck-building allows for memorable gameplay, elevated by a truly warm and bubbly atmosphere.
 </p>
 <p>
  Be it the charming pixel art, charismatic characters, or the dream-like soundtrack,
  <em>
   Cobalt Core's
  </em>
  presentation builds a steady atmosphere that's consistently relaxing. The colorful graphics and lighthearted dialogue only help to elevate the game's joyful tone, and the turn-based nature of the game ensures players are able to steep themselves in its cheerful ambiance.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="darkest-dungeon">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Darkest Dungeon
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-gothic-style-amp-tone-supported-by-powerful-narration">
  A Gothic Style &amp; Tone Supported By Powerful Narration
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1368506949" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1368506949" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1368506949" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1368506949" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1368506949-img" id="article-gallery-7-1368506949">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1368506949" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-779080190">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players looking for a darker experience may find themselves at home with
  <em>
   Darkest Dungeon
  </em>
  ; the game's dreary, downtrodden atmosphere is supported by a dark and scratchy Gothic art style, mean-spirited gameplay, and a haunting soundtrack.
 </p>
 <p>
  Best of all,
  <em>
   Darkest Dungeon's
  </em>
  moment-to-moment gameplay is supported by a distinctive narrator with true gravitas, heightening every spike of emotion that the game instills, whether in turn-based combat or tense exploration. The gloomy atmosphere won't be for everyone, but
  <em>
   Darkest Dungeon's
  </em>
  dreary ambiance no doubt elevates its Lovecraftian horror and Gothic style to startling heights, providing a near-perfect dark fantasy setting in which players can immerse themselves.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mutant-year-zero-road-to-eden">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Mutant Year Zero: Road To Eden
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-vibrant-post-apocalyptic-world">
  A Vibrant Post-Apocalyptic World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-704454167" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-704454167" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-704454167" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-704454167" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-704454167-img" id="article-gallery-8-704454167">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-704454167" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1184339075">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero: Road To Eden
  </em>
  is a post-apocalyptic strategy game driven by turn-based combat, similar to games such as
  <em>
   XCOM
  </em>
  . What allows
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero
  </em>
  to stand out, however, is its unique world, real-time exploration, and stealth mechanics. The world of
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero
  </em>
  , though dark and hostile, is full of untamed wilderness; plant-life and greenery surround dingy, abandoned buildings, elevating the otherwise standard post-apocalyptic environments.
 </p>
 <p>
  Presented with stylish visuals and elevated by a soundtrack that balances drama with ambiance,
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero
  </em>
  is able to create a mysterious and at-times tranquil atmosphere. Furthermore, the free-form exploration that breaks up the game's turn-based battles allows players to steep themselves in the dense atmosphere of its enigmatic world.
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero
  </em>
  is a can't-miss title for players eager for a strategy game steeped in an immersive atmosphere.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Players Feel One Skin Is Pay-to-Lose</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-jeff-the-shark-incognito-dolphin-skin-covers-screen/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fans criticize Jeff the Land Shark's Incognito Dolphin skin in Marvel Rivals as pay-to-lose due to its bulky design.
     </li>
     <li>
      Jeff, a Strategist, has healing abilities, a powerful ultimate, and a controversial skin that affects gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      In Marvel Rivals, players can earn Units to buy skins through challenges and achievements, making it a rewarding free-to-play title.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans took to social media to express disappointment with Jeff the Land Shark's Incognito Dolphin skin, claiming it is pay-to-lose. Jeff was the focus of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' recent Winter Celebration, which featured a mode where every participant played as the tiny shark while attempting to cover the map in frost. By the end of the event, gamers were able to earn a free Cuddly Fuzzlefin skin for the hero.
 </p>
 <p>
  Jeff the Land Shark is a Strategist in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , which means his main objective is to provide healing and support to his allies while occasionally taking out foes during opportune moments. His primary ability creates a healing stream, which he can sweep across the field to heal allies. He also has the ability to create bubbles that players can run through to both heal and gain a speed boost. The tiny shark even has one of the most powerful ultimates in the game, which allows him to swallow up enemies, damage them while they're held, and potentially launch foes off the edge of the map when he spits them out.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent post on Reddit, Deva_Way claimed that Jeff the Land Shark's Incognito Dolphin skin is pay-to-lose. After using all the Units they'd earned while playing the hero shooter, the Redditor decided to purchase the popular skin for Jeff in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  . Unfortunately, once they equipped the costume, the player noticed that Jeff took up more space on the screen. This is because the outfit doesn't simply recolor Jeff, it places him in a thick fuzzy pink dolphin costume, which adds length and width to the character's profile.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-rsquo-incognito-dolphin-skin-may-be-pay-to-lose">
  Marvel Rivals’ Incognito Dolphin Skin May Be Pay-to-Lose
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1421997116" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1421997116" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1421997116" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1421997116" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1421997116-img" id="article-gallery-1-1421997116">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1421997116" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-134044573">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Jeff's Incognito Dolphin bundle is labeled as "Hot" within the game's shop, meaning it's one of the title's better selling cosmetics. While many fans empathized with Deva_Way, others still claimed that Incognito Dolphin is one of the best skins in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , insisting that its cute design outweighed any possible downside. One player claimed that they will continue to use the skin in the game's Competitive mode, despite the visual bulk and vibrant colors that make Jeff more visible to enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  By completing challenges and achievements, gamers can earn Units to buy skins in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  <em>
   .
  </em>
  While some seasonal quests reward players with currency, Heroic Journey achievements provide the most Units, along with two free skins for Storm and Star-Lord. Fans can also use Lattice to supplement Units when buying cosmetics, allowing players to use a combination of earned and purchased currency. With a variety of ways to acquire skins for popular heroes, many fans feel NetEase Games has created a free-to-play title that truly allows gamers to earn rewards.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
