<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Fan Makes Incredible Sweater Based on the Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-handmade-sweater/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Handmade Stardew Valley sweater impresses community.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans devoted to the game due to regular updates.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans can recreate sweater with free pattern if skilled.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A fan of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  has spent an incredible six months creating a sweater based on the game. The
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  sweater uses some of the most iconic images from the title, and is a loving tribute to a game that means a great deal to many people.
 </p>
 <p>
  As
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  gets closer to its 10th anniversary, players are still as in love with the game as ever. Regular official updates from the developer help to keep
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fresh and exciting, and the core cozy elements and lack of a clear-cut ending keep players coming back. Some fans have spent upwards of a thousand hours in
  <em>
   Stardew
  </em>
  at this point, and many don't keep their love for the game limited to the experience of playing it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Such is the case with Reddit user IsabelleA_A, who shared their incredible handmade
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  sweater with the community. The fan notes that they love
  <em>
   Stardew
  </em>
  and have already spent over 700 hours in the game, and wanted to create something to celebrate both it and its developer, ConcernedApe. They modified a cardigan pattern from another fan of the game and spent an impressive six months crocheting in order to create the sweater. The sweater is made up of squares of pinks and blues, with alternate squares featuring pixel art of some of the game's icons, like Ancient Fruit, blue chickens, Junimo, Starfruit, and a pet cat.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-creation-excites-players">
  Stardew Valley Creation Excites Players
 </h2>
 <p>
  With nearly 6000 upvotes at the time of writing, it's clear that the community is very impressed with IsabelleA_A's work. Many have expressed interest in having one of these sweaters for themselves. Due to the amount of time the sweater took and the overall labor involved, IsabelleA_A doesn't sell them. However, the pattern they based their design on is free, so
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fans who know how to crochet may want to check it out and see if their skills are up to the task.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-766273063" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-766273063" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-766273063" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-766273063" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-766273063-img" id="article-gallery-1-766273063">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-766273063" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-747834195">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  community seems to be just as committed to the game as its developer is. ConcernedApe is constantly surprising fans by doing more work for the game than even he seems to expect, releasing content updates and surprise patches that add new content and fix issues that players have reported. The constant care has led to the game being nominated for Steam's Labor of Love award for the year, which it also received a nomination for back in 2018. While ConcernedApe has said that a ton of work has been done on
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  , it seems neither players nor the developer can leave
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  alone for long.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Genshin Impact Leaks Popular Character's Banner Rerun for Version 5.4</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-wriothesley-banner-rerun-version-5-4-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      According to a leak, Wriothesley may get a rerun in Genshin Impact Version 5.4 after waiting over a year in the Fortress of Meropide.
     </li>
     <li>
      Genshin Impact struggles to maintain a fair schedule with over 90 playable characters and limited rerun slots.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite a new Spiral Abyss buff benefiting Wriothesley, players may face longer rerun wait times until triple banners are introduced.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  According to a recent
  <em>
   <strong>
    Genshin Impact
   </strong>
  </em>
  leak, Wriothesley will allegedly get his first rerun in Version 5.4 after over a year of waiting in the Fortress of Meropide. With over 90 playable characters, it has become a struggle for
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  to maintain a fair and just schedule system for its Event Banners. Assuming only one 5-Star is released per patch on average, there are still 43 limited 5-Star characters that deserve a rerun once per year. However, with only 27 possible slots for them on the Event Banners, this has become an impossibility.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the Chronicled Banner in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  was an attempt by the developers to address the problem, many players see it as a band-aid fix, rather than a long-term solution. Despite the existence of the Chronicled Banner, Shenhe still went over 600 days before her rerun was confirmed for Version 5.3. However, until the developers are ready to entertain the idea of Triple Banners,
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  players will likely need to endure longer wait times between a rerun.
 </p>
 <p>
  A notable victim of this format's shortcomings has been Wriothesley, a Cryo Catalyst who had his debut banner in Version 4.1, and hasn't been featured on the Event Banners since. Wriothesley in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  is a modern take on the Cryo hypercarry, and his Burnmelt teams are capable of dishing out respectable amounts of damage. However, players have been unable to pull for Wriothesley since November 8, 2023. According to Flying Flame, this will change in Version 5.4, as Wriothesley will feature on its Event Banners.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-could-feature-a-wriothesley-banner-in-version-5-4">
  Genshin Impact Could Feature a Wriothesley Banner in Version 5.4
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-650352982" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-650352982" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-650352982" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-650352982" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-650352982-img" id="article-gallery-1-650352982">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-650352982" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-670805577">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It should be noted that Flying Flame has had a spotty record when it comes to Natlan. While they were the first to claim that a new Chronicled Banner was coming in Version 5.3, and that it would be themed around the Lantern Rite, their other leaks turned out to be false. As such,
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  players should take this information with a grain of salt. That being said, the new Spiral Abyss buff in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  does benefit Wriothesley's playstyle, so there is some notable merit to the rumor.
 </p>
 <p>
  Version 5.4 is also expected to introduce Mizuki to
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , who will potentially be Inazuma's first Standard Banner character. Assuming Mizuki and Wriothesley end up being one half of the Event Banners, the other half is expected to have either Furina or Venti as one of the featured 5-Stars. Archon characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  notably get their reruns in a sequence, and the two are the only Archons who haven't done so. Version 5.4 is expected to launch on February 12, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Battlefield 1!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-battlefield-1/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players score syringe eliminations in Battlefield 1 and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New World of Warcraft Video Explains Feast of Winter Veil Lore</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/world-of-warcraft-feast-of-winter-veil-platinumwow-lore-video/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Feast of Winter Veil in WoW is like Christmas, with special rewards and new items every year.
     </li>
     <li>
      The lore video details holiday origins, including the Dwarven myth, a Titan-forged giant, and Tauren traditions
     </li>
     <li>
      This video is thanks to a collaboration with PlatinumWoW.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    World of Warcraft
   </strong>
  </em>
  recently teamed up with PlatinumWoW to release a lore video detailing the history of the Feast of Winter Veil. From the in-universe origins of the holiday to the many kidnappings of Metzen the Reindeer, the ongoing
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  Christmas event has a storied history in Azeroth.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Feast of Winter Veil is
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  ’s equivalent to Christmas. Every year, Blizzard brings back the in-game event with special rewards and activities – often adding a few new items players can collect as random drops, gold, or through other means.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now,
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  has released a new video that goes into the history of the in-game holiday. Narrated by
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  lore expert and content creator PlatinumWoW, the short video talks about the holiday’s origins – the Dwarven myth of Greatfather Winter, a Titan-forged giant who leaves snow in his wake, and the Tauren traditions of spiritual reflection, renewal, and giving thanks to the Earthmother. He then explains the rise of Smokeywood Pastures, the Goblin-run business that commercialized Winter Veil in the modern day, similar to Christmas in real life.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="history-of-the-feast-of-winter-veil-in-world-of-warcraft">
  History of the Feast of Winter Veil in World of Warcraft
 </h2>
 <p>
  Of course, no Winter Veil lore video would be complete without talking about Metzen the Reindeer. Named after
  <em>
   Warcraft
  </em>
  executive creative director Chris Metzen, this ill-fortuned cervid has been kidnapped three different times: by pirates and Dark Iron Dwarves in
  <em>
   Classic
  </em>
  , and again by the Greench in modern
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  . The video fittingly and hilariously ends with Metzen the Reindeer thanking the viewer in Thrall’s voice, as the Orc Shaman is famously voiced by Chris Metzen.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1278550239" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1278550239" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1278550239" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1278550239" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1278550239-img" id="article-gallery-1-1278550239">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1278550239" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-378574156">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This isn’t the first time
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  has teamed up with PlatinumWoW for an officially sponsored video. Over the last couple of years, he has made lore breakdowns about Nerubians, Vrykul, and the Scourge for
  <em>
   Wrath of the Lich King Classic
  </em>
  , World Trees and Blackrock Depths for modern
  <em>
   WoW
  </em>
  , and even helpful videos for events like Season of Discovery and Plunderstorm. Between these, Taliesin &amp; Evitel’s tips for returning players in
  <em>
   Dragonflight
  </em>
  , and the gorgeous cinematic trailers for
  <em>
   World of Warcraft Classic
  </em>
  by Hurricane, Blizzard has had no shortage of content creator collaborations recently.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fans still have until January 5, 2024, to enjoy the Feast of Winter Veil in the game. This year, Hunters in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  can tame the Dreaming Festive Reindeer, and all players can collect new holiday transmogs and the Grunch pet. Once their own real-life festivities are concluded, fans should be sure to log in and check under the tree in Orgrimmar or Stormwind, as there will undoubtedly be a special Winter Veil gift for them, like last year’s Junior Timekeeper’s Racing Belt toy.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: How to Get Samurai Star Wars Skins</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-samurai-darth-vader-samurai-star-wars-skins-how-to-get/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get the Darth Vader Samurai Skin in Fortnite
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get the Stormtrooper Samurai Skin in Fortnite
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  Celebration heading to Japan in 2025, it's no surprise that another collab between
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  x
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  sees the iconic Sith Lord, Darth Vader, in the armor of a samurai from Feudal Japan. The Darth Vader Samurai skin works perfectly in Fortnite Chapter 6 Season 1, and players can grab it now to bring balance to the Force and to the Battle Royale.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  Samurai skins in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  provide players with a fresh look for some classic villains, and below is a showcase of the famed Stormtrooper and Darth Vader, who both feature as different V-Buck costs and aesthetics to mesh wonderfully with Chapter 6's Japanese map.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-the-darth-vader-samurai-skin-in-fortnite">
  How to Get the Darth Vader Samurai Skin in Fortnite
 </h2>
 <h3 id="4-item-bundle-for-1-800-v-bucks">
  4 Item Bundle for 1,800 V-Bucks
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="darth vader samurai" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png" decoding="async" height="1280" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/darth-vader-samurai.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Darth Vader Samurai Outfit
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While players can't get their hands on the actual Darth Vader thanks to his exclusivity to the Chapter 3 Season 3 Battle Pass, they can now head to the Item Shop as of December 24, 7 PM ET to grab the Darth Vader Samurai skin for 1,800 V-Bucks. This samurai rendition of the iconic Star Wars villain comes with a few goodies, including Vader's Katana, which acts as a samurai sword version of Darth Vader's lightsaber, complete with Japanese aesthetics, a glowing red blade, and the iconic hilt of Vader. This can also be used as a Back Bling, and Darth Vader Samurai also comes with a LEGO variant.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Darth Vader Samurai is purchasable until January 6, 7 PM ET.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-the-stormtrooper-samurai-skin-in-fortnite">
  How to Get the Stormtrooper Samurai Skin in Fortnite
 </h2>
 <h3 id="3-item-bundle-for-1-500-v-bucks">
  3 Item Bundle for 1,500 V-Bucks
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="stormtrooper samurai" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png" decoding="async" height="1280" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/stormtrooper-samurai.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Stormtrooper Samurai Outfit
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The loyal foot soldier of the Galactic Empire, the Stormtrooper joins Darth Vader as a purchasable skin for 1,500 V-Bucks. While it's no Sith Lord, the Stormtrooper Samurai still stands out as a unique variant of the classic
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  enemy. While lacking the Force, the Stormtrooper Samurai comes with a few goodies, like the Imperial Banner Back Bling to raise the Empire's sigil in Palaptine's name, and a LEGO variant for LEGO modes.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Stormtrooper Samurai is purchasable until January 6, 7 PM ET.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_16">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players can also grab the Star Wars Samurai Bundle for 3,200 V-Bucks, which comes Darth Vader Samurai, Stormtrooper Samurai, along with additional cosmetics like the Lil' TIE Attack Traversal Emote and the Samurai Star Wars Wraps.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
