<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>6 Best Brother-Sister Relationships In Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-brother-sister-sibling-relationships-video-games-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Complex sibling dynamics in games like Oxenfree showcase how player choices can impact relationships.
     </li>
     <li>
      Claire and Chris Redfield's dedication in Resident Evil shows that strong sibling bonds can help drive a franchise.
     </li>
     <li>
      Amicia and Hugo's bond in A Plague Tale exemplifies how sibling relationships can shape the entire narrative.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Family dynamics have been a part of storytelling since the dawn of time, and video games are no exception. Whether it's marriage stress like in
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  or the adoptive father-daughter relationship in
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  , gamers love to see the complex interpersonal relationships between characters — especially when they can affect the eventual outcome of said relationship. Siblings are a great example of this, with several games containing sibling relationships of all kinds.
 </p>
 <p>
  This list looks at six of the best examples of brother-sister relationships in gaming, pitting them against each other to rank them based on how important each relationship is to their respective games and how well the characters work together. While not every example has the happiest of endings, they are all well-written relationships with individual merits to be given for their depictions of sibling dynamics.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Spoiler Warning: expect to see some narrative spoilers for the games detailed below.
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="claire-amp-chris-redfield-resident-evil">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Claire &amp; Chris Redfield (Resident Evil)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="resident-evil-39-s-resident-siblings">
  Resident Evil's Resident Siblings
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1941737643" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1941737643" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1941737643" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1941737643" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1941737643-img" id="article-gallery-1-1941737643">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1941737643" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1299141023">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Chris Redfield first graced gamers' screens in 1996 in
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  , with his sister Claire joining two years later in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 2,
  </em>
  and since then, the two have become beloved by many. Despite the two being some of the most iconic protagonists of the franchise (second only to Leon S. Kennedy), they have only ever appeared together in one game,
  <em>
   Resident Evil - Code: Veronica.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Thanks to the series's habit of somewhat neglecting Claire and Chris' relegation to side a character in
  <em>
   Resident Evil: Biohazard
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Village
  </em>
  , the two haven't seen a huge amount of development, landing them at the bottom of the list. While they don't interact much, Claire's dedication to finding Chris throughout the games she appears in implies a pretty good relationship, without which the
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  franchise would struggle.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hannah-beth-amp-josh-washington-until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Hannah, Beth, &amp; Josh Washington (Until Dawn)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-relationship-that-might-not-last-until-dawn">
  A Relationship That Might Not Last Until Dawn
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1111165185" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1111165185" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1111165185" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1111165185" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1111165185-img" id="article-gallery-2-1111165185">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1111165185" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1163820646">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The relationship between the three Washingtons is a little strained throughout
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  , partially due to the sisters' missing status, and eventually revealed fates. Despite this, in the brief time the player gets to see Hannah and Beth directly interact, their relationship is a strong one, the two appearing close. This closeness is, however, what inevitably leads to both girls going missing, prompting the rest of the game's events to occur, as a prank gone wrong causes Hannah to run out into the mountains, with Beth following.
 </p>
 <p>
  Josh's role in the relationship is a little less clear. However, after their disappearance, it becomes clear that he had enough of a positive relationship with his sisters to blame himself for their fates. Returning to the site a year later with the rest of the party, Josh enacts his revenge for the prank the others pulled. Despite his messed-up way of showing it, Josh cares for his sisters deeply, and this relationship is the catalyst for many of the events in the game.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="alex-amp-jonas-oxenfree">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Alex &amp; Jonas (Oxenfree)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="make-or-break-a-step-sibling-relationship">
  Make Or Break A Step-Sibling Relationship
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-318007889" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-318007889" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-318007889" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-318007889" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-318007889-img" id="article-gallery-3-318007889">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-318007889" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-846816795">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Oxenfree
  </em>
  is a game of choices, each one leading to different outcomes for each character, eventually shaping how their relationships are made (or broken) by the end of the narrative. The best example of this in the game is the relationship between step-siblings Alex and Jonas. Throughout the game's mind-bending, time-traveling story, the fledgling relationship of these new siblings is tested as ghosts possess people and alternate realities bleed together.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes this relationship so powerful is the way that the player can choose its outcome, each decision pushing the two apart or bringing them closer together by the conclusion of the game. While their relationship isn't as central to the narrative as others on this list, the interactive nature makes it central to the gameplay, which feels unique in its execution.
 </p>
 <h2 id="evie-amp-jacob-frye-assassin-39-s-creed-syndicate">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Evie &amp; Jacob Frye (Assassin's Creed Syndicate)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-deadly-duo">
  A Deadly Duo
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-39512835" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-39512835" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-39512835" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-39512835" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-39512835-img" id="article-gallery-4-39512835">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-39512835" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-576633709">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before the complex familial concepts of
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Odyssey
  </em>
  introduced Alexios and Kassandra as sibling assassins,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Syndicate
  </em>
  had the Frye twins leading an underground war against the Templars in London. These two well-dressed assassins are a perfect example of the sibling dynamic in gaming, being the two playable protagonists in
  <em>
   Syndicate
  </em>
  , each having their own sections of the game and each being a major cog in the narrative events.
 </p>
 <p>
  With each sibling having their own gameplay style, Evie is more akin to the traditional assassin and Jacob a melee brawler. The two work well off each other, as well as being entertaining characters from a writing perspective. The main pitfall of this duo is the game they find themselves in. While a fantastic game,
  <em>
   Syndicate
  </em>
  was released during a decline for the franchise, and so the twins went unappreciated by many fans of the older games.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="alisaie-amp-alphinaud-leveilleur-final-fantasy-14">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Alisaie &amp; Alphinaud Leveilleur (Final Fantasy 14)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-siblings-of-the-scions-of-the-seventh-dawn">
  The Siblings Of The Scions Of The Seventh Dawn
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1401005748" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1401005748" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1401005748" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1401005748" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1401005748-img" id="article-gallery-5-1401005748">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1401005748" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1118790827">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hailing from an MMORPG, Alisaie and Alphinaud are the only entries on this list not to include a playable protagonist.
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  follows the Warrior of Light, the player-created character, as they navigate their way through a world in turmoil, eventually joining the Scions of the Seventh Dawn. It is with this group of heroes that a majority of the relationships are formed and perceived, and Alisaie and Alphinaud are two of the stand-out members.
 </p>
 <p>
  Another set of twins, these two are major players in the plot of most of the storylines seen in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  , and both work to strengthen the other as well as the almost voiceless protagonist. Alisaie is a compassionate yet cynical Red Mage who is less interested in the city-state politics of Eorzea her brother deals in. Alphinaud is more mature and learned than his sister, using a magic grimoire to fight rather than blades and often acting as a political emissary for various nations. What is most compelling about their relationship is their devotion to each other and the legacy of their grandfather, which makes for some moving moments in an otherwise political and action-heavy narrative.
 </p>
 <h2 id="amicia-amp-hugo-de-rune-a-plague-tale">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Amicia &amp; Hugo de Rune (A Plague Tale)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="survive-the-plague-and-dodge-the-inquisition">
  Survive The Plague And Dodge The Inquisition
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-499374790" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-499374790" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-499374790" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-499374790" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-499374790-img" id="article-gallery-6-499374790">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-499374790" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1177428285">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The final duo on this list is the de Runes of the
  <em>
   Plague Tale
  </em>
  games. Amicia and Hugo are the main protagonists of both games, forced to rely on each other from a young age thanks to an inquisition killing their parents amid a plague ravaging 14th-century France. The entire narrative of both games in the franchise hinges on the relationship between the two, Amicia having to learn to survive and fight in order to keep her brother safe, with Hugo learning to control a supernatural power that allows him to control the swarms of rats.
 </p>
 <p>
  Without the relationship between the two, the narrative of both games wouldn't exist. Outside of the franchise entirely hinging on Amicia and Hugo growing and developing as people, they are impeccably written, allowing their relationship to feel real. It goes through highs and lows, and ultimately, both characters are better for it. The deep love Amicia has for Hugo, even when he is incredibly annoying, makes for some heartbreaking moments that set them firmly atop this list.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South of Midnight: Burning Questions, Answered</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/south-of-midnight-platforms-price-size-requirements-faq/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The gaming world is eagerly awaiting the release of
  <em>
   <strong>
    South of Midnight
   </strong>
  </em>
  , an upcoming action game by Compulsion Games. This game promises a unique storyline based on the Deep South's mythology, folklore, and tales. Players will face legendary creatures while looking for the main character's mother, and they can do all of this while appreciating a game that is visually stunning and features a beautiful soundtrack.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Whether players are planning on getting it early on or are simply curious to learn more about it, this article will answer some questions that might've come up about
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-is-south-of-midnight-about">
  What Is South of Midnight About?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-447652639" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-447652639" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-447652639" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-447652639" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-447652639-img" id="article-gallery-1-447652639">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-447652639" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1620545927">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  is about a girl named Hazel who is looking for her mother following a devastating disaster that hit her town in the American Deep South. With Hazel's mending and weaving abilities, players must defeat monsters and learn more about Hazel's family story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="on-which-platforms-can-you-play-south-of-midnight">
  On Which Platforms Can You Play South of Midnight?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="south of midnight world" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-world.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Players can play
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   on Xbox Series X, Xbox Series S, Windows 10, Windows 11, and Steam
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Game Pass Ultimate subscribers will also be able to play
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  on other devices via cloud gaming. Additionally, it is possible to play
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  with a controller on PC - it includes full support for Xbox controllers.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="will-south-of-midnight-be-on-game-pass">
  Will South of Midnight Be on Game Pass?
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Game Pass subscribers will be able to play
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   on day one
  </strong>
  . They will be able to launch the game as soon as it becomes available on
  <strong>
   April 8, 2025
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-much-does-south-of-midnight-cost">
  How Much Does South of Midnight Cost?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="South of Midnight Cover" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/south-of-midnight-cover-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   The standard version of
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   costs $39.99, while the deluxe version costs $49.99
  </strong>
  . However, the latter includes special features that might be worth it to some fans. Here is the difference between the two, for gamers who aren't sure which version of
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  they should purchase:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Standard Version
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Deluxe Version
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        <em>
         South of Midnight
        </em>
        game
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        <em>
         South of Midnight
        </em>
        game
       </li>
       <li>
        5 days early access
       </li>
       <li>
        <em>
         South of Midnight
        </em>
        artbook
       </li>
       <li>
        <em>
         South of Midnight
        </em>
        OST
       </li>
       <li>
        The Boo-Hag Comic Book
       </li>
       <li>
        Music Video:
        <em>
         Songs &amp; Tales of South of Midnight
        </em>
       </li>
       <li>
        Documentary:
        <em>
         Weaving Hazel’s Journey
        </em>
        , Director’s Cut
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Price
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       $39.99
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       $49.99
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since some players will have access to
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  thanks to Game Pass, they can purchase the
  <strong>
   <em>
    South of Midnight
   </em>
   Premium Upgrade for $10
  </strong>
  and get access to all of the deluxe version's perks without paying for the game in full - and this includes the days of early access.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="south-of-midnight-file-size">
  South of Midnight File Size
 </h2>
 <p>
  The size of the file containing
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  depends on the player's platform. If gamers are playing
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  on an Xbox Series X/S, they need
  <strong>
   58 GB
  </strong>
  of free space. On PC, gamers need
  <strong>
   61.1 GB
  </strong>
  of storage space in order to install
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="south-of-midnight-system-requirements">
  South of Midnight System Requirements
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="south of midnight pc requirements" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/south-of-midnight-pc-requirements.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  According to the system requirement information on the official
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  page on Steam, these are the minimum as well as the recommended requirements to play the game:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       System Requirements
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Minimum
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Recommended
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Processor
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        AMD Ryzen 3 1300X
       </li>
       <li>
        Intel i3-8100
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        AMD 1600X
       </li>
       <li>
        Intel i5-7600K
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Memory
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        12 GB RAM
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        16 GB RAM
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Graphics
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        AMD RX 580
       </li>
       <li>
        Nvidia GTX 1060
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        AMD RX 6600
       </li>
       <li>
        Nvidia RTX 2060
       </li>
       <li>
        Intel Arc A580
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-long-is-south-of-midnight">
  How Long Is South of Midnight?
 </h2>
 <p>
  According to reports and interviews with Compulsion Games, it should take players about 12 hours to finish
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  's main story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="is-south-of-midnight-a-scary-game">
  Is South of Midnight a Scary Game?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-250446549" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-250446549" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-250446549" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-250446549" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-250446549-img" id="article-gallery-2-250446549">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-250446549" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-375169951">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  is not a horror game, but it does feature some
  <strong>
   creepy elements as it promises to dive deep into dark folklore
  </strong>
  . Some players might find this too eerie or off-putting, so they might want to look at some images before dipping their toes into it.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Legends: Z-A Leaks Details of Starters' Mega Evolutions</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-legends-z-a-starters-mega-evolutions-details-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mega Evolutions for final forms of starter trio in Pokemon Legends: Z-A leaked, offering new adventures in Lumiose City.
     </li>
     <li>
      Leak reveals Mega Evolution details for Pokemon like Meganium, Feraligatr, and Emboar, along with type changes.
     </li>
     <li>
      Take leaks about Mega Evolutions in Pokemon Legends: Z-A with caution until official confirmation from developers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Legends: Z-A
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak has allegedly revealed details about the Mega Evolutions of the final forms of the starter trio.
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  is the sequel to
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Arceus
  </em>
  , which came out in 2022, and like its predecessor, players will have a trio of starter Pokemon from different generations.
 </p>
 <p>
  Chikorita and Totodile were introduced in Gen 2 and, along with Cyndaquil, are the first starters from Johto. Tepig, meanwhile, is one of the Gen 5 Pokemon and forms
  <em>
   Pokemon Black and White
  </em>
  's starter trio with Snivy and Oshawott. Along with trainers, Chikorita, Totodile, and Tepig will experience new adventures in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  and explore the city of Lumiose. Players will also see the return of the Mega Evolutions, including some already known and some never seen before. A new rumor is circulating, giving players an idea of what to expect from the Mega forms of the starter trio.
 </p>
 <p>
  Centro Leaks shared details about the Mega Evolutions of Meganium, Feraligatr, and Emboar on Twitter. According to them, Mega Meganium will have four flowers around its neck in different colors, and its antennae will be larger than usual. Its legs will have a different design from the Johto monster's regular form, and its body is more robust. For Mega Emboar, the leak teases a design similar to that of a soldier from ancient China, with larger flames around its head and a more complex appearance. Its head has a decorative black ornament, and it carries a spear made completely of fire.
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan art has given various ideas for Mega Feraligatr, but according to the leak, it will have a red extension starting at the base of its neck that can be used to protect the actual head. It will also develop three red spikes on its arm and back.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-legends-z-a-leak-details-meganium-feraligatr-and-emboar-mega-evolutions">
  Pokemon Legends: Z-A Leak Details Meganium, Feraligatr, and Emboar Mega Evolutions
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1368593030" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1368593030" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1368593030" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1368593030" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1368593030-img" id="article-gallery-1-1368593030">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1368593030" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1621246288">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The leak also revealed the type of each Mega Evolution and some changes that will reportedly happen. Mega Meganium will be a Grass/Fairy-type, unlike its regular form, a pure Grass-type Pokemon. Feraligatr, meanwhile, will no longer be a Water-type but a Water/Dragon-type when it Mega Evolves. The only one that won't see any changes will be Emboar, which in its regular version and Mega evolved form will be a Fire/Fighter type.
 </p>
 <p>
  As usual, leaks should be treated with caution until an official announcement is made by the developers. In the meantime, this new claim joins other leaks that have shed light on different aspects of the game, such as that there may be no new pocket monsters and the potential list of new Mega Evolutions available in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed Shadows Has a Clear and Dominant Theme</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/assassins-creed-shadows-story-theme-found-family/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_0">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     This article contains spoilers for
     <em>
      Assassin's Creed Shadows
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While
  <strong>
   <em>
    Assassin's Creed Shadows
   </em>
  </strong>
  may deliver a brand-new adventure set within 16th-century Japan, there are also many story beats that some may find familiar. For starters, the entire tale is still built around taking out the Templars, which has been a staple of this franchise forever. On top of that, players will spend much of their time rebuilding the Brotherhood and recruiting allies to save Japan. But at its core, the main theme of the entire story in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  may be the most familiar of all: found family.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The theme of found family has become an incredibly popular story to tell over the years, with so many different titles using it as a backdrop.
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  is no stranger to it either, with
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  seemingly being built around it. The characters within the story spend much of their time finding their place, building new unbreakable bonds, and doing all they can to protect those around them. Even though that set-up may be familiar, it makes for an enthralling adventure nonetheless.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="assassin-39-s-creed-shadows-is-built-around-found-family">
  Assassin's Creed Shadows is Built Around Found Family
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-80022803" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-80022803" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-80022803" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-80022803" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-80022803-img" id="article-gallery-1-80022803">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-80022803" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-333014826">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="naoe-39-s-beginning-is-all-about-finding-a-new-family">
  Naoe's Beginning is All About Finding a New Family
 </h3>
 <p>
  From the very beginning of
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , the theme of found family is pretty evident. After Oda Nobunaga takes out the Iga, kills Nagato, and leaves Naoe for dead, she is saved by a mysterious man named Sorin and a child named Junjiro. Although distrustful at first, as Naoe heals from her injuries, she grows to trust them and care for them. They not only build strong relationships, but they also play a vital role in helping her to rebuild the Brotherhood that has been destroyed.
 </p>
 <p>
  Throughout her adventure, Naoe meets even more characters that she grows to trust and vows to protect. However, none are closer to her than the child Junjiro, whom she treats as if he is truly a part of her family. She will seemingly do anything for him, and even though she was responsible for the death of his father, Junjiro will also seemingly do anything for her. That story drives much of their interactions and Naoe's adventure through Japan, which makes for an incredibly intriguing and heartfelt tale.
 </p>
 <h3 id="naoe-and-yasuke-must-also-learn-to-work-together">
  Naoe and Yasuke Must Also Learn to Work Together
 </h3>
 <p>
  Naoe is not only growing closer to and vowing to protect all sorts of NPCs throughout her journey, but her and dual protagonist, Yasuke, are also built around the theme of found family. When they first meet, they are on completely opposite sides of the conflict. Yasuke is working for Oda Nobunaga and is responsible for the death of one of the few remaining Japanese assassins, while Naoe is seeking revenge against Nobunaga for her father's death. While it seems like they will be at odds for the majority of the story, they too forge a powerful bond as their adventure continues.
 </p>
 <p>
  With a little help from Junjiro, Naoe chooses not to kill Yasuke and Yasuke vows to assist her in her quest. The two of them team up to rid the world of the Shinbakufu, and as they do, they become inseparable allies. They constantly have each other's backs, they go out of their way to assist each other, and they both work together to rebuild what was lost. While Naoe may not grow as close to Yasuke as she does to those that saved her, this story still leans heavily on that found family theme.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both Naoe and Yasuke's stories seem to be built around the concept of found family, with both of them spending a lot of time doing whatever they can for those that they call allies. Because players get to see said story from both perspectives, it makes for a very intriguing tale, the likes of which
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  has not really explored before. And since this is only the start of
  <em>
   Shadows
  </em>
  ' lifespan, there is no telling where it will go from here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Designs Their Own Take on Mega Starmie</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-legends-z-a-mega-starmie-fan-art/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A fan shares Mega Starmie art inspired by leaked details from Pokemon Legends: Z-A.
     </li>
     <li>
      The artist created a detailed concept of Mega Starmie with longer appendages.
     </li>
     <li>
      The community reception of the fan art has been positive, sparking hope that the potential in-game design will turn out well.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With the release of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Legends: Z-A
   </em>
  </strong>
  coming in 2025, one fan created their version of a Mega Starmie, sharing the result online. While not all the details about
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  have been revealed, fans know the game will feature Mega evolutions. As a result, many gamers have been inspired to create artwork imagining what various Pokemon could look like in this form, creating impressive designs.
 </p>
 <p>
  While not officially confirmed, recent
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  leaks claimed to reveal the list of Pokemon receiving Mega evolutions. Among the names was Starmie, the Gen 1 evolution of Staryu. Additional leaks have described what the Mega evolution for the starfish Pokemon might look like, noting that it will be larger and feature long legs. This design feature will supposedly allow the Pokemon to “run around.” While leaks should be taken with a grain of salt, one fan has used this description to make their own version of a potential Mega evolution.
 </p>
 <p>
  Posted on Reddit, the fan art was created by HertzBurst and provided an eye-catching version of a Mega Evolution for Starmie. Specifically, the design added another layer to Starmie, including more appendages and making the body look larger. HertzBurst also incorporated the leaked information about the longer legs into their custom artwork. As seen in the images, the bottom two appendages of the Pokemon were longer, which would allow the creature to potentially run. Interestingly, the artist shared a mockup, revealing what the design could look like in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  ’s Kalos region.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fan-39-s-mega-evolution-design-for-starmie-based-on-leaked-details">
  Pokemon Fan's Mega Evolution Design for Starmie Based on Leaked Details
 </h2>
 <p>
  This Mega evolution artwork for Starmie has caught the attention of some fans on the game’s subreddit. With the post receiving many upvotes, users commented that HertzBurst’s design gave them hope that the leaked description could turn out well in the game. According to the artist, the goal was to make the long-legged Starmie look as natural as possible. Fortunately, many Reddit users think they accomplished this in the artwork.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is worth pointing out that HertzBurst is a prolific
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan artist, sharing much of their work on Reddit. While they have created all sorts of designs based on the series, including Paradox forms inspired by
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  , they have recently taken an interest in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . For example, the artist previously imagined what Mega Victreebel could look like, among others.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1602834123" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1602834123" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1602834123" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1602834123" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1602834123-img" id="article-gallery-1-1602834123">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1602834123" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-783604461">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  looks to be taking the franchise in an exciting direction in terms of gameplay, it has also opened the floodgates for more fan art. As the game gets closer to its release in 2025, it will be interesting to see what other Mega evolution concepts are shared by the community.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
