<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Slender: The Arrival VR - Official Release Date Announcement Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/slender-the-arrival-vr-official-release-date-announcement-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Slender: The Arrival is about to become a whole lot more immersive in virtual reality. Watch the official release date announcement trailer for Slender: The Arrival VR here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Legends: Z-A Mega Evolutions Teased by Leaker</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-legends-za-how-many-new-mega-evolutions-number-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon Legends: Z-A will reportedly have 27 new Mega Evolutions.
     </li>
     <li>
      Game Freak has so far confirmed over a dozen returning Mega Evolutions for Pokemon Legends: Z-A.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Legends: Z-A
   </em>
  </strong>
  will feature 27 new Mega Evolutions, a well-known Nintendo leaker has said. The claim suggests that Game Freak is still holding off on revealing quite a few
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  Mega Evolutions.
 </p>
 <p>
  Game Freak and The Pokemon Company originally announced
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  in February 2024. A year later, the RPG was treated to its first-ever gameplay trailer, which premiered during Pokemon Day 2025. While the game has been slated for a 2025 launch since its reveal, no release date has yet been given.
 </p>
 <p>
  Long-time Nintendo leaker Pyoro has recently shared one new alleged detail about the upcoming title, suggesting that the game will have 27 new Mega Evolutions. Initially cryptic, the leaker hinted that the "upper left corner" of a PC keyboard reveals the total number of new Mega Evolutions in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . Several social media users interpreted this as 27—the ASCII code for the Escape key—after which Pyoro flat-out confirmed the number as "real."
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-legends-z-a-has-already-confirmed-many-returning-mega-evolutions">
  Pokemon Legends: Z-A Has Already Confirmed Many Returning Mega Evolutions
 </h2>
 <p>
  Game Freak has so far revealed over a dozen returning Mega Evolutions that will be present in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . Charizard and Pidgeot are both on the list of the game's confirmed Megas, as are Kangaskhan, Pinsir, and Gyarados. Ditto for Aerodactyl, Ampharos, Steelix, Heracross​​​​​​​, and Houndoom. Tyranitar​​​​​​​ and Gardevoir​​​​​​​ will also have Mega Evolutions in the upcoming game, as will Sableye, Altaria​​​​​​​, and Absol​​​. Salamence, Lucario, and Gallade are part of this group as well.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-51968444" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-51968444" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-51968444" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-51968444" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-51968444-img" id="article-gallery-1-51968444">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-51968444" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1022163060">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In terms of new forms, one recent leak claimed that
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  will introduce a Mega Evolution of Victreebel, the iconic Gen 1 pitcher plant Pokemon. Prior leaks also hinted at Mega Aegislash and Mega Delfox being part of the package, together with the Mega variants of Greninja, Chesnaught, and Excadrill. Zygarde and Zeraora are also rumored to be getting the Mega treatment in the upcoming game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Looking at the slightly bigger picture, the claim that
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  will have 27 new Mega Evolutions aligns with the series' track record. The first
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends
  </em>
  game,
  <em>
   Arceus
  </em>
  , introduced around 20 new creature designs—ranging from regional variants to brand-new Pokemon—while past expansions of Mega Evolutions also came in batches of around 20. Therefore, 27 new Mega Evolutions in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  wouldn’t be out of step with Game Freak’s usual approach. More news about the upcoming
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  spin-off should materialize before long, assuming that the game is still on course to hit its 2025 release window.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed Shadows: How To Equip Engravings On Gear</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/assassins-creed-shadows-equip-engravings-perks-weapons-armor-equipment/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Assassin's Creed Shadows
   </strong>
  </em>
  has a helpful gear upgrade system that allows players to keep using their favorite piece of equipment without replacing it with higher-level loot. Another component of this upgrade system is engravings, which lets players pick and choose various perks that work best with their overall build. The game doesn't really tell you how to engrave weapons or armor from the get-go, so here's everything you need to know about this system.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-equip-engravings-on-gear-in-assassin-39-s-creed-shadows">
  How to Equip Engravings on Gear in Assassin's Creed Shadows
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-858140022" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-858140022" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-858140022" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-858140022" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-858140022-img" id="article-gallery-1-858140022">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-858140022" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2038771892">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players can apply engravings on their weapons and equipment
  <strong>
   through Heiji the Blacksmith
  </strong>
  in the hideout in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  . However, this feature isn't available at the start, as you'll need to invest some wood and other building materials towards
  <strong>
   upgrading the forge to at least level 2
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you've upgraded the forge, talk to Heiji, and you'll enter the familiar upgrading menu. However, there will be a new second tab on top that will take players to
  <strong>
   the Engrave menu
  </strong>
  . Here's how you can apply engravings to a piece of gear.
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Choose the category of equipment you want to engrave, i.e. Katana, Tanto, Kusarigama, Headgear, Light Armor, and Trinket.
  </li>
  <li>
   Now, select a specific weapon or equipment from the category.
  </li>
  <li>
   Now, players will need to browse a list of available perks and add them to the weapon.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <p>
  Now, the equipment will have two perks, making it even more powerful in combat.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     To add legendary engravings to equipment, players will need to
     <strong>
      upgrade the Forge to level 3
     </strong>
     . This will also allow players to store the special perks of any legendary gear acquired and apply them to another legendary piece. So, it's possible for a gear piece to have two legendary perks.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="where-to-find-the-missing-engravings-perks">
  Where to Find the Missing Engravings (Perks)
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Clues to Find Missing perks in Assassin's Creed Shadows" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/clues-to-find-missing-perks-in-assassin-s-creed-shadows.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you've seen the list of perks that can be engraved on gear, you may have noticed
  <strong>
   a lot of perks that are missing or locked
  </strong>
  . These are the perks that you haven't come across yet and will need to find them before you can use them to engrave equipment.
 </p>
 <p>
  However,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  does not keep players in the dark when it comes to the location of said perks. Under the locked indication, players can
  <strong>
   check out the location clue for individual perks
  </strong>
  . Using the clue, players can track down the perk and add it to their engravings collection.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Perks aren't limited-use items and can be applied, and re-applied to weapons as the players see fit (by paying the engravings fee).
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Confirms Banner Characters for Phase 1 of Version 5.5</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-banner-characters-phase-1-version-5-5/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Genshin Impact's Version 5.5 will feature two new characters: Varesa and Iansan.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Phase 1 banner characters include Varesa, Xianyun, Iansan, Chevreuse, and Gaming.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans are excited about the diverse four-star lineup, particularly Chevreuse, a well-loved character.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  has officially revealed all the banner characters that will appear in the first phase of the upcoming Version 5.5.
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  updates are always divided into two parts, each offering a different set of limited characters for approximately three weeks.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's Special Program previously confirmed that the next update will feature two new characters, Varesa and Iansan. Varesa is the only new five-star character, which means the update will feature three rerun characters, and HoYoverse has already confirmed who they are.
 </p>
 <p>
  Each banner cycle features two five-star characters with a shared lineup of three four-star units.
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's official social media accounts have finally revealed which four-star characters will appear on the banner. According to their recent post, Phase 1 of
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  Version 5.5 will feature Iansan, Chevreuse, and Gaming. The two limited five-star characters will be Varesa and Xianyun. HoYoverse likely paired these two characters because both of their kits revolve around a special type of attack, the Plunging Attack. To perform Plunging Attacks, players only need to use the attack button while mid-air, causing their character to launch into the ground and deal AoE damage.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-version-5-5-phase-1-banner-characters-revealed">
  Genshin Impact Version 5.5: Phase 1 Banner Characters Revealed
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Varesa (five-star Electro catalyst user)
  </li>
  <li>
   Xianyun (five-star Anemo catalyst user)
  </li>
  <li>
   Iansan (four-star Electro polearm user)
  </li>
  <li>
   Chevreuse (four-star Pyro polearm user)
  </li>
  <li>
   Gaming (four-star Pyro claymore user)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Many fans are excited about the announcement, claiming this will be one of the best banners in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  ’s history in terms of its four-star lineup. Some comments pointed out that they hesitated to pull for Varesa, but the four-star selection has convinced them to commit to this banner. One of the main reasons for the community’s excitement is that the oldest character on the banner, Chevreuse, was released on January 9, 2024.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-237596976" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-237596976" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-237596976" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-237596976" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-237596976-img" id="article-gallery-1-237596976">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-237596976" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-635871492">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This means it is highly unlikely that most players have already maxed out the constellations for these characters, so pulling for them will not result in essentially useless copies. The previous livestream event confirmed that Varesa will be a new five-star DPS character in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . Despite being her teacher, Iansan has a lower rarity and is expected to be a powerful Electro polearm support. The five-star rerun character, Xianyun, is also an off-field support who uses Anemo elemental powers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both Gaming and Chevreuse are fan-favorite four-star characters due to their unique gameplay. Gaming is an off-field support who also relies on Plunging Attacks, making him a perfect pairing for Xianyun. Chevreuse is best used in Pyro and Electro team compositions in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  due to her ability to shred these specific elemental resistances.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why One Baldur's Gate 3 Death Still Hits Hard Over a Year Later</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-zevlor-death-tragic-sad/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  is filled with choices that shape the world and the fates of its characters. Among these, the story of Zevlor stands out as particularly devastating. A Tiefling Paladin and former Hellrider of Elturel, Zevlor's journey is one of resilience, sacrifice, and the unbearable weight of failure. Despite his efforts to protect his people, the tragic consequences of his entanglement with the Absolute make his death one of the game's most emotionally charged moments.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Zevlor’s arc in
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  is not only a reflection of the challenges that refugees face in a world that rejects them, but also a pointed commentary on manipulation and the corrupting nature of power. Even those with unwavering convictions are vulnerable when their hope is weaponized against them. Through Zevlor, Larian Studios effectively explores how trauma and desperation can push even the most righteous to their breaking point.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3-highlights-consequences-of-leadership">
  Baldur's Gate 3 Highlights Consequences of Leadership
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1117449993" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1117449993" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1117449993" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1117449993" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1117449993-img" id="article-gallery-1-1117449993">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1117449993" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-176369602">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the heart of Zevlor's tragedy is the burden of leadership. As the leader of a displaced people, Zevlor's decisions are shaped by the constant pressure to ensure their survival. His past as a Hellrider further complicates this role. Once sworn to protect Elturel, he was forced to watch the city descend into Avernus. The guilt of surviving when so many others perished haunts him, driving his determination to keep the Tieflings safe at any cost.
 </p>
 <p>
  When the Absolute's influence seeps into the lives of those around him, Zevlor becomes a victim of its manipulative grasp. His enthrallment is not a product of malice or weakness but of layered psychological trauma. The narrative makes it clear that no one is immune to the seductive promise of relief from suffering. Despite the player's best efforts, Zevlor’s death may still occur — a grim reminder of how even the most heroic figures can fall.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Hellriders, once a symbol of Zevlor's proud past, become a painful reminder of what he has lost. Even in a scenario where he survives, the burden of his choices lingers. Yet, if he dies, it’s not simply the loss of a leader but the extinguishing of a spirit that once stood tall against unimaginable odds.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-emotional-impact-of-zevlor-39-s-fate-in-baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  The Emotional Impact of Zevlor's Fate in Baldur's Gate 3
 </h3>
 <p>
  Zevlor’s death resonates deeply because it is a culmination of failed attempts at redemption. If the player cannot intervene in time, he may die at the hands of Orin the Red, sacrificed in a twisted display of power. This outcome is particularly brutal given Zevlor’s constant struggle to maintain his moral compass. The game's refusal to offer a purely victorious path reinforces the weight of its choices, ensuring that every loss is felt.
 </p>
 <p>
  The survivors’ reactions to Zevlor’s death further emphasize the tragedy. Asharak or Cerys may step into the role of leader, but the void left by Zevlor is palpable. His death serves as a painful acknowledgment that no matter how noble one’s intentions, the consequences of past failures often echo long after. The lack of complete resolution for his character adds to the realism of
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  ’s storytelling, underscoring that closure is not always attainable.
 </p>
 <p>
  Zevlor's legacy is also reflected in the shifting dynamics of the Tiefling refugees. While Asharak may lead with a more hardened resolve, and Cerys provides a gentler form of guidance, neither can truly replace Zevlor’s presence. For players, this loss is particularly poignant, as it’s a reminder that heroism is not always enough to shield others from harm.
 </p>
 <h3 id="larian-studios-rsquo-approach-to-narrative-and-morality">
  Larian Studios’ Approach to Narrative and Morality
 </h3>
 <p>
  Larian Studios has crafted
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  with a commitment to morally complex storytelling. Zevlor’s downfall is not merely a plot device, but a reflection of the game’s central themes. His story forces players to confront the reality that good intentions can still lead to devastating outcomes. Through the lens of player agency, the developers highlight the unpredictability of leadership and the emotional toll it takes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Moreover, the community’s divided response to Zevlor's actions reveals another layer of the game's impact. While some condemn his perceived failures, others empathize with his impossible circumstances. The absence of a clear moral judgment from the game encourages players to grapple with their own interpretations, a hallmark of Larian’s narrative design.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s also worth noting how the game’s design intentionally withholds the full scope of the Absolute’s manipulation from many of the NPCs. Unlike the player, who gains an intimate understanding of the cult’s influence, Zevlor and others are left without the same clarity. This deliberate narrative choice emphasizes how easily fear and desperation can cloud judgment. For players, it serves as a humbling reminder that those who fall victim to manipulation are not inherently weak — they are often just human.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the end, Zevlor’s fate is a reminder that
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  is not a game about winning or losing. It is about the people players meet, the choices they make, and the stories they carry with them. Through Zevlor, the game captures the devastating truth that even the most valiant efforts may not be enough — and that is what makes his potential death so profoundly tragic.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
