<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Female Characters From Supermassive Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/supermassive-games-best-female-characters/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Female characters stand out for their backgrounds, abilities, and personalities in Supermassive games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Luger from Killzone proves strength after tragic events in her life.
     </li>
     <li>
      Emily from Until Dawn is iconic, showcasing fantastic writing and voice performance.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Supermassive Games has become best known for titles such as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Until Dawn
   </em>
  </strong>
  and the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dark Pictures Anthology
   </em>
  </strong>
  , thrusting a troupe of unsuspecting characters into situations of absolute torture and unrelenting horror, but there are plenty of other games under their belt diverging into other genres, drawing on completely disparate characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  In whichever Supermassive game players look, there are going to be characters that stand out, whether it is due to their background, their ability, or their personality, all of which shine through interactions, dialogue, and gameplay segments. From their eclectic catalog, here are the best female characters of all.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Warning! Spoilers Ahead!
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fliss-man-of-medan">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Fliss (Man Of Medan)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="cooler-heads-will-always-prevail">
  Cooler Heads Will Always Prevail
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1084944402" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1084944402" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1084944402" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1084944402" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1084944402-img" id="article-gallery-1-1084944402">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1084944402" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-215229995">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Man of Medan
   </em>
  </strong>
  was the debut game in the
  <em>
   Dark Pictures Anthology
   <strong>
   </strong>
  </em>
  starting players off on a sea-faring adventure that soon becomes a nightmare as the group finds themselves trapped on a ghost ship with the pirates that kidnapped them, and horrific entities that stalk them throughout the ship. There are hints dropped throughout the game that what they see is not quite real, as the gold aboard the ship isn't treasure but a powerful hallucinogenic weapon.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the playable characters and the captain of the ship, Fliss, remained the more pragmatic member of the group. Though she may seem like a stick in the mud with her constant warnings, if they were heeded, the group might not have ended up in such a predicament. Some of her sections remain the best in the game, such as the iconic ballroom.
 </p>
 <h2 id="shadow-marshal-luger-killzone">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Shadow Marshal Luger (Killzone)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-heroic-and-independent-woman-who-holds-her-own">
  A Heroic And Independent Woman Who Holds Her Own
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1519822233" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1519822233" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1519822233" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1519822233" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1519822233-img" id="article-gallery-2-1519822233">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1519822233" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-754772051">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though the majority of the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Killzone
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise was mostly created by Guerilla Games, Supermassive has also delved into the world of FPS, responsible for handling the development of the PS3 version of the first game. Set in a post-nuclear war world in the not-so-distant future, humanity has made efforts to colonize planets after much of the Earth has become unsuited for human habitation.
 </p>
 <p>
  Luger was one of the Shadow Marshals who valiantly defended Vekta against Helghast, earning no medals for her efforts. But given the reason for her joining the militia efforts, Luger isn't in it to earn herself glory and attention. Following the murder of her parents right before her eyes, Luger was left traumatized but became all the stronger for it. She jumped at the chance to become a Shadow Marshal and proved it was where she belonged. She doesn't need or want protection and proves it time and time again.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="emily-davis-until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Emily Davis (Until Dawn)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="responsible-for-one-of-the-most-quotable-lines-in-the-game">
  Responsible For One Of The Most Quotable Lines In The Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1077408518" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1077408518" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1077408518" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1077408518" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1077408518-img" id="article-gallery-3-1077408518">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1077408518" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1114118776">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A group of teens plays a mean-spirited prank on Hannah Washington, a girl with an unfortunate crush on Emily's boyfriend. The prank leads to her running away embarrassed, and her twin sister Beth following after. The two run into danger and fall to their deaths. The group of friends gather back in the mountain lodge one year later, falling victim to their brothers' pranks, and more, as the mountains are home to dangerous monsters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Emily is one of the most to blame for the prank, and she showed little remorse for her actions even as Hannah fled into the freezing snow with little more than jeans and a shirt on. Her mean streak is present throughout the game, but she is one of those characters people love to hate. She was not designed to be pleasant like Samantha, and as such, showcased fantastic writing and voice performance. But the iconic line "Understand the palm of my hand, b****", delivered with a smack to Ashley's face, was an utterly excellent one that fans still quote, even years after the game's original release.
 </p>
 <h2 id="six-little-nightmares-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Six (Little Nightmares 2)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="once-a-playable-character-and-now-a-companion">
  Once A Playable Character, And Now A Companion
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1069096711" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1069096711" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1069096711" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1069096711" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1069096711-img" id="article-gallery-4-1069096711">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1069096711" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-276832939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Supermassive took it upon themselves to develop the enhanced edition of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Little Nightmares 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , a follow-up to the original survival horror game that saw players control a tiny protagonist exploring the huge sea vessel called the Maw while contending with the massive dangers that threatened them.
  <em>
   Little Nightmares 2
  </em>
  introduced a new playable character, Mono, but was accompanied by Six from the first game, who was instrumental in aiding them to explore and survive their surroundings.
 </p>
 <p>
  Six's indispensable help with puzzles, and the fact she is a legacy character, helped players bond with her throughout
  <em>
   Little Nightmares 2
  </em>
  , which only made her betrayal, and fate at the end of the game all the sadder. In a twist no one could have seen coming, Six lets Mono drop from a fall and becomes a dangerous long-limbed monstrosity. All of this was still not enough to make Six a hated character, and instead, she remains one of the greatest in Supermassive's library.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="linda-the-casting-of-frank-stone">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Linda (The Casting Of Frank Stone)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-level-headed-and-practical-movie-maker">
  A Level-Headed and Practical Movie Maker
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1751958261" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1751958261" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1751958261" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1751958261" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1751958261-img" id="article-gallery-5-1751958261">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1751958261" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-35009667">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The crossover between Behaviour's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dead by Daylight
   </em>
  </strong>
  universe and Supermassive Games was an unexpected one, resulting in the development of
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Casting of Frank Stone
   </em>
  </strong>
  . It followed the formula fans were familiar with, containing a group of playable characters that change each chapter, and most of the gameplay comprised of QTEs that can result in a character's gruesome death following failure. But it was set in the
  <em>
   DbD
  </em>
  world, making use of its rich lore, and sprinkled with a healthy dose of easter eggs for devoted fans to seek out and collect.
 </p>
 <p>
  Among the cast was Linda, who appears in both timelines. Once an amateur filmmaker, she rose to the heights of horror fame, her artistic eye earning her many fans. In the 80s, she is more reserved and not as outgoing as her fellow filmmakers, but comes out of her shell in her old age, and even shows compassion toward characters such as Madi. One thing is a constant for Linda, and that's her protective nature, and her dedication to the craft, which are both admirable traits.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kate-wilder-the-devil-in-me">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Kate Wilder (The Devil In Me)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-headstrong-and-independent-character">
  A Headstrong And Independent Character
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-2066278137" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-2066278137" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-2066278137" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-2066278137" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-2066278137-img" id="article-gallery-6-2066278137">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-2066278137" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1844113552">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Season 1 finale in
  <em>
   The Dark Pictures Anthology
  </em>
  involved the story of the infamous real-life killer H.H. Holmes, as his aptly named Murder Castle. A team of paranormal investigators who are struggling to keep their show on air takes up an offer from a mysterious man that seems too good to be true, and it turns out it is. Their host vanishes, and the group finds themselves embroiled in the dangerous Murder Castle, full of deadly traps and a sinister figure.
 </p>
 <p>
  The poster child of this game was Kate Wilder, modeled and played by actress and singer Jessie Buckley. She is one of the more outspoken members of the group and is guaranteed to immediately draw attention. Her penchant to speak openly and honestly may make her seem abrasive, but it is one of her most shining qualities, even if it does create some friction with other characters. But this only adds to the drama, intrigue, and excitement in
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Devil in Me
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="laura-kearney-the-quarry">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Laura Kearney (The Quarry)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-more-courageous-counselors">
  One Of The More Courageous Counselors
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1963743541" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1963743541" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1963743541" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1963743541" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1963743541-img" id="article-gallery-7-1963743541">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1963743541" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-276093732">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The night before Hackett Quarry is open for business, Laura and Max decide to drive down early to feel out the place. They are stopped on the way by a police officer, who warns them away and directs them to a nearby motel to stay for the night. Of course, the adventurous Laura isn't going to take his advice, and the pair continue to the summer camp, and soon find out why they were told to stay away.
 </p>
 <p>
  Normally, the first two playable characters die at the start of the game, but the pair survives, and Laura ends up as one of the more heroic characters of the bunch. Her courage is already displayed at the beginning of the game when she explores the surrounding area alone after hearing some strange noises, but it becomes even more apparent when she stands up to the Hackett family and fights not only for her survival but the survival of the other counselors.
 </p>
 <h2 id="samantha-giddings-until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Samantha Giddings (Until Dawn)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-underrated-final-girl">
  An Underrated Final Girl
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1214400054" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1214400054" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1214400054" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1214400054" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1214400054-img" id="article-gallery-8-1214400054">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1214400054" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-773013687">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Even though there are multiple women in Supermassive's most famous game, it is Samantha who takes on the role of final girl, exhibiting many of the traits found in these heroic characters in movies. Smart, resourceful, and compassionate, she is everything a final girl should be, and it is about time she is recognized as such.
 </p>
 <p>
  Not a member of the harsh prank that led to Hannah and Beth's deaths, Sam still falls victim to Josh's machinations, pursued and attacked by the Masked Killer that is just him in disguise. It is during these moments that players see Sam's grit and her resolve to survive. These are just a few of the traits that make Samantha the most likeable character not only from
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  , but the entirety of Supermassive's library.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Strategy Games On Xbox Game Pass (February 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-game-pass-best-strategy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Best Xbox Game Pass Strategy Games
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Aliens: Dark Descent
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Age Of Empires 4: Anniversary Edition
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Age of Mythology: Retold
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Halo Wars
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Kunitsu-Gami: Path of the Goddess
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Wartales
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Metal Slug Tactics
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Dungeons 4
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Humankind
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Mount &amp; Blade 2: Bannerlord
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Slay The Spire
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Wildfrost
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Stellaris
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Gears Tactics
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Crusader Kings 3
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Minecraft Legends
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Best PC Game Pass Strategy Games
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        StarCraft Remastered &amp; StarCraft 2
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Frostpunk 2
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Against The Storm
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Rise Of Nations: Extended Edition
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Dungeon Keeper 2
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Command &amp; Conquer Remastered Collection
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Strategy Games That Should Be Coming To Game Pass
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Strategy games
  </strong>
  were once practically non-existent in the console market, save for notable exceptions and ill-fated attempts (such as
  <em>
   Starcraft’s
  </em>
  remarkably awkward landing on the Nintendo 64). However, over the years, several titles have emerged to deliver their micro-management goodness to living room accessible formats — particularly when it comes to the Xbox line of consoles.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  If someone is looking to channel their inner armchair general, then
  <strong>
   Xbox
  </strong>
  <strong>
   Game Pass
  </strong>
  has several titles that are right up their alley. Whether directing the nuanced machinations of a galaxy-spanning empire is their bag, or they'd prefer just telling wacky invertebrates when to sling bombs at one another, Game Pass has got a strategy game for them.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Although technically belonging to a different genre, tactical games will be considered since they share similarities to strategy games.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated February 3, 2025 by Mark Sammut:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   As not too many great strategy games have been added to Game Pass over the last few weeks, a section dedicated to upcoming projects has been added. This part focuses on titles that should/could debut in March 2025.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="aliens-dark-descent">
  Aliens: Dark Descent
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-stressful-tactics-game-that-is-perfect-for-fans-of-the-source-material">
  A Stressful Tactics Game That Is Perfect For Fans Of The Source Material
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1845406403" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1845406403" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1845406403" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1845406403" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1845406403-img" id="article-gallery-1-1845406403">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1845406403" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-205215712">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Alien
  </em>
  is no stranger to video games, most of which tend to go down the FPS or horror route. While real-time tactics might not seem like the most obvious direction,
  <em>
   Aliens: Dark Descent
  </em>
  does a surprisingly good job of capturing the classic movies' tension, particularly the 1986 sequel. Taking inspiration from
  <em>
   XCOM
  </em>
  , Tindalos put together a project that streamlines RTS mechanics while incorporating some horror elements like the use of a stress meter that gradually causes the colonial marines to develop psychological trauma during missions. Like
  <em>
   XCOM
  </em>
  , permadeath is part of the equation, so there is always a risk that a mission will go wrong and result in the death of valuable squad members.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dark Descent
  </em>
  does not necessarily explore too many novel concepts, but it blends a myriad of well-worn ideas to create an enjoyable whole that should hit the mark with RTS fans who do not care about
  <em>
   Aliens
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Aliens
  </em>
  fans who are not familiar with the tactics genre. While quite punishing, the gameplay is somewhat simplified as players control the full squad rather than individual marines, removing some of the more minute control that tends to be a pretty big part of the genre's releases.
 </p>
 <h2 id="age-of-empires-4-anniversary-edition">
  Age Of Empires 4: Anniversary Edition
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-safe-but-solid-evolution-of-a-strategy-standard">
  A Safe But Solid Evolution Of A Strategy Standard
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1516552763" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1516552763" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1516552763" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1516552763" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1516552763-img" id="article-gallery-2-1516552763">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1516552763" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1902888217">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After spending more than a year as a PC exclusive,
  <em>
   Age of Empires 4
  </em>
  made its way to Xbox consoles in August 2023. Relic and World's Edge's project garnered a primarily positive reception upon launch, with many regarding it as a safe but polished continuation of arguably the most beloved and popular RTS franchise of all time. Launching with four campaigns and eight civilizations (although two more were added later on),
  <em>
   AoE 4
  </em>
  offers a great deal of content for solo players, along with containing an active and robust multiplayer scene.
 </p>
 <p>
  Xbox owners have two
  <em>
   Age of Empires
  </em>
  at their disposal, while PC Game Pass subscribers can play through the entire series thanks to the inclusion of the original trilogy's definitive edition. All four games are fantastic by most metrics, and an argument could certainly be made that
  <em>
   AoE 2
  </em>
  is the best RTS game of all time. However, newcomers should start with
  <em>
   AoE 4
  </em>
  , especially if they plan to try their hand at multiplayer.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_19">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Age of Empires 2: Definitive Edition
     </em>
     is also on Xbox Game Pass.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="age-of-mythology-retold">
  Age of Mythology: Retold
 </h2>
 <h3 id="now-for-a-mythological-twist">
  Now, For A Mythological Twist
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-885983574" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-885983574" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-885983574" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-885983574" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-885983574-img" id="article-gallery-3-885983574">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-885983574" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-496119771">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  An
  <em>
   Age of Empires
  </em>
  spin-off,
  <em>
   Age of Mythology
  </em>
  takes the core gameplay loop of the main series and adds gods to the mix, blending staple RTS realism with devastating enemy-destroying attacks. Although a relative footnote in
  <em>
   AoE
  </em>
  's legacy, the 2002 original is considered a cult classic in its own right, and the lack of a sequel was always disappointing. Fortunately, in 2024,
  <em>
   Age of Mythology
  </em>
  received a much-needed facelift in the form of
  <em>
   Retold
  </em>
  , an update that walks the line between remaster and remake.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   AoM: Retold
  </em>
  allows players to pick from four pantheons, along with an array of deities associated with each. They can then work their way through a fairly long single-player campaign that highlights the many differences of each civilization, all of which come with unique units and specializations.
  <em>
   Retold
  </em>
  does an admirable job of preserving the original version's charm while incorporating enough modern touches to ensure the gameplay does not feel too archaic.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Age of Empires 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   4
  </em>
  are arguably better-rounded games,
  <em>
   Age of Mythology: Retold
  </em>
  is a charming side quest that has enough fresh ideas to feel like its own entity rather than just a reskin.
 </p>
 <h2 id="halo-wars">
  Halo Wars
 </h2>
 <h3 id="strategy-game-made-for-consoles">
  Strategy Game Made For Consoles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-841922732" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-841922732" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-841922732" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-841922732" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-841922732-img" id="article-gallery-4-841922732">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-841922732" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1156891301">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though many people associate the
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  name with the mainline entries that are straightforward FPS titles,
  <em>
   Halo Wars
  </em>
  takes the series in a new direction in terms of genre. Players are treated to grand-scale skirmishes involving factions from the
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  universe in a highly approachable RTS title. Since the game was made specifically for the Xbox 360, it features one of the most comfortable controller configurations for an RTS on a console. The story takes place before the events of the first
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  game, detailing what happened to the UNSC crew of the Spirit of Fire.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Halo Wars 2
  </em>
  is also available on Xbox Game Pass and serves as a fine continuation of its predecessor. In some ways, the sequel is superior to the first game, although it is certainly designed with non-RTS fans in mind. Therefore, people who want to spend more time in this universe but are reluctant to jump into a genre they are not familiar with can rest easy in knowing that
  <em>
   Halo Wars 2
  </em>
  is for them.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kunitsu-gami-path-of-the-goddess">
  Kunitsu-Gami: Path of the Goddess
 </h2>
 <h3 id="capcom-39-s-creative-blend-of-action-amp-strategy">
  Capcom's Creative Blend Of Action &amp; Strategy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1779942482" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1779942482" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1779942482" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1779942482" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1779942482-img" id="article-gallery-5-1779942482">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1779942482" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-818567411">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A new Capcom IP is always a cause for celebration, particularly one as unique as
  <em>
   Kunitsu-Gami: Path of the Goddess
  </em>
  . Before its debut, the project was somewhat hard to pin down in terms of genre, seemingly blending strategy, hack and slash combat, and village management; in practice, the game mostly fits these categories, although it is best described as a real-time strategy tower defense title. Regardless,
  <em>
   Kunitsu-Gami
  </em>
  has a lot to offer for different audiences.
 </p>
 <p>
  Before diving into the strategy component, let's give a quick rundown of the campaign's structure. Charged with protecting the divine maiden as she purges evil spirits from a mountain, Soh spends his days saving villagers and exploring, all in preparation for a nightly onslaught. During the latter, Soh becomes something of an army leader in charge of placing the saved villagers as strategic points to ensure the maiden's safety. The "soldiers" have roles they excel in and can be upgraded, making for fun management and progression systems.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Kunitsu-Gami
  </em>
  's strategy gameplay mostly arrives through the villager management aspect. While Soh is a capable fighter, he cannot be everywhere at once, and he will need to use all his human resources well to keep the spirits at bay.
 </p>
 <h2 id="wartales">
  Wartales
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-open-world-fantasy-epic-with-strategy-combat-and-rpg-elements">
  An Open-World Fantasy Epic With Strategy Combat And RPG Elements
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-639903012" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-639903012" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-639903012" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-639903012" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-639903012-img" id="article-gallery-6-639903012">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-639903012" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-367921152">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A sandbox RPG with turn-based combat and player-driven gameplay,
  <em>
   Wartales
  </em>
  combines popular concepts to create something fresh and, more importantly, niche. Depending on the person, the lack of a main story could either be enticing or off-putting, and their reaction is likely to determine if they will fall in love with Shiro Games' project or not. That said, if the idea of leading a ragtag group of mercenaries across a medieval-style world in search of contracts, food, and success sounds fun, then they should give
  <em>
   Wartales
  </em>
  a go, regardless of whether they generally prefer to follow a standard questline structure. And, to be clear, the campaign tells plenty of small-scale stories while allowing room for players to craft tales that are solely their own.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Wartales
  </em>
  is complicated. In an expansive and visually impressive sandbox, players lead 12 characters with traits, skills, and professions on a directionless journey beyond their need to make a living and survive. The latter is literal too, and the mercenaries must be kept fed, clothed, and paid; after all, they are people with needs and wants. The "strategy" and "tactical" elements are most apparent in the grid-based combat system, which shares similarities with the likes of
  <em>
   Fire Emblem
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin
  </em>
  . Most contracts/quests involve a combat scenario, and these battles tend to be quite difficult and could result in the death of the player's party members (if they die, they are gone). Furthermore, the game also complements the strategy genre by constantly requiring players to make tough and occasionally hopeless decisions.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="metal-slug-tactics">
  Metal Slug Tactics
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-refreshing-revamp-of-a-classic-franchise-that-is-still-designed-around-sprints">
  A Refreshing Revamp Of A Classic Franchise That Is Still Designed Around Sprints
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-678035736" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-678035736" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-678035736" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-678035736" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-678035736-img" id="article-gallery-7-678035736">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-678035736" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1374160254">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Metal Slug
  </em>
  's return has been long sought-after, but a turn-based tactics spin-off was probably not on too many people's cards. Beloved in arcades, the franchise has crafted some of the most decorated run and gun shooters of all time, games that tend to focus on fast-paced and relentless action above everything else. On the surface, that mantra does not seem like a great fit for a grid-based isometric tactics game that prioritizes slow-paced planning.
 </p>
 <p>
  Yet,
  <em>
   Metal Slug Tactics
  </em>
  works pretty darn well, not only in terms of mechanics but also in its implementation of some IP staples. Despite being so widely different at its core, this release still fits into the
  <em>
   Metal Slug
  </em>
  universe, largely due to incorporating a similar aesthetic and tone. Utilizing a roguelike formula, the campaign is designed around short bursts rather than one extensive adventure, with players having to start fresh if their three chosen characters all fall.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dungeons-4">
  Dungeons 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fun-throwback-to-a-classic">
  Fun Throwback To A Classic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1712998122" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1712998122" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1712998122" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1712998122" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1712998122-img" id="article-gallery-8-1712998122">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1712998122" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-216192506">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Game Pass Ultimate's PC version has some
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper
  </em>
  representation thanks to EA Play, but that won't mean much to players who only have access to Xbox. Despite its legacy,
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper
  </em>
  looks set to remain a thing of the past as EA has shown little interest in revisiting the franchise; consequently, fans must look elsewhere to get their fill of evil. The most obvious spiritual successor is the
  <em>
   Dungeons
  </em>
  series, which has produced a couple of cult favorites that have not really broken into the mainstream consciousness. The 2023 entry did not change that, but it is a fine and charming game that should keep someone busy for a couple of weeks.
 </p>
 <p>
  The concept is simple: world domination requires building an army and demolishing heroes.
  <em>
   Dungeons 4
  </em>
  understands that the fun parts of these games are the base building, unit development, and all-out wars, so the campaign emphasizes these elements as much as possible. The result is an efficient project that does not waste a lot of time, despite featuring a fairly lengthy campaign. The performance can struggle at times, and some of the story's later missions do threaten to get repetitive, but the overall experience is a positive one. Multiplayer is also an option for those who want to test out their strategic master plans against non-AI opponents.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="humankind">
  Humankind
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ambitious-4x-turn-based-strategy-game">
  Ambitious 4X Turn-Based Strategy Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-775187400" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-775187400" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-775187400" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-775187400" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-775187400-img" id="article-gallery-9-775187400">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-775187400" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-453876589">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Taking a break from its
  <em>
   Endless
  </em>
  franchise, Amplitude Studios created
  <em>
   Humankind
  </em>
  , an ambitious 4X strategy game that allows players to work their way through seven eras. Starting out as nomadic tribes, players will gradually roam unclaimed land as they find food, survive, and slowly start to set the groundwork for a civilization. Eventually, they can move over to the Ancient Era, which is where the campaign opens up through the introduction of Cultures.
  <em>
   Humankind
  </em>
  's scope is incredible and flexible, granting users quite a lot of freedom in how they want to lead their civilizations.
 </p>
 <p>
  Incorporating diplomacy, religion, and even turn-based combat, Amplitude cast a wide net as it sought to cover as many preferences and play styles as possible. Surprisingly, most of the game's mechanics and ideas are fleshed out well, making most avenues for growth viable.
  <em>
   Humankind
  </em>
  can be overwhelming at times, but it is not a bad option for 4X beginners. The game is available on PC and Xbox.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mount-amp-blade-2-bannerlord">
  Mount &amp; Blade 2: Bannerlord
 </h2>
 <h3 id="genre-blender-that-does-all-of-them-justice">
  Genre Blender That Does All Of Them Justice
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1219356740" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1219356740" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1219356740" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1219356740" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1219356740-img" id="article-gallery-10-1219356740">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1219356740" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-496236051">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Similar to its predecessor,
  <em>
   Warband
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Mount &amp; Blade 2: Bannerlord
  </em>
  combines a few different genres to create a package with no direct peers in the gaming landscape, despite sharing similarities with many prominent names. Set in Calradia, players are dropped in a world defined by battle as they set out to leave their mark on history. From humble beginnings, players will steadily amass an army en route to conquering towns and villages, with the end goal being to dominate the whole map.
 </p>
 <p>
  During physical conflicts, players can join their soldiers on the field, engaging in epic wars that are chaotic, bloody, and irresistibly fun. Outside the battlefield,
  <em>
   Bannerlord
  </em>
  opens up a range of management and strategy options that will dictate the player's growth, reputation, and presence. Due to casting a wide net,
  <em>
   Mount &amp; Blade 2
  </em>
  is not the deepest
  <strong>
   strategy game on Game Pass
  </strong>
  , but it is ambitious and addictive.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="slay-the-spire">
  Slay The Spire
 </h2>
 <h3 id="addictive-roguelike-with-strategic-deck-building-system">
  Addictive Roguelike With Strategic Deck Building System
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-918751971" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-918751971" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-918751971" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-918751971" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-918751971-img" id="article-gallery-11-918751971">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-918751971" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1262455231">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A popular deck-builder,
  <em>
   Slay the Spire
  </em>
  's roguelike structure has allowed the game to maintain its relevancy. Players pick a character and receive a deck along with a unique power in the form of a relic. From there, they enter the spire, a tower consisting of multiple levels filled with enemy encounters and culminating in a boss fight. Along the way, players unlock new cards in the form of loot.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Slay the Spire
  </em>
  constantly reshuffles the player's deck as they receive a fresh batch for every turn, along with a few energy cards that determine how many actions they can turn. Along with eradicating their opponents, players must also develop a strategy on how to counter the enemies' revealed moves.
 </p>
 <h2 id="wildfrost">
  Wildfrost
 </h2>
 <h3 id="difficult-roguelike-deck-builder-with-an-adorable-presentation">
  Difficult Roguelike Deck-Builder With An Adorable Presentation
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1228616453" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1228616453" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1228616453" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1228616453" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1228616453-img" id="article-gallery-12-1228616453">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1228616453" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-419030528">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sticking to the same subgenre for the time being,
  <em>
   Wildfrost
  </em>
  is another great Game Pass option for people craving a roguelike deck-builder that emphasizes player choice, all the while incorporating quite a bit of luck into the equation. Each run starts with players being handed a leader and a companion (they get a choice for the former, although the options are randomized), and then they set off to defeat enemies, collect more cards, overcome a zone's boss, and eventually defeat the final big bad.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Wildfrost
  </em>
  blends cute cards and a lively presentation with challenging combat that requires players to constantly consider the full picture and try to think ahead. This is 100% a pure strategy game that pulls no punches and lays the smackdown on any significant mistakes made by players. The result is a roguelike that is divisive but worth a try if someone is generally into deck-builders.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="stellaris">
  Stellaris
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-large-scale-sci-fi-4x-strategy-game">
  A Large-Scale Sci-Fi 4X Strategy Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-852552667" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-852552667" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-852552667" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-852552667" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-852552667-img" id="article-gallery-13-852552667">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-852552667" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1953413337">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If strategy games are a rare sight on consoles, then
  <strong>
   grand strategy Xbox games
  </strong>
  are something of a mythological creature. However,
  <em>
   Stellaris
  </em>
  adapts to the platform in fine fashion.
 </p>
 <p>
  Featuring nuanced layers of resource management, diplomacy, and even interstellar warfare, players will have all sorts of empire management to contend with as they guide their species through the stars — speaking of species, there’s a wide variety to choose from. From religiously fanatical frog people to democratic felines, players can truly design the spacefaring civilization of their dreams (or nightmares).
 </p>
 <h2 id="gears-tactics">
  Gears Tactics
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fairly-standard-tactics-game-elevated-by-the-gears-of-war-license">
  Fairly Standard Tactics Game, Elevated By The Gears Of War License
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1795217501" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1795217501" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1795217501" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1795217501" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1795217501-img" id="article-gallery-14-1795217501">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1795217501" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-1853290214">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite its reputation for being a gritty third-person, cover-based shooter, the
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  series is set in an engrossing world, and the games usually feature gripping narratives. So, even though
  <em>
   Gears Tactics
  </em>
  took the turn-based-strategy route, it is a thoroughly entertaining title thanks to the universe it is set in and the lore it provides.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Gears Tactics
  </em>
  is a prequel to the first
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  game, but it also connects to plot points seen in later titles in the series, such as
  <em>
   Gears of War 4
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Gears 5
  </em>
  . The top-down perspective suits the narrative well, as COG soldiers are deployed across a map, eliminating Locust enemies and clearing out objectives.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="crusader-kings-3">
  Crusader Kings 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-character-driven-strategy-rpg-about-family">
  A Character-Driven Strategy RPG About Family
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-828938795" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-828938795" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-828938795" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-828938795" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-828938795-img" id="article-gallery-15-828938795">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-828938795" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-103591064">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Crusader Kings 3
  </em>
  started as a PC exclusive, but the grand strategy RPG eventually made its way to the PS5 and Xbox Series X/S. Paradox's project builds upon the foundations of its predecessors, delivering an engaging and challenging experience that covers a wide spectrum of themes and mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Taking over a dynasty and leading it through multiple generations,
  <em>
   Crusader Kings 3
  </em>
  blends complex mechanics with strong characters who have plenty of personality to them. While the game has the lofty ambition and large-scale scope synonymous with the grand strategy genre,
  <em>
   Crusader Kings 3
  </em>
  also delivers personal stories.
 </p>
 <h2 id="minecraft-legends">
  Minecraft Legends
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fine-entry-level-action-strategy-game">
  A Fine Entry-Level Action Strategy Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-631408977" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-631408977" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-631408977" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-631408977" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-631408977-img" id="article-gallery-16-631408977">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-631408977" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-311932963">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Minecraft Legends
  </em>
  is not for everyone. The obvious target audience should be
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  fans, but to be honest, the spin-off does not share enough in common with the main entry to warrant a recommendation solely on its title. That said, if someone wants to experience a different take on the Overworld,
  <em>
   Legends
  </em>
  is worth considering. As a strategy game, this 2023 release is very stripped down, to the point of being way too simplistic for die-hard fans of the genre. That's not to say they might not get some enjoyment out of the game's blend of exploration, combat, base upgrading, and team management, but they are unlikely to be too impressed by its strategic gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately,
  <em>
   Minecraft Legends
  </em>
  is for young players who are familiar with the IP and are taking their first steps into strategy territory. As an introductory course that wraps the commonly overwhelming genre in an accessible skin,
  <em>
   Legends
  </em>
  does its job. Not every game needs to be complex or even innovative; sometimes, a simple but fun project is enough.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="best-strategy-games-on-xbox-game-pass-for-pc">
  Best Strategy Games On Xbox Game Pass For PC
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="battletech game battlefield" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/battletech-game-battlefield.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unsurprisingly,
  <strong>
   Xbox Game Pass for PC
  </strong>
  has a far more robust selection of strategy games. The genre has historically flourished on computers, with the mouse + keyboard setup complementing the pinpoint controls required by these titles. While console owners only have a small selection of games to pick from, the PC scene is considerably more impressive.
 </p>
 <p>
  For those with Xbox Game Pass for PC, here are a handful of the
  <strong>
   best strategy games
  </strong>
  on the subscription service.
 </p>
 <h2 id="starcraft-remastered-amp-starcraft-2">
  StarCraft Remastered &amp; StarCraft 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-definitive-sci-fi-rts-series">
  The Definitive Sci-Fi RTS Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1201744189" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1201744189" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1201744189" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1201744189" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1201744189-img" id="article-gallery-17-1201744189">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1201744189" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-827978852">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list even-cards">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   StarCraft
  </em>
  has not received a new game in more than 5 years, but it is still by far the definitive sci-fi real-time strategy franchise. The 1998 original was incredibly influential, and it was followed up by a belated 2010 sequel that produced multiple campaign expansions and continues to be played regularly more than a decade after its introduction.
 </p>
 <p>
  While aspects of the original title are dated,
  <em>
   StarCraft
  </em>
  's 2017 remaster incorporates more than enough modern touches to make the game an easy recommendation in the mid-2020s.
  <em>
   StarCraft 2
  </em>
  is arguably even better, and it comes packed with enough content to keep somebody busy for months.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="frostpunk-2">
  Frostpunk 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-survival-strategy-city-building-epic">
  A Survival Strategy City-Building Epic
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1654699749" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1654699749" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1654699749" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1654699749" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1654699749-img" id="article-gallery-18-1654699749">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1654699749" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-1619366862">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_126">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Frostpunk 2
     </em>
     will be coming to Xbox Game Pass eventually, but it is currently only available on PC. That said,
     <em>
      Frostpunk: Console Edition
     </em>
     is on Game Pass.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  11 Bit Studios created something special with
  <em>
   Frostpunk
  </em>
  , a survival city-builder strategy hybrid that somehow shines in all three genres. A sequel was only a matter of time, and there was a slight worry that the next project would lack its predecessor's freshness. Fortunately,
  <em>
   Frostpunk 2
  </em>
  shines entirely on its own, offering a fantastic evolution that is different enough at its core to not render the first game obsolete. In fact,
  <em>
   Frostpunk
  </em>
  is still on Game Pass and well worth a playthrough, regardless of its successor's existence.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once again, players find themselves leading a city, New London, during a hellish era defined by harsh weather, and they will need to constantly make choices that have notable benefits and consequences, both for themselves and especially for their citizens.
  <em>
   Frostpunk 2
  </em>
  is a deep city-builder that uses a grid system to allow Stewards to stitch together districts, carving a "utopia" that is efficient enough to survive, even if not necessarily prosper. This time around, players will be venturing away from their city's walls, heading out on expeditions in search of resources and new locations. The sequel emphasizes its faction system as well, which means there will always be groups with different goals pushing their agendas on the player. Keeping everybody happy is nearly impossible, so tough decisions need to be made.
 </p>
 <p>
  Newcomers and veterans should start with
  <em>
   Frostpunk 2
  </em>
  's story since it works well as a tutorial, along with just being pretty fun. After that, Utopia Builder will be the next step, and it provides plenty of replay value.
 </p>
 <h2 id="against-the-storm">
  Against The Storm
 </h2>
 <h3 id="satisfy-the-queen">
  Satisfy The Queen
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-288654069" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-288654069" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-288654069" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-288654069" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-288654069-img" id="article-gallery-19-288654069">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-288654069" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-902990079">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although not garnering as much attention as a few other late-2023 releases,
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  was among the year's best projects across a plethora of genres and subgenres. If someone is into city-builders, strategy titles, or even roguelites, they need to try this game as it might scratch a hard-to-reach itch. Set in a fantasy world that looks pretty but is extremely dangerous due to storms that periodically destroy everything outside the main city, players are tasked by their queen to gradually explore the unknown and find a solution.
 </p>
 <p>
  This process involves establishing settlements that can dig deeper into the woods, and each mini-village has an expiry date; consequently, players have to make regular smart decisions if they want to progress and satisfy their ruler. By randomizing quite a few key elements,
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  makes unpredictability one of its cornerstones, ensuring players cannot simply rely on a winning formula to get them through each situation. As with most city-builders, players are in charge of workers who need to be kept happy, something that is easier said than done.
 </p>
 <h3 id="other-city-builders-on-xbox-game-pass-amp-pc-game-pass">
  Other City-Builders On Xbox Game Pass &amp; PC Game Pass:
 </h3>
 <p>
  City-builders are essentially their own genre, although they do share a lot of things in common with strategy or simulation games.
  <em>
   Against the Storm
  </em>
  incorporates more strategy mechanics than most city-builders, but the following Game Pass titles are worth noting for anyone fond of these types of releases:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Cities: Skylines
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    Cities: Skylines 2
   </em>
   (PC Game Pass)
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    SimCity/SimCity 2000/SimCity 4
   </em>
   (PC Game Pass)
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    SteamWorld Build
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rise-of-nations-extended-edition">
  Rise Of Nations: Extended Edition
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-classic-rts-revamped-for-modern-accessibility">
  A Classic RTS Revamped For Modern Accessibility
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-292575223" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-292575223" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-292575223" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-292575223" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-292575223-img" id="article-gallery-20-292575223">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-292575223" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-382323845">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although not carrying the same name recognition as
  <em>
   Age of Empires
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Total War
  </em>
  , or
  <em>
   Civilization
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Rise of Nations
  </em>
  is still highly regarded within the strategy gaming sphere. The 2003 original features nations from across human history, and they can all be played within any of the game's eras. Gameplay-wise,
  <em>
   Rise of Nations
  </em>
  is more economy-driven than most of its contemporaries, with the focus being on expanding a nation's territory through sustainable growth rather than just overwhelming enemies via brute strength.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like many of these titles,
  <em>
   Rise of Nation
  </em>
  's multiplayer was its main selling point. Nowadays, lobbies are not particularly active; however, the game also includes an extensive single-player campaign as well, one that is more than good enough to justify a recommendation. The
  <em>
   Extended Edition
  </em>
  also contains the Thrones and Patriots expansion pack, which is fantastic and some might argue even superior to the base game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dungeon-keeper-2">
  Dungeon Keeper 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="charming-classic-with-a-unique-setting-amp-gameplay-loop">
  Charming Classic With A Unique Setting &amp; Gameplay Loop
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-21-644187123" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-21-644187123" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-21-644187123" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-21-644187123" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-21-644187123-img" id="article-gallery-21-644187123">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-21-644187123" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-21">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-21-slides-container-1871408771">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bullfrog Productions' time in the sun came to an end in 2001. While the company's run was fairly short-lived in the grand scheme of things, projects like
  <em>
   Populous
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Syndicate
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Theme Park World
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper
  </em>
  ensured Bullfrog would not be forgotten anytime soon, particularly by strategy and management fans. Out of all those licenses,
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper
  </em>
  and its sequel are probably the most fondly remembered, although
  <em>
   Populous
  </em>
  ' influence on the God game genre cannot be understated either. Through EA Play, PC Game Pass subscribers can play a few of Bullfrog's masterpieces, specifically both
  <em>
   Populous
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper
  </em>
  games. All four titles are worth checking out, and while they might seem antiquated through a modern lens, the games are still quite a bit of fun to play.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dungeon Keeper 2
  </em>
  is slightly divisive as it swapped its predecessor's 2D visuals for 3D, a change that dates the sequel more than its predecessor. However, fundamentally, it is still the same experience as its decorated ancestor. Cast as an overlord, players are put in charge of a dungeon as they lay out traps to capture heroes trying to sneak in. The goal is to expand the dungeon's size and achieve world domination. Fairly challenging, the strategy game has a lengthy single-player campaign that is more than capable of keeping something entertained for a few weeks.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="command-amp-conquer-remastered-collection">
  Command &amp; Conquer Remastered Collection
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-compilation-including-remasters-of-two-rts-masterpiees">
  A Compilation Including Remasters Of Two RTS Masterpiees
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-22-2098476398" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-22-2098476398" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-22-2098476398" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-22-2098476398" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-22-2098476398-img" id="article-gallery-22-2098476398">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-22-2098476398" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-22">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-22-slides-container-395267113">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In 1995, Westwood Studios released
  <em>
   Command &amp; Conquer: Tiberian Dawn
  </em>
  , changing the real-time strategy genre for the better. The series went on to produce a couple of fantastic sequels such as
  <em>
   Red Alert, Tiberian Sun
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Red Alert 2
  </em>
  , before fading into nothingness during the 2010s. Nowadays, EA seems happy to leave the license untouched, with the only PC entry of the last five years being a compilation package containing revamped versions of
  <em>
   Tiberian Dawn
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Red Alert
  </em>
  . This iconic franchise deserves better, although that has nothing to do with the quality of the
  <em>
   Command &amp; Conquer Remastered Collection
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Developed by Petroglyph Games, who have ties to Westwood, the 2020 release serves as a love letter to the franchise's glory days and comes packed with three expansions and a range of bonus content. At their hearts, these are still the same games that defined the '90s, but Petroglyph still implemented a wide range of changes to ensure they are accessible to both a modern and nostalgic audience. While the presentation can seem a bit simplistic compared to contemporary strategy games,
  <em>
   Command &amp; Conquer
  </em>
  's core mechanics are still rock solid, and they are enhanced by charming writing.
 </p>
 <h2 id="strategy-games-that-should-be-coming-to-game-pass">
  Strategy Games That Should Be Coming To Game Pass
 </h2>
 <h3 id="current-focus-march-2025">
  Current Focus: March 2025
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-23-2015230728" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-23-2015230728" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-23-2015230728" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-23-2015230728" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-23-2015230728-img" id="article-gallery-23-2015230728">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-23-2015230728" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-23">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-23-slides-container-1225150610">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list even-cards">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Clicking on Xbox Game Pass' "Coming Soon" section will reveal a handful of titles that should be debuting on the service within the coming weeks or months. While some exciting names are usually included, the selection is not typically exhaustive, and plenty of projects that have announced plans to land on Game Pass are not mentioned. This is likely because these games do not have announced release dates, a criterion that makes sense for Game Pass to include. After all, subscribers might not find it that useful to know that a title might arrive at some point in the next year or two.
 </p>
 <p>
  Looking at the "Coming Soon" section might suggest that no new strategy games announced for the service will launch in the immediate future; however, that should not be the case. Two projects that fit the genre are targeting March 2025 debuts, but they have not specified a date yet. Let's highlight these upcoming
  <strong>
   Game Pass strategy games
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Commandos: Origins
   </em>
   – A real-time tactics franchise,
   <em>
    Commandos
   </em>
   enjoyed a relatively successful run from 1998 to 2006, producing four mainline entries and a spin-off in the process. Since then, the series has only produced two 2022 HD remasters, both of which garnered reasonably positive receptions. In March 2025, the IP should be making its proper comeback, with Claymore Game Studios handling
   <em>
    Commandos: Origins
   </em>
   , which seems set to show the early days of WW2. As always, players will guide a group of Alliance commandos through an array of missions, and they will have to make use of each of their skills and abilities to overcome the Axis forces. Besides solo-play,
   <em>
    Commandos: Origins
   </em>
   will also support 2-player co-op.
  </li>
  <li>
   <em>
    Football Manager 25
   </em>
   – For decades now,
   <em>
    Football Manager
   </em>
   has dominated the sports management scene, producing reliably entertaining annual games while rarely ever missing a beat. However,
   <em>
    FM25
   </em>
   has seemingly not had the greatest development cycle so far. Not only was the game delayed from its original November 2024 release, but a date has yet to be confirmed for March 2025. Communication and information have been scarce during this time as well. This entry will mark the franchise's first outing with the Unity engine, which is likely the main cause for the delays.
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring Nightreign Beta Invites On Sale for Ridiculous Prices</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elden-ring-nightreign-beta-invites-selling-expensive/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Elden Ring Nightreign playtest invites are being resold at high prices on eBay, ranging from $30 to $300 USD.
     </li>
     <li>
      Buyers risk losing access as transferring/selling codes violates rules, potentially leading to revoked access.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite high demand, it's advised not to purchase codes as scams target hopeful players.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Elden Ring Nightreign
   </strong>
  </em>
  playtest invitations are being resold for ridiculous prices, taking advantage of eager fans' desperation. Lucky entrants are eagerly awaiting the upcoming
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  playtests, but those who didn't get their chance may feel tempted to spend money to get in.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  is the upcoming roguelike spin-off of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , putting a single player or groups of three into the world and giving them three days to fight and prep for a big boss fight at the end of the third day. While the game doesn't have a set release date yet, players won't have to wait long for their first taste of it, with a network test kicking off on February 14.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, not everyone can get into every playtest, especially with hype as high as it is for this upcoming title, and resellers are now taking advantage of that.
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  network test access codes are now being sold on eBay, with prices ranging from $30 to a stunning $300 USD at the time of writing. At the moment, it remains to be seen if any of the high-priced listings will actually sell. The completed listings indicate that several codes have sold for $50 USD or under. However, as the date draws closer, the supply of available codes could dwindle, leading to some of the higher-priced listings selling.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1011367743" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1011367743" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1011367743" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1011367743" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1011367743-img" id="article-gallery-1-1011367743">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1011367743" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-705653975">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="buying-elden-ring-nightreign-access-codes-isn-39-t-advised">
  Buying Elden Ring Nightreign Access Codes Isn't Advised
 </h2>
 <p>
  While some might be desperate enough to try this method of getting into the
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  playtest, it's not a great idea. The rules of the playtest indicate that transferring, buying, or selling codes to the playtest is prohibited. In the event that a playtest was found to have been sold or was utilized by someone other than the person who won it, their access would likely be revoked. That's assuming that a purchase made would even yield an actual invite, as this could be prime territory for scammers taking advantage of the situation.
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  scams have already targeted playtest hopefuls in other ways, so fans should take care.
 </p>
 <p>
  While many fans were still hoping for more
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , many were surprised to see the developer go in this direction with the IP. Following the monumental success of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  and its DLC, it will be interesting to see how this spin-off twist fares compared to its predecessor. Fans will start getting their first taste of what
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  has to offer starting with this network test, but with a general release window of 2025, gamers shouldn't have to wait too long to get their hands on the title.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Best Stories In PS2 Horror Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-ps2-horror-game-stories-playstation-2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The PS2 was a platform for outstanding horror narratives driven by writing, voice acting, and world-building.
     </li>
     <li>
      The horror games like The Thing, Resident Evil, Manhunt, Silent Hill 2, and Rule of Rose explored dark themes and human emotions.
     </li>
     <li>
      The captivating horror games on PS2 deliver chilling atmospheres, engaging stories, and exceptional performances.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The horror genre has historically been a perfect breeding ground for storytelling, as its ability to examine the darkest side of the human condition and its complicated problems has been paramount to some of the most incredible video game narratives of all time. And the PS2 was home to some of the genre's most outstanding tales of terror, as Sony's impeccable next-gen hardware granted new ways for developers to create intimate, deeply frightening escapades.
 </p>
 <p>
  Thanks to the PlayStation 2's outstanding advancements in detail and character modeling, the complexity and range of human emotions were more impressive than ever. It allowed horror stories to thrive, to use the combination of technology and art in order to create some of the genre's most fascinating narratives, driven by excellent writing and voice acting. These games have been ranked based on their writing, performances, world building, and art direction, as these elements are crucial to outstanding horror experiences.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-thing">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   The Thing
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="video-game-sequel-to-1982-horror-film-is-excellent">
  Video Game Sequel To 1982 Horror Film Is Excellent
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1926217032" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1926217032" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1926217032" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1926217032" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1926217032-img" id="article-gallery-1-1926217032">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1926217032" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-323183174">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The 1982 horror film
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Thing
   </em>
  </strong>
  , directed by John Carpenter, was based on a short story known as
  <em>
   Who Goes There,
  </em>
  and in 2002, Vivendi Universal teamed up with Computer Artworks to create a video game sequel that took place three months after the events of the movie. Pulling from the paranoia and isolation that the classic Carpenter film crafted,
  <em>
   The Thing
  </em>
  tells the tale of J.F. Blake as he attempts to uncover the horrifying truth about what happened to Outpost 31.
 </p>
 <p>
  With a focus on subtle writing and strong performances,
  <em>
   The Thing
  </em>
  perfectly captures the eerie tone and atmosphere of the film. The cast is a charming collection of characters, and their distinct personalities both clash and mesh in some excellent ways.
  <em>
   The Thing
  </em>
  was recently remastered for modern hardware by Nightdive Studios, making it easier than ever to experience this outstanding tale of obsession and body horror.
 </p>
 <h2 id="resident-evil-code-veronica">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Resident Evil CODE: Veronica
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="first-3d-resident-evil-features-harrowing-exploration-of-two-different-sibling-dynamics">
  First 3D Resident Evil Features Harrowing Exploration Of Two Different Sibling Dynamics
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-498186215" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-498186215" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-498186215" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-498186215" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-498186215-img" id="article-gallery-2-498186215">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-498186215" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1431006951">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Designed as a way to introduce Sega players to the franchise,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Resident Evil CODE: Veronica
   </strong>
  </em>
  continued the tale of Claire Redfield and her brother Chris, as their ongoing quest to take out Umbrella takes the duo to an isolated prison on Rockfort Island. Swapping between the two characters,
  <em>
   CODE: Veronica
  </em>
  sees the siblings attempting to survive a t-virus outbreak and find each other all at the same time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Chris and Claire's loving brother-sister bond is in sharp contrast to antagonists Alfred and Alexia Ashford, whose twisted tale of identity does an incredible job of solidifying the relationship between the Redfield siblings. It is one of
  <em>
   Resident Evil's
  </em>
  most incredible stories, with some outstanding voice acting and genuinely fascinating writing. It would be perfect for a reboot akin to the recent
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  remakes, but it is currently available on PlayStation and Xbox platforms, where it is absolutely worth jumping into today.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="manhunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Manhunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="twisted-tale-of-violence-and-exploitation">
  Twisted Tale Of Violence And Exploitation
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2145772886" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2145772886" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2145772886" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2145772886" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2145772886-img" id="article-gallery-3-2145772886">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2145772886" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1653243355">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Set in the ultra-violent Carcer City, which is located somewhere in the darkest parts of the
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto
  </em>
  universe, Rockstar's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Manhunt
   </em>
  </strong>
  veered off into some pretty twisted territory when it launched in 2003. Telling the tale of James Earl Cash, a man sentenced to death row, it explores the dark side of the American prison system and is still one of the most fantastic video game stories ever told.
 </p>
 <p>
  Abducted by a deranged man named Lionel Starkweather, who goes by an alias known as The Director, James is forced to take part in a snuff film and kill gang members on camera. Featuring an absolutely incredible performance by Brian Cox as Starkweather and the trademark dark humor that Rockstar is known for,
  <em>
   Manhunt
  </em>
  remains one of the console's most riveting explorations of humanity's most sinister traits.
 </p>
 <h2 id="resident-evil-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Resident Evil 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bombastic-fourth-entry-in-resident-evil-franchise-stars-leon-kennedy">
  Bombastic Fourth Entry In Resident Evil Franchise Stars Leon Kennedy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-432464055" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-432464055" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-432464055" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-432464055" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-432464055-img" id="article-gallery-4-432464055">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-432464055" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1040539152">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following the events of
  <em>
   Resident Evil CODE: Veronica
  </em>
  , it seemed like the good guys were well on their way to eliminating Umbrella once and for all. But
  <em>
   <strong>
    Resident Evil 4
   </strong>
  </em>
  , which was directed by series creator Shinji Mikami, took the series into a sharp left turn and sees Leon Kennedy in an isolated village in rural Spain as he attempts to protect the President's daughter, Ashley.
 </p>
 <p>
  Umbrella is no more, and Leon's new mission is one far removed from the previous events of the game, creating a new, much more dangerous atmosphere.
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  leans into the outright absurdity of the franchise's past, crafting a story built around Leon and Ashley's mutual understanding of each other. Their relationship matures and grows over the course of the game, as their bond forms the basis of the game's outrageous story. It was recently remade by Capcom, proving that this story of survival and friendship is one that is still well worth experiencing.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="silent-hill-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Silent Hill 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="terrifying-examination-of-grief-and-trauma">
  Terrifying Examination Of Grief And Trauma
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-756086426" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-756086426" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-756086426" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-756086426" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-756086426-img" id="article-gallery-5-756086426">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-756086426" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-2045372953">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the first
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  game explored the unbreakable bond between a father and daughter, the sequel took the series into a bold new direction. Chronicling the disturbing tale of James Sunderland as he travels to the mysterious town in search of his wife, who passed away years prior,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Silent Hill 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  examines the themes of guilt and trauma in some truly profound ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  James' quest to find his wife is wrought with some of the most intense, visceral fear that one can find in the genre, as
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  sees its protagonist put to the ultimate test on multiple occasions. His encounters with characters like Eddie, a man on the brink of madness, as well as a fragile girl named Angela, form some of the game's most haunting moments. Its voice acting and writing has a sort of otherworldly quality to it that still resonates to this day, which was something that Bloober Team took to heart when they remade
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  in 2024. This landmark horror release is still worth playing today and is an excellent place to start the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rule-of-rose">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Rule Of Rose
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dark-fairy-tale-explores-the-corruption-of-youth">
  Dark Fairy Tale Explores The Corruption Of Youth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1268957515" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1268957515" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1268957515" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1268957515" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1268957515-img" id="article-gallery-6-1268957515">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1268957515" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1927262383">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Wanting to explore darker themes of childhood, developers Punchline teamed up with Atlus to produce
  <strong>
   <em>
    Rule of Rose
   </em>
  </strong>
  , an absolutely incredible PS2 survival horror game that tells the story of a girl named Jennifer who becomes trapped in a mysterious orphanage with a sinister purpose. Discovering a hierarchy that is ruled over by the Red Crayon Aristocrats, Jennifer and her dog Brown find themselves in the middle of something much darker.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Rule of Rose
  </em>
  is one of the console's most incredible games, as its fabulous writing and rich, detailed world come together effortlessly. Featuring one of the most chilling endings of all time and a terrific twist ending, Rule of Rose is an absolutely stellar horror experience that is worth diving into today. Unfortunately, due to its dark tone and controversial story, it has remained without a remaster for the past twenty years. It's a shame, as this twisted tale of corruption and childhood is a prime example of what great horror video games can accomplish.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Hill: 8 Biggest Traditions In The Series</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/silent-hill-biggest-traditions-in-the-series/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Unnerving Sound Design: Creepy, industrial soundscapes enhance the atmosphere in each game.
     </li>
     <li>
      Radio: Crackling noise alerts players of nearby enemies, increasing the fear factor.
     </li>
     <li>
      Otherworld: Blood, rust, and surreal scenarios indicate the entrance to a terrifying, physics-defying realm.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When the first
  <strong>
   <em>
    Silent Hill
   </em>
  </strong>
  dropped in 1999 for the PlayStation, it immediately made its mark on the survival horror genre thanks to its unique story, environment, and characters. However, since that first entry, the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  games have carried forward several trends, or 'traditions', that have gone a long way in making the franchise feel different from other horror games. Traditions can be anything the developers will purposefully bring back for each new game, whether it be a mechanic, theme, or even an enemy type.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  IP being shared between numerous developers over the years, many of the teams have gone out of their way to feature these specific trends, which is important since many of them feed into the gameplay and overall tone of the series. Now that
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  is experiencing a long-awaited revival with the huge success of
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2 Remake
  </em>
  , it's time to reflect on the traditions that have helped to make this iconic franchise what it is today.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="unnerving-sound-design">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Unnerving Sound Design
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="silent-hill-developers-always-get-extra-creative-when-designing-the-sounds-of-the-games">
  Silent Hill Developers Always Get Extra Creative When Designing The Sounds Of The Games
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2004285806" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2004285806" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2004285806" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2004285806" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2004285806-img" id="article-gallery-1-2004285806">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2004285806" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1552141349">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Compared to many other survival horror games,
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  has always been known for its atmosphere, and one way the developers amplify this as much as possible is through sound design. In the first game, players would be able to hear loud drums and slams in the background as they explore the town, creating an industrial-esque audio soundscape that managed to make everything feel just a little more off and creepy.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  would go even further by incorporating more ambient and hypnotic audio, along with including a few jumpscares here and there, such as the horse who can be heard galloping around the courtyard, or the whispered message in Room 209. Sound design would become such a prominent element of
  <em>
   Silent Hill's
  </em>
  aesthetic that it would be one of the biggest priorities for every developer, which is why it is always such a standout feature in each entry.
 </p>
 <h2 id="radio">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Radio
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="this-handy-tool-is-designed-to-help-players-but-it-also-makes-the-core-gameplay-so-much-more-terrifying">
  This Handy Tool Is Designed To Help Players, But It Also Makes The Core Gameplay So Much More Terrifying
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-351271777" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-351271777" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-351271777" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-351271777" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-351271777-img" id="article-gallery-2-351271777">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-351271777" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-760388532">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once players pick up the radio at the beginning of a
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  game, they will be able to detect whenever enemies are nearby thanks to the static noise the radio will emit. While this is clearly very useful, the fact the crackling noise from the radio will get louder and louder, even if an enemy isn't in sight, simply enhances the fear factor of the games rather than making them more relaxed.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some of the games have switched out the radio for other items, such as how it appears as a phone in
  <em>
   Shattered Memories
  </em>
  or a walkie-talkie in
  <em>
   Downpour
  </em>
  . Regardless of how it may appear though, these items have shown up in every game to help give players a fighting chance by preparing them in advance for any nearby enemies.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="red-save-points">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Red Save Points
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-glowing-red-save-points-are-the-only-safe-havens-for-players-in-silent-hill-games">
  The Glowing Red Save Points Are The Only Safe Havens For Players In Silent Hill Games
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1342862531" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1342862531" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1342862531" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1342862531" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1342862531-img" id="article-gallery-3-1342862531">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1342862531" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1106440867">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A save point in any survival horror needs to catch the player's eye when they walk near one. After all, these are the safe havens that allow players to take a quick breather, so for the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  games, Team Silent decided to make them bright red so they can easily be spotted, even from a fair distance away. Though they were only small red and white books in the first game, the save points would be much brighter and more visible in the second game and its remake.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Silent Hill 3
  </em>
  would tinker around with them again by making the save points red cult symbols which are far larger and harder to miss. It similarly takes on a red occult appearance in
  <em>
   Origins
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Homecoming
  </em>
  , which were developed by entirely different teams, showing just how much of a mainstay this small but recognizable feature really is for the series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="otherworld">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Otherworld
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="if-the-walls-start-turning-red-and-the-enemies-become-more-aggressive-players-have-officially-entered-the-otherworld">
  If The Walls Start Turning Red And The Enemies Become More Aggressive, Players Have Officially Entered The Otherworld
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2023410502" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2023410502" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2023410502" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2023410502" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2023410502-img" id="article-gallery-4-2023410502">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2023410502" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1505517284">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There have long been debates among the community about what the Otherworld actually is, but regardless of whether it's a second world or simply a warped version of the existing one, it's terrifying all the same. The Otherworld first appeared in the original
  <em>
   Silent Hill,
  </em>
  and has become a recurring concept in almost every game since, but no matter how many times it shows up, it never gets any less creepy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will know if they've entered the Otherworld by the blood and rust that will be splattered all over the walls. Additionally, since physics seems to not apply in the Otherworld, it results in all kinds of weird and creepy scenarios, such as the bleeding mirror in
  <em>
   Silent Hill 3
  </em>
  , or the clocks that rotate their hands much faster than normal in
  <em>
   Silent Hill 4
  </em>
  . Needless to say, the Otherworld is often the scariest part of any
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  playthrough.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-order">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Order
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-shady-cult-who-are-at-the-core-of-many-silent-hill-stories">
  A Shady Cult Who Are At The Core Of Many Silent Hill Stories
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1894019632" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1894019632" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1894019632" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1894019632" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1894019632-img" id="article-gallery-5-1894019632">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1894019632" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1142653807">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though there have technically been several antagonists throughout the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  series, many of them are connected to a much bigger group known as The Order, who act as the central antagonists of the franchise. This evil group believes it is their duty to deliver apocalypse to the world so the 'loyal' members will be sent to a paradise. In order to achieve this, the group commit some downright despicable acts to anyone who doesn't follow their ideals, including abuse and torture.
 </p>
 <p>
  Outside of the second game, The Order has shown up in every single entry, including those not developed by Team Silent, and even the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  movie. However, they still manage to crop up in one of the endings to
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  when James pays them a visit in an attempt to bring Mary back to life.
 </p>
 <h2 id="joke-endings">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Joke Endings
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-can-always-unlock-a-lighthearted-ending-to-end-things-off-on-a-comedic-note">
  Players Can Always Unlock A Lighthearted Ending To End Things Off On A Comedic Note
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-389647005" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-389647005" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-389647005" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-389647005" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-389647005-img" id="article-gallery-6-389647005">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-389647005" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1056523435">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  All the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  games feature multiple endings which can be unlocked through particular means, but one that always makes an appearance, except in
  <em>
   Silent Hill 4
  </em>
  , is the joke ending. It all started when Harry Mason was randomly abducted by aliens at the end of the first game. Since then, aliens, villainous dogs, and even bunny mascots have all made appearances in the joke endings which have appeared in every single entry in the series.
 </p>
 <p>
  For
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2's
  </em>
  joke ending, James discovers that a cute little dog was orchestrating the entire story from behind the scenes from the very beginning. Meanwhile, in
  <em>
   Silent Hill Origins
  </em>
  , Travis hitches a ride with some aliens after they assure him his truck is on their planet. There's literally no telling what weird and whacky secret ending is going to be included for each new entry, which is why it's a top priority for many players to unlock them as quickly as possible.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="manifested-enemies">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Manifested Enemies
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-majority-of-silent-hill-39-s-enemies-are-conjured-up-through-a-person-39-s-repressed-memories">
  The Majority Of Silent Hill's Enemies Are Conjured Up Through A Person's Repressed Memories
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1708367614" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1708367614" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1708367614" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1708367614" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1708367614-img" id="article-gallery-7-1708367614">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1708367614" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-676026380">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Many of the grotesque and violent enemies seen in the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  games are products of a character's mind. This trend started with the first entry, where Alessa's repressed memories and fears manifested themselves into the many horrific monsters that players face during their playthrough. It was then James' turn to conjure up some monsters in the second game, which represent his underlying feelings once Mary was sent to the hospital.
 </p>
 <p>
  This trend has continued in every single game, and whether it's feelings of anxiety, loneliness, or misery that a character is feeling, all of these negative emotions can be manifested into pure nightmare fuel which the player is forced to tackle head-on.
 </p>
 <h2 id="silent-hill">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Silent Hill
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fog-covered-town-that-is-full-of-nightmarish-horrors">
  A Fog-Covered Town That Is Full Of Nightmarish Horrors
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1788489801" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1788489801" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1788489801" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1788489801" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1788489801-img" id="article-gallery-8-1788489801">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1788489801" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-380864613">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Silent Hill isn't just some creepy name Team Silent decided to use as the tagline for their series, as it actually refers to the quaint and creepy town that shows up in almost every single game. Though Silent Hill was once a beautiful getaway destination, it would turn into something much more nightmarish after the cult's experiments tried to summon a demon god in the first game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since then, it has cropped up in nearly every game as a destination the protagonists, unwillingly, will need to visit. What makes the town so eerie is that, at first glance, it can seem relatively normal with its small cafés and peaceful parks, but with the whole area being covered in fog, it keeps players in suspense as they wonder what horrors could really be lurking around this long-forgotten town.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
