<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Best Character-Action Games With Skill-Based Combat, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-character-action-games-skill-based-combat/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Different character-action games offer varying levels of combat challenge.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like God of War focus on skill-based combat, while others offer by-the-numbers action.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sifu excels in skill-based combat with utility-driven moves, creating a high skill ceiling.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Character-action games can vary depending on how much they demand of the player. These games tend to focus on long combat move lists and constant action, but not all of them make that combat challenging. In some games, combat can be a by-the-numbers affair, with options for the player but no real reason to use them. Yet, other games in the genre offer skill-based combat with depth and variety.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are benefits and drawbacks to both styles. Limiting the challenge can create a more fluid pacing for story experiences that draw players in with a narrative. More traditional character-action games tend to forego this narrative depth to provide a more robust and varied combat experience, and both approaches are valid. The games in this topic all take an action-first approach to character-action games with deep, skill-based combat systems.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="god-of-war-2018">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   God Of War (2018)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dad-of-war">
  Dad Of War
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-99486995" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-99486995" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-99486995" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-99486995" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-99486995-img" id="article-gallery-1-99486995">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-99486995" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-401518936">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The 2018 reboot of
  <strong>
   <em>
    God of War
   </em>
  </strong>
  redesigned the series' signature combat in a significant way. As well as mixing Kratos' familiar blades of chaos with the now iconic axe, the game switched to a fluid over-the-shoulder melee combat system with a focus on blocks and parries. Not that the older
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  games didn't require some skill, but the modern reboot managed to make the new combat system feel more reactive and tactical.
 </p>
 <p>
  This was emphasized through some of the games' more memorable encounters. Optional bosses like the Valkyries offer a way for players to test the limits of their skills with the new systems. While there are some mixed opinions on whether the follow-up
  <em>
   God of War: Ragnarok
  </em>
  managed to build on these systems effectively, the 2018 reboot nailed the redesigned skill-based combat elements.
 </p>
 <h2 id="devil-may-cry-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Devil May Cry 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-stylish-return">
  A Stylish Return
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1846882261" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1846882261" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1846882261" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1846882261" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1846882261-img" id="article-gallery-2-1846882261">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1846882261" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-837495775">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Devil May Cry 5
   </em>
  </strong>
  marked a return to form for the series for most fans, after the highly divisive
  <em>
   DMC
  </em>
  . The multi-protagonist action-combat systems continue to evolve throughout the game and even beyond its ending. Some would even argue that combat doesn't show its true depth until players have beaten the game at least once.
 </p>
 <p>
  With that said, there's already a lot of variety among the three main characters' varied playstyles, allowing players to get to know each of Nero, V, and Dante's moves in their respective sections of the game. Players who click with the combat system have much more to experience after the main campaign is done though, with New Game+ and arena modes allowing players to fully unlock move lists and experiment with different characters more freely.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sifu">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Sifu
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-path-of-vengeance">
  The Path Of Vengeance
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1735200548" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1735200548" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1735200548" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1735200548" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1735200548-img" id="article-gallery-3-1735200548">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1735200548" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1925746761">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sifu
   </em>
  </strong>
  might have the most skill-based combat system in any character action game. Execution and timing are as important as memorizing button combos in the game. Despite having fewer flashy combos than your typical character-action game,
  <em>
   Sifu
  </em>
  's lengthy move list is made up of semi-realistic martial arts moves that give players utility in combat as opposed to higher damage special attacks.
 </p>
 <p>
  Each move that players can unlock as they progress has its own use and purpose, meaning the rogue-like choices of what to invest in on a given run have a real impact on the player's progress. By incorporating weapon styles, and giving players several defensive and offensive options to use at any given time,
  <em>
   Sifu
  </em>
  manages to create a deep skill-based combat system with an exceedingly high skill ceiling.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bayonetta-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Bayonetta 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="witch-time">
  Witch Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-877179555" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-877179555" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-877179555" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-877179555" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-877179555-img" id="article-gallery-4-877179555">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-877179555" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1530826636">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Some players might prefer the earlier games, but
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bayonetta 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  managed to build on an already well-established skill-based, combo-driven, combat system in some interesting ways. As with previous games, the core concepts of timed dodges to activate witch-time, and combining melee and ranged combat on the fly return. However,
  <em>
   Bayonetta 3
  </em>
  replaces the climax-summoning mechanics of the previous games with a more active system.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Demon Slave and Demon Masquerade systems offer different ways to interact with Bayonetta's demonic minions. The former allows players to control the Infernal Demons directly, with several different combat applications. The Masquerade system lets Bayonetta fuse with the demons to gain new combat and traversal abilities. This arguably brings these systems more into line with the rest of the skill-based combat, as opposed to the previous games' flashy combat finishers.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ninja-gaiden-black">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Ninja Gaiden Black
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="izuna-drop">
  Izuna Drop
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-720969617" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-720969617" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-720969617" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-720969617" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-720969617-img" id="article-gallery-5-720969617">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-720969617" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-394597771">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  2004's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Gaiden
   </em>
  </strong>
  was Team Ninja's take on the Tecmo series of the same name. The game was subsequently re-released with additional content as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Gaiden Black
   </em>
  </strong>
  on the Xbox, and again as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Gaiden Sigma
   </em>
  </strong>
  on the PS3. No matter which version of the game early 2000s players happened to play, though,
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  remains one of the best interpretations of the series' challenging character-action combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  As an original action game concept, Team Ninja was unable to lean on the series' previous games for mechanical inspiration. Instead, they set out to create an action game system that relied on player reflexes and responsiveness, as opposed to memorization, to convey challenge. The combat in
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  is difficult to master but satisfying to execute well, and the Izuna Drop remains one of the most iconic character action game moves of all time, so it's safe to say they succeeded.
 </p>
 <h2 id="darksiders">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Darksiders
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fallen-horseman">
  Fallen Horseman
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1176480715" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1176480715" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1176480715" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1176480715" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1176480715-img" id="article-gallery-6-1176480715">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1176480715" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-980411488">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before the sequels branched out into open-area settings, ARPG loot, and souls-like mechanics, the original
  <strong>
   <em>
    Darksiders
   </em>
  </strong>
  was much more of a straightforward character action game. Taking the role of War, a fallen horseman of the apocalypse, players are sent on a questionable quest of redemption that crosses both heaven and hell.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combat has a similar design to other character-action games, like the earlier
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  entries. War has a sword and scythe for melee combos, as well as some ranged options to mix in. In an interesting twist on the typical structure of these games,
  <em>
   Darksiders
  </em>
  introduced light metroidvania elements to its exploration. The player acquires new traversal abilities for War as they progress, which open up new areas and can be used to backtrack for hidden upgrades.
  <em>
   Darksiders
  </em>
  is a varied series, but the original is still the best entry for character-action fans.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="no-more-heroes-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   No More Heroes 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="parody-paradise">
  Parody Paradise
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1384643233" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1384643233" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1384643233" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1384643233" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1384643233-img" id="article-gallery-7-1384643233">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1384643233" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-364669884">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    No More Heroes 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  builds on the combat established by the series' previous games, incorporating elements from each while fleshing out the combo abilities of the beam katana. If there were any doubts about the character-action credentials of the previous games,
  <em>
   No More Heroes 3
  </em>
  eliminates them, giving players a wide array of techniques to express themselves in combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game also reverts to the format of the first
  <em>
   No More Heroes
  </em>
  , giving players a semi-open world to explore as they complete side jobs to earn enough cash to challenge the games' bosses. By blending familiar hallmarks of the series with a more modern design,
  <em>
   No More Heroes 3
  </em>
  provides a solid character-action game with a unique brand of humor.
 </p>
 <h2 id="metal-gear-rising-revengeance">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Metal Gear Rising: Revengeance
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dynamic-melon-slicing">
  Dynamic Melon Slicing
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-405586069" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-405586069" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-405586069" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-405586069" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-405586069-img" id="article-gallery-8-405586069">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-405586069" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1120178319">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the time, a lot was made of the "dynamic slicing" technology that underpinned
  <strong>
   <em>
    Metal Gear Rising: Revengeance
   </em>
  </strong>
  's melee combat. But that unique mechanic overshadowed the tightly designed character-action combat that made up 90% of the game. The dynamic slicing made for flashy finishes, but Raiden's combo-driven katana combat style is what makes the game fun to play.
 </p>
 <p>
  The two modes of combat work well together, with the player stringing together combos, pulling off parries, and activating blade mode to slow time and perform precision cuts. The game deviates a long way from
  <em>
   Metal Gear Solid
  </em>
  's serious political thriller angle, instead doubling down on the fantastical elements of
  <em>
   Metal Gear
  </em>
  , hence the cyborg ninja main character. As a character-action game, though, it offers a unique and entertaining ride.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afterlove EP Review</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/afterlove-ep-review/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  is the latest game by Mohammed Fahmi, a game designer best known for his work on the
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  games. While you can certainly get a whiff of the
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  formula in
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  , the latter is at once more nuanced, sobering, and relatable than the urban fantasy duology. These differences are enough to make
  <em>
   Afterlove
  </em>
  a breath of fresh air for anyone who bounced off
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  , but still familiar for returning fans.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Taking place a year after the death of the protagonist's girlfriend Cinta,
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  offers a stark and honest look at the grieving process, made all the more poignant by the unfortunate passing of Fahmi in 2022, when the game was only partially completed. The loss of the game's creative lead may have had a material impact on the final product, which is marred by at-times devastating bugs and a general lack of polish, which weigh down an otherwise heart-rending experience. But looking past these shortcomings will reveal a painfully earnest and endlessly charming story that burrows in the mind, not to be forgotten about any time soon.
 </p>
 <p>
  I've played through
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  twice now—logging a total of about 14 hours in just two days—so perhaps the greatest single-sentence compliment I can pay the game is that I wanted to continue living in its sketchy, vibrant world, even into the wee hours of the night. Indeed, it's a surprisingly compelling game, though players lacking a tolerance for slower, less dramatic narratives and stripped-down gameplay might want to look elsewhere. But if you're looking for something original that can pull on your heartstrings, then
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  might just be up your alley.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="afterlove-ep-sticky-grief">
  Afterlove EP: Sticky Grief
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2128494475" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2128494475" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2128494475" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2128494475" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2128494475-img" id="article-gallery-1-2128494475">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2128494475" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1952496564">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Afterlove
  </em>
  centers on Rama, a young man struggling with the passing of his girlfriend, who we only get to meet properly during the game's prologue. The details of her death are never fully expounded, but suffice it to say that it was traumatic by virtue of its suddenness—the first eerie parallel between the game's story and Fahmi's real-world death. But despite only seeing Cinta for a few minutes at the start of the game, she is a constant presence, both literally and figuratively: Rama hallucinates her speaking to him.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Afterlve EP
  </em>
  is about grief, but it's not shouting-at-the-sky, pulling-your-hair-out grief. It's mature, complex, and messy grief that doesn't let its victims move on, even while the world keeps moving around them. This is the conundrum Rama finds himself in at the start of the game, when he feels inspired to bring his old band together with a renewed creative vigor. This driving force—his passion for expressing his grief about Cinta—is stunted by the emotional and creative needs of his friends and bandmates, who have moved on with their lives in the wake of Cinta's death. Rama's trauma, manifested in his hallucinations of Cinta, stands in the way of his empathy for these bandmates, who he once considered his closest friends before he faded into a year-long depressive miasma.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's in these awkward and down-to-earth interactions, wherein Rama is usually in the wrong, that
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  is at its best. Rama is effectively learning how to function again after the loss of his partner. The hallucinations of Cinta serve a starkly pragmatic purpose, but this phantasmagoric shell blocks the light of the outside world as much as it keeps psychic threats from breaking in. This complex interplay between Rama's desire to move forward and his reluctance to let go of the past is what informs
  <em>
   Afterlove
  </em>
  's intimate storytelling, which feels infinitely authentic and charming, even as the game reveals some of its cracks.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-moment-to-moment-afterlove-ep-experience">
  The Moment-to-Moment Afterlove EP Experience
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-586501416" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-586501416" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-586501416" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-586501416" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-586501416-img" id="article-gallery-2-586501416">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-586501416" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1131830736">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  has been marketed as a cross between a visual novel and a rhythm game, but that might send the wrong message. The truth is,
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  is almost entirely a visual novel with some dating sim mechanics sprinkled on top: the meat-and-potatoes of the experience is the player's interactions with its NPCs, all of whom are instantly lovable and surprisingly complex.
 </p>
 <p>
  After a second playthrough, I'm happy to share that the player's decisions do alter the course of
  <em>
   Afterlove
  </em>
  's story. Dialog options don't often do much to steer conversations in a particular direction, but who Rama spends his time with will certainly impact the overall narrative. These alterations take the form of pure narrative content—you'll miss out on impactful scenes with Satria if you choose to romance Mira, for example—but they also factor into the game's finale. This mostly takes the form of a different final scene and epilogue, but it's still nice to see how Rama's future may be molded by your in-game choices, even if most of the actual differences feel isolated from the core of the narrative.
 </p>
 <p>
  The rhythm game slice of the
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  pie is unfortunately understated, to say the least. These gameplay sections, which usually take the form of band practices or live performances, are few and far between, and you'll usually go several in-game days before running into one. When you do get to engage with these minigames, they hardly pose any mechanical challenge. They are all straightforward, and even players with little to no experience with the rhythm genre will cruise through them with ease. There's a persistent lack of variety and surprise in these gameplay sections, and they can sometimes feel like an afterthought. But if you view these gameplay sections more as punctuations for emotional story beats, then their minimalist design is a bit more forgivable.
 </p>
 <p>
  It helps that the music, courtesy of Indonesian rock band L'Alphaalpha, is genuinely fantastic, making it easy to melt into the deep emotion of the broader narrative. But at the end of the day, the rhythm minigames are little more than extended quicktime events set against a banger soundtrack. They're nice if taken at face value, but they aren't mechanically interesting. My interpretation of them as glorified cutscenes was confirmed when I tried to intentionally fail a few of them and found you can't. Even if you miss every single note, the performance will go on, and characters in the subsequent scenes usually don't comment on your fumbles.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bugs-plague-afterlove-ep">
  Bugs Plague Afterlove EP
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2132638481" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2132638481" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2132638481" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2132638481" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2132638481-img" id="article-gallery-3-2132638481">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2132638481" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1698336928">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The fact that Cinta is the only human voice you hear—outside the rhythm sections, of course—helps to better establish her as an obtrusive, overpowering force in Rama's world. It's unfortunate, then, that I ran into a repeated glitch that skipped all her dialog, as if I hit the fast-forward button. The only way to fix this bug was to close the game entirely and boot it back up, but it proved to be pervasive, repeatedly cropping up for no obvious reason. Other immersion-breaking disruptions included character portraits not lining up with who Rama was speaking with, and characters talking off-screen.
 </p>
 <p>
  But these inconveniences pale in comparison to the biggest glitch during my first playthrough. Throughout the game, players can choose to speak with a therapist, who will grant insight into what Rama may be going through at a given point in the story. Towards the end of the game, when I was reaching the climax of my chosen romance subplot, I decided to visit the therapist, only to watch in disbelief as Rama recounted scenes that had yet to occur in said romance subplot, spoiling its finale. In a game that lives and dies on the back of its narrative, this sort of issue is tantamount to game-breaking.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  lacks meaningful gameplay, and its bugs can range from inconvenient to apocalyptic, so it says a lot that it's still worth recommending it to anyone who likes smaller, story-driven games. Make no mistake, the aforementioned issues do drag down the overall experience, but at the end of the day,
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  is more than the sum of its parts. Its music, charming characters, nuanced portrayal of grief, and beautiful manga-inspired art design are all worth the price of admission. If developer Pikselnesia can hammer out its more troubling bugs, then
  <em>
   Afterlove EP
  </em>
  has a chance to become an all-timer in the visual novel genre.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Afterlove EP
   </em>
  </strong>
  is currently available on Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PC, and Nintendo Switch. Game Rant was provided a PS5 code for this review.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nolan North's 10 Best Characters</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nolan-north-best-characters-performances/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   Nolan North
  </strong>
  is one of the most prolific actors in gaming, and his roles have reached the status of icons that others only strive towards. Nolan North has been responsible for the voice behind some of the greatest and most varied characters in video games, and he deserves the utmost appreciation for his talent and his roles.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With almost 3 decades of acting credits, incredible voice work, and performance capture, it’s time to look back at some of Nolan North’s best characters and the content that they come from to see how his own work stacks against each other for the top spot.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="david">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   David
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-disturbing-cannibal-leader">
  The Disturbing Cannibal Leader
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-434060932" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-434060932" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-434060932" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-434060932" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-434060932-img" id="article-gallery-1-434060932">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-434060932" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-837760098">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: The Last of Us
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  is filled with plenty of horrors both from the cordyceps virus and from surviving humans, and David is perhaps one of the worst survivors who thrives in this new world as a cannibal. Nolan North brings such a gentle intensity to David with his calming voice, but it’s obvious that there’s something not quite about the character in the way he carries himself and speaks.
 </p>
 <p>
  David is a true monster, and seeing Nolan North inhabit a role so dark and opposite from Nathan Drake just goes to show how talented he is, as David is truly unforgettable in a plethora of disturbing ways that make players feel unsafe around him entirely.
 </p>
 <h2 id="raphael">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Raphael
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-always-angry-new-yorker-turtle-with-more-than-just-a-shell-on-his-shoulders">
  The Always-Angry New Yorker Turtle With More Than Just a Shell On His Shoulders
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-717616901" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-717616901" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-717616901" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-717616901" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-717616901-img" id="article-gallery-2-717616901">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-717616901" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1657352111">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: TMNT (2007)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  was an interesting
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  movie that definitely deserved a sequel, as it sought to ask the question of what would happen with the four turtle brothers after the total defeat of Shredder – and Nolan North was the perfect choice to play the aggressive and angst of Raphael, who is always in a constant state of disdain over losing the vigilante life.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nolan North’s performance as Raphael embodies the New York accent and the aggressive style that audiences have come to love about the red bandana-wearing and sai-wielding Ninja Turtle, and his relationship with the other turtles, especially the “leader” Leonardo, embodies such frustration that it’s a shame there wasn’t more of this story-rich character.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-penguin">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   The Penguin
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-sadistic-and-greedy-mobster-of-gotham-city">
  The Sadistic and Greedy Mobster of Gotham City
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-787717838" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-787717838" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-787717838" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-787717838" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-787717838-img" id="article-gallery-3-787717838">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-787717838" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1066931648">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Batman: Arkham City, Batman: Arkham Knight, Batman: Arkham Origins, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Penguin is easily one of Nolan North’s best characters, especially for how most people who have played the
  <em>
   Batman Arkham
  </em>
  games fail to even register that it’s Nolan North behind the voice. Oswald Cobblepot has a cockney accent this time around, providing him with a harsh voice that’s unlike the other works of Nolan North.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nolan North’s portrayal of the Penguin is one of the most unique, and easily one of the best, highlighted throughout various appearances to display his talents. Nolan North gets Penguin’s cadences down to a tee, along with his sheer greed, sadistic nature, and overwhelming cowardice when facing Batman’s fists.
 </p>
 <h2 id="desmond-miles">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Desmond Miles
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-young-man-destined-for-the-ultimate-fate-of-an-assassin">
  A Young Man Destined for the Ultimate Fate of an Assassin
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-101240059" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-101240059" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-101240059" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-101240059" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-101240059-img" id="article-gallery-4-101240059">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-101240059" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-72724598">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Assassin’s Creed, Assassin’s Creed 2, Assassin’s Creed: Brotherhood, Assassin’s Creed: Revelations, Assassin’s Creed 3
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When most think about the classic era of
  <em>
   Assassin’s Creed
  </em>
  , it’s more often than not that they think of Ezio Auditore rather than the sections featured in the modern day, but that doesn’t mean the pieces with Desmond Miles are not worth engaging in, and they still feature as some of the most story-rich character-driven moments from the series, led by Nolan North as the protagonist, Desmond Miles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nolan North’s Desmond Miles is far calmer than other characters, but he can become frequently frustrated after being out of his depth when it comes to this massive world of Assassins and Templars that he’s seemingly been thrust into. Desmond’s inexperience, willingness to learn, and rebellious streak make him a fun modern-day protagonist that the series definitely misses.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="iron-man">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Iron Man
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-confident-and-snarky-genius-to-rival-rdj">
  The Confident and Snarky Genius to Rival RDJ
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-903888543" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-903888543" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-903888543" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-903888543" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-903888543-img" id="article-gallery-5-903888543">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-903888543" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1550547763">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: The Avengers
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While Square Enix’s
  <em>
   The Avengers
  </em>
  didn’t get its time in the sun (much like the next entry), it still had its redeeming qualities in its cast and characters. One such character was Iron Man and Tony Stark, played by Nolan North with such confidence and a snarky attitude that it definitely becomes more than just another standard Robert Downey Jr. impression.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nolan North brings his own characterization to Iron Man, and while it’s easy to hear his distinctive voice, it’s also nice to hear a different side of it along with a new personality befitting of a comic-accurate Iron Man that Nolan North brings to the gaming scene, and hopefully for another game in the future.
 </p>
 <h2 id="superman">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Superman
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-booming-man-of-steel-with-a-dark-streak">
  The Booming Man of Steel with a Dark Streak
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1102441575" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1102441575" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1102441575" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1102441575" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1102441575-img" id="article-gallery-6-1102441575">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1102441575" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-804639815">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Like
  <em>
   The Avengers
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  didn’t get the time it deserved, but at least audiences got to hear Nolan North’s portrayal of Superman – even if that was rather short-lived. Before Brainiac’s corruption, Superman can be heard in various audio logs and seen in museum holograms in the Hall of Justice, and he comes off as so friendly and so Superman-like thanks to his strong voice that has such a gentleness that it’s hard not to admire him.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s a shame that after Brainiac’s corruption, there are still elements of that bolstering chest-carrying voice attributed to an iconic Superman, but with a more sadistic streak – a smirk that knows that he can tear the world in two with his palms should he choose to.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-guardian-rsquo-s-best-friend-a-loving-voice-in-dark-times">
  The Guardian’s Best Friend, a Loving Voice in Dark Times
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1150568097" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1150568097" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1150568097" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1150568097" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1150568097-img" id="article-gallery-7-1150568097">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1150568097" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-467946908">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Destiny, Destiny 2
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Peter Dinklage once voiced the Ghost in
  <em>
   Destiny
  </em>
  , but despite his talent, it’s safe to say that Nolan North left much more of a lasting impression, and it’s always a treat to hear the Ghost get more voice lines with each season and expansion. The Ghost in
  <em>
   Destiny
  </em>
  isn’t just any Ghost – he’s your ghost, and he’s with you through thick and thin to resurrect you and experience the wonders and the pains of the war of Light and Dark from day one.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nolan North’s portrayal of the Ghost is one filled with curiosity, bravery, and devotion to the Vanguard – but most importantly, you, Guardian. The Ghost is the little light that we love, and Nolan North brings such life to such a small and robotic thing that we can’t help but cherish it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="deadpool">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Deadpool
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-defining-voice-for-the-merc-with-a-mouth">
  A Defining Voice for the Merc with a Mouth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-843922146" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-843922146" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-843922146" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-843922146" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-843922146-img" id="article-gallery-8-843922146">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-843922146" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1053134378">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Deadpool, Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3: The Black Order, Marvel’s Midnight Suns
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Before Ryan Reynolds took the character to live-action to gross over a billion dollars, there was Nolan North in the red spandex and the disfigured skin. Nolan North still voices Deadpool and Wade Wilson, and it’s always a treat to hear. Nolan North’s Deadpool has grit, snark, sass, and a bundle of mayhem and hilarity in every line.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s hard not to hear Nolan North’s ramblings as Deadpool without growing a smile, as it’s obvious from the voice that this is such a fun character to be for Nolan North, that it only makes audiences want more of him as the Merc with a Mouth who has an irresistible charm and obnoxious personality we just can’t get enough of.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="edward-richtofen">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Edward Richtofen
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-crazed-german-scientist-of-ultimis-and-the-doomed-genius-of-primis">
  The Crazed German Scientist of Ultimis and the Doomed Genius of Primis
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1506490991" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1506490991" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1506490991" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1506490991" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1506490991-img" id="article-gallery-9-1506490991">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1506490991" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-487625326">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Call of Duty: World at War, Call of Duty: Black Ops, Call of Duty: Black Ops 2, Call of Duty: Black Ops 3, Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Call of Duty quite simply wouldn’t be the same without Nolan North as Edward Richtofen, a character that has featured in practically every Treyarch title since
  <em>
   Call of Duty: World at War
  </em>
  , and for good reason. Edward Richtofen is the voice, face, and soul of
  <em>
   COD Zombies
  </em>
  , as it’s a character brimming with so much personality, and it’s clear that Nolan North has such fun doing the voice.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether it’s the intense acting featured in cutscenes and audio logs, or the fun voice lines of characters reacting to new weapons from the Mystery Box, the taste of Perk-a-Colas, or simply talking to the crews of Primis and Ultimis, Richtofen is essential to the DNA and soul of
  <em>
   COD Zombies
  </em>
  , and this mad German scientist can only ever be portrayed by Nolan North.
 </p>
 <h2 id="nathan-drake">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Nathan Drake
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-humorous-treasure-hunter-who-seeks-dangers-and-fortune">
  A Humorous Treasure Hunter Who Seeks Dangers and Fortune
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1834519623" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1834519623" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1834519623" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1834519623" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1834519623-img" id="article-gallery-10-1834519623">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1834519623" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-547406841">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Featured in: Uncharted: Drake’s Fortune, Uncharted 2: Among Thieves, Uncharted 3: Drake’s Deception, Uncharted: 4: A Thief’s End
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Nathan Drake is easily Nolan North’s most defining character, and this character received four incredible games from Naughty Dog with Nate in the protagonist role – with Nolan North providing an incredible performance each and every time. Nathan Drake evolved with each game, both in terms of graphics and emotion, but that snarky and sarcastic explorer always kept his sense of adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nathan Drake’s admiration for treasure hunting, deep-rooted care for the ones he loves, and his talents at anything to do with parkour and killing people, make him an action icon, and it’s great to see Nolan North bring so much charm to the role to make this gaming’s Indiana Jones.
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Open-World Games Where the Villain is a More Interesting Character Than the Hero</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/open-world-games-villain-more-interesting-than-hero/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Open world games pose challenges for narrative designers due to player freedom in pace.
     </li>
     <li>
      Complex and well-written villains like Handsome Jack, Alduin, Radagon, and Mr. House are more compelling than the heroes in their respective games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Villains like Handsome Jack, Joseph Seed, and Alduin add depth and intrigue, overshadowing the uninteresting protagonists.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Open world games are something of a challenge for narrative designers, because the player can feasibly do the story at any pace they like. That means any urgency or dread an antagonist might be trying to get across just won't work. This challenge means that developers need to work harder, and sometimes, that means the villain becomes not only great, but far more interesting than the hero character.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether it be Machiavellian masterminds operating events from the background or in-your-face charismatic dictators spouting pseudo-philosophy, there are plenty of great
  <strong>
   overshadowing villains to choose from in the world of open-world gaming
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="borderlands-2---handsome-jack">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Borderlands 2 - Handsome Jack
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-iconic-villain-of-considerable-depth">
  An Iconic Villain Of Considerable Depth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-951218121" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-951218121" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-951218121" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-951218121" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-951218121-img" id="article-gallery-1-951218121">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-951218121" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-108012132">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Borderlands
  </em>
  franchise has a strange tendency to make the protagonist characters more interesting in the following games, rather than the game they first feature in. For example, Lilith is nothing in the original game, but she becomes incredibly important in the second. This vacuum for the hero means the franchise has increasingly leaned on outlandish and bravura villains, with none being as famous as Handsome Jack.
 </p>
 <p>
  From the very beginning of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Borderlands 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the CEO of the Hyperion corporation makes himself known, and his presence looms large throughout the entire game, taunting the player constantly through brash humor and becoming the central way of personifying the unfeeling corporations. Yet, by the end of the game, Handsome Jack becomes a villain of considerable depth, and his enduring presence in the canon of the franchise's villains speaks volumes about how beloved he is.
 </p>
 <h2 id="skyrim---alduin">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Skyrim - Alduin
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-anti-dovahkiin">
  The Anti-Dovahkiin
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-976589106" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-976589106" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-976589106" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-976589106" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-976589106-img" id="article-gallery-2-976589106">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-976589106" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1440523673">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bethesda RPGs tend to have a pretty major problem with uninteresting protagonists. This is for good reason, though, because they're meant to be blank spaces that the player can project themselves onto. However, this also means that other characters in the story need to pick up the slack, especially in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Skyrim
   </strong>
   .
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Enter Alduin. Taking a leaf from the kinds of intellectual dragons found in the Forgotten Realms world, Alduin is not just a big scary dragon; he occupies a philosophical position about the nature of death in the world of Tamriel, and he single-handedly forces other characters, like the Greybeards, to become more interesting by proxy. Though he's not in-game in-person very much, Alduin is a memorable foe who is far more interesting than the hero.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="elden-ring---radagon">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Elden Ring - Radagon
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="put-these-foolish-ambitions-to-rest">
  Put These Foolish Ambitions To Rest
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1674874412" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1674874412" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1674874412" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1674874412" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1674874412-img" id="article-gallery-3-1674874412">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1674874412" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-397301317">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It wouldn't be a surprise if many gamers played through the entirety of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Elden Ring
   </strong>
  </em>
  without fully understanding what the story actually was about, and like
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  , the Tarnished is a complete uninteresting blank slate with little perspective of their own.
 </p>
 <p>
  Luckily, FromSoftware makes some of the most depth-filled characters in modern RPGs if players are willing to do their homework, and no FromSoftware antagonist has reached the levels of complexity, mystery, and sheer intensity as Radagon, the counter-part to Marika in more ways than one. He's a mystery that befuddles the lore community to this day, making him a fascinating counterpoint to the blank slate of the Tarnished as they journey to become Elden Lord.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-legend-of-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom---ganondorf">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   The Legend Of Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom - Ganondorf
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-franchise-39-s-best-incarnations-of-the-tragically-evil-villain">
  One Of The Franchise's Best Incarnations Of The Tragically Evil Villain
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1833005124" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1833005124" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1833005124" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1833005124" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1833005124-img" id="article-gallery-4-1833005124">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1833005124" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-517900715">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though it can be painful to admit, one of the weakest parts of every
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda
  </em>
  game is Link himself. Again, he's something of an audience insert character, but it's hard not to wonder whether he could be a more interesting character if any of his games chose to shine a spotlight on him with a bit more detail.
 </p>
 <p>
  This remains true in
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which actually features one of the best incarnations of the franchise's perennial villain, Ganondorf, a tragically evil character who is willing to go to extreme lengths to disrupt the peace. He's a compelling counterpoint to Link, and he is also the most memorable character of the game by far.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077---johnny-silverhand">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Cyberpunk 2077 - Johnny Silverhand
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dystopia-of-moral-grays">
  A Dystopia Of Moral Grays
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-330629092" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-330629092" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-330629092" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-330629092" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-330629092-img" id="article-gallery-5-330629092">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-330629092" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1384032994">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  First thing's first, Silverhand is a very complicated character. Anyone who has played
  <em>
   <strong>
    Cyberpunk: 2077
   </strong>
  </em>
  knows that this ghost that haunts V's mind is abrasive, rude, and often antagonistic. In many versions of V's journey, he can be a friend, but in others, he is the exact force V is fighting against, literally and metaphorically.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite V being something of a fleshed-out character, they can't hope to stand up to the brilliant writing of Silverhand, who is a flawed foil to V the entire way through the game, even through the side quests, constantly questioning, bargaining, hijacking, and being a general nuisance. Some may not even see him as a villain at all, but he's certainly one of the most compelling antagonists to come out of video games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="far-cry-5---joseph-seed">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Far Cry 5 - Joseph Seed
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-compelling-and-incredibly-well-written-villain">
  A Compelling And Incredibly Well-Written Villain
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1238499064" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1238499064" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1238499064" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1238499064" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1238499064-img" id="article-gallery-6-1238499064">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1238499064" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1516263559">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  By the time
  <em>
   <strong>
    Far Cry 5
   </strong>
  </em>
  rolled around, the
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  franchise had become well known for its focus not just on the villain but the villain's entire family and philosophy, defining the marketing for each game and the themes therein.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Far Cry 5
  </em>
  , the well-armed player character faces off against Joseph Seed, the leader of a Christian fundamentalist cult who has apocalyptic plans for the world. Like other
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  villains, he is certifiably insane, but he is incredibly compelling, really well-written, and entirely overshadows the nothing character of the protagonist.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="fallout-new-vegas---mr-house">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout: New Vegas - Mr. House
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-house-always-wins">
  The House Always Wins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-634997313" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-634997313" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-634997313" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-634997313" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-634997313-img" id="article-gallery-7-634997313">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-634997313" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-634644955">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite being a broadly silent character, Obsidian Entertainment's brilliant writing actually makes the Courier perspective character of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fallout: New Vegas
   </strong>
  </em>
  pretty interesting. That said, the Courier has to contend with some of the best-written villains in all gaming, which is a bit of an unfair comparison.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of the many great choices that could have filled this spot from
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  's diverse and interesting factions (Joshua Graham or Ulysses were strong alternates), none loom so large as Mr. House, the epitome of nihilistic corporate greed who manipulates the world into a libertarian dictator state. He's complex, insane, and utterly compelling, making him not just the best villain in the game, but one of the best villains in gaming.
 </p>
 <h2 id="far-cry-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Far Cry 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-definition-of-insanity">
  The Definition Of Insanity
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1208884747" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1208884747" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1208884747" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1208884747" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1208884747-img" id="article-gallery-8-1208884747">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1208884747" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1365357007">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Expectations were generally low for
  <em>
   <strong>
    Far Cry 3
   </strong>
  </em>
  when it was first announced. That all changed, however, when Ubisoft realized the pure gold they were sitting on with Michael Mando's performance of Vaas, the psychopathic pirate captain who has taken over one of the main islands of the game, muses over the philosophy of insanity, and dominates the pantheon of
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  villains.
 </p>
 <p>
  Vaas, as a character, entirely changed how villains were presented in video games. Instead of afterthoughts, they became central to how games were pitched, and Vaas himself would go down as one of gaming's greatest baddies. While dude-bro Jason Brody as a hero is actually more interesting than he seems at first, he is nothing compared to Vaas, who has rightly become famous even outside of the video game world.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Open-World Games with Hack and Slash Combat, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-open-world-games-hack-slash-combat-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Open-world games offer big levels for players to entertain themselves with mayhem and exploration.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some open-world games focus on creative combat like hacking and slashing enemies in various ways.
     </li>
     <li>
      Open-world games like NieR: Automata, Dragon's Dogma 2, and others offer unique combat mechanics and engaging storylines.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The open-world and sandbox genres often go hand in hand. It’s because they give players a big open level where they can do anything to entertain themselves. Particularly the
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto
  </em>
  series, where they could ride around Liberty City/Vice City/San Andreas, and cause so much mayhem that the authorities have to break out tanks and choppers against them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some games tone down the mayhem but generally stick to guns, fisticuffs, or even superpowers to fight off foes and rule the land. But there are some that prefer a more artful way of dispatching enemies: breaking out a sharp blade and cutting their way to the end of the game. If players want open-world games with hack and slash combat, these are the best of the bunch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="nier-automata">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   NieR: Automata
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="where-death-is-just-an-opportunity-to-make-new-friends-or-enemies">
  Where Death is Just an Opportunity to Make New Friends or Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1136197999" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1136197999" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1136197999" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136197999" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1136197999-img" id="article-gallery-1-1136197999">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1136197999" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1086688912">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After
  <em>
   NieR
  </em>
  managed to improve on
  <em>
   Drakengard
  </em>
  with its open-zone action gameplay,
  <strong>
   <em>
    NieR: Automata
   </em>
  </strong>
  stepped up from its predecessor by going open-world. Kind of. Compared to its rivals, its world is rather small and linear. But then there’s not much to explore in a proxy war between Androids and Machines. Its combat is rather straightforward too.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players mix light and heavy attacks into different combos to rack up damage. With the right timing, they could create openings by launching counterattacks on striking foes or slip past them altogether. What is unique is that, if they die, they can respawn and find their old body, where they can retrieve or repair it. If the repair works, they’ll gain a temporary ally. If it fails, they’ll become an enemy they must fight.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-rsquo-s-dogma-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon’s Dogma 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="hacking-and-slashing-with-the-help-of-some-friends">
  Hacking and Slashing With The Help Of Some Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1544676739" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1544676739" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1544676739" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1544676739" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1544676739-img" id="article-gallery-2-1544676739">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1544676739" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-415239762">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hack and slash games don’t have to be set in the past or a medieval-looking fantasy world. It just helps would-be swordfighters to be in a time and place when guns were either not a thing or were much clunkier to use. However, when it comes to helping the Arisen take down the dragon who marked them in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dragon’s Dogma 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , guns might be the least of their worries.
 </p>
 <p>
  As the Arisen, the player must make their way through a world torn into civil strife by picking the right class and weaponry for themselves and their Pawns. These are AI-controlled NPCs who can help make a difference, either as blade-wielding knights, spellcasting Tricksters, or more. The more the player and their Pawns work at the right vocation, the better they’ll be at handling foes, emergent events, and eventually the dragon itself.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Middle Earth: Shadow of Mordor
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="making-enemies-in-middle-earth">
  Making Enemies in Middle Earth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2127825796" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2127825796" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2127825796" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2127825796" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2127825796-img" id="article-gallery-3-2127825796">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2127825796" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-271853635">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Middle Earth
  </em>
  games were a case of snatching defeat from victory, as players loved its approach to the world of J.R.R Tolkien, but weren't as big on Warner Bros’ business practices, particularly regarding microtransactions, with a big stink needed for them to get removed later on. Even then, players generally prefer the first game,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Middle Earth: Shadow of Mordor
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Here, players take control of Talion in his search for revenge on the forces of Sauron for killing his family.
 </p>
 <p>
  The combat resembled the
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham
  </em>
  games, of all things, as building up combo chains from its freeflow fights could help players pull off different moves. But it was best known for its Nemesis system, where the game will track specific Uruk orcs, letting players decide whether to cut them down ASAP, or get stronger, so they can get better rewards for beating them later.
 </p>
 <h2 id="like-a-dragon-ishin">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Like a Dragon: Ishin
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="modernize-japan-with-just-4-different-fighting-styles">
  Modernize Japan with Just 4 Different Fighting Styles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-269670087" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-269670087" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-269670087" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-269670087" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-269670087-img" id="article-gallery-4-269670087">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-269670087" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1678667724">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Style-switching feels like it’s been part of the
  <em>
   Yakuza/Like a Dragon
  </em>
  series since the beginning. But RGG Studio only began dabbling in it with their samurai games,
  <em>
   Ryu Ga Gotoku: Kenzan
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Ryu Ga Gotoku: Ishin
  </em>
  . The former is still locked to Japanese PS3s, but the latter got remade for the West as
  <em>
   <strong>
    Like a Dragon: Ishin.
   </strong>
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  It follows Ryōma Sakamoto as he hunts down the masked assassin responsible for killing his lord. Players can swap between beating enemies with their fists, hacking them with Ryoma’s sword, shooting them with a pistol, or in a new style that combines sword slashes and gunshots in a whirling frenzy. All of them have their own uses (though some are better than others) and can be chained together for some impressive combos.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost-of-tsushima">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="save-tsushima-by-mastering-the-blade">
  Save Tsushima By Mastering the Blade
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1245985624" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1245985624" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1245985624" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1245985624" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1245985624-img" id="article-gallery-5-1245985624">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1245985624" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-142072298">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sucker Punch hasn’t been a stranger to open-world games, but the melee combat in the
  <em>
   InFamous
  </em>
  games was pretty simplistic. By joining forces with Japan Studio, and visiting the real island of Tsushima, the studio made
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ghost of Tsushima
   </em>
  </strong>
  , where samurai Jin Sakai is caught between upholding the warrior code or breaking it to defend the island against the Mongols.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can distract foes with smoke bombs and firecrackers before taking them out with chain assassinations for stealth sections, while head-to-head combat involves matching their stance to their armed opponent (stone stance for swordsmen, water stance for shield bearers, etc.). It’s a more involved process that’s got fans looking forward to how it’ll evolve for its upcoming sequel,
  <em>
   Ghost of Yotei
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
