<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>8 Horror Game Characters Who Would Be Perfect Dates For Valentine's Day</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/horror-game-characters-perfect-dates-valentines-day/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Some horror game characters can make surprisingly good dating options, such as the Spirit from Dead by Daylight.
     </li>
     <li>
      Regina from Dino Crisis and Juliet Starling from Lollipop Chainsaw could also offer unique dating experiences.
     </li>
     <li>
      While unconventional, characters like Pyramid Head and Alcina Dimitrescu have the potential to be intriguing dating prospects.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Horror and Valentine's Day are two things that don't often go hand-in-hand, but there are times when lines can be blurred, such as with the horror dating simulator
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hooked on You
   </em>
  </strong>
  , based on
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dead by Daylight
   </strong>
  </em>
  . This is just one example of how the two can be combined, and it may have people thinking about what other characters from different stories they could potentially date.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether they are more interested in the scary monsters or the heroes of the stories, creative gamers could potentially find an appropriate suitor even in the most terrifying of situations. These horror game characters have the potential to prove that love can still blossom even in the strangest of places.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="spirit-dead-by-daylight">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Spirit (Dead By Daylight)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="who-doesn-39-t-want-a-goth-girlfriend">
  Who Doesn't Want A Goth Girlfriend?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1959637104" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1959637104" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1959637104" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1959637104" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1959637104-img" id="article-gallery-1-1959637104">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1959637104" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-775474585">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are constant jokes made in the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dead by Daylight
   </em>
  </strong>
  community about potentially smooching the killers that players are supposed to be afraid of, and Behavior ran with it, resulting in an actual dating simulator that uses some of the characters. One of these potentially dateable killers is the Spirit. Known as one of the strongest killers in the game, her inclusion was to be accepted, as she was already popular in the scene as one of the most attractive killers.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a university student, they would know she is smart and driven, and who doesn't want a spooky dead goth girlfriend in their life? If one is able to look past her murderous proclivities and the fact she is dead, she would probably make for a fantastic date.
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hooked on You
   </strong>
  </em>
  has only helped strengthen this case, as Spirit proved to be the most popular choice.
 </p>
 <h2 id="regina-dino-crisis">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Regina (Dino Crisis)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="cares-a-great-deal-for-others">
  Cares A Great Deal For Others
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1405645680" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1405645680" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1405645680" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1405645680" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1405645680-img" id="article-gallery-2-1405645680">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1405645680" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1837638887">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As part of S.O.R.T., Regina was tasked with infiltrating a research facility and extricating Edward Kirk, only to find out that the base is overrun with dinosaurs, a very dangerous and unexpected threat that can be surprisingly terrifying. Regina mostly approaches her missions with an air of cold detachment, hardly ever being fazed by the horrors she is met with or the bloody gore she witnesses.
 </p>
 <p>
  But lonely hearts need not fret. Regina isn't a total ice queen who will ignore or harshly rebuke their advances; she actually shows great care and compassion for others, which she could also show for a potential lucky date.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="juliet-starling-lollipop-chainsaw">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Juliet Starling (Lollipop Chainsaw)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="she-can-chew-bubblegum-and-kick-ass">
  She Can Chew Bubblegum And Kick Ass
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-904638858" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-904638858" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-904638858" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-904638858" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-904638858-img" id="article-gallery-3-904638858">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-904638858" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1850398294">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Lollipop Chainsaw
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the most zany and outlandish horror games out there, verging heavily into the horror-comedy route. Starring senior high school cheerleader Juliet Starling,
  <em>
   Lollipop Chainsaw
  </em>
  begins with a sudden zombie outbreak that she is all too ready and capable of dealing with, thanks to her trusty chainsaw.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a bubbly and positive personality, a date with Juliet is bound to be filled with fun and laughter, as such personalities tend to be rather infectious. The fact she carries around the sentient head of her deceased boyfriend may cause a little difficulty in the relationship, but maybe she is just looking for the right person to move on with.
 </p>
 <h2 id="leon-s-kennedy-resident-evil-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Leon S. Kennedy (Resident Evil Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fierce-and-devoted-protector">
  A Fierce And Devoted Protector
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1747637252" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1747637252" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1747637252" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1747637252" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1747637252-img" id="article-gallery-4-1747637252">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1747637252" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-704632915">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Leon is one of the major playable characters in the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil
   </em>
  </strong>
  series, first appearing in the second game as a rookie police officer who was supposed to be on his first day on the job. He was in for one heck of a first shift, however, with Raccoon City falling to the virus and becoming overrun by zombies and other creatures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Leon was at first an earnest and kindhearted character who had rather idealistic views, but he became more mature and jaded as the series progressed. This, however, does not diminish what an excellent date he would make, as he is shown to be devoted and protective in his interactions with other characters such as Claire Redfield, Ashley Graham, and Ada Wong. But with the number of women showing genuine interest in him, it might take some work to earn his affection.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="aya-brea-parasite-eve">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Aya Brea (Parasite Eve)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="strong-independent-and-cool">
  Strong, Independent, And Cool
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2081636308" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2081636308" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2081636308" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2081636308" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2081636308-img" id="article-gallery-5-2081636308">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2081636308" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1435651063">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  From the PS1 horror classic, police officer Aya Brea finds herself saddled with the responsibility of saving the world from Eve, who threatens all of humanity with her power and dangerous plans to unleash the Ultimate Being on the world. She is not sure what this creature could be, but Aya knows she must put a stop to its creation, showing great courage and a sense of responsibility, which can be quite an attractive characteristic for someone to possess.
 </p>
 <p>
  It also helps that Aya is strong-willed, independent, strong, and open to the idea of dating, as the game opens with her on a date at the opera. She also looked killer in a black dress (or as much as someone would be able to in pixelated PS1 graphics).
 </p>
 <h2 id="pyramid-head-silent-hill-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Pyramid Head (Silent Hill 2)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-quiet-ones-are-often-great-listeners">
  The Quiet Ones Are Often Great Listeners
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-726543818" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-726543818" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-726543818" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-726543818" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-726543818-img" id="article-gallery-6-726543818">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-726543818" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2061837114">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A tragic romance story was at the center of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Silent Hill 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , as James struggled with the death of his late wife, who actually died at his hands while she was wasting away from a disease. As such, characters such as Mary and James should probably not be considered as prospective dates, but that doesn't mean that the mist of Silent Hill itself doesn't hold a potential romantic prospect for people.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fans of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Silent Hill
   </em>
  </strong>
  have made it no secret they have a curious interest in Pyramid Head. While he may not make for a very conventional date or partner, there is something intriguing about the quiet types. At the very least, it is guaranteed that he would be a great listener, even if he wouldn't be the most skilled at conversation. There are also the two small caveats that he is a manifestation of James's guilt and wields a massive weapon that could be used to cut people in half, but hey, people have to be willing to accept others' flaws for relationships to work.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ethan-winters-resident-evil-7-resident-evil-village">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Ethan Winters (Resident Evil 7/Resident Evil Village)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="would-throw-himself-head-first-into-danger">
  Would Throw Himself Head First Into Danger
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1498214377" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1498214377" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1498214377" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1498214377" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1498214377-img" id="article-gallery-7-1498214377">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1498214377" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-908781888">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 7
   </em>
  </strong>
  introduced a brand-new storyline and brand-new characters, including protagonist Ethan Winters and his family. The game opens with him traveling to the backwaters of Louisiana in search of his wife Mia, who has been missing for three years. He finds her in the Baker house and also has the misfortune of meeting the family she has been the prisoner of.
 </p>
 <p>
  This, combined with his fervent efforts to rescue his daughter in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Village
   </em>
  </strong>
  , demonstrates that Ethan is one of the most protective and loyal characters in the
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  franchise and showcases that he would go to some dangerous and terrifying places for the people he cares about. He may be infected by mold, but hey, no one is perfect, and at least it doesn't transform him into a horrific creature.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alina-dimitrescu-resident-evil-village">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Alina Dimitrescu (Resident Evil Village)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-internet-39-s-biggest-video-game-crushes">
  One Of The Internet's Biggest Video Game Crushes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-13640361" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-13640361" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-13640361" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-13640361" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-13640361-img" id="article-gallery-8-13640361">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-13640361" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-131364519">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Alcina Dimitrescu took the internet by storm when she was revealed, with her attractive appearance and astonishing height earning her much praise and adoration. Even though her part in
  <em>
   Village
  </em>
  was small and ended pretty quickly, her shadow still loomed over the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though there is every chance Alcina might collect her dates blood to feed herself and her daughters, it might be worth the risk for a date with one of the most beloved horror game characters of all time. Her murderous side might even add a little bit of excitement for those who are tired of the mundanity of most traditional dates.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hades 2 Has One Final Frontier to Reach Among the Boons of the Gods</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hades-2-greek-gods-boons-dead-post-game-melinoe-relatationship-father/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Boons play a vital role in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hades 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  's gameplay. Just like in its predecessor,
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's Boons offer powerful upgrades inspired by individual Greek gods that each have a significant impact on gameplay, such as the ability to eliminate projectiles by sprinting into them or the ability to freeze enemies with casts and strikes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's godly Boons don't just play a role in gameplay. Boons are also used as a more subtle way for
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  to continue developing its character relationships throughout the game, with dialogue from the god coming after the player has accepted their blessing. Thanks to last year's "Olympic" update,
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  now has Boons from just about every major Olympian, but there's one incredibly important Greek god who still needs to join the roster in a full capacity.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="hades-should-start-offering-full-boons-in-hades-2-39-s-post-game">
  Hades Should Start Offering Full Boons in Hades 2's Post-Game
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1658897473" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1658897473" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1658897473" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1658897473" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1658897473-img" id="article-gallery-1-1658897473">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1658897473" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2084492188">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <h3 id="releasing-hades-should-give-players-a-wealth-of-new-abilities-in-hades-2-39-s-post-game">
  Releasing Hades Should Give Players A Wealth of New Abilities in Hades 2's Post-Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  In its current early access state, players can find the eponymous Greek God of the Dead and King of the Underworld deep in the bowels of Tartarus, where he's been restrained by his Titan father, Chronos. Though Hades tries to dissuade his daughter (player-character Melinoe) from attempting to fight Chronos, he offers a handful of Boons to assist her. With Chronos being the final confrontation in
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's underworld path, Hades' Boons essentially last for just one encounter, and his Boons don't appear anywhere else in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the 1.0 release of
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  , it would be great to see Hades get his own set of unique Boons. These could be unlocked after players defeat Chronos for the first time, thus freeing Hades from his underworld prison and allowing him to provide Boons throughout Melinoe's journey to the surface and Mount Olympus.
 </p>
 <p>
  Being the God of the Dead, there are plenty of unique abilities that Hades' Boons could have. For instance, players could be given the ability to summon the spirits of deceased warriors to temporarily aid them in battle, adding a new defensive strategy to
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's combat.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The next major
     <em>
      Hades 2
     </em>
     update is set to launch in "early 2025," and will add new Boons, new enemies, and one more region to the game's Surface route.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="hades-and-melinoe-39-s-relationship-could-be-explored-via-boons">
  Hades and Melinoe's Relationship Could Be Explored Via Boons
 </h3>
 <p>
  Another major benefit of giving Hades his own fully-fledged set of Boons would be the new opportunities it gives developer Supergiant to explore Hades and Melinoe's relationship as father and daughter, something that's only briefly touched on in
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's current early access build. This relationship could be slowly built upon through the little exchanges made when Melinoe accepts Hades' Boons.
 </p>
 <p>
  These exchanges would also give
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  an easy way to address Zagreus' whereabouts, if that's something that isn't already planned to be explored in future
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  updates. Though much of
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  's story already feels fleshed out, the relationship between Melinoe and her family is something that certainly feels a little lacking right now. And if
  <em>
   Hades 2
  </em>
  fully launched without exploring these dynamics in more detail, it would probably feel a bit incomplete.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2’s Map Makes the Original’s Feel Like a Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-map-improvements-size-visuals/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 has a much larger and more beautiful map than its predecessor.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game emphasizes player agency, allowing freedom in exploration without a burdensome checklist.
     </li>
     <li>
      Improved visuals, dynamic NPC interactions, and substantial side quests make the world more rewarding.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Warhorse Studios'
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  game was rather niche for its time, achieving cult-classic status as it offered a level of realism that didn't quite meet the more balanced standards of today's RPGs. However, its world was nonetheless beautiful and innovative, as it made every effort to provide players with an incredibly detailed and historically accurate depiction of medieval Bohemia. Well,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  has somehow taken that to the next level and then some, with an experience that is not only more accessible than its predecessor, but also more beautiful, much larger, and far more rewarding than ever before.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like its predecessor,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  takes place in medieval Bohemia. This time, however, things have vastly improved in its open world, as it offers two massive open-world regions that are more alive than the first game's world, thanks to the sequel's emphasis on urban areas, more dynamic NPC interactions, and more exciting discoveries to be found around every corner. Effectively,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's map makes the first game's feel like a tutorial.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2-39-s-map-outshines-the-original">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2's Map Outshines the Original
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1803377137" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1803377137" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1803377137" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1803377137" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1803377137-img" id="article-gallery-1-1803377137">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1803377137" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1030487871">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2-39-s-map-is-nearly-twice-as-large-and-far-more-beautiful-than-the-original">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2's Map Is Nearly Twice as Large and Far More Beautiful Than the Original
 </h3>
 <p>
  Firstly,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's map is nearly twice as large as the first game's, and while a change like that across installments has been known to be a negative in open-world games, it's quite the opposite in Warhorse's sequel. Open-world games have often shown that bigger doesn't always mean better, but it's never the size of an open world that inherently makes a game bad. Instead, it's how the size of that open world is presented and executed that can lead to shortcomings. Fortunately,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  uses the increased size of its open world in a way that doesn't make it feel empty, bloated, or both.
 </p>
 <p>
  This ultimately comes down to
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's emphasis on player agency. Instead of forcing players to complete a checklist of chores on its map, or even pressuring them to do one thing or another,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's historical open world gives its players the freedom to do just about anything they want. Unless players unlock the Explorer passive in the Scholarship tree (which requires a lot of effort to do), the map is largely free of icons, allowing players to play unburdened by the increased size of the map.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     <em>
      Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
     </em>
     's map is nearly twice as large as the first game's, and while a change like that across installments has been known to be a negative in open-world games, it's quite the opposite in Warhorse's sequel.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's world is also far more beautiful than the original, showcasing a level of detail that the first game wasn't able to achieve. Those who played the first
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  when it was released in 2018 might not readily notice how significant the visual upgrade is in
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  , but when the two are put next to one another, the distinctions are abundantly clear. In the end, these visual enhancements make
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's world more immersive than before.
 </p>
 <h3 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2-39-s-world-is-more-rewarding-overall">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2's World Is More Rewarding Overall
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's map is also more rewarding than its predecessor's. While many open-world games make exploration more rewarding through collectibles and equipment upgrades, however,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  makes its open world more rewarding by improving the first game's approach to side quests and NPC interactions.
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's world is far more reactive than its predecessor's, with NPCs that more dynamically respond to the player's actions, thereby making the world feel alive.
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's side quests are also more substantial and interconnected with the main narrative, with multiple ways to resolve each one.
 </p>
 <p>
  Overall,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  is a masterclass in open-world design, taking everything that made its predecessor a cult classic and refining it into a truly immersive medieval experience. By expanding its world without compromising its depth, emphasizing player freedom over restrictive, boxed-in design, and enhancing its visuals and quest design, Warhorse Studios has crafted an open world in
  <em>
  </em>
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  that not only honors the original but surpasses it in nearly every way.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel's Spider-Man 2: Every Gadget In The Game, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvels-spiderman-2-every-gadget-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Gadgets are an important aspect of being Spider-Man, almost as much as saving people and keeping a secret identity in a pretty cool superhero outfit. When it comes to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel’s Spider-Man 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Peter and Miles will have access to 5 gadgets, with each of them providing the two Spider-Men with new ways of dealing with the criminals of New York City.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The best gadgets in
  <em>
   Marvel’s Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  will easily allow Peter and Miles to knock out their enemies and subdue them with an overwhelming blast of webs, so if the two Spider-Men are to tinker with new gadgets, it’s best to know how each of them works and which of them will serve as a defining piece of equipment for their arsenal to keep NYC safe.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="upshot">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Upshot
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="web-up-enemies-in-the-air">
  Web-Up Enemies in the Air
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1827909274" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1827909274" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1827909274" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1827909274" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1827909274-img" id="article-gallery-1-1827909274">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1827909274" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1036664331">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Suspend multiple enemies in the air, making them vulnerable to Air Combos or Yank Down.
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fire with R1+Triangle
  </li>
  <li>
   How to Get: Unlocked during One Thing at a Time (Mission 2)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  There’s nothing more satisfying than using Spider-Man’s brutal punches and kicks, paired with his extreme agility, to juggle someone in the air with a flurry of justice. Spider-Man’s air combat is extremely fun, so engaging in Air Combos is made even easier with Upshot, allowing Spider-Man to beat on the baddies with a fun gadget.
 </p>
 <p>
  Upshot isn’t just used for engaging in air combat, as it can also be used for the Yank Down, allowing the Upshot gadget to pull enemies in the air down to the ground so that they can stick to the floor and be out for the count.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ricochet-web">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Ricochet Web
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-gadget-to-bounces-suspending-webs-between-multiple-enemies">
  A Gadget to Bounces Suspending Webs Between Multiple Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1595647392" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1595647392" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1595647392" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1595647392" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1595647392-img" id="article-gallery-2-1595647392">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1595647392" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-858761344">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Web up multiple enemies with a shot that bounces repeatedly between them.
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fire with R1+X
  </li>
  <li>
   How to Get: Unlocked at Level 13 for 200 Tech Parts &amp; 6 Hero Tokens
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  With so many enemies for two Spider-Men to deal with, the Ricochet Web will ensure that their web shooters are always working above and beyond to counter the dreaded weaponry of the enemies that they will face in New York City. The Ricochet Web will help players web up multiple enemies, shooting enemies one after another.
 </p>
 <p>
  With each enemy webbed up, and the Ricochet Web bouncing off of them to keep the attacks coming, players will have vulnerable foes that won’t be able to engage in a fight while players give them a punch from their webbed state. In some instances, these webbed enemies might even end up webbed to a wall to negate their combat encounters altogether.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sonic-burst-concussive-burst">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Sonic Burst (Concussive Burst)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="knock-back-enemies-and-stun-symbiotes">
  Knock-Back Enemies and Stun Symbiotes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-528733550" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-528733550" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-528733550" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-528733550" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-528733550-img" id="article-gallery-3-528733550">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-528733550" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1574480396">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Stun all nearby Symbiote enemies and Knock Back non-Symbiote enemies.
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fire with R1+Circle
  </li>
  <li>
   How to Get: Unlocked at Level 11 for 170 Tech Parts &amp; 4 Rare Tech Parts
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  If players want a way of dealing with pesky enemies and those dreaded Symbiotes, then the Sonic Burst is the gadget that they need. With a quick fire of this gadget, players will be able to fire out a sonic burst that will stun Symbiotes thanks to the devastating sounds it produces, allowing Spider-Man to punch his way through the Symbiotes to free the innocent humans that have been kidnapped from within.
 </p>
 <p>
  If players aren’t using the Sonic Burst on Symbiotes, then they can use it to a decent enough effect on non-Symbiote enemies which will cause them to get knocked back. This knockback effect is great and can throw enemies into walls and deal some nasty damage.
 </p>
 <h2 id="web-grabber">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Web Grabber
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="pull-enemies-into-one-location-to-web-them-and-punch-them">
  Pull Enemies Into One Location to Web Them and Punch Them
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1155844815" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1155844815" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1155844815" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1155844815" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1155844815-img" id="article-gallery-4-1155844815">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1155844815" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1878160789">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Pull multiple enemies into one place, making them vulnerable to Area Attacks.
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fire with R1+Square
  </li>
  <li>
   How to Get: Unlocked at Level 2 for 115 Tech Parts &amp; 3 City Tokens
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Some combat situations have way too many enemies, even for the amazing Spider-Man. Luckily, the Web Grabber gadget will seek to weaken enemies, forcing them into the gadget by pulling them with webbing so that they are knocked into each other and so that Spider-Man can whack and pow his way through the crooks of New York.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Web Grabber is really the only way that Spider-Man is going to dish out more damage with his intellect over his two fists, as the gadget in action will pull enemies towards it to make for a rather hurtful collision.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="web-shooter">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Web-Shooter
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="shoot-enemies-with-webs-to-subdue-them-and-stun-them">
  Shoot Enemies With Webs to Subdue Them and Stun Them
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-260358569" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-260358569" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-260358569" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-260358569" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-260358569-img" id="article-gallery-5-260358569">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-260358569" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-7412209">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Web up enemies with multiple rapid-fire shots. Target enemies that are prone or near walls to stick them to the surface.
   </em>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fire with R1
  </li>
  <li>
   How to Get: Automatically unlocked in Surface Tension (Mission 1)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Spider-Man’s classic and most important weapon in his tool kit is his web shooter, and their feature in
  <em>
   Marvel’s Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  is an excellent and necessary addition that allows players to rapidly fire multiple webs at their enemies to web them up.
 </p>
 <p>
  When webbed, enemies are more vulnerable to attacks, or they can be stuck to walls and other surfaces to take them out of the action. The Web-Shooters are always accessible, and always reliable, providing players with a gadget that can constantly stick more bad guys to a knockout.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Xbox Game Pass Game is a Big Hit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-new-xbox-game-pass-games-lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders has attracted 500,000 players since its launch.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game has also earned mostly positive reviews from critics.
     </li>
     <li>
      This makes Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders one of the biggest new Xbox Game Pass games of 2025 so far.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The newly-added
  <strong>
   Xbox Game Pass
  </strong>
  game
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  has already hit half a million players. New games are added to Xbox Game Pass every month, with the end of January 2025 proving to be especially busy for the subscription service. The last couple of weeks saw multiple day one games added to Xbox Game Pass, including
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper 2: Starward Vector
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Eternal Strands
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Sniper Elite: Resistance
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  is a skiing game with single-player and online multiplayer options. A sequel to the well-received 2019 game
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Downhill
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Snow Riders
  </em>
  has earned strong marks from fans and critics alike. The game currently enjoys an 81 overall rating on review aggregate site OpenCritic, making it one of the highest-rated new game releases of the year so far.
 </p>
 <p>
  It seems fans have been flocking to
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  in large numbers as the game has reached 500,000 players. This was announced by the developer on Bluesky, with Xbox exec Sarah Bond congratulating the team "on an amazing launch." It's unclear exactly how many players came from Xbox Game Pass and how many were paid customers on PC and Xbox, but regardless,
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  is clearly resonating with people and is a game that Game Pass subscribers should be sure to check out ASAP if they haven't done so already.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="lonely-mountains-snow-riders-hits-500-000-players">
  Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders Hits 500,000 Players
 </h2>
 <p>
  Day one games like
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Rider
  </em>
  s
  <em>
  </em>
  that were added to Xbox Game Pass at the end of January 2025 gave subscribers some incredible value. More games are scheduled to join the Xbox Game Pass lineup in February 2025, with the headliner easily being Obsidian Entertainment's
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  , an ambitious new RPG set in the
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity
  </em>
  universe. While it technically doesn't have a truly open world, it should still greatly appeal to fans of games like
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-148576563" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-148576563" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-148576563" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-148576563" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-148576563-img" id="article-gallery-1-148576563">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-148576563" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1554056356">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Plenty more big Xbox Game Pass games are on deck for later in 2025 as well. April 2025 alone will see two huge day one games added to the subscription service in the form of
  <em>
   South of Midnight
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  , while May 2025 will see the debut of
  <em>
   Doom: The Dark Ages
  </em>
  on Xbox Game Pass. Xbox Game Pass subscribers should try
  <em>
   Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders
  </em>
  and the other recent additions while they wait for the future titles to be added in the months ahead.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
