<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Apex Legends - Beast Mode Event Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/apex-legends-beast-mode-event-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Apex Legends Beast Mode event kicks off on March 25, 2025, featuring a special Power Sword Royale, the return of Solos, and April Fools' shenanigans. The special event in Apex Legends runs through April 15, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God of War Fans Have New Code to Redeem, But They Aren't Happy</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/god-of-war-code-free-avatar/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Santa Monica Studio disappoints fans with a simple Greek omega avatar for 20th anniversary celebration.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans had high hopes for new game announcements or Greek Saga remasters.
     </li>
     <li>
      God of War Ragnarok released a new patch with a Dark Odyssey Collection celebrating 20 years of the franchise.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Santa Monica Studio has announced a special bonus for
  <strong>
   <em>
    God of War
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans to celebrate the 20th anniversary of the franchise, but it's falling far short of players' expectations. While
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  fans on PlayStation can now claim a free avatar to be used on their PlayStation Network profiles, it's clear that a lot of fans were expecting more to mark the momentous occasion.
 </p>
 <p>
  Originally introduced as a pure action-adventure series before incorporating action-RPG elements later into its run, the first
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  game was released exclusively on PlayStation 2 for North American audiences on March 22, 2005, with a European release following a little over three months later. The series saw four home console games with Kratos under the Greek pantheon, including the prequel
  <em>
   God of War: Ascension
  </em>
  , before shifting the
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  franchise's focus to Norse Mythology with 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  and 2022's
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  To commemorate the 20th anniversary, a special new free avatar is now available on the PlayStation Network. Released on March 20, the free avatar had been announced on the PlayStation Blog six days ago along with items for players on PC in the Steam Points shop, though that announcement didn't reveal any information on what the avatar would look like. The result has been disappointing to a lot of players, with the now-released avatar simply showing a stylized gold Greek omega — a symbol that has been associated with the franchise since its first game — laid against a plain black background.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="playstation-store-codes-for-god-of-war-20th-anniversary-avatar">
  PlayStation Store Codes for God of War 20th Anniversary Avatar
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Americas: F27X-L946-8PTH
  </li>
  <li>
   Europe/Australia: HMCJ-N3JM-4TT2
  </li>
  <li>
   Japan: 6F3K-RR8X-2KEM
  </li>
  <li>
   Korea: HRLN-L4AG-88GD
  </li>
  <li>
   Asia: 8RC3-DEFT-NJPC
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While there is no charge to redeem the free avatar, its reveal has left a lot of players feeling deflated on such a special day for the franchise. Several fans have posted responses of displeasure to the big reveal, with reactions ranging from GIFs of a thumbs down motion to comments of "That's it?" From the reactions, it seems that many were expecting the official confirmation of a new
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  game in development at Santa Monica Studio or remasters of the Greek Saga that covered the earliest games in the mainline series.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-944054605" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-944054605" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-944054605" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-944054605" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-944054605-img" id="article-gallery-1-944054605">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-944054605" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1462643792">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Recent news about the game franchise hasn't all been so negative. On March 20,
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  rolled out a new patch featuring the Dark Odyssey Collection, an in-game bundle filled with throwback items that honor earlier entries in the series as a way of celebrating 20 years of
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  . Along with that bundle, the patch also introduced a system for modifying the appearance of weapon and shield attachments in the game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Game Pass is Losing 10 Games on March 31</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-game-pass-games-leaving-march-2025-yakuza-monster-hunter/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      MLB The Show 24, multiple games in the Yakuza series, Monster Hunter Rise, and more are leaving Xbox Game Pass on March 31.
     </li>
     <li>
      These departures are pretty high-profile and will hurt the Game Pass library.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  10 games are leaving
  <strong>
   Xbox Game Pass
  </strong>
  on Monday, March 31, including some of the service's highest-rated games. Longtime Xbox Game Pass subscribers are likely very familiar with the service's patterns by now. While games are added on various days throughout each month, titles are generally removed on two specific days: the 15th and the last day of the month.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Xbox Game Pass games leaving in March 2025 are no exception. After March 31, the departing games will no longer be available to Game Pass subscribers, and while that's not enough time to beat them all, there is enough time to at least try before you buy. Xbox Game Pass games are available at a 20% discount while they're on the service, letting subscribers pick up the games at a lower price than usual.
 </p>
 <p>
  The 10 games leaving Xbox Game Pass on March 31 are
  <em>
   MLB The Show 24
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Lil Gator Game
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Hot Wheels Unleashed 2
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Open Roads
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Yakuza 0
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Yakuza Kiwami
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Yakuza Kiwami 2
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   The Lamplighter's League
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  . These are some pretty high-profile Xbox Game Pass games, and so it's definitely going to be a blow to the service once they're removed.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="xbox-game-pass-games-leaving-march-2025">
  Xbox Game Pass Games Leaving March 2025
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Hot Wheels Unleashed 2
  </li>
  <li>
   Lil Gator Game
  </li>
  <li>
   MLB The Show 24
  </li>
  <li>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </li>
  <li>
   Open Roads
  </li>
  <li>
   The Lamplighter's League
  </li>
  <li>
   Yakuza 0
  </li>
  <li>
   Yakuza Kiwami
  </li>
  <li>
   Yakuza Kiwami 2
  </li>
  <li>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   MLB The Show 24
  </em>
  leaving Xbox Game Pass will be especially disappointing for baseball fans. Ever since
  <em>
   MLB The Show
  </em>
  games became multiplatform, each new game has been featured as a day one Xbox Game Pass release. That changed with
  <em>
   MLB The Show 25
  </em>
  , which is available on Xbox, but is not on Game Pass. So not only is
  <em>
   MLB The Show 24
  </em>
  leaving Game Pass at the end of the month, baseball fans don't have a replacement to play unless they purchase it outright.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  games leaving Game Pass also sting, especially since some of the best ones in the series are getting the boot. There are many who hold
  <em>
   Yakuza 0
  </em>
  up as one of the finest games in the series, and, of course, the game-changing
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  also earned a great deal of critical acclaim. The
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  franchise continues to reach new heights of popularity, and the removal of the games from Game Pass means that fewer people may discover them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  leaving Game Pass is also a bummer, as the franchise is hot right now thanks to the release of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  . I also have a soft spot for
  <em>
   Lil Gator Game
  </em>
  , though that one is at least short enough that Game Pass subscribers should have no problem completing it before it's removed on March 31.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25: Best Wrestlers To Draft First In MyGM Mode</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-best-wrestlers-draft-first-mygm-mode/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Cody Rhodes is a top pick in the WWE 2K25 MyGM draft due to his promo skills and in-ring abilities.
     </li>
     <li>
      Securing a female giant early in the draft is crucial for a balanced roster in MyGM mode.
     </li>
     <li>
      Picking at least one specialist for both the men's and women's divisions helps create compelling matches and rivalries.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    WWE 2K25
   </strong>
  </em>
  is the latest entry into 2K's annual WWE franchise, updating the roster to include superstars both old and new, while refining the different game modes introduced in last year's game. The latest game features The Island, a new game mode where players enter an open-world city to become the best and earn a contract in the WWE from superstar Roman Reigns. Additionally, the game's showcase mode features a deep dive into the history of The Bloodline, allowing the player to participate in matches that established The Bloodline and the Aona'i family as a dominant force in the world of sports entertainment.
 </p>
 <p>
  One game mode that has seen several incremental changes is MyGM mode, with the introduction of cross-brand PLEs, a host of new general managers, and a new brand, NXT Mutiny. The game mode allows players to take control of their favorite brand to become the dominant brand within the WWE. This all begins with drafting the right superstars to generate the best matches and rivalries for the players' roster. So, who are the best wrestlers to draft first in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM?
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="cody-rhodes">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Cody Rhodes
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-current-face-of-the-wwe-is-a-great-first-pick">
  The Current Face Of The WWE Is A Great First Pick
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1236781841" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1236781841" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1236781841" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1236781841" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1236781841-img" id="article-gallery-1-1236781841">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1236781841" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1673164561">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The biggest superstar available in the draft
  </li>
  <li>
   Great promo skills and in-ring abilities
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The American Nightmare is the undeniable face of the WWE, being the Undisputed WWE Champion and one of the most popular superstars on the planet. His popularity is reflected in MyGM with Cody Rhodes being the most expensive star available in the draft.
 </p>
 <p>
  This price tag may put some players off choosing Rhodes, but his stats reflect that he would be a great first-round pick. With a maxed-out promo skill, Cody is able to start rivalries with ease, and his popularity is often the highest available in the draft. He is a level 20 wrestler, and he's a specialist, meaning he can match up with anyone on the player's roster. This makes Cody a no-brainer for players looking to get an advantage in the WWE draft in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM.
 </p>
 <h2 id="a-female-giant">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   A Female Giant
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="there-are-fewer-female-giants-than-any-other-class-in-the-draft">
  There Are Fewer Female Giants Than Any Other Class In The Draft
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="WWE 2K25 screenshot of Becky Lynch, Jade Cargill, and Charlotte Flair" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-myrise-becky-lynch-jade-cargill-charlotte-flair-survivor-series.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Female giants are in short supply in MyGM mode
  </li>
  <li>
   Getting a female giant early allows for the roster to be built effectively
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM's draft, only five female giants are available for selection: Charlotte Flair, Nia Jax, Jade Cargill, Piper Niven, and Raquel Rodriguez. This makes securing a female giant early in the draft incredibly important for making a balanced and rounded roster.
 </p>
 <p>
  If playing a game with four brands, these giants will be taken quickly. Therefore, acting fast is in the players' best interest to take the female giant with the best ability, stamina, and promo skill still available in the draft. There is an abundance of female cruisers, meaning they can be saved for later in the draft to create a great pairing, but securing a female giant should be a priority for players in MyGM's draft.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rhea-ripley">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Rhea Ripley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-female-bruiser-with-great-popularity-and-promo-skills">
  A Female Bruiser With Great Popularity And Promo Skills
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="WWE 2K25 Character Creation Change Rhea Ripley" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/wwe-2k25-character-creation-change-rhea-rippley.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The highest-ranked female bruiser in the draft
  </li>
  <li>
   Rhea brings great popularity and promo skills to the players' brand
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Rhea Ripley is arguably the biggest female wrestler on the planet, with her first WWE world title reign lasting for over a year, showcasing that she is a dominant force in the WWE. This is shown in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM, with Ripley being a top female superstar for players to draft.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ripley is capable of becoming a dominant force for the player's brand. When paired with a strong fighter like Michin or Chelsea Green, the rivalry can be enhanced by Ripley's promo or in-ring skills. Alternatively, pairing her with a specialist like Becky Lynch can also create incredible matches capable of taking the main event spot at the player's go-home shows. Additionally, due to Rhea's in-ring quality, she becomes useful in cross-branded PLEs. All of this makes Rhea Ripley a great choice for players in the
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM draft.
 </p>
 <h2 id="luke-gallows">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Luke Gallows
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-legend-39-s-ability-at-a-bargain">
  A Legend's Ability At A Bargain
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='"WWE 2K25"' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Luke Gallows WWE 2K25 MyGM" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1150460.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
    <figcaption class="body-img-caption">
     WWE 2K25
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Great in-ring skills to pair with an experienced wrestler
  </li>
  <li>
   Comes in at a bargain price of $191k
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Luke Gallows is a sleeper pick in the
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM draft, often showing up for under $200k and possessing a great in-ring ability that will only grow when participating in matches. The only downside to Gallows is his popularity often starts on the lower side.
 </p>
 <p>
  But within MyGM, an instant boost of popularity is given to champions, meaning their major weakness can be improved immediately. Players are then left with a talented superstar with decent promo skills, capable of rivaling the likes of Cody Rhodes, CM Punk, and AJ Styles, all of which begin with the legend level in-ring ability. His lower price point makes Luke Gallows a great pick-up for players looking to save a bit of cash for the early weeks while still developing a talented roster.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="anyone-above-level-three-promo-skills">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Anyone Above Level Three Promo Skills
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="promo-is-vital-to-a-successful-brand">
  Promo Is Vital To A Successful Brand
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-55184342" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-55184342" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-55184342" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-55184342" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-55184342-img" id="article-gallery-2-55184342">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-55184342" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-863306739">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   An important factor when drafting superstars is keeping the budget in check
  </li>
  <li>
   Capturing cheaper stars with good promo skills is a tactic that benefits the player
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When drafting a roster, it's tempting for players to swing for the fences, taking huge superstars from the get-go without much consideration of their budget. This becomes problematic toward the latter stages of the draft when players run out of money to spend and are scrambling to fill the remaining slots on their roster.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is why, after selecting the initial heavy hitters mentioned above, players should operate tactically, looking to pick up less expensive superstars with above-average promo skills. Their in-ring ability may put the player off selecting cheaper superstars, but this will increase when they participate in matches; promo skills will not. Therefore, selecting superstars like Brooks Jensen with a level four promo skill for $106k becomes a no-brainer, as he'll be able to grow as a performer, while his promos will always yield the desired result.
 </p>
 <h2 id="at-least-one-specialist-for-both-the-men-39-s-and-women-39-s-divisions">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   At Least One Specialist For Both The Men's And Women's Divisions
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="specialists-can-perform-against-any-other-class">
  Specialists Can Perform Against Any Other Class
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='"WWE 2K25"' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Specialists in WWE 2K25 MyGM Draft" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/share_20250322_1217330.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
    <figcaption class="body-img-caption">
     WWE 2K25
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Specialists pair with any other class on a roster to create a compelling match
  </li>
  <li>
   Selecting one for both the Men's and Women's Divisions makes creating rivalries easier
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Finally, picking up a specialist or two for each division is a crucial step to maintaining a balanced roster. Despite not showing as an immediate class match for the other classes, knowing that they can pair with anyone for a good match is extremely useful later down the line.
 </p>
 <p>
  For players looking to create a balanced roster, selecting someone like Tony D'Angelo, who often appears lower in terms of cost but has solid promo skills, is a great option to round out a roster, while Bailey is an immediate level 15 superstar from the get-go in the women's division. This makes a specialist or two for each division a great choice to draft first in
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  MyGM mode.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaphor: ReFantazio's Dragon Trials are a Must-Have Feature for Persona 6</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/metaphor-refantazio-persona-6-dragon-trial-feature-inspiration-must-have/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Metaphor: Refantazio
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a crowning achievement from a studio already known for its stellar, influential JRPGs. Indeed, there are many who believe, quite rightly, that
  <em>
   Metaphor: Refantazio
  </em>
  offers the best rendition of the schedule-based, life-sim-integrated RPG framework that Atlus honed through the likes of
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Shin Megami Tensei
  </em>
  , and it will be interesting to see how the famed company learns from this most recent outing.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are a number of ways in which
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  improves upon the foundations of its predecessors, some of them more obvious than others. But perhaps the most impactful change comes in relation to combat:
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  ’s Archetype system can be viewed as a more streamlined, but also more expressive, version of Persona’s titular avatar-based combat framework. It’s easier to get the hang of, as it's far more focused on patterns and trends than disparate stats, but just as difficult to master, if not more so. Progression is also more rewarding due to clever features like the ability to transfer abilities from already-unlocked Archetypes. All of these more nuanced mechanical elements are further buttressed by
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  ’s broader structural choices, which future
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  games could learn from.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="metaphor-rsquo-s-dragon-trials-serve-as-terrific-late-game-content">
  Metaphor’s Dragon Trials Serve as Terrific Late-Game Content
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1800796050" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1800796050" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1800796050" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1800796050" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1800796050-img" id="article-gallery-1-1800796050">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1800796050" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2139480888">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="metaphor-refantazio-rsquo-s-dragon-trials-are-the-perfect-venue-for-expressing-mastery">
  Metaphor: Refantazio’s Dragon Trials Are the Perfect Venue for Expressing Mastery
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  offers four particularly brutal late-game boss fights, all with powerful lore significance:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Devourer Of Nations
  </li>
  <li>
   Devourer Of Stars
  </li>
  <li>
   Devourer Of Flames
  </li>
  <li>
   Elegy Of The Soul
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  These fights aren’t for the faint of heart: those playing on higher difficulties may very well abandon them entirely due to their unforgiving nature. But like any good late-game challenge, these boss battles yield high-end gear and loads of XP upon completion, which makes overcoming them even more gratifying. These material rewards are nice, but the real value of these encounters is derived from a more intrinsic source.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  is a long game, longer than many of Atlus’ other JRPGs, which is certainly saying something. The Dragon Trials aren’t unlocked until its final stretch, during the preparation for the final, decisive encounter with Louis. This makes the rewards gleaned from these fights more pivotal, of course, but the fights themselves take on new meaning.
 </p>
 <p>
  These encounters are not means to an end—they are totally optional, after all. Their real value is as final, overwhelming challenges, allowing players to celebrate their dozens of hours of grinding, experimenting, and build-crafting in a metaphorical arena of champions. Indeed, alongside
  <em>
  </em>
  <em>
   Metaphor Refantazio
  </em>
  's literal arena, these fights are the final frontier of gameplay, a chance for players to test their mettle and be rewarded for their mastery of complex, overlapping combat mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, this sort of late-game challenge is hardly unique to Metaphor. Numerous RPGs, from
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  , feature similar optional battles that don’t directly influence the main story. But
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  ’s particular implementation of this concept, hinged upon its clever and engaging turn-based combat and progression models, makes it a standout example, and the perfect one for
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  to learn from.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s not clear how much
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  will derive from
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  , and Atlus could very well aim to keep the two franchises as distinct as possible to keep one from cannibalizing the other. But even if
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  doesn’t borrow any of
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  ’s more fine-grained mechanical ideas, the former’s implementation of late-game challenges seems like a particularly beneficial well to draw from.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  series features late-game challenges of this sort, but they have a tendency to lack narrative/lore significance. For example, the Elizabeth fight in
  <em>
   Persona 3
  </em>
  is difficult, but lacks drama, almost coming across as more of an Easter egg. By mixing high-level challenge and narrative weight,
  <em>
   Persona 6
  </em>
  ’s late-game bosses can be just as powerful and rewarding as
  <em>
   Metaphor
  </em>
  ’s.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
