<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Atomfall: June's Key Location</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/atomfall-find-junes-key-location/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The characters that reside in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Atomfall's
   </strong>
  </em>
  quarantine zone tend to have a lot of secrets. They either know something that they shouldn't know about the disaster at the Windfall Plant, or they're stashing away valuable items so looters and outlaws can't steal them.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There is one character we don't meet named June who seems to be hiding quite a few secrets. She has a lockbox that can only be opened with a key, so we need to find it. Finding June's key will require you to follow some directions and uncover a hidden cache. So let's get to hunting and find June's Key.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-june-39-s-key-in-atomfall">
  Where To Find June's Key In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1070085279" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1070085279" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1070085279" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1070085279" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1070085279-img" id="article-gallery-1-1070085279">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1070085279" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1314489302">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before you begin the search for
  <strong>
   June's Key,
  </strong>
  you'll need to find a
  <strong>
   Metal Detector.
  </strong>
  This tool can be found in a few different spots, but the earliest location you can find one is by looting it from
  <strong>
   a corpse in Slatten Dale found at the coordinates 29.1 E, 73.9 N.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you have a Metal Detector, head to the coordinates
  <strong>
   27.9 E, 78.9 N in Slatten Dale.
  </strong>
  This will be in a swampy area, so watch out for the leeches in the water that will swarm you. With the Metal Detector, you can dig up a hidden cache with a note inside titled "Farewell, Doctor." This will be from June and will talk about a doctor she knew that told her secrets about The Protocol. This note will begin
  <strong>
   The Little Tea Room Lead
  </strong>
  that you can track.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now head to Wyndham Village. For the most part, The Protocol soldiers here won't become aggressive to you. Unless you enter a building which has been seized by the soldiers and boarded up. In that case, they will become hostile and attack you. You need to find
  <strong>
   The Little Tea Room building, which is found at 34.6 E, 80.4 N in the village.
  </strong>
  Get inside the building through a windhow without alerting The Protocol. Head upstairs and
  <strong>
   you'll find June's Key next to a skeleton
  </strong>
  that presumably belongs to June.
 </p>
 <h2 id="where-to-find-june-39-s-lockbox">
  Where To Find June's Lockbox
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1406995267" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1406995267" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1406995267" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1406995267" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1406995267-img" id="article-gallery-2-1406995267">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1406995267" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-680830658">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Now that we have June's Key, we need to find her lockbox so we can use it.
  <strong>
   June's Lockbox is located inside the Village Hall in Wyndham Village at the coordinates 33.4 E, 79.3 N.
  </strong>
  Enter the building and head to the back. You'll find June's Lockbox next to a desk with the Burn Salve crafting recipe on it. Use the key to open it up and you'll find that the only thing inside is a note titled "June's Errands." All this note will say is that someone needs to visit the boathouse and plant some flowers.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   The boathouse in question is at the coordinates 35.6 E, 82.7 N in Wyndham Village.
  </strong>
  When you reach it, your Metal Detector will go off. Equip it, and follow the lights on it to find another hidden cache. This one will have two notes. One titled "June's Diary" will talk about the scientist that June knew from The Interchange. The other note will be titled "Protocol's Secrets" and will reveal the location of a secret Protocol bunker.
 </p>
 <p>
  This bunker will be the
  <strong>
   Protocol Workshop in Skethermoor located at the coordinates 38.0 E, 77.4 N on the map.
  </strong>
  It will be full of soldiers, so be prepared for a fight. It will also have plenty of B.A.R.D. Crates with Training Stimulants inside along with the Windfall Keycard.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inZOI: How To Change Zoi Schedule</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/inzoi-how-use-edit-schedule/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Although there are comparisons with
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  came out with some mechanics that set it apart from the Life Sim by
  <em>
   EA Games
  </em>
  , in addition to its realistic visuals. Both games share a similar concept, but players will discover a few key differences that shape each gameplay, such as the Scheduler system found in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Through this mechanic, players can schedule certain spots for their Zois to visit on set days, which automates parts of each character’s routine and saves time. This guide explores the best ways to use the Schedule in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  , as well as its potential to personalize each Zoi’s daily life in a unique yet easy way.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-does-the-schedule-in-inzoi-work">
  How Does The Schedule In InZOI Work?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-62952143" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-62952143" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-62952143" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-62952143" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-62952143-img" id="article-gallery-1-62952143">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-62952143" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2147127984">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Schedule is a core feature of
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  that lets players set a timetable for their Zois during the game. It enables them to choose exact days of the week for each character to visit a certain place, which is useful for establishing a fixed routine, like going to a gym in the city at a chosen time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can access each Zoi’s calendar in different ways, and these are the most common:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   From the character’s phone, select the Schedule among the apps.
  </li>
  <li>
   When opening the city map, pick Edit Schedule at the top.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div style="list-style-type:disc">
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-modify-a-zoi-rsquo-s-calendar-in-inzoi">
  How To Modify A Zoi’s Calendar In InZOI?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1019228620" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1019228620" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1019228620" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1019228620" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1019228620-img" id="article-gallery-2-1019228620">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1019228620" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-947884960">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Certain events will appear on the calendar as players set up in-game commitments in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  . One example is a job, because after being hired by one of the various places seeking employees in Bliss Bay or Dowon, players will notice a large blue bar on the Schedule, which shows the time to head to work.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, players can also change these times manually in a simple way. For instance, clicking the plus sign on a chosen slot offers two options:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Make Event,
   </strong>
   for scheduling dates, parties, or weddings when certain conditions are met
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Select Location,
   </strong>
   which sends a Zoi to a specific location at a set time.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <ul>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Once something is added to the Schedule, players can also set how long it stays on a Zoi’s schedule by clicking the event again and adjusting the time with the arrows. Beyond that, it is possible to drag the action along the timeline and change how it unfolds in the Schedule of
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  , which offers a flexible way to plan every moment.
 </p>
 <p>
  Normally, if they are not directed controled and autonomy is active, Zois will go on their own to tasks marked in their Schedules within
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  , so players need not worry about that in most cases. However, a pop-up also appears in the lower-left corner of the screen as a reminder, which makes it hard to miss these events.
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-can-be-done-with-the-schedule-in-inzoi">
  What Can Be Done With The Schedule In InZOI?
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A zoi working in inZOI" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/04/a-zoi-working-in-inzoi.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the Schedule of
  <em>
   inZOI,
  </em>
  players cannot appoint certain actions to be done, only the place where the character must appear at a set time. For instance, if the aim is to have a Zoi go to the gym every morning, it is possible to place that activity on the Schedule, but there is no way to make it use exercise machines, so control is still required for that part.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still, even without a high level of automation for certain tasks, the Schedule of
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  is great for anyone who wants to plan specific activities but tends to forget. It helps with each character’s life management, and new activities might appear or get scheduled without player input at certain times, like when a character moves on to another life stage.
 </p>
 <p>
  Therefore, it is important to keep a close watch on the Schedule of
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  and set each event in a way that suits each plan, without missing any key details. Doing so guarantees a steady routine and helps keep the entire experience organized, which makes life management easier and smooth overall in the long run.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A Good Ending' Baldur's Gate 3 Stardew Valley Mod is Back</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-baldurs-gate-3-mod-return-swen-vincke-comment/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Baldur's Village, a popular Baldur's Gate 3 mod for Stardew Valley, is back after being mistakenly taken down.
     </li>
     <li>
      The mod adds more characters, locations, and romance options, with creators working on further updates depending on support.
     </li>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley received an update in 2025, with Patch 8 for Baldur's Gate 3 expected to add new subclasses and gameplay features.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  -themed mod for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Stardew Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  is available again after being taken down.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  was initially released in 2016 and has stood the test of time thanks partly to dedicated players creating content for the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  ConcernedApe's game has a creative community that consistently finds new features and content to add to the simulator, making the gameplay unique. Because of this,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has a variety of mods: some make subtle additions, such as seasonal clothing and changing character portraits, making the experience more immersive. Other mods go beyond visuals, adding features such as visible fish, and allowing players to obtain any information about anything within the game. Recently, the release of a mod called Baldur's Village attracted players' attention, but to their surprise, Wizards of the Coast nixed it.
 </p>
 <p>
  That has now changed, as the popular
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  mod for
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , is back on Nexus Mods. In a statement to PC Gamer, Wizards of the Coast says that the DMCA notification was sent mistakenly, resulting in the incorrect removal of the
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  mod that quickly became a hit. After being taken down, the mod remained marked as “under moderation review.” Now, to gamers' joy, it is available for download once again. In a post on Twitter, Larian CEO Swen Vincke celebrated the swift solution, calling it "a good ending." In addition, he said that he hopes to see it developed further.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-mod-based-on-baldur-39-s-gate-3-is-available-again">
  Stardew Valley Mod Based on Baldur's Gate 3 is Available Again
 </h2>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players have reacted positively to learning that Baldur's Village is available again, given its popularity. Released at the beginning of March, it takes place after the events of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  . According to the official description, it adds more than 20 characters, six new locations and stores with special items, dynamic events, and more. Another highlight of the mod is making Astarion, one of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's most beloved characters, fully romanceable. The creators also plan to support the mod with future updates. However, they emphasize that this part depends on financial support, downloads, endorsement count on Nexus Mods, and dealing with issues such as piracy, reselling, and re-uploads.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2020172322" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2020172322" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2020172322" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2020172322" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2020172322-img" id="article-gallery-1-2020172322">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2020172322" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1428767314">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After releasing update 1.6.15 for
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  in December last year, the first patch the game received in 2025 was 16.15.1. Released on February 12, the update fixed various issues affecting the console version of the game and synchronized with the latest content available for PC. Players of Larian's RPG, meanwhile, are waiting for the release of Patch 8, which will add 12 new subclasses to
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , as well as photo mode, cross-play, and other gameplay features.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Shares Clever Kecleon Cake Pop Design</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-kecleon-cake-pop/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A fan created an adorable Kecleon cake pop with clever design twists for April Fools' Day.
     </li>
     <li>
      Certain Pokemon, like Farfetch'd, are considered edible in the original series.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans praised the Kecleon cake pop design, with some joking about it disappearing, showing creativity.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has created an adorable Kecleon cake pop with a clever twist to its design for April Fools' Day. It's one of the latest
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  edible treats made by a fan that has gained attention from the community.
 </p>
 <p>
  To some fans' horror, certain Pokemon are considered edible in the original series, with the most iconic of them probably being Farfetch'd. Farfetch'd stands out in particular, as it carries a leek, which is commonly used as an ingredient when preparing a Farfetch'd as a meal. While fans may not want to eat a real Pokemon, treats based on Pokemon designs have been quite popular with the fandom.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, a prolific
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  treat creator has shared their latest work, turning Kecleon into a cake pop. The adorable creation by miscellaneousmao does a great job of recreating Kecleon's look, and it has some clever twists that set it apart from prior
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  cake pops. To start, Kecleon is clinging to the stick that the cake pop is built upon, making it look like the Color Swap Pokemon is climbing up the stick. Another additional touch that adds to its charm is the artist's decision to make Kecleon's tongue out of a strawberry Starburst candy, which, as demonstrated in the video, allows the creator to stretch its tongue out to a considerable length. The video also includes a cute moment where Kecleon is invisible, referencing its ability to camouflage itself to match its surroudnings.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fans-react-to-disappearing-kecleon-cake-pop">
  Pokemon Fans React to Disappearing Kecleon Cake Pop
 </h2>
 <p>
  Fans in the comments have been quite positive about the cake pop, applauding the artist for their work and creativty. Some have joked about how they would be frustrated to buy a cake pop only for the Kecleon to disappear, while others have shared how they're charmed by the design. One fan made an amusing reference, saying they had to turn out their Devon Scope to see the post. Fans of
  <em>
   Pokemon Ruby
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Sapphire
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Emerald
  </em>
  - and their subsequent remakes,
  <em>
   Pokemon Omega Ruby
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Alpha Sapphire
  </em>
  - will remember the Devon Scope as a tool that lets players see invisible Pokemon, with a pair of special hidden Kecleon that can be uncovered with it in the remakes.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-593574202" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-593574202" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-593574202" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-593574202" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-593574202-img" id="article-gallery-1-593574202">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-593574202" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2112693599">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While this might be the only
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  dessert themed around April Fools' Day, it's not the only nod to the holiday from the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  series this year.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  rolled out its annual April Fools' Day event, this time leaving a slew of Poke Balls scattered around the world map that contain surprise encounters or items. It will be interesting to see what the series - and the fans - create for April Fools' Day next year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Final Fantasy Characters Who Are Playable In The Most Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-characters-playable-most-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  began as a last-ditch effort for Squaresoft to pull out a hit and they certainly succeeded. No one could have imagined back then that the series, which started in Japan in 1987, would still be going strong today.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Besides dozens of mainline games, there have been more spinoffs than anything else related to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  . Most spinoffs tend to include nods from mainline characters, like Yuffie from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  . This begs the question though. Discounting mobile games, what character from the series has been playable the most? The results may be obvious to diehards, but let’s dive in regardless.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="zidane-tribal-final-fantasy-9">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Zidane Tribal (Final Fantasy 9)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-charismatic-thief">
  A Charismatic Thief
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-586783503" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-586783503" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-586783503" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-586783503" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-586783503-img" id="article-gallery-1-586783503">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-586783503" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-828629714">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   9 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Zidane is the main hero from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 9
  </em>
  who is a swashbuckling thief. He’s also in two
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  games including
  <em>
   Dragon Quest &amp; Final Fantasy in Itadaki Street Portable
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Itadaki Street: Dragon Quest &amp; Final Fantasy 30th Anniversary
  </em>
  . Itadaki Street is like Monopoly but with RPG elements. Zidane is also in all three Dissidia games including
  <em>
   Dissidia Final Fantasy
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dissidia 012 Final Fantasy
  </em>
  , and Dissidia Final Fantasy NT. Dissidia is a fighting game franchise that began on the PSP, focusing on heroes and villains duking it out in crossover battles. Finally, Zidane is playable in all three Theatrhythm games including
  <em>
   Theatrhythm Final Fantasy
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Theatrhythm Final Fantasy: Curtain Call
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Theatrhythm Final Bar Line
  </em>
  . These are all rhythm-based RPGs featuring characters and music across the franchise.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tidus-final-fantasy-10">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Tidus (Final Fantasy 10)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="number-one-dad-hater">
  Number One Dad Hater
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1906506706" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1906506706" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1906506706" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1906506706" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1906506706-img" id="article-gallery-2-1906506706">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1906506706" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1340779169">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   9 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Tidus is the main character from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  who is a bit divisive in the eyes of fans as he can be a bit much with all of his whining about his dad. Besides his original game, Tidus is playable in the first previously unnamed Itadaki Street game,
  <em>
   Dragon Quest &amp; Final Fantasy in Itadaki Street Special
  </em>
  , along with the last game. Tidus is also in all three
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  and all three
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games. He’s a well-used character but there are no unique games with Tidus returning at least as a playable character.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="yuna-final-fantasy-10">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Yuna (Final Fantasy 10)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="summoning-courage">
  Summoning Courage
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-699471388" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-699471388" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-699471388" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-699471388" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-699471388-img" id="article-gallery-3-699471388">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-699471388" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1387814223">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   9 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Yuna is also from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  and she’s the love interest of Tidus. As a Summoner of the group, she’s also the strongest in the game. This may be why she was given her own spinoff,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10-2
  </em>
  , which was another turn-based RPG but this one used a Job system.
 </p>
 <p>
  Besides epic RPGs, Yuna is in the same Itadaki Street games as Tidus which makes sense since they are a couple. The only difference is that her
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10-2
  </em>
  version also appears in
  <em>
   Dragon Quest &amp; Final Fantasy in Itadaki Street Special
  </em>
  . She’s in the last two
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  games and all three
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="vaan-final-fantasy-12">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Vaan (Final Fantasy 12)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="to-the-skies">
  To The Skies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-840461581" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-840461581" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-840461581" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-840461581" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-840461581-img" id="article-gallery-4-840461581">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-840461581" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-707368051">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   10 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Vaan is from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 12
  </em>
  and like Zidane, he’s a sky pirate albeit one in training. Like Yuna, Vaan got a direct sequel via
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 12: Revenant Wings
  </em>
  which was an RTS experience on the DS. Around this same time, Vaan appeared as a secret character players could unlock in the tactical RPG
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Tactics A2: Grimoire of the Rift
  </em>
  . Vaan appeared in the first two
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  games, the last two
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  games, and all three
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="squall-leonhart-final-fantasy-8">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Squall Leonhart (Final Fantasy 8)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="scarred-beyond-repair">
  Scarred Beyond Repair
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-198319078" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-198319078" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-198319078" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-198319078" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-198319078-img" id="article-gallery-5-198319078">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-198319078" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-930056875">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   11 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Squall is the protagonist from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 8
  </em>
  and fans probably remember him the most for his distinct scar and Gunblade weapon. Despite his lack of conformity in his game, Squall was seemingly up to playing ball with other titles. For example, he’s unlockable in
  <em>
   Chocobo Racing
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Chocobo GP
  </em>
  which are two racing games akin to the
  <em>
   Mario Kart
  </em>
  series. Squall is in the first and third
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  games, all three
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  games, and all three
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games making him a legend.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tifa-lockhart-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Tifa Lockhart (Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="beware-her-fists-of-fury">
  Beware Her Fists Of Fury
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-643879203" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-643879203" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-643879203" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-643879203" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-643879203-img" id="article-gallery-6-643879203">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-643879203" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2114708697">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   11 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  It’s time to enter the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  block of characters because they have all been in a staggering amount of games. Tifa was a playable party member in the original game along with
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  and she will most likely be playable in the final remake whenever that comes out.
 </p>
 <p>
  Before the
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  series began,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  characters appeared in the wrestling fighter,
  <em>
   Ehrgeiz: God Bless the Ring
  </em>
  which includes Tifa. Tifa is also in the first two
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  games, the last two
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  games, and all three
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games making her the most used female character in the franchise.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sephiroth-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Sephiroth (Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-villain-appears">
  A Villain Appears
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1489609927" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1489609927" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1489609927" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1489609927" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1489609927-img" id="article-gallery-7-1489609927">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1489609927" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-547786387">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   12 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Sephiroth is the main villain of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  who technically was a party member in a flashback sequence. However, players didn’t have much control over him, unlike
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  which made him more of a character in the same flashback scene. He was also in
  <em>
   Ehrgeiz: God Bless the Ring
  </em>
  and another unique fighting game,
  <em>
   Super Smash Bros. Ultimate
  </em>
  . Nintendo even commemorated Sephiroth with an Amiibo alongside its release. Finally, he is in all three
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games making him the villain who has appeared in the most games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cloud-strife-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Cloud Strife (Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="god-bless-the-king">
  God Bless The King
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-395153360" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-395153360" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-395153360" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-395153360" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-395153360-img" id="article-gallery-8-395153360">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-395153360" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-258191407">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   18 Games
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Cloud is easily one of the most popular characters in the franchise let alone video games as a whole. He’s playable in the original game alongside the two remake projects so far. He’s a secret character in the original Final Fantasy Tactics and a pain to unlock to boot. Like Squall, Cloud raced in the wacky
  <em>
   Chocobo Racing
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Chocobo GP
  </em>
  adventures. He brawled in
  <em>
   Ehrgeiz: God Bless the Ring
  </em>
  like most of his fellow cast members. Cloud is in
  <em>
   Super Smash Bros. Ultimate
  </em>
  like Sephiroth but he also got into the 3DS and Wii U versions of
  <em>
   Super Smash Bros.
  </em>
  before that which could almost be counted as two separate games. To top it off, Cloud is in all three
  <em>
   Itadaki Street
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dissidia
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Theatrhythm
  </em>
  games and who knows what else after this.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
