<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Why Final Fantasy 6 Fans Should Keep an Eye on FF14 Patch 7.2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-6-fans-ff14-patch-7-2-mechs-magitek/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 14
   </em>
  </strong>
  Patch 7.2 is set to introduce a host of new features, including futuristic mechs that bear a striking resemblance to the Magitek armor from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  . As players collaborate with the Loporrits to transform barren celestial bodies into thriving colonies, the addition of these high-tech machines may serve as a nostalgic callback to one of the most beloved titles in the series. While some fans see
  <em>
   Dawntrail
  </em>
  as a step back from
  <em>
   Endwalker
  </em>
  , Square Enix is working to address community concerns by rolling out ambitious updates designed to reinvigorate engagement.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players have arguably been primarily funneled into Savage and Ultimate Raids, leaving those who enjoyed large-scale, cooperative activities with fewer options. Patch 7.2 aims to change that by expanding
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  ’s endgame experience, potentially capturing the interest of fans who have been looking for something fresh while still paying tribute to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6’s
  </em>
  iconic mechanical designs.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="futuristic-mechs-offer-a-nostalgic-connection-to-ff6-in-final-fantasy-14">
  Futuristic Mechs Offer a Nostalgic Connection to FF6 in Final Fantasy 14
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-341120923" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-341120923" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-341120923" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-341120923" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-341120923-img" id="article-gallery-1-341120923">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-341120923" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1337700366">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Throughout the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  series, magitek has been synonymous with imperial ambition and the fusion of magic with advanced technology. In
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  , the Gestahlian Empire harnessed magitek to create devastating war machines, including the iconic Magitek Armor. While
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  ’s version of magitek has largely been tied to the Garlean Empire’s ceruleum-fueled machinery, Patch 7.2’s introduction of new futuristic mechs suggests a shift toward a different kind of high-tech warfare.
 </p>
 <p>
  These mechs will be featured as part of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  ’s Cosmic Exploration content, where players assist the Loporrits in colonizing new worlds. This interstellar theme is a significant departure from previous expansions, but the inclusion of advanced machinery reminiscent of magitek suggests a deliberate nod to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6’s
  </em>
  technological aesthetic. If Square Enix further leans into this connection—perhaps by incorporating similar designs, abilities, or even a questline referencing magitek’s origins—it could offer longtime fans a satisfying blend of nostalgia and innovation.
 </p>
 <h3 id="final-fantasy-14-rsquo-s-sci-fi-direction-gains-traction">
  Final Fantasy 14’s Sci-Fi Direction Gains Traction
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of
  <em>
   Dawntrail’s
  </em>
  most praised elements has been its embrace of science fiction, particularly with locations like Solution Nine, a neon-lit metropolis filled with towering skyscrapers and holographic billboards. The Arcadion raid series, another major addition, has also leaned heavily into this futuristic aesthetic, offering a stark contrast to the medieval and high-fantasy settings of previous expansions.
 </p>
 <p>
  The introduction of the mechs in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  Patch 7.2 builds on this momentum, reinforcing
  <em>
   FF14
  </em>
  ’s evolution into a game that blends fantasy with cutting-edge technology. For players who enjoyed the sci-fi elements of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 8
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 13
  </em>
  , this could make
  <em>
   Dawntrail’s
  </em>
  ongoing updates even more appealing. Moreover, the expansion of high-tech content might serve to distinguish
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  from other MMORPGs, keeping the game fresh while still maintaining ties to its
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  roots.
 </p>
 <h3 id="phantom-jobs-and-large-scale-battles-arrive">
  Phantom Jobs and Large-Scale Battles Arrive
 </h3>
 <p>
  Beyond mechs and Cosmic Exploration, Patch 7.2 is set to introduce significant gameplay changes, including Phantom Jobs within the Occult Crescent. These new roles allow players to mix and match abilities in ways that weren’t previously possible, offering a level of customization reminiscent of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  ’s Esper system. Just as characters in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  could learn magic from Espers, Phantom Jobs may grant players access to unique skills that deviate from traditional job mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, large-scale battles similar to Eureka and Bozja are returning, providing an alternative to high-end raiding for those who prefer open-world cooperative challenges. These additions aim to create a more diverse endgame experience.
 </p>
 <h3 id="nostalgia-could-be-the-key-to-engagement-in-final-fantasy-14">
  Nostalgia Could Be the Key to Engagement in Final Fantasy 14
 </h3>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  entering a new phase post-
  <em>
   Dawntrail
  </em>
  , finding ways to keep players engaged is critical. Nostalgic elements like magitek-inspired mechs could help rekindle interest among longtime fans, while the sci-fi “expansion” of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14’s
  </em>
  world offers something fresh for those eager for innovation. By blending classic
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  themes with new gameplay mechanics, Patch 7.2 has the potential to strike the right balance between honoring the past and embracing the future.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether or not this approach will be enough to win over those who felt
  <em>
   Dawntrail
  </em>
  lacked impact remains to be seen, but with Cosmic Exploration, Phantom Jobs, and large-scale battles on the horizon,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  is making a strong case for why fans of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  should keep an eye on what’s coming next.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sci-fi RPG Is Like Crazy Taxi Meets Cyberpunk 2077</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cybertaxi-lunatic-nights-steam-demo/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A demo for the sci-fi RPG CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights is now available to download on Steam.
     </li>
     <li>
      The title will be released in early access on March 4.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players will be tasked with picking up and dropping off cab fares, battling enemies, collecting loot, and much more.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As part of Steam Next Fest, developer Hed Media Games has launched a demo for its sci-fi RPG
  <strong>
   <em>
    CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
   </em>
  </strong>
  , giving fans a taste of what to expect from this cyberpunk taxi-driving simulator.
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic
  </em>
  <em>
   Nights
  </em>
  is set to launch in early access on March 4, and players can now jump into the high-octane world of neon destruction and impeccable driving with this exclusive Steam demo.
 </p>
 <p>
  Offering a unique combination of the retro classic
  <em>
   Crazy Taxi
  </em>
  and games like
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  is inspired by 90s action flicks and combines semi-realistic driving mechanics with familiar RPG exploration elements. Fans of futuristic settings and chaotic simulators may want to take a closer look at the explosive entertainment awaiting in
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Developed by solo creator Hed Media Games,
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  will take players to the dystopian noir world of Prison City where they must track down their wrongfully accused sister and rescue her from a corrupt detention facility. Players will be tasked with picking up and successfully dropping off cab fares while battling it out in over-the-top encounters against rival taxis. A full-scale taxi-driving simulator game, players will need to be mindful of their car battery and fuel levels, utilize windshield wipers and headlights for safe driving, and keep their beloved cab fully kitted-out with an array of firearms and weapons to keep street gangs at bay. Players can also step outside their taxi for a more direct approach with FPS action against drones, crazy clowns, and the pesky competition.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="cybertaxi-lunatic-nights-early-access-trailer">
  CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights Early Access Trailer
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-4b9ebec74f9e3f69" id="emaki-video-player-4b9ebec74f9e3f69">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  features an array of engaging gameplay mechanics and retro story elements to give players plenty of variety on their cab-driving adventure. Each fare will have additional requests, such as finding a missing cat, retrieving lost keys from the sewer, or defending a local school from lurking thugs, giving players the opportunity to step out of the taxi and enjoy the action RPG gameplay. But players will also need to be mindful of their driving, as the game features a rating system that could make or break their future as a cab driver. Featuring taxi customization, ragdoll physics, hidden minigames, collectible loot, and the irreverent humor of timeless 90s action movies, the
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  demo is available now on Steam.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-119129501" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-119129501" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-119129501" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-119129501" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-119129501-img" id="article-gallery-1-119129501">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-119129501" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1263668973">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Both intentionally ridiculous and surprisingly realistic simulation video games have found popularity in recent years, with the genre continuing to expand with comical and life-like offerings. Looking to find a delightful balance between humor and realism,
  <em>
   CyberTaxi: Lunatic Nights
  </em>
  launches in early access exclusively for PC on March 4.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mecha BREAK Hands-On Preview</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/mecha-break-hands-on-preview/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mecha BREAK
   </em>
  </strong>
  is Amazing Seasun games' answer to the problem mecha fans—including its development team—have grappled with for decades: there simply aren't many competitive mecha games that deliver a sense of speed, power fantasy, and mechanized violence to a satisfying degree. If anything can be said about
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  , it's that the game ticks all three boxes with extreme prejudice. Aside from
  <em>
   Armored Core
  </em>
  by which
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  is heavily influenced, the most popular mecha games are also limited by how preexisting franchise mecha must be adapted to fill a gameplay role. With a distinctly hero shooter-feeling collection of Strikers,
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  benefits from its freedom to tailor each design to a specific, unique playstyle suitable for equally specific tastes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  That hero shooter feel also carries over to
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's overall live service structure: a battle pass, daily sign-in bonuses yielding currency for purchasing new Strikers, challenges to pursue, and a dizzying amount of cosmetics to unlock. It currently offers three modes: 3v3, casual or ranked 6v6, and its capstone 30-player extraction shooter mode, Mashmak. Ahead of
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's open beta, Game Rant visited Amazing Seasun Games to experience each of these facets, and while there are some concerns about its currency system and stat-altering mods,
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's moment-to-moment gameplay is the high-octane spectacle of skyscraper-sized robotic chaos that genre fans have been waiting for.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="mecha-break-39-s-gameplay-is-pure-chaos">
  Mecha BREAK's Gameplay Is Pure Chaos
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1224225968" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1224225968" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1224225968" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1224225968" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1224225968-img" id="article-gallery-1-1224225968">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1224225968" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1961944130">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unbound by the laws of physics or constraints like franchise lore accuracy,
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's combat is blazing fast, with the gigantic Strikers boosting, dashing, and soaring at speeds one would normally expect from a
  <em>
   Dragon Ball
  </em>
  fighting game. Each mech is designed with a combination of specialties: a heavy sniper that can hover above the battlefield, a light attacker that transforms into a fighter jet, a heavy brawler armed with a massive melee energy weapon, and an ultra-heavy attacker that transforms into a devastating stationary weapons emplacement. Each has a useful role in team play, and the mixture of ground, air, ranged, and melee combat ensures that no Striker is best in every situation.
 </p>
 <p>
  In such a fast-paced game with lasers, missiles, and artillery, melee Strikers are still a menace; they're quite capable of boosting into the air and swatting down a Falcon in jet mode with a well-timed swing. Being struck by melee attacks briefly stuns a Striker, which makes close-quarters fighting a cinematic dance of towering robots boosting in every direction to find an opening. On the other hand, Strikers armed with shields can parry melee attacks, leaving their opponent vulnerable to a follow-up.
 </p>
 <h3 id="every-mecha-break-striker-has-a-clear-role">
  Every Mecha BREAK Striker Has a Clear Role
 </h3>
 <p>
  While the offensive and defensive Strikers cover the full spectrum of combat playstyles,
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's support Strikers particularly stood out. Our favorite Striker of the day was the light support Striker, Luminae. Luminae can launch up to two drones to each friendly Striker that will heal them over time and Luminae can project a healing aura for nearby allies. Meanwhile, Luminae can switch to attack mode at will, transforming these abilities into offensive variants. By strategically switching between both modes, we were able to turn the tide in many incidents by recovering an endangered teammate before sapping the life out of their opponent.
 </p>
 <p>
  Each Striker seemed to gravitate naturally to a suitable role: the heavy sniper Aquila hovers in the distance taking potshots, Tricera guards a key objective in its fortified stationary mode, the brawler Welkin applies pressure with a relentless melee assault, while the agile Falcon zips by delivering a deadly volley of missiles on strafing runs. While some Strikers were subjectively more interesting than others according to our playstyle preferences, none felt particularly out of balance, with
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's Strikers having clear strengths and weaknesses. All participants agreed that a skilled Aquila sniper can be a diabolical presence, but Aquila is still extremely vulnerable to direct pressure due to limited close-range capabilities.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mecha-break-39-s-customization-is-a-game-on-its-own">
  Mecha BREAK's Customization Is a Game on Its Own
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="mecha-break-paint" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png" decoding="async" height="1439" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-paint.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2558"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The mecha genre has a decades-long tradition of delivering extreme customizability dating back to tabletop games like
  <em>
   BattleTech
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  is no different. Similar to
  <em>
   Armored Core
  </em>
  's paint system, Strikers can be meticulously painted, all the way down to individual segments on either held weapon. For less artistically inclined players, full palettes can also be applied. There are hundreds of color options, each with varying degrees of wear, gloss, and saturation. While many colors are available by default, others are acquired through loot boxes or as rewards for completing specific challenges. The only missing thing is part swapping to modify Strikers further, but that may be to ensure each Striker retains a recognizable silhouette.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  also features a robust character creator that allows players to modify every detail of the game's pilot avatars. There's body and face sculpting, an assortment of makeup options, voices, hairstyles, and a sizeable wardrobe of outfits and accessories. The pilots are more than just portraits: between matches, players can walk around their base as the pilot, and there are plans to implement a bar where players can socialize. Given mecha genre fans' penchant for personalization, unlocking new pilot clothing or Striker paints is an attractive carrot to chase.
 </p>
 <h3 id="mecha-break-39-s-free-to-play-model">
  Mecha BREAK's Free-to-Play Model
 </h3>
 <p>
  As a free-to-play live service game, it can't be avoided that much of this is tied to a purchasable currency that can also be earned through gameplay. So far, the pace of earning currency didn't feel overly punishing, but the more expensive Strikers won't come overnight. Thankfully, the game allows players to try every Striker in a simulation, so players know exactly what they're in for before investing.
 </p>
 <p>
  Regarding unlocks and currency, one potential concern is the game's Striker mods, which alter the performance of Strikers in myriad ways. These mods have tiered rarities and can be obtained from loot boxes, which could be a slippery slope toward a feeling of pay-to-win if not handled carefully. However, each mod bears an equal drawback: one might give the Striker 3% more aerial speed, but with 3% less energy to remain airborne. A rarer variant might offer 6% more speed but at the cost of even less energy. In some instances, we opted not to slot a mod at all because we favored a more balanced performance from that component. So long as mods carry drawbacks in this manner, the system shouldn't be too disruptive to the overall game balance; like the specialized Strikers, players enjoy a strength at the cost of a weakness.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="mecha-break-39-s-extraction-shooter-mode-is-a-welcome-addition">
  Mecha BREAK's Extraction Shooter Mode Is a Welcome Addition
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="mecha-break-extract" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/mecha-break-extract.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's three game modes bring surprisingly diverse gameplay options. 6v6 is its chief competitive format with team deathmatch, free-for-all, and objective-based matches. In one map, we needed to capture and defend a vehicle on rails as it traveled toward our team's victory point. In another, we were tasked with capturing and holding points around the map to score points. These objective-based modes are where the arsenal of Strikers truly shines, encouraging players to coordinate their roles to secure and defend objectives.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mashmak is
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  's PvPvE extraction shooter mode, and it's a wildly different experience. 10 squads of three players are dropped into a massive 16x16km map—large enough that it takes 10 full minutes for Falcon to fly from end to end—to defeat NPC bosses, acquire loot, and reach an extraction point. The map is dotted with NPC bases filled with small-fry enemies that are satisfying to dispatch en masse, and multi-phase bosses overseeing these bases are the primary source of loot. There's also a time pressure element: a deadly storm moves about the map, and begins expanding gradually after 15 minutes. By the 30-minute mark, the storm will envelope 90% of the map. Compared to the enclosing
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  -style circle, this storm presents more unique challenges: it may move between the squad and its chosen extraction point, calling for a change of plans if they can't make it to extraction before the point expires.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's quite a change of pace since the map's enormous size allows for stealth and ambush tactics against preoccupied players, and the gunfire might attract other squads looking to join the fray. In this mode, players can also airdrop supplies including ammo, additional weaponry—important for support players with limited offensive capabilities—and respawns for downed teammates. Less mobile Strikers might wish to order a handy glider to keep up with more agile teammates. In the meantime, Mashmak pits players against some truly huge world bosses like a Titan Striker that dwarfs the players' own Strikers, or Constantine, a heavily-armed battleship. Loot from this mode is an excellent source of mods, paints, and currency, serving as a core progression path rather than a gimmicky distraction.
 </p>
 <p>
  So far,
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  is one of the most promising PvP mecha games the genre has hosted in years. As long as it balances its freemium approach in a player-friendly manner, its frantic gameplay, diverse arsenal, and variety of game modes should easily satisfy hungry mecha fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Mecha BREAK
  </em>
  open beta is now available on PC and Xbox Series X|S.
 </p>
 <p>
  Game Rant was provided travel and lodging for the purposes of this preview.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Version 5.5: Predicting Varesa's Place in the Meta</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-version-55-varesa-dps-hypercarry-battery-good-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Ahead of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s upcoming version 5.5 update releasing on March 26, 2025, the new characters coming in this update have already been officially revealed. This update for
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  will introduce the long-awaited Iansan as a four-star character, and Varesa as a five-star character.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While these characters’ ability kits haven’t yet been officially revealed, there are already plenty of leaks from trusted community sources about these characters. Based on the latest leaks for these new characters coming to
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , players should know what to expect from Varesa in anticipation of her debut Wish Banner in the version 5.5 update.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="predicting-how-varesa-will-compare-to-genshin-impact-rsquo-s-current-meta">
  Predicting How Varesa Will Compare to Genshin Impact’s Current Meta
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1162158917" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1162158917" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1162158917" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1162158917" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1162158917-img" id="article-gallery-1-1162158917">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1162158917" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1342222498">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="varesa-39-s-rating-predictions">
  Varesa's Rating Predictions
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   A-Tier DPS
  </li>
  <li>
   S-Tier Battery
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="varesa-rsquo-s-strengths">
  Varesa’s Strengths
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Can enter states where her Elemental Skill and Elemental Burst can be cast more frequently than other characters
  </li>
  <li>
   Generates and consumes high amounts of Nightsoul Points quickly
  </li>
  <li>
   Provides herself with stagger resistance
  </li>
  <li>
   Long attack and ability combos can activate personal buffs for increased damage
  </li>
  <li>
   Synergizes well with other Natlan characters and Electro characters
  </li>
  <li>
   Nightsoul’s Blessing state provides exploration and combat utility
  </li>
  <li>
   Catalyst weapon type provides natural Electro damage
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="varesa-rsquo-s-weaknesses">
  Varesa’s Weaknesses
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Optimal damage output requires a long ability/attack rotation setup
  </li>
  <li>
   Varesa’s damage buffs and interruption resistance don’t extend to other characters
  </li>
  <li>
   Kit based on plunging attacks requires niche Artifact sets
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Varesa’s leaked attributes, attacks, and abilities are subject to balancing changes ahead of her official release in
     <em>
      Genshin Impact
     </em>
     ’s 5.5 update.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="varesa-rsquo-s-long-attack-combos-could-give-her-a-disadvantage-over-dps-hypercarry-characters-with-nukes">
  Varesa’s Long Attack Combos Could Give Her a Disadvantage Over DPS/Hypercarry Characters With Nukes
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of Varesa’s biggest weaknesses is the timing required to activate her own damage buffs, since Varesa’s optimal damage setup seemingly relies on a rotation of specific attacks and abilities. Taking into account how long this process can take each time and then considering the limited amount of time that buffs from other support characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  are active, Varesa might not be able to fully utilize buffs from multiple support characters before these buffs, and/or her own buffs expire.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hence, Varesa likely won’t be able to outperform DPS/Hypercarry characters whose damage is concentrated in one attack or ability nuke that deals a single instance of damage, as these characters can generally utilize stackable, temporary buffs more reliably. However, instead of replacing meta DPS/Hypercarry characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , Varesa would seemingly be better as a sub-DPS and battery unit, specifically on team compositions with other Natlan or Electro characters.
 </p>
 <h3 id="varesa-could-be-a-top-tier-battery-for-natlan-and-electro-characters">
  Varesa Could be a Top-Tier Battery for Natlan and Electro Characters
 </h3>
 <p>
  Since Varesa can both generate and consume high amounts of Nightsoul Points on her own by rapidly landing plunging attacks and casting both her Elemental Skill and Elemental Burst, she will be an efficient way to fuel other Natlan characters’ Nightsoul’s Blessing states. Considering that Varesa also benefits from other characters triggering their Nightsoul’s Blessing state, using her as a battery on a Natlan team composition can create nearly endless cycles of fueling Natlan characters’ Nightsoul Points. Overall, Varesa could potentially replace Ororon as a better battery unit for both Electro and Natlan team compositions.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_17">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Varesa could be a good battery for Mavuika, in particular, because Varesa’s efficiency with generating and consuming Nightsoul Points can fuel Mavuika’s Fighting Spirit mechanic.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  While Varesa can activate various damage buffs, the majority of these buffs don't extend to other characters, and they could be difficult to manage together with buffs from other support characters. Although this limits her flexibility as a primary DPS unit, her efficiency as a battery arguably makes up for this. Ultimately, while Varesa’s reliance on long attack combos may not be able to outperform nukes from some of the best DPS/Hypercarry meta characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , Varesa can still be a powerful character when slotted onto a team composition with Natlan characters or other Electro characters as a battery.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Leak Reveals Important Varesa Changes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-leaks-varesa-changes-version-5-5/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Varesa's changes in Version 5.5 make her less reliant on teammates like Xianyun.
     </li>
     <li>
      Varesa's adjustments include more Plunging Attack damage.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The latest build for Version 5.5 has introduced some important changes to Varesa in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  , making her less reliant on having Xianyun as a teammate. An argument could be made that the odd patches of Natlan in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  have had rather exciting beta cycles. Version 5.1 saw the rise of Xilonen as a premium Support character; Version 5.3 featured Citlali and Mavuika pushing the limits of Melt; and Version 5.5 is now set to introduce an alternative to Bennett and a powerful Plunge Hypercarry.
 </p>
 <p>
  Given Bennett's position as one of the best 4-Star characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , many players wondered if he could ever be replaced. The developers finally provided the
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  community with an answer by designing Iansan as an Electro Support – featuring major ATK buffs and limited healing in her ability kit. Iansan was made with Varesa in mind, and Varesa is expected to be a worthwhile investment for any
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  player interested in Plunge characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  The recent changes to Varesa were documented via HomDGCat, and they primarily attempt to address two things: her reliance on Xianyun, and the lack of synergy with the new Artifact Set from Version 5.5. This appears to be accomplished via altering her first Passive to provide more Plunging Attack damage that scales off her ATK. Her second Passive has also undergone changes, as Varesa will now benefit even more from Natlan characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , especially Xilonen, who is capable of triggering two Nightsoul Bursts on her own.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-varesa-changes-in-version-5-5-v3">
  Genshin Impact: Varesa Changes in Version 5.5 (v3)
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-977472385" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-977472385" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-977472385" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-977472385" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-977472385-img" id="article-gallery-1-977472385">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-977472385" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-807584660">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Charged Attack DMG: 160.704% (down from 200.880%).
  </li>
  <li>
   Fiery Passion Charged Attack DMG: 166.752% (down from 208.368%).
  </li>
  <li>
   P1: Momentum, Triple Leap!
   <ul>
    <li>
     After casting the Elemental Skill, Night Rainbow Leap, Varesa gains "Rainbow Crash" for 5 seconds.
    </li>
    <li>
     During the duration, when Varesa performs a falling attack, Falling Impact deals an additional 60% ATK.
    </li>
    <li>
     If Varesa is in a state of Blazing Passion, the Falling Impact will be increased by 150% ATK.
    </li>
    <li>
     The "Rainbow Crash" effect is removed when the Ground Crash hits an enemy or the duration ends.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   P2: Hero, Back For the Second Time!
   <ul>
    <li>
     When a nearby character in the party triggers "Night Soul Burst", Varesa's Attack is increased by 30% and 35% for 12 seconds. The effect stacks up to two stacks, with each stack calculating its duration independently.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players can consider these changes as an overall buff to Varesa in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , as this makes characters such as Chevreuse viable (if not preferable alternatives). Assuming she survives beta testing in her current form, Varesa will likely have two premium teams: one built around Overload with Chevreuse, and one built around Xilonen and Furina. Xianyun would be a decent teammate for Varesa in the latter team (due to her group healing), but players shouldn't feel obligated to pull for her on the upcoming Event Banners.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Mavuika's release and Varesa's impending debut in Version 5.5, Chevreuse is rapidly becoming a coveted 4-Star in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . Those who have invested in Chevreuse since Version 4.3 have effectively opened up a new playstyle via Overload, and all signs point that her value will only continue to grow. In terms of the Event Banners for Version 5.5, those who aren't interested in Varesa's gameplay should at least try to pull for Xilonen, who continues to firmly establish herself as one of the best Support characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . Version 5.5 is set to come out on March 26, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
