<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How Capcom Is Reviving The Game Genre It Once Pioneered</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/capcom-hack-slash-genre-revival-how-onimusha-okami/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  While 2024 was a low-key year for
  <strong>
   Capcom
  </strong>
  , the Japanese publisher has been on a recent tear of bringing back beloved franchises. Finishing its spree of
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  remasters and translations with
  <em>
   Ace Attorney Investigations Collection
  </em>
  was just the start, as it quickly followed that with the launch of
  <em>
   Marvel vs. Capcom Fighting Collection: Arcade Classics
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dead Rising Deluxe Remaster
  </em>
  . What really blew old Capcom fans away, though, was its announcements at The Game Awards 2024. Not only was
  <em>
   Onimusha: Way of the Sword
  </em>
  a new mainline entry in its franchise, nearly twenty years after the last one, a console sequel for
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  was finally announced.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Capcom's investor relations website quickly followed up The Game Awards with a short overview of the announcements, with some additional paragraphs declaring its intent to revive dormant IPs that haven't launched new games recently. Few gaming companies have libraries with as many potent franchises as Capcom, so following Sega's ongoing example of bringing series back en masse would be a well-received move. However, Capcom starting with new installments for
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  in particular will also have the happy side effect of jump-starting a particular game genre’s return from the very era they hail from.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="capcom-has-more-than-just-franchises-sleeping-in-its-library">
  Capcom Has More Than Just Franchises Sleeping In Its Library
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-525446378" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-525446378" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-525446378" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-525446378" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-525446378-img" id="article-gallery-1-525446378">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-525446378" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-956488058">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are a lot of genres under Capcom's banner, from puzzle games like
  <em>
   Ghost Trick
  </em>
  to turn-based RPGs like the old
  <em>
   Breath of Fire
  </em>
  titles. Above all else, though, Capcom is best known for its action games. They are spread across many categories, like
  <em>
   Street Fighter
  </em>
  ’s fighting games,
  <em>
   Final Fight
  </em>
  ’s beat-'em-ups,
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  ’s hack-and-slash, and even
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  ’s takedown-integrated third-person shooting, but all of these Capcom titles are genre-defining examples of their respective gameplay style.
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  fall closest to
  <em>
   DMC
  </em>
  , which is a relief after how the last decade has treated their shared subgenre.
 </p>
 <h3 id="stylish-3d-action-nearly-died-in-the-2010-rsquo-s">
  Stylish 3D Action Nearly Died In The 2010’s
 </h3>
 <p>
  3D hack-and-slash action, with minimal RPG elements attached, has been scarce since the PS3 and Xbox 360 generation. Capcom's AAA and AA output narrowed alongside the rest of the industry, and
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  ’s releases slowed down before the series’ primary director, Hideaki Itsuno, left in 2024. Ex-
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   God Hand
  </em>
  developers continued their hack-and-slash career as Platinum Games, but eventually many key staff left over creative differences and growing financial concerns. Other genre pillars like Koei Tecmo’s Team Ninja and Sony’s
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  franchise introduced RPG mechanics to expand their audience. Even accounting for indies, it's hard to downplay how much ground 3D melee action has lost.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hack-and-slash-is-creeping-back-into-capcom-rsquo-s-output">
  Hack-And-Slash Is Creeping Back Into Capcom’s Output
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1260597766" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1260597766" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1260597766" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1260597766" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1260597766-img" id="article-gallery-2-1260597766">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1260597766" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2069030162">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Action-RPG dominance isn't a bad thing, as Soulslikes are popular for a reason, and other hybrid approaches like
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Dynasty Warriors
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  , the
  <em>
   Tales
  </em>
  series,
  <em>
   Ys
  </em>
  , and even Capcom's own
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dragon’s Dogma
  </em>
  offer plenty of variety. More options are still better for everyone, though, and Capcom seems dead-set on bringing some back. It's already on its way, too, as summer 2024’s
  <em>
   Kunitsu-Gami: Path of the Goddess
  </em>
  harkens back to the experimental period of hack-and-slash’s PS2 golden age. Now,
  <em>
   Onimusha
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  just need to make this revival worth Capcom's trouble.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-onimusha-and-okami-can-correct-capcom-39-s-combat-course">
  How Onimusha and Okami Can Correct Capcom's Combat Course
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Onimusha: Way of the Sword
  </em>
  is an offshoot of
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  like
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  itself, and could once again strike a middle ground between the two. It might also be Capcom’s first Soulslike in disguise, but would likely stay close to
  <em>
   Sekiro
  </em>
  due to parrying and careful offense already being part of its identity. More pertinently,
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  ’s sequel is being helmed by its original director, Hideaki Kamiya, on top of an unknown number of ex-Platinum staff. That should guarantee being able to match the surprising combat depth of the first
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  , and could pave the way for future action endeavors at
  <strong>
   Capcom
  </strong>
  , just like old times.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remaster Rumors Heat Up</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remaster-reveal-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xbox insider Jez Corden hints that Bethesda may reveal an Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion remake or remaster during a January 2025 event.
     </li>
     <li>
      While Xbox hasn't confirmed a showcase for January, the company previously held Developer Directs in both January 2023 and January 2024.
     </li>
     <li>
      Bethesda formally announced The Elder Scrolls 6 in June 2018, but news regarding the project has been scarce since then.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  According to Xbox insider Jez Corden, Bethesda may be gearing up to reveal a remake or remaster of the 2006 RPG
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion
   </em>
  </strong>
  in January 2025. This corroborates a leak first seen earlier in December, prompting fans of
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion
  </em>
  to begin their celebrations a tad early.
 </p>
 <p>
  First released in 2006,
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion
  </em>
  was the long-awaited follow-up to 2002's
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 3: Morrowind
  </em>
  and quickly grabbed the attention of critics and fans alike. Still dubbed one of the greatest games ever made by many players,
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  won a flood of year-end awards and continues to be praised for its lore, open world, story, and music. While its graphics were notable at release, nearly two decades have passed since
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  hit store shelves, prompting many fans of the title to ask Bethesda for a new coat of paint. While a popular fan-created mod has reimagined
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  with
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  's engine, an official remaster may be announced in the coming weeks.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a Twitter comment from Jez Cordon, the insider and Windows Central Executive Editor noted that he's expecting to see an
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  remaster during the rumored Xbox Developer Direct in January 2025. Cordon also noted that while he's only expecting to see a remaster, a remake of the beloved title is also a possibility. This new intel follows similar comments made by the YouTuber eXtas1s earlier in December, with a 2025 release date for the revamped
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  also predicted. While Xbox hasn't confirmed a showcase for January, the company previously held Developer Directs in both January 2023 and January 2024.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="an-elder-scrolls-4-oblivion-remaster-or-remake-could-be-revealed-in-january-2025">
  An Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion Remaster or Remake Could Be Revealed in January 2025
 </h2>
 <p>
  On December 9, Corden took to Twitter to predict that Xbox wouldn't feature many first-party announcements during The Game Awards 2024, instead planning an event for Q1 2025. While the proposed showcase would likely focus on planned 2025 releases like
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  , many fans are wondering what's happening at Bethesda following the release of
  <em>
   Starfield
  </em>
  in 2023.
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  was formally announced in June 2018, with barely any news to be found in the years since. In 2023, Phil Spencer went on record to estimate that the highly anticipated RPG was at least five years away from launch, with no platforms announced.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1710044636" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1710044636" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1710044636" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1710044636" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1710044636-img" id="article-gallery-1-1710044636">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1710044636" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-16063715">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While an
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  remake or remaster isn't guaranteed to appear at the next Xbox presentation, multiple sources are pointing towards the massive project being a real possibility. Bethesda has made it clear that it will work on
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  before tackling
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , but in the meantime, the development team may have been busy cooking up this surprise for fans of one of its most loved role-playing titles.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: Xur Exotic Armor, Weapon, and Recommendations for December 27</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/destiny-2-xur-exotic-armor-weapon-recommendations-december-27/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xur returns to Destiny 2 with new exotic and legendary gear in The Dawning's final week.
     </li>
     <li>
      Exotic armor this week includes Dunemarchers, class items, The Bombardiers, and Phoenix Protocol.
     </li>
     <li>
      Xur's exotic weapons includes a new Hawkmoon roll, Cerberus+1, The Wardcliff Coil, and Merciless.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Xur has returned again to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Destiny 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , complete with new exotic and legendary gear for players to check out for a limited time. It's the final week of The Dawning in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  , giving players one last chance to find the weapon rolls they want, continue baking cookies, and earning those three rare emblems.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Bungie is away on holiday break, fans have seemingly embraced the most recent community challenge. Players were tasked with baking specific cookies for certain NPC characters over the course of the past three weeks, hitting a certain number to make 3 rare emblems easier to spawn when opening A Gift In Return boxes. During the first week,
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  players baked a huge amount of cookies for Commander Zavala, going well over 3 million Gjallardoodles.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the meantime, the weekend merchant Xur is back with a new inventory of gear for
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  players. Follow this guide for his current weekend location, news on his exotic cipher quest, as well as a review of all the exotic and legendary gear he's brought for the weekend of December 27, 2024.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-is-xur">
  Where is Xur?
 </h2>
 <p>
  Xur has now taken up permanent residence in the Bazaar area inside The Tower, so there's no more hunting when the weekend comes around.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Destiny 2 Xur" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg" decoding="async" height="720" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xurs-location-and-wares-feb-14-2020_feature.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1280"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since the Bazaar is located between both fast travel points, players can pick either one to load into. Head into the area where Ikora and Hawthorne are and look for the Ramen Shop towards the back wall. While facing the shop, the alley is to the right, where Xur is standing.
 </p>
 <h2 id="destiny-2-class-armor-and-exotic-cipher">
  Destiny 2 Class Armor and Exotic Cipher
 </h2>
 <p>
  Xur's role continues to offer the usual weekly quests, exotics, and legendary gear. Not only are these quests required to purchase a second fated engram, but they're necessary to acquire legacy exotic gear from the Tower kiosk. Players can earn a new cipher by completing strikes and winning crucible or gambit matches. Gain bonus points for playing with clan mates or finishing more challenging activities.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xur-39-s-exotic-armor">
  Xur's Exotic Armor
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="destiny 2 phoenix protocol" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/destiny-2-phoenix-protocol.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Phoenix Protocol - Warlock chest armor
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Exotic Perk
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703345" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/6985c5f8dbe4d38b0702df7f55d50172-1.png"/>
    Battle-Hearth
   </span>
   - Kills and assists you make while standing in your Well of Radiance return Super energy.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This is a solid exotic for PvE activities, especially for newer Warlock players who may have picked the game up over the Black Friday or Holiday season. The roll is also pretty nice, so for those who don't have one or want to replace a worse roll, this is worth a look.
 </p>
 <p>
  Stat Values (67 Total):
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mobility +4
  </li>
  <li>
   Resilience +20
  </li>
  <li>
   Recovery +12
  </li>
  <li>
   Discipline +14
  </li>
  <li>
   Intellect +15
  </li>
  <li>
   Strength +2
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="destiny 2 the bombardiers" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/destiny-2-the-bombardiers.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   The Bombardiers - Hunter leg armor
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Exotic Perk
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703424" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/97c352f8ad87a9c7ea68b2a643d821ed-1.png"/>
    Parting Gift
   </span>
   - Dodging leaves behind an explosive that detonates after a short delay, damaging targets around it and creating a secondary effect based on your Super's element.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Not a required buy this week, it's more of a fun exotic to mess around with than anything that will be at the top of the meta. The big problem this week is the roll, which is very low.
 </p>
 <p>
  Stat Values (61 Total):
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mobility +15
  </li>
  <li>
   Resilience +2
  </li>
  <li>
   Recovery +12
  </li>
  <li>
   Discipline +7
  </li>
  <li>
   Intellect +7
  </li>
  <li>
   Strength +18
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="destiny 2 dunemarchers leg exotics" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="960" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/3790373072-Cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Dunemarchers - Titan leg armor
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Exotic Perk
  </em>
  :
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703408" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/10eb32a307eaadd26eb0fe4550bcdbfb-1.png"/>
    Linear Actuators
   </span>
   - Increases sprint speed. Sprinting builds up a static charge. After melee-attacking an enemy, that charge will chain damage to nearby enemies.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A good exotic for dealing with groups of enemies, as it is able to chain melee damage after sprinting. The roll is actually tied for the highest of the week as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  Stat Values (67 total):
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mobility +17
  </li>
  <li>
   Resilience +7
  </li>
  <li>
   Recovery +10
  </li>
  <li>
   Discipline +12
  </li>
  <li>
   Intellect +14
  </li>
  <li>
   Strength +7
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="xur-inventory-items">
  Xur Inventory Items
 </h2>
 <p>
  Year 7 in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  has upgraded Xur's inventory, adding a true rank progression system, rewards, as well as focusing options. Xur also has more than just weapons and armor as well, including:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Vigilance Wing Catalyst
  </li>
  <li>
   MIDA Multi-Tool Catalyst
  </li>
  <li>
   The Xurfboard (Skimmer Board Vehicle)
  </li>
  <li>
   Essentialism/Stoicism/Solipsism OR Exotic Cipher
  </li>
  <li>
   Exotic Engram
  </li>
  <li>
   Ascendant Shard
  </li>
  <li>
   Glimmer
  </li>
  <li>
   Enhancement Core
  </li>
  <li>
   Crucible Engram
  </li>
  <li>
   Strange Gift (Random Item for 1 Strange Coin)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xur-39-s-exotic-weapons">
  Xur's Exotic Weapons
 </h2>
 <p>
  Year 7's Xur revamp has also added the ability to offer multiple exotic weapons in one visit. Here is what Xur has this weekend:
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Destiny 2 Hawkmoon Exotic Hand Cannon" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg" decoding="async" height="600" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Destiny-2-Hawkmoon-(1).jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="hawkmoon---hand-cannon">
  Hawkmoon - Hand Cannon
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703774" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/243f5529bbd845871803181958599473-1.png"/>
    Paracausal Shot
   </span>
   - Final blows and precision hits with Hawkmoon grant stacks of Paracausal Charge. The final round in the magazine deals bonus damage based on the number of stacks. Stowing Hawkmoon on the final round removes this bonus.
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703683" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/260eba9dd149dbb94b1306c9ed4dd8db-1.png"/>
    Fluted Barrel
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703144" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/069170916c98748b7b3e33b80bd7d689-1.png"/>
    Alloy Magazine
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703201" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/438cbb2a46dda1ec4412a77d01d8dcd2-1-1.png"/>
    Smooth Grip
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   Eye of the Storm
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="destiny 2 forsaken cerberus+1 exotic auto rifle" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg" decoding="async" height="600" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/Destiny-2-Cerberus-Plus-1-Exotic-Auto-Rifle.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1080"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="cerberus-1---auto-rifle">
  Cerberus+1 - Auto Rifle
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703245" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/4de9cb8fc9c1c4e6129c14a196b3ed73-1.png"/>
    Four-Headed Dog
   </span>
   - Shoots erratic bullets from all gun barrels at the same time.
  </li>
  <li>
   Spread Shot Package - Aiming this weapon reduces the spread of its projectiles.
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703686" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/79d5f1f469d3290cfb849f4b3e6fc16b-1.png"/>
    Rifled Barrel
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703683" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/260eba9dd149dbb94b1306c9ed4dd8db-1.png"/>
    Fluted Barrel
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703681" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/40a4bdcf0f5a4e492927f9569eaf529d-1.png"/>
    Full Bore
   </span>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Destiny 2 Merciless" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg" decoding="async" height="800" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Destiny-2-Merciless.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1600"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="merciless---fusion-rifle">
  Merciless - Fusion Rifle
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703785" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/9517548e73ff619a2e19f5432ee3c32b-1.png"/>
    Conserve Momentum
   </span>
   - Hits with projectiles decrease this weapon's charge time for a short duration.
  </li>
  <li>
   Impetus - Reloading immediately after a kill increases weapon damage for a short time.
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703172" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/0b451cbccc7f11f6aec9c153e59474cb-1.png"/>
    Chambered Compensator
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703143" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/66cfea124e24e73cca1ce6370b44ca7e-1.png"/>
    Extended Mag
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   Fitted Stock
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A creative Destiny 2 player gave his PC case a Wardcliff Coil makeover." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/destiny-2-wardcliff-coil-pc-case.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-wardcliff-coil---rocket-launcher">
  The Wardcliff Coil - Rocket Launcher
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703800" style="color: #ebc11d; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/37b8b2948487e3cd7b912e07ebaa1059-1.png"/>
    Mad Scientist
   </span>
   - Grenades spawn cluster bombs upon detonation. Defeating targets creates Arc explosions.
  </li>
  <li>
   Mechanized Autoloader - This weapon automatically reloads on ammo pickup.
  </li>
  <li>
   Volatile Launch
  </li>
  <li>
   <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="703143" style="; ;">
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/12/66cfea124e24e73cca1ce6370b44ca7e-1.png"/>
    Extended Mag
   </span>
  </li>
  <li>
   Composite Stock
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Xur with his treasure hoard from Destiny 2." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/xur-destiny-2-treasure-hoard-dares-of-eternity.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h2 id="xur-39-s-destiny-2-legendary-armor-set-and-weapons">
  Xur's Destiny 2 Legendary Armor Set and Weapons
 </h2>
 <p>
  Xur's Set of Legendary Armor and Weapons. All gear costs 50 Legendary Shards and 1000 Glimmer.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Different Times (Kinetic Pulse Rifle)
  </li>
  <li>
   Legal Action II (Kinetic Pulse Rifle)
  </li>
  <li>
   Persuader (Energy Sniper Rifle)
  </li>
  <li>
   Seventh Seraph VY-7 (Energy Submachine Gun)
  </li>
  <li>
   Falling Guillotine (Heavy Sword)
  </li>
  <li>
   Negative Space (Heavy Sword)
  </li>
  <li>
   Crown-Splitter/Quickfang/Eternity's Edge (Heavy Sword)
  </li>
  <li>
   Strange Weapon Engram
  </li>
  <li>
   Opulent Armor Set
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best JRPGs For Fast-Paced Gameplay, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-jrpgs-games-fast-paced-action-gameplay/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fast-paced JRPGs like Granblue Fantasy: Relink and Neo: The World Ends with You offer intense combat and strategic depth.
     </li>
     <li>
      Unique combat mechanics in games like Star Ocean: The Second Story R and Ys 8 provide fluid battles and customizable abilities for players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Titles like Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth and Nier: Automata offer action-oriented combat with dynamic combos and engaging gameplay experiences.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  JRPGs are widely recognized for their rich narratives and turn-based combat, but some titles stand out by introducing more dynamic gameplay, challenging the genre's traditions. This approach combines
  <strong>
   JRPGs with fast combat
  </strong>
  and classic elements, creating engaging experiences that attract players who prefer a faster pace, moving away from the slower battles found in many games of the genre.
 </p>
 <p>
  A good fast-paced JRPG balances frantic action with traditional mechanics, offering plenty of action without sacrificing a deeper narrative. The accelerated combat pace, combined with moments of exploration and story development, provides an exciting and innovative experience, ideal for those seeking deep immersion without giving up the adrenaline.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="granblue-fantasy-relink">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Granblue Fantasy Relink
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="intense-game-with-an-excellent-post-game">
  Intense Game With An Excellent Post-Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1127040841" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1127040841" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1127040841" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1127040841" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1127040841-img" id="article-gallery-1-1127040841">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1127040841" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-187344588">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Featuring frenetic gameplay from start to finish, the combat in
  <em>
   Granblue Fantasy: Relink
  </em>
  is among the best for players seeking JRPGs with fast combat, as amidst battle attacks, it's still possible to combine colorful special abilities. These visual effects, though intense, perfectly match the game's anime aesthetic.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although the main story isn't the focus of
  <em>
   Granblue Fantasy: Relink
  </em>
  , the title shines in the endgame, offering a vast number of combat-filled missions to challenge adrenaline-loving players. Additionally, it's possible to assemble a party with other characters, which contributes to the combat maintaining this more intense pace.
 </p>
 <h2 id="neo-the-world-ends-with-you">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Neo: The World Ends With You
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fast-paced-jrpg-for-those-who-also-enjoy-action">
  A Fast-Paced JRPG For Those Who Also Enjoy Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-385832163" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-385832163" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-385832163" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-385832163" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-385832163-img" id="article-gallery-2-385832163">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-385832163" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-814174732">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although one of the main strengths of
  <em>
   NEO: The World Ends with You
  </em>
  is the unique style the art direction brings to the title, the game also features perfect combat for players who enjoy button-mashing. This is because it combines frantic battle action with an excellent soundtrack, in addition to requiring some strategy from the characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  The use of pins to activate different protagonist abilities is fun, while the Beatdrop system encourages creative and well-timed combos among the party to maximize damage. Additionally, there are various options to customize the game's characters, offering different build choices and also solidifying
  <em>
   NEO: The World Ends with You
  </em>
  as one of the best action-oriented JRPGs available.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="star-ocean-the-second-story-r">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Star Ocean: The Second Story R
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-real-time-action-jrpg-with-deep-strategies">
  A Real-Time Action JRPG With Deep Strategies
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-609764303" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-609764303" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-609764303" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-609764303" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-609764303-img" id="article-gallery-3-609764303">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-609764303" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1113502163">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The combat in
  <em>
   Star Ocean: The Second Story R
  </em>
  is fluid and real-time, allowing free movement across the battlefield. With up to four active characters, the system combines basic attacks and special abilities, encouraging team coordination to maximize damage and effectively control enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, the combat system offers mechanics such as stun-locking and advanced combos, similar to the
  <em>
   Tales of
  </em>
  games, but without the same complexity. Moreover, the diversity of classes and customizable abilities provides a highly customizable experience for players, where character synergy is crucial for the game's most challenging encounters.
 </p>
 <h2 id="xenoblade-chronicles-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Xenoblade Chronicles 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-game-for-those-who-enjoy-having-many-active-characters-in-the-party">
  A Game For Those Who Enjoy Having Many Active Characters In The Party
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1168872685" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1168872685" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1168872685" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1168872685" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1168872685-img" id="article-gallery-4-1168872685">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1168872685" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-846175723">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the main features of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles 3
  </em>
  's combat system is the number of active party members players can have during gameplay, with up to 7 characters joining to face enemies. This makes combo sequences and other combat elements visually impressive for players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Thus, the Nintendo Switch exclusive uses these mechanics to create intense battles, maintaining the trilogy's essence, which heavily focuses on JRPGs with fast combat, and also brings improvements over its predecessors. The story of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles 3
  </em>
  is also well-crafted, delivering a satisfying result in all aspects.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tales-of-vesperia">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Tales Of Vesperia
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="being-a-fast-paced-jrpg-is-the-series-39-trademark">
  Being A Fast-Paced JRPG Is The Series' Trademark
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1556182117" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1556182117" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1556182117" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1556182117" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1556182117-img" id="article-gallery-5-1556182117">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1556182117" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-299878425">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Real-time and fluid combat is the franchise's hallmark, and in
  <em>
   Tales of Vesperia
  </em>
  players enjoy continuous gameplay with the battle environment, allowing quick switching between characters to exploit enemy weaknesses. Each team member has exclusive abilities that complement each other, promoting diversified strategies.
 </p>
 <p>
  The system evolves as the game progresses, introducing new techniques and combinations that enhance battles and make them more enjoyable. Additionally, character customization allows adapting combat to preferred playstyles, whether focused on powerful attacks, support, or crowd control. This flexibility makes the fights engaging and challenging, keeping players always involved.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-39-s-dogma-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon's Dogma 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-great-references-in-fast-paced-jrpgs">
  One Of The Great References In Fast-Paced JRPGs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-756738613" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-756738613" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-756738613" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-756738613" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-756738613-img" id="article-gallery-6-756738613">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-756738613" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1447615819">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Few games offer combat as fun and frenetic as
  <em>
   Dragon’s Dogma 2
  </em>
  , since it blends elements of action-oriented JRPGs
  <strong>
  </strong>
  with the ability to scale enemies, identifying various weak points across their bodies. This results in quick and dynamic battles, where excellent reflexes are necessary to challenge numerous formidable monsters.
 </p>
 <p>
  Furthermore, the gameplay of
  <em>
   Dragon’s Dogma 2
  </em>
  is highly varied, as each class chosen by players provides a different approach to combat. This allows extensive experimentation with different combos during battles, especially as vocations evolve and each one's fighting style changes accordingly.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-7-rebirth">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-remake-made-changes-to-the-game-39-s-turn-based-combat">
  The Remake Made Changes To The Game's Turn-Based Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1297544756" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1297544756" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1297544756" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1297544756" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1297544756-img" id="article-gallery-7-1297544756">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1297544756" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1543647802">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the late 90s, the game was one of the great references among Turn-based JRPGs, but for the remake of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  , Square Enix was bold, tweaking the formula of one of the best games ever produced by the developer and making it more action-oriented JRPGs. In the end, it was the right choice, as combat is one of the game's best aspects.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here, the fights are quite fast-paced for a JRPG, especially considering how they were in the original game, with players moving characters across the battlefield and performing attacks. Additionally, the animations of both protagonists and allies are well done, making the experience even more satisfying.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ys-8-lacrimosa-of-dana">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Ys 8: Lacrimosa Of Dana
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="frenetic-combat-that-encourages-precision">
  Frenetic Combat That Encourages Precision
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-822900260" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-822900260" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-822900260" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-822900260" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-822900260-img" id="article-gallery-8-822900260">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-822900260" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1785046184">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Combat in
  <em>
   Ys 8: Lacrimosa of Dana
  </em>
  is fast and dynamic, testing reflexes in fluid battles against visible enemies on the map. The system allows instant character switching, each specialized in different damage types, and the game promotes an intense rhythm as abilities consume SP, quickly replenished through basic attacks.
 </p>
 <p>
  Meanwhile, the Flash Guard and Flash Dodge mechanics reward precise dodges and blocks, offering temporary invulnerability, critical damage, and slow-motion effects. This fast-paced combat style delivers an engaging experience, featuring unique bosses and various difficulty levels, perfect for fans of action-oriented JRPGs.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kingdom-hearts-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Kingdom Hearts 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="game-offers-one-of-the-best-combats-in-the-series">
  Game Offers One Of The Best Combats In The Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-27650541" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-27650541" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-27650541" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-27650541" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-27650541-img" id="article-gallery-9-27650541">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-27650541" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-149858957">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although the blend of franchises that compose the
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  universe is exotic, it is undeniable that the game offers some excellent mechanics, especially the second installment, which features some of the best combats ever created in the entire series. The developers successfully evolved the dynamics of its predecessor, delivering an excellent title among fast-paced JRPGs that performed exceptionally well throughout the entire adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here, Sora's skill set is well-crafted, with combos that keep all of the character's physical combat satisfying and fluid. Additionally, utilizing the character's Drive Forms is also enjoyable, as they allow the protagonist to transform into something even more powerful, aiding in tougher battles, especially in the Final Mix version.
 </p>
 <h2 id="nier-automata">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Nier Automata
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="action-jrpg-with-one-of-the-best-combats-ever-created">
  Action JRPG With One Of The Best Combats Ever Created
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1982319660" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1982319660" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1982319660" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1982319660" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1982319660-img" id="article-gallery-10-1982319660">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1982319660" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1390051156">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Developed by PlatinumGames,
  <em>
   Nier: Automata
  </em>
  offers some of the most fluid and engaging combats among fast-paced JRPGs. Although it may seem simple initially, the battle system conceals a depth that rewards players who explore its possibilities. Weapon combinations, pod abilities, and customizable chips allow for dynamic and stylish combos, maintaining fast and visually impactful action.
 </p>
 <p>
  Furthermore, combat emphasizes reflexes and precision, with dodges timed correctly and attacks chaining moves in sequence, highlighting the identity of action-oriented JRPGs. While the narrative and soundtrack are standout features, the combat system of
  <em>
   Nier: Automata
  </em>
  excels by offering freedom for players seeking to customize their strategies without compromising the gameplay's frenetic pace.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring: Best Endings, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elden-ring-best-endings/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Blessing Of Despair Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Age Of The Duskborn Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Age Of Fractured Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Age Of Order Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Lord Of The Frenzied Flame Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Age Of The Stars Ending
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In true RPG tradition,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring
   </em>
  </strong>
  also has several endings. Attaining them is often a litmus test for patience or curiosity, two virtues that
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  wants from its players. Those who oblige such demands will be rewarded with something more colorful or something entirely different, but all of them have one thing in common: players will have no idea what the endings mean.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  At least, that's the case for most people who didn't read the guides or lore explanations. However, after about a dozen playthroughs, one begins to understand the nuances between these endings. By then, it's easier to evaluate which endings are the best – here's how they all rank up.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated December 27, 2024 by Erik Petrovich
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   : There are a total of six Elden Ring endings, and though none were added with the Shadow of the Erdtree DLC (unfortunately), reaching the end of SOTE complicates your ultimate choice after beating the Elden Beast. You may feel more sympathetic to Miquella's goals, and may feel that the Age of the Duskborn most aligns with your own beliefs on how the world should progress past the Age of Fracture. Either way, it's a hard choice to make, and the best Elden Ring ending still has downsides that are worth considering if such things matter to you. Ultimately, the best endings in Elden Ring are those that provide mostly benevolent effects on the world or give a unique ending cutscene – this guide to the best Elden Ring endings has been updated to display the pros and cons for every option available, to help players quickly figure out the effects of each ending without having to worry too much about the nitty-gritty details.
  </em>
 </p>
 <h3 id="does-the-elden-ring-dlc-add-a-new-ending">
  Does The Elden Ring DLC Add A New Ending?
 </h3>
 <p>
  Throughout the Realm of Shadow in
  <em>
   Shadow of the Erdtree
  </em>
  , players follow in the footsteps of Miquella, who seeks to establish an Age of Compassion as a God. The name Age of Compassion harkens back to the endings in the base game of
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , like the Age of Order, the Age of the Duskborn, etc. So, until players began to beat the DLC and figure it out for themselves, it was thought that the Age of Compassion could be a new unlockable ending in the DLC.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unfortunately, this is not the case. Without spoiling too much about the final encounter of the
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  DLC, you will unlock a special piece of content, but it is not a new ending. All of the endings in the base game change something about the world as you, the Tarnished, ascend to some kind of higher power – whether that be the Elden Lord themself or Consort to another. You always get a Mending Rune to use, or a unique interaction, after beating the Elden Beast.
 </p>
 <p>
  After beating the
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  DLC, you will not get any new interaction or Mending Rune to fix the Elden Ring in Miquella's image. Credits will roll for the DLC, you will see a short cutscene, but then you will be transported back to the final encounter room with the Remembrance of the final boss in your inventory.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="blessing-of-despair-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Blessing Of Despair Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-lands-between-is-overtaken-with-a-reviled-curse">
  The Lands Between Is Overtaken With A Reviled Curse
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="blessing of despair ending in elden ring (1)" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/blessing-of-despair-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Become best buds with the Dung Eater
       </li>
       <li>
        Mohg and Morgott won't feel so alone
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Everything in The Lands Between become defiled by the Omen Curse
       </li>
       <li>
        You side with the psychotic Dung Eater
       </li>
       <li>
        The world becomes almost comically more evil
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Blessing of Despair is essentially the true "bad" ending to
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . That's because the summarized result of picking such an ending is that everyone in the Lands Between gets a free and mandatory curse, courtesy of the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659562" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-enemy-icon-3-802.png"/>
   Dung Eater
  </span>
  and his benefactor, presumably the Formless Mother or some other yet-nameless entity.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Formless Mother, whom
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659489" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-enemy-icon-3-662.png"/>
   Mohg, Lord of Blood
  </span>
  also serves, is an Outer God who seeks to wrestle control of the Lands Between from the Greater Will's grasp. She is thought by many to be responsible for the curse of the Omens, a mutation of sorts that grows horns on the afflicted individual's body; it's worth noting that both Mohg and
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659491" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-enemy-icon-3-666.png"/>
   Morgott, the Omen King
  </span>
  share this curse.
 </p>
 <p>
  Granted, the true nature of the Blessing of Despair's curse is unspecified. This curse only implies that souls will no longer be able to return to the Erdtree, rendering all the denizens of the Lands Between afflicted with the loathsome curse — one that might turn them into Omens, or do something far more wicked and horrid as would befit the Dung Eater.
 </p>
 <p>
  Either way, it's a psychotic way to end
  <em>
   Elden Ring,
  </em>
  and it's not really rewarding since it's a re-skinned version of the default ending.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players won't even be fully aware of the implications and repercussions of what they did because it plays out the same cinematic as the default ending. In reality, they'll become an Elden Lord of cursed and suffering individuals.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-blessing-of-despair-ending">
  How to Get Blessing of Despair Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  To unlock the Blessing of Despair questline, you must complete the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659562" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-enemy-icon-3-802.png"/>
   Dung Eater
  </span>
  's lengthy collection-based questline. Over the course of this quest, you will provide the Dung Eater with 5x
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="660567" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/seedbed-curse-4.png"/>
   Seedbed Curse
  </span>
  to finally create the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="660524" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/mending-rune-of-the-fell-curse-4.png"/>
   Mending Rune of the Fell Curse
  </span>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  As is standard for most endings, you must not have inherited the Frenzied Flame, or must have removed its influence by the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  To activate the Blessing of Despair ending, beat the final boss, then interact with the Fractured Marika statue. Select the option to use the Mending Rune of the Fell Curse.
 </p>
 <h2 id="age-of-the-duskborn-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Age Of The Duskborn Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-despairing-fog-engulfs-the-lands-between-ridding-the-world-of-immortality">
  A Despairing Fog Engulfs The Lands Between, Ridding The World Of Immortality
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="age of the duskborn ending in elden ring (1)" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/age-of-the-duskborn-ending-in-elden-ring-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age of the Duskborn Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age of the Duskborn Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Those Who Live In Death are given a place in the world
       </li>
       <li>
        Rid the world of the concept of Immortality
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        No more coming back - once you're dead, that's it
       </li>
       <li>
        Do you really want Tibia Mariners to be redeemed?
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Age of the Duskborn, for all its intents, is the most "neutral" ending in
  <em>
   Elden Ring.
  </em>
  Its proponents all strive to remove the Greater Will's gift and curse of immortality which was also its primary method of maintaining control over its constituents. If no one is immortal, then the hollow souls that have been maddened from constant rebirths will be saved from their suffering.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659852" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-150.png"/>
   Fia
  </span>
  merely wants those who have fallen in the Lands Between to finally succumb to the peace of death instead of being manipulated and recycled by the Greater Will. It's a noble goal that gives more agency to the people of the Lands Between and depending on one's perspective on immortality and freedom, how one perceives it ethically might be ambiguous.
 </p>
 <p>
  As for the visual treat, there's none. Players merely get a different lighting effect compared to the sunnier default ending, which is why it might be disappointing for those expecting something more expository. Still, the idea behind it is radical and appealing to some, providing a natural balance between life and death and ridding the world of immortality for people and creatures, perhaps peace can engulf the land through the fog.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-the-age-of-the-duskborn-ending">
  How to Get the Age of the Duskborn Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  To unlock the Age of the Duskborn ending, you must complete the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659852" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-150.png"/>
   Fia
  </span>
  questline to acquire the Mending Rune of the Death-Prince. This quest begins in Roundtable Hold, progresses alongside
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659845" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-140.png"/>
   D, Hunter of the Dead
  </span>
  's questline, and finishes high above the depths of the Deeproot Depths.
 </p>
 <p>
  As is standard for most endings, you must not have inherited the Frenzied Flame, or must have removed its influence by the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  To activate the Age of the Duskborn ending, beat the final boss, then interact with the Fractured Marika statue. Select the option to use the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="660523" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/mending-rune-of-the-death-prince-4.png"/>
   Mending Rune of the Death-Prince
  </span>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="age-of-fractured-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Age Of Fractured Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-tarnished-becomes-elden-lord-and-repeats-a-new-age">
  The Tarnished Becomes Elden Lord And Repeats A New Age
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-fracture-ending.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age Of Fractured Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age Of Fractured Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        The most neutral ending, with no real benefits or drawbacks
       </li>
       <li>
        You get to be the Elden Lord and continue the current Age
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Default ending in which nothing gets solved, just delayed
       </li>
       <li>
        The world is still deteriorating and fracturing
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The default
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  ending, the Age of Fractured will see the Tarnished fulfill the promise that started them on this path. The player will mend the Elden Ring itself and begin a new age for the Lands Between, with a new Lord. Yet, in this new age, nothing really changes, and it's seemingly a repeating cycle until someone else comes along to cause a new bout of chaos and frenzy.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Tarnished sits on the throne, and despite this ending being the default, there are still layers to it worth exploring. Even the default ending in
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  is not so simple, and often despite the promise to fix things and link the world back together, fates can have a funny way of helping.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Age of Fracture is not a solid solution, and simply throwing duct tape over the issue. There is nothing to stop the Elden Ring from shattering, nor is there anything stopping another from confronting the Tarnished and the remains of the Golden Order.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-the-age-of-fracture-ending">
  How to Get the Age of Fracture Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  This is the default ending in
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , and all you have to do to unlock the Age of Fracture ending is beat the final boss. As is standard for most endings, you must not have inherited the Frenzied Flame, or must have removed its influence by the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  After beating the game, simply select the option to Mend The Elden Ring to unlock this ending. This is one of three endings required to 100% the game, the others being the Age of the Stars and the Frenzied Flame endings.
 </p>
 <h2 id="age-of-order-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Age Of Order Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-new-age-without-conflict-or-the-fickleness-of-gods">
  A New Age Without Conflict Or The Fickleness Of Gods
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="elden-ring-age-of-order-ending" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/elden-ring-age-of-order-ending.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age Of Order Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Age Of Order Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        No more meddling of Gods and Demigods (like Marika) creates stability
       </li>
       <li>
        Brings back the flourishing Age of the Erdtree in all but name
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        The Golden Order is still in charge, and still spurns those not seen as deserving of Grace
       </li>
       <li>
        Brother Corhyn and Goldmask die before acquiring the Mending Rune
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Age of Order ending is what players get if they follow through with the rather obscure and strict
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659843" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-138.png"/>
   Brother Corhyn
  </span>
  questline. It's a decent ending, especially if one considers the Erdtree and the Greater Will's ideals to be...ideal. But that one's a rather bigoted and superficial philosophy — one that yearns to hide what it perceives as ugly in the world.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nevertheless, this ending has an appealing twist since even Goldmask saw through the hypocrisy and inefficiency of the Erdtree. In this ending, players will usher in a new age of stability as an Elden Lord under the guidance of
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659833" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-158.png"/>
   Goldmask
  </span>
  's
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="660521" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/mending-rune-of-perfect-order-4.png"/>
   Mending Rune of Perfect Order
  </span>
  . It is what many players can perceive as the overall "good" ending, as in the goody-good ending where everyone lives happily.
 </p>
 <p>
  The only in-game issue with the Age of Order is that it uses the default ending scene for the Age of Fracture. Something so satisfying should have been treated as more special rather than just a re-skin of the default congratulatory ending. Plus, though things might be better for most, some thrived under the old ways and your own powers might be diminished in an age without the meddling of Gods.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-the-age-of-order-ending">
  How to Get the Age of Order Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  To unlock the Age of Order ending, you must complete both the Brother Corhyn questline and the Goldmask questlines. At the very end of the Goldmask questline, you will receive the
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="660521" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/mending-rune-of-perfect-order-4.png"/>
   Mending Rune of Perfect Order
  </span>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  As is standard for most endings, you must not have inherited the Frenzied Flame, or must have removed its influence by the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  To activate the Age of Order ending, beat the final boss, then interact with the Fractured Marika statue. Select the option to use the Mending Rune of Perfect Order.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="lord-of-the-frenzied-flame-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Lord Of The Frenzied Flame Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="become-the-lord-of-chaos-and-burn-the-world-creating-a-devoted-enemy-with-melina">
  Become The Lord Of Chaos And Burn The World, Creating A Devoted Enemy With Melina
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="elden ring frenzied flame ending" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/elden-ring-frenzied-flame-ending.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Burn away everything that distinguishes and divides the people of the Lands Between
       </li>
       <li>
        Gain revenge for those who were treated unjustly by the Age of Marika, like the Merchants of the Grand Caravan
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Burns away everything, and everyone, with endless maddening flames that blanket the world
       </li>
       <li>
        Is revenge worth destroying the world and erasing everything good from it, too?
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  All these endings and their exhausting agendas might be too much for players who expect to have more of a say in the Lands Between. There are times when all that frustration must go somewhere, and
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  gives no better release than mass arson for such a state of vexation. Just burn everyone away in the maddening blaze of the Frenzied Flame.
 </p>
 <p>
  That's what being the Lord of the Frenzied Flame entails. Instead of becoming an Elden Lord, the players take up the mantle of Lord of Chaos. The pompous Erdtree is burned to a stump, and Melina departs after seeing the Tarnished commit a sin so grave.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's no predictable or reasonable outcome for the Lands Between and its people in this kind of ending. Everything just falls into chaos, madness, and irrationality. The players are thus free to return ten-fold the insanity that the Lands Between has inflicted upon them, especially those bosses.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arguably, it's also the meatiest ending in the game, with its own extended cutscene that features
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659882" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-188.png"/>
   Melina
  </span>
  vowing to take revenge against the players for defying her and burning everything.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_66">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     If players meet with the Three Fingers, they will be locked out of the other Elden Ring endings. However, they can reverse this by using Miquella's Needle at the Dragonlord Placidusax's arena for a permanent reversal.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-the-frenzied-flame-ending">
  How to Get the Frenzied Flame Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  To unlock the Frenzied Flame ending, you must do a few things: complete the Hyetta questline, find the Three Fingers and inherit the Frenzied Flame deep beneath Leyndell, and burn the Erdtree with the Frenzied Flame instead of Melina.
 </p>
 <p>
  After you beat the final boss, interact with the Fractured Marika statue and select the option to Become the Lord of Frenzied Flame.
 </p>
 <p>
  You do not need a Mending Rune to unlock this ending, you just have to inherit the Frenzied Flame and maintain it until the end. This is one of three endings required to 100% the game, the others being the Age of the Stars and the Age of Fracture endings.
 </p>
 <h2 id="age-of-the-stars-ending">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Age Of The Stars Ending
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-thousand-years-of-ranni-39-s-order-takes-to-the-stars-leaving-the-lands-between-without-a-lord">
  A Thousand Years Of Ranni's Order Takes To The Stars, Leaving The Lands Between Without A Lord
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ranni full quest walkthrough in elden ring" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ranni-full-quest-walkthrough-in-elden-ring.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Pros
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Blessing of Despair Cons
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Become Ranni's consort and go on a little thousand-year vacation as a different kind of Elden Lord
       </li>
       <li>
        A complete overhaul of the power dynamics of the Lands Between as you usher in an age of Sorcery
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Ranni's intents may not necessarily be more benevolent than Marika's, just different, and could have other effects
       </li>
       <li>
        You're giving Ranni a lot of power, and she is no stranger to deception and betrayal (see Godwyn)
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </thead>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
 </ul>
 <p>
  As for an ending that still gives players a substantial reward and reprieve yet doesn't compel them to go mad, the Age of the Stars ending is the most thoughtful one yet. Instead of playing along with the Greater Will's game, the players will replace Marika with
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="659860" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-npc-icon-226.png"/>
   Ranni the Witch
  </span>
  who herself rises to become a God of a different nature than the Greater Will would like.
 </p>
 <p>
  The more important bit here is that Ranni will pick the players as her consort, her own royal spouse, and Elden Lord.
 </p>
 <p>
  Yet the players won't be shackled to another ending of bittersweet servitude to some deity. Instead, they'll go on a thousand-year journey with Ranni to the unknown and the great beyond, leaving the wretched Lands Between in its own boiling stew of discord.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, there's a special cinematic that's vastly different compared to the default ending. It's mysterious and cryptic still, but it's a lot less ominous and more hopeful than some other endings.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-the-age-of-stars-ending">
  How to Get the Age of Stars Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  To unlock the Age of Stars ending, you must complete the Ranni the Witch questline. This begins in the Three Sisters just northwest of
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="661095" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <span>
    <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/elden-ring-missing-icon-3-180.png"/>
    Caria Manor
   </span>
  </span>
  in northern Liurnia, after speaking with Ranni in person for the first time.
 </p>
 <p>
  As is standard for most endings, you must not have inherited the Frenzied Flame, or must have removed its influence by the end of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  To activate the Age of Stars ending, after you beat the final boss, search the area for Ranni's summon sign. Summon her to become her Consort and activate the Age of the Stars ending. This is one of three endings required to 100% the game, the others being the Age of Fracture and the Frenzied Flame endings.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
