<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Makes Major Change to Camo Challenges With Season 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-season-2-camo-challenge-change-explained/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 developer announces major adjustment to camo challenges in Multiplayer.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players will now only need to unlock 5 Military Camos to then unlock and equip Special Camos.
     </li>
     <li>
      Previously, players needed to complete 9 Military Camos, which equates to 100 headshots per weapon.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  will allow players to unlock and equip any Special Camos to a weapon after unlocking just five Military Camos for that weapon, which means only 30 headshots will be required per weapon instead of the usual 100. The change will take effect following the launch of
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  Season 2, which will be released later today, January 28.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  's player count continuing to decline on Steam, there's a lot riding on the game's Season 2 update. The first season of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  has been one of the longest in the franchise's history, so fans are eager to jump into some brand-new content and check out all of the new features. Publisher Activision also confirmed earlier this month that it would be addressing many of the community's biggest gripes with Season 2, including updates to Ranked Play that allow console users to disable crossplay. The decision comes after months of outrage from players due to the ongoing hacking issues plaguing both
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  on PC.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="black-ops-6-makes-major-camo-challenge-changes-with-season-2">
  Black Ops 6 Makes Major Camo Challenge Changes With Season 2
 </h2>
 <p>
  In the official patch notes for
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  Season 2, developer Treyarch Studios confirmed a big change to the game's camo challenges. The studio said that it had seen "significant feedback" from players surrounding the underutilization of the 250+ unique Special Camos in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6.
  </em>
  As such, Treyarch has decided to allow players to unlock and equip Special Camos earlier. From Season 2, players will only need to unlock 5 Military Camos (which equates to 30 headshots for most weapons) to then unlock and equip the Special Camos for that weapon. Previously, all 9 Military Camos would need to be unlocked, requiring a total of 100 headshots.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1531043225" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1531043225" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1531043225" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1531043225" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1531043225-img" id="article-gallery-1-1531043225">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1531043225" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2004987359">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The camo grind in
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  has been a big motivator for many players following the latest
  <em>
   Call of
  </em>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
    Duty
   </em>
  </span>
  release in 2024. To unlock Dark Matter, which is the highest camo available in Multiplayer, players are required to unlock all 9 Military Camos (which equates to 100 headshots for the majority of weapons), followed by 2 Special Camos, and then 4 Mastery Camos. While the Special and Mastery Camos vary in terms of what challenges players need to complete, the Military Camos have been referred to by players as "tedious" due to the huge number of headshots required.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is just one of the many adjustments coming to
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  in Season 2. For players still working their way to Dark Matter, tracking those headshots is about to become a whole lot easier as the new season will finally see the introduction of a camo challenge tracker. This was a feature previously available in 2023's
  <em>
   Modern Warfare 3
  </em>
  and has been highly-requested by players ever since the launch of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  in October 2024. The feature will work similarly to
  <em>
   Modern Warfare 3
  </em>
  's, allowing players to track a total of 10 camo challenges at once with real-time updates in-game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Leaks Important Details About New Region for Update 5.5</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-new-region-update-55-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Version 5.5 of Genshin Impact is rumored to introduce new region, including the Great Voldan of Tollan.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players are excited for areturn to Natlan in the storyline and the potential addition of new tribe Collective of Plenty.
     </li>
     <li>
      The upcoming update may feature new characters Veresa and Ifa.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  leak has revealed a couple of interesting details about a new region that is expected to arrive in the coming months.
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  introduced a major new region back in Version 5.0, which launched at the end of August 2024. Since then, HoYoverse has been adding new characters to the roster and occasionally expanding Natlan's playable terrain.
 </p>
 <p>
  While many fans claim that Natlan is one of the best regions introduced to the game, others complain that HoYoverse has been slower in unlocking its subregions compared to its approach with previous primary nations. Fortunately, players may finally get a new expansion in one of the upcoming
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  updates.
 </p>
 <p>
  A credible
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  leaker named LeakFlow has provided further corroboration of previous rumors suggesting that Version 5.5 will finally introduce a new map expansion. The new part of the map is expected to feature one of the most anticipated areas of Natlan, the Great Voldan of Tollan. This famous location was once inhabited by ancient dragons whose palace was located far below the magma. Unfortunately, their civilization crumbled and the volcano was taken over by the Abyss, one of the main antagonist factions in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . One of the reasons players are excited about this volcano is that its eruptions can be heard periodically every few minutes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-story-will-return-to-natlan-in-version-5-5">
  Genshin Impact Story Will Return to Natlan in Version 5.5
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1758514789" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1758514789" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1758514789" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1758514789" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1758514789-img" id="article-gallery-1-1758514789">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1758514789" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1105001815">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The next update is also rumored to feature a new tribe named the Collective of Plenty, the only one of Natlan's six mentioned tribes that has yet to appear in the game. Overall, fans seem eager to return to Natlan as part of the main storyline. The second part of the ongoing Version 5.3 update has players participating in the annual Lantern Rite Festival, always hosted in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's Geo nation, better known as Liyue.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Special Program for the upcoming
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  Version 5.4 will take Travelers back to the Electro nation, Inazuma. This doesn't come as a big surprise, as HoYoverse tends to pause the development of its Archon Quest storyline around this time of year. Regarding new roster additions, multiple leaks suggest that Version 5.5 will feature two new characters: Veresa and Ifa.
 </p>
 <p>
  Veresa has been mentioned in the main storyline and is known as a competitive eater from the Collective of Plenty tribe. Ifa is a renowned Saurian veterinarian from the Flower-Feather clan, and he's known to be friends with
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's Ororon. However, these leaks should still be taken with a grain of salt, as update 5.5 is expected to arrive at the end of March, giving HoYoverse plenty of time to make further changes.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Fighter 6 - Official Character Guide: Mai Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/street-fighter-6-official-character-guide-mai-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  This official character guide gives players a comprehensive look at Mai, who joins Street Fighter 6 on February 5th, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA Sports FC 25: Tips For Defending</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ea-sports-fc-25-tips-how-defend-better/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Defend Better In EA Sports FC 25
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Reduce Your Use Of The Tackle Button
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Slide Tackle As A Last Resort
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Apply Gegenpressing
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Guard All The Passing Lanes
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Use L2/LT To Stop Passes
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Use Players In The Meta
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Defending is one of the most difficult things to master in
  <em>
   <strong>
    EA Sports FC 25
   </strong>
  </em>
  . In challenging modes like Ulitmate Team Champions, patience and consistency are vital to defending successfully. A solid defense can win you games and separate the professionals from the masses.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Even though attacking is important, being unable to stop attacks will result in you losing matches, no matter how much you score. The better players will play with your weak backline and move around without resistance. This can make playing against decent
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  players quite frustrating.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-defend-better-in-ea-sports-fc-25">
  How To Defend Better In EA Sports FC 25
 </h2>
 <p>
  Defending is not an easy skill to master in
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  , especially with players who have low defensive stats. In cases like that, it can be tough to win the ball without using some unique techniques. If you can utilize these tips, then you can effectively maintain your backline, even with strikers in your central defense. Here are a few tricks that you can practice to slowly but surely
  <strong>
   improve your defensive capabilities in
   <em>
    EA Sports FC 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  :
 </p>
 <h3 id="reduce-your-use-of-the-tackle-button">
  Reduce Your Use Of The Tackle Button
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='"EA Sports"' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ea-sports-fc-25-best-center-backs.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
    <figcaption class="body-img-caption">
     EA Sports
    </figcaption>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A useful tip that most players don’t know is that
  <strong>
   using the jockey button makes it easier to win back the ball compared to tackling
  </strong>
  . Even when there is some distance between you and the attacker., your defender will move and position themselves more effectively, allowing you to win the ball more easily.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     On PlayStation, the jockey button is L2, and on Xbox, it’s LB.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Despite its simplicity, jockeying requires some practice. If you constantly press the button, you won’t win the ball. Instead, try to focus on timing, and if done correctly, you’ll beat the attacker easily. Because of how easy this is, you’ll find yourself not depending on tackling all the time. This also reduces the chances of players committing a foul and giving away a free kick from a risky spot.
 </p>
 <h3 id="slide-tackle-as-a-last-resort">
  Slide Tackle As A Last Resort
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="All Playstyles in EA Sports FC 25 - Slide Tackle" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc3-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Just like how
  <em>
   EA Sports FC 25
  </em>
  players should minimize the use of the tackling button, they should also do the same with slide tackles. Even though it can work out in certain situations, it's too risky, as there is the chance of causing a foul and getting a card. Besides, not winning the ball from a slide tackle means that your defender will fall very far behind the attacking player and will have no chance of catching up in time.
 </p>
 <p>
  The only time you can even consider a slide tackle is during a fast counterattack when the opposition does not have full control of the ball. Even then, however, it is advised to be cautious because of the risk of a suspension.
 </p>
 <h3 id="apply-gegenpressing">
  Apply Gegenpressing
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="All Playstyles in EA Sports FC 25 - Vini. Jr." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/fc-1-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gegenpressing is a tactic popularized by Jurgen Klopp in the Premier League. This team, Liverpool, has found massive success thanks to it, and you can translate this into the game as well. The basic concept of this technique is to apply pressure on the man with the ball while he is high up on the pitch. This denies any chance of counter-attacking and allows your team to create a goal-scoring opportunity out of nothing. In the game, this is known as second-man pressing.
 </p>
 <p>
  By pressing
  <strong>
   the R1 button on PlayStation
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   the RT button while on Xbox
  </strong>
  , you’ll see a green arrow appear on one of your teammates, and they will pressure the player with the ball with you. This forces the opponent to make mistakes, allowing you to win the ball more effectively. Even though you shouldn’t use it all the time, as it makes your players fatigue faster, in the right spot, this technique can save your team from a tricky spot.
 </p>
 <h3 id="guard-all-the-passing-lanes">
  Guard All The Passing Lanes
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="rush cross ea sports fc 25" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rush-cross-fc-25.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In real football, one of the factors that can determine a squad's merit is their ability to push through the center of the field. It is easier to glide down the wings, but it becomes hard to score, as you’re too far away from the post. So, the best teams in the world develop their movement and pass in such a way that they can run through the middle without breaking a sweat.
 </p>
 <p>
  This also translates into
  <em>
   EAFC
  </em>
  ; while attacking, the best players will try to utilize all the pathways given to them to reach the posts. So, it is crucial to cover these lanes and block their path. Effectively using the space between every defender and covering the angles from which the runner can pass to his teammates will tear apart a counterattack. This also denies the chances of the attackers getting a through ball between the defensive line.
 </p>
 <p>
  This may take some time to visualize and apply, but once you do, it will be extremely effective in helping you control the field.
 </p>
 <h3 id="use-l2-lt-to-stop-passes">
  Use L2/LT To Stop Passes
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="finesse shot rush ea sports fc 25" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/finesse-shot-rush-fc-25.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This technique allows you to be more in control during duels and deny your target the chance of passing to a teammate. It’s quite a simple thing, but it makes such a difference in breaking the momentum of a counterattack. You can make use of it by holding the left trigger while dueling an attacker.
 </p>
 <p>
  Doing so will reduce the range by which your defender is around the attacker, minimizing the distance between you and the ball and making your turns quicker. You also sprint while doing this. So, holding down L2/LT and R2/RT together will not only let you move faster but also give you more time to focus on the ball without slowing down.
 </p>
 <h3 id="use-players-in-the-meta">
  Use Players In The Meta
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="FC 25 - Theo Hernandez stats" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg" decoding="async" height="960" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/fc-25-theo-hernandez-stats.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unfortunately, you can apply all the tactics in the world and still lose out to a quick attack. No matter how effective your skills are, you simply won’t be bulletproof without strong players in your defense. Thankfully, the game adds new special cards every week, allowing you to pick your own crops, but you need to keep some things in mind before choosing your defenses.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pace is one of the most important factors in
   <em>
    EA FC 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  . The intensity of the game can be hard to match, and players without at least 80 pace might struggle to keep up with counter-attacks and all the throws. You also need to filter out the cards where the players are composed, have good physicality, and are defensively aware. These are all vital aspects for a defender to possess in this game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some of the best defenders in the game right now are
  <strong>
   Micky van de Ven
  </strong>
  from Tottenham,
  <strong>
   Theo Hernandez
  </strong>
  from AC Milan, and
  <strong>
   Kounde
  </strong>
  from Barcelona. If you can’t get these players, you can hold them as the standard and collect cards with stats similar to them. A good example of internal stats is Micky van de Ven, who only has a base rating of 82. However, his defensive capabilities are through the roof, mainly because of his high physical stats and defense awareness. Numbers like this are the ones that matter more than base ratings, so when searching for defenders, make sure you keep these criteria in mind.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canceled Warhammer RPG Details Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/canceled-warhammer-rpg-details-revealed/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The canceled Warhammer game was based on Age of Sigmar, with significant time and money already invested.
     </li>
     <li>
      Rumors and layoffs hinted at a canceled Warhammer RPG, disappointing fans despite the series' recent success.
     </li>
     <li>
      The success of Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 has fueled anticipation for an upcoming series, leaving fans eager for more.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Details about the upcoming
  <strong>
   <em>
    Warhammer
   </em>
  </strong>
  game, which was recently canceled due to funding issues, have been revealed. The now-canceled project was rumored to have been several years into development before the door was slammed shut.
  <em>
   Warhammer
  </em>
  has long been one of the most iconic tabletop wargames in video game history, boasting an impressive legacy of hit titles spanning multiple decades.
 </p>
 <p>
  The legendary series had just wrapped up a stellar 2024, with the smash hit
  <em>
   Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2
  </em>
  becoming one of the biggest games of the year. The game's immense popularity will help to drive anticipation for the upcoming series set in the
  <em>
   40K
  </em>
  universe that stars Henry Cavill of
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  fame. Despite the recent widespread success of the franchise, it wasn’t enough to save the planned project.
 </p>
 <p>
  As reported by Eurogamer, the canceled project was based on
  <em>
   Warhammer: Age of Sigmar
  </em>
  . A spokesperson from game developer Thought Pennies cites a strategic shift as the reason for its abandonment. Planning and development began in 2021, suggesting that a significant amount of time and money had already been invested in the project.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-canceled-warhammer-game-was-based-on-age-of-sigmar">
  The Canceled Warhammer Game Was Based on Age of Sigmar
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-606080044" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-606080044" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-606080044" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-606080044" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-606080044-img" id="article-gallery-1-606080044">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-606080044" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-697654053">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rumors about a canceled
  <em>
   Warhammer
  </em>
  RPG have been circulating recently. The reports coincided with news that Thought Pennies had been laying off developers who were working on an undisclosed
  <em>
   Warhammer
  </em>
  game. Considering the recent momentum the series has picked up, it's somewhat surprising that the game won’t be hitting the shelves.
 </p>
 <p>
  The release of
  <em>
   Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2
  </em>
  was initially delayed, but that did little to dampen the excitement and anticipation surrounding it. The subsequent overwhelming success of the game has breathed new life into the already beloved series, with the timing lining up perfectly for a long-awaited screen adaption. For many fans, the transition to film and television is long overdue, and a series that captures the essence of the games will only fuel further excitement for more titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  With plenty of
  <em>
   Warhammer
  </em>
  factions still yet to appear in the games, developers have a wealth of source material to draw on for future releases. Combined with the stunning success of
  <em>
   Space Marine 2
  </em>
  and an upcoming series on the horizon, fans of the franchise have a lot to look forward to. However, these are the same reasons that a new
  <em>
   Warhammer
  </em>
  game with years of development under its belt would likely have been welcomed with open arms. For now, fans will just have to wait and see what comes next.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
