<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>How Aspyr Is Making 2025's Jedi Power Battles The Definitive Version</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/aspyr-2025-jedi-power-battles-definitive-remaster/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  25 years ago,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Star Wars: Episode I: Jedi Power Battles
   </em>
  </strong>
  hit the PS1, a nostalgic gauntlet of action-platforming that contains a treasure trove of relics from an older era—such as the appearance of Mace Windu's original blue lightsaber. In 2025, Aspyr is bringing
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  back with a bang, rolling out a remaster with everything a fan could want.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In October 2024, a remaster of
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  was announced. Helmed by Aspyr, the studio behind a vast catalog of
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  video game remasters, the remaster will be released on January 23rd. With how much the original game differed between its multiple ports and the issues present throughout all versions of the classic title, Aspyr has done much to tidy things up and unify the game's disparate platform-specific content. To learn more about Aspyr's up to, Game Rant sat down with director of product Chris Bashaar.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-aspyr-is-bringing-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-to-modern-systems">
  How Aspyr Is Bringing Star Wars: Jedi Power Battles To Modern Systems
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-618782272" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-618782272" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-618782272" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-618782272" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-618782272-img" id="article-gallery-1-618782272">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-618782272" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-755784089">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="polishing-up-a-classic">
  Polishing Up A Classic
 </h3>
 <p>
  Aspyr's next
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  remaster is focused on fine-tuning to smooth over the disparities in ports, the original's bugs, and some accessibility pitfalls. Bashaar explained how Aspyr has been approaching the remaster, emphasizing polish while preserving the past:
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "Our goal with
   <em>
    Star Wars
   </em>
   : Episode I: Jedi Power Battles was to preserve the challenging, action-packed experience fans remember while improving accessibility and quality-of-life features. Unlike some of our other projects, we focused on improving the controls and gameplay while staying true to the original Dreamcast version. A core rule at Aspyr is “additions not revisions,” so players will find modern and classic controls in our version. It’s really exciting to get to play both versions and build two fully different strategies on how you can play."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Bashaar also detailed the changes arriving with the classic
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  game remaster, pointing to specific quality-of-life features like toggling lightsaber colors, adjusting UI options, and switching between modern and classic controls. The remaster won't give players full rein over their experience with a plethora of menu options, but streamlining the UI and controls is probably the most critical element when revisiting older action games.
 </p>
 <h3 id="balancing-the-dreamcast-and-ps1-ports">
  Balancing The Dreamcast And PS1 Ports
 </h3>
 <p>
  The upcoming remaster of
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  is based on the original Dreamcast version, which introduced a number of improvements from the PS1 iteration. However, fans nostalgic for
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  on the PS1 aren't without hope, as Bashaar brought up how the ports will be balanced in this definitive edition.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "This release is based on the Dreamcast version, as it represents the most refined iteration of the original. However, we also incorporated select features that fans loved about the PS1 release, like preserving elements of its iconic UI."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  It's important to note the distinction between a remaster and a remake, with the former aimed at polishing and refining an already-finished product. The latter would be more like the
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  remake, a ground-up redevelopment of the entire game. Preservation is the primary goal of Aspyr's take on
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  , even with its new bells and whistles. Given Bashaar's mention of changing UI settings to suit preferences, players may be able to toggle certain aspects of the Dreamcast and PS1 UI. Changing lightsaber colors is also a welcome addition, allowing for franchise accuracy and preservation of the past—a brief, little-known period in
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  history where Windu's iconic purple lightsaber was not yet established.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aspyr received criticism earlier in 2024 for some mishaps with the launch of
  <em>
   Battlefront Classic Collection
  </em>
  . However, given the studio's success with
  <em>
   Star Wars: Bounty Hunter
  </em>
  , Aspyr has all the cards to make
  <em>
   Jedi Power Battles
  </em>
  a slam dunk.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 5 Could Turn Over a New Leaf with a Brotherhood of Steel Protagonist</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-5-brotherhood-of-steel-protagonist-maximus-similiar-good-why-how/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fallout 5 could feature a Brotherhood of Steel protagonist like Maximus from the Amazon TV series.
     </li>
     <li>
      The next installment might need to shift gears from the usual Vault Dweller protagonist to offer a unique and compelling narrative.
     </li>
     <li>
      Bethesda has the opportunity to explore different perspectives by allowing players to either directly embody a Brotherhood member or including it as a possible character background.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Another mainline
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout
   </em>
  </strong>
  game has long been all but guaranteed. While developer Bethesda hasn't offered much in the way of its plans for the next installment of the hugely popular post-apocalyptic franchise, the discussion and speculation around the fifth
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  entry has been ongoing ever since the most recent title,
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  , dropped back in 2015. Following that nearly 10-year gap, last year's Amazon TV series put the series back into the spotlight while also introducing its world to a whole new slew of fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  The show featured Maximus (Aaron Moten) as one of the main characters, initially a member of the Brotherhood of Steel, one of the most iconic aspects of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  . Though it's possible the next game will break from tradition, for now it seems reasonable to assume that the organization will appear in the course of the narrative, even if it isn't a more central focus, like in
  <em>
   Fallout 3.
  </em>
  As fans still await further word about
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , and it likely being years down the line, this might give Bethesda the time and chance to potentially shift gears, specifically regarding its standard Vault Dweller protagonists. For
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , the studio could instead look to include one that, similar to Maximus, is more immediately and firmly connected to the Brotherhood.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Two somewhat lesser-known spin-offs,
     <em>
      Fallout: Brotherhood of Steel
     </em>
     (2004) and
     <em>
      Fallout Tactics: BoS
     </em>
     (2001), saw players step into the shoes of a faction member. However, these were released prior to Bethesda taking over the IP.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fallout-5-could-walk-a-new-road-by-having-a-brotherhood-of-steel-protagonist">
  Fallout 5 Could Walk a New Road By Having a Brotherhood of Steel Protagonist
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1388176521" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1388176521" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1388176521" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1388176521" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1388176521-img" id="article-gallery-1-1388176521">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1388176521" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-217755266">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="fallout-5-already-has-some-excellent-ways-to-feature-a-brotherhood-of-steel-main-character">
  Fallout 5 Already Has Some Excellent Ways to Feature a Brotherhood of Steel Main Character
 </h3>
 <p>
  Present throughout all the major games
  <em>
   ,
  </em>
  the Brotherhood of Steel is literally and figuratively a
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  institution. Bethesda's first outing after acquiring the property rights,
  <em>
   Fallout 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  put an interesting spin on the established Brotherhood of Steel lore, history, and its role in the canon.
  <em>
   FO3
  </em>
  depicted a Brotherhood marked by the Schism, a splintering between the traditionalist Brotherhood Outcasts who were at odds with the local Capital Wasteland contingent headed by Elder Lyons. This angle is just one way
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  can set up a possible Brotherhood protagonist. The TV series contained another intriguing one, though, that might be an even better fit for the next entry.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     One rumor suggests
     <em>
      Fallout 5
     </em>
     will be set around San Francisco, which could provide room for another interpretation or new Brotherhood subsect.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="how-fallout-5-could-have-a-brotherhood-of-steel-protagonist-like-maximus">
  How Fallout 5 Could Have a Brotherhood of Steel Protagonist Like Maximus
 </h3>
 <p>
  Maximus' story in the show is compelling, and his characterization and portrayal were widely hailed. After being saved as a child by the Brotherhood following a devastating attack on his hometown of Shady Sands, Maximus idolized the group and was set on joining them and working his way up the ranks. But as he does so and gains their trust, he slowly discovers that the Brotherhood of Steel isn't always quite what it seems or espouses to be. During his time serving, Maximus becomes increasingly disillusioned both with other members and the Brotherhood's behavior and methods. After encountering a more traditional
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  protagonist, Vault 33's Lucy MacLean, he eventually departs to seek his own path in the Wasteland.
 </p>
 <p>
  In this vein, rather than another Vault Dweller,
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  could thrust fans into a starting role as a Brotherhood Initiate similar to Maxmius. A few possible setups could see this being the case, such as the player character being born and raised under Brotherhood doctrine and training, with them going through their final rites before being assigned a major mission. The plot could entail the main character subsequently questioning its ways and goals, ultimately deciding to leave, and having to face the consequences while surviving on their own.
 </p>
 <p>
  Another avenue would be for
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  to offer a variety of character backgrounds, with one option being a former Brotherhood soldier who left for personal or mysterious reasons, but still retains many of the skills and knowledge of the organization. This creates a way to build upon some of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's major RPG elements, and would feel right at home in the next game. While it presently remains unknown exactly how it will be incorporated next,
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  has the chance to show the Brotherhood of Steel from different perspectives, and letting fans play directly as a member would open up some great narrative and role-playing opportunities.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Within Interview: A Compelling Live-Action VR Experience [EXCLUSIVE]</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/interview-human-within-vr/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Signal Space Lab's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Human Within
   </em>
  </strong>
  is undoubtedly one of 2025's more unique VR releases thanks to a well-crafted blend of engaging storytelling devices. Blurring the lines between virtual reality games and interactive fiction,
  <em>
   Human Within
  </em>
  shifts from choose-your-own-adventure live-action cinematics to more hands-on virtual reality puzzle sequences.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Human Within
  </em>
  's story touches on philosophical and ethical questions regarding humanity's relationship with technology. In
  <em>
   Human Within
  </em>
  , a new invention harnesses the power of the human brain, allowing users to upload their consciousness into the digital realm. Like all technological advancements, there are risks and rewards, and
  <em>
   Human Within
  </em>
  explores these viscerally. Players take on the role of protagonist Linh's uploaded consciousness, and this digitized existence lays the groundwork for some thought-provoking perspectives in VR.
 </p>
 <p>
  Game Rant sat down with
  <em>
   Human Within
  </em>
  creative director Avi Winkler and director Anne Weigel to discuss the title's inception, the importance of meaningful choices for players, and the clever techniques that make it possible.
  <strong>
   This interview has been edited for brevity and clarity.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-research-and-technology-behind-human-within">
  The Research and Technology Behind Human Within
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-1.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Can you talk about Human Within's early days? How did the idea take shape initially and what inspired you?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Our goal was to tell a unique story about technology using technology. We also wanted to create an experience that incorporated the user as an active participant in the story. VR is a technology that immerses players in ways that otherwise aren't possible in traditional gaming.
 </p>
 <p>
  We took a great deal of inspiration from movies like Lawnmower Man and Transcendence with their emphasis on technology and the focus on technology, and we wanted to explore the concept of ethical concerns behind technological advancements, especially at a time when new technology is being developed at an exponential rate from year to year. It seemed very relevant in today's day and age as a topic to cover.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  From the filmmaking perspective, it was important to adequately understand what the fictional technology in Human Within is capable of, and what it might look like. We dove deep into current research on brain-computer interfaces, which helped us shape the story's world from the filmmaking perspective.
 </p>
 <p>
  We wanted the technology to feel plausible, but it's a movie, right? We still leave room for imagination. The idea that the character Linh and her consciousness exist in digital limbo became a perfect way to explore the consequences of pushing innovation too far.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-11" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-11.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Did your findings in that research influence Human Within’s narrative outlook? Did it make you more optimistic or pessimistic?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  I'm not sure if it did, because I'm also working in research in a similar area, so I'm an optimist. Sometimes it's surprising to see what is already possible. I think what helped to go into the research–especially with my crew and the different departments–is that we’ve gotten a much better understanding of how this could look, how we could explain it to the actors, and how they can interact with it.
 </p>
 <p>
  You don't have any of this in the dialog and the live-action, but it's important for everyone involved to understand how we envision the technology so that we all align on the vision and our department works the way the directors envision it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Human Within blends a few different formats like 360-degree live action, Point Cloud digital spaces, and puzzle sequences. Can you talk about what it was like building a VR game around such distinct perspectives? What challenges were involved?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  I come from a video game background, so I was able to craft the design around choice mechanics and gameplay mechanics. I also come from a narrative background, so crafting the story came naturally to me, but I've never been involved in live-action filming before, so partnering up with Anne was fantastic. She brought in her live-action experience and opened my eyes to how that development goes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Crafting a story with a long-form narrative that keeps the user engaged was important. Many VR experiences are very short; live-action experiences in VR are typically anywhere from five to 20 minutes max. They aren’t long-form narratives.
 </p>
 <p>
  We wanted to tap into that market and bring that quality production to users by switching from full live-action 360-degree scenes to internet space scenes incorporating live-action.
 </p>
 <p>
  There’s live-action throughout the 360 scenes, while the internet space scene has panels with live-action footage from multiple camera angles allowing you to see the world from the digital space. Then the point cloud sequences are different types of visual presentations that help to keep the experience fresh.
 </p>
 <p>
  We were also careful not to have these scene types be too short. Switching back and forth from one to the other too quickly could be very disorienting for users, so we needed to make the scenes long enough so that you could get settled into the experience before transitioning to another scene type.
 </p>
 <p>
  That brought on another challenge in that these scenes were long. Our internet spaces have displays with multiple screens and camera angles in front of you. These scenes often had to be filmed in a single take, and some of them are five to six minutes long with no cuts so it's very challenging.
 </p>
 <p>
  Thankfully, we had a group of actors who were incredible. They became so immersed in the story and knowing and performing the content in a way that is more akin to stage plays rather than film.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-10" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-10.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Did filming those scenes in 360 degrees present unique challenges?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  It was a great challenge for the actors, the crew, and everyone involved. The script was massive because you have all the different decisions players can make. I think one of the key challenges was to ensure we have the right approach for the acting so that no matter what decision players make, the acting is on point. You don't have one story, you have a complex web of stories. That was a big challenge for me as a director and for the actors because we really had to rethink how we approached it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shooting in 360 comes with its own challenges because you really have to envision the scene in every direction. The camera captures every little detail, and there's literally no place to hide, making it very different from traditional filmmaking.
 </p>
 <p>
  I really enjoyed this challenge because it forced me to completely rethink how to approach storytelling, from how the scenes are staged to every little detail supporting the player's choices.
 </p>
 <p>
  I'll admit I was a bit scared of the challenge. I’m thankful for Avi's expertise and the production company I worked with. I’ve never asked so many questions before. I enjoyed it because shooting in 360 opens up so many possibilities that aren’t available in traditional filmmaking.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  I think about it like a stage play. In many ways, VR is like watching a play, but rather than being an audience member sitting in a seat in the theater hall, you're on the stage in the middle of the act and there is no hall. There's another wall, or maybe some more actors behind you. You're in the room with the actors in the scene, rather than observing it from a seat.
 </p>
 <p>
  Other than there being no cuts, there's a similarity between watching a play from an audience seat and viewing something on a movie screen, because everything's over there, right? Whereas with VR, everything's around you. It's a whole other world of storytelling.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-4.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Typically in filmmaking, you’re working with a linear story. How did you tackle Human Within’s branching narrative?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  I come from a background working on non-linear, branching narratives. I worked on Deus Ex Mankind Divided with dialog choice wheels and gameplay that can affect the story and the endings. For the branching aspect in Human Within, there's a great deal of carryover from traditional games such as telegraph interfaces that let the user know a choice needs to be made.
 </p>
 <p>
  In games with virtual characters made of polygons and animation, you can seamlessly have the character continue from their animation into choice A or B. With live-action, you can't seamlessly continue without having a shift or a pop in the actor's position as you cut from one action to the next.
 </p>
 <p>
  In traditional games or even some live-action 2D content where choices are made, you can solve that by cutting to another camera, but in VR, typically changes in camera angle are not something that's often done.
 </p>
 <p>
  We developed a system that allowed us to cut to another camera position in the room without disorienting the user. This helped us with the branching quite a bit.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-8" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-8.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: What was your approach to Human Within's more interactive moments like the point cloud and puzzle scenarios? Can you talk about what players can do during these sequences and what went into making them feel meaningful?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  You are an active participant in the story. You embody the digital consciousness of one of the characters in the story, and the entire story is told from her perspective–or rather the perspective of her digital consciousness within the digital space.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the 360 scenes, you make choices about what happened in the past, and in the internet space scenes, there are forms of interaction where the scene won't progress until you solve a puzzle or interact with certain panels to get things going.
 </p>
 <p>
  The point cloud sequences are where the most interaction is in the experience. They were designed for players to engage in the story and the environment in a way that the 360 memory scenes and the internet space scenes couldn't.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, knowing that a large portion of our audience was going to be more casual gamers than hardcore gamers, we were very careful to have just enough interactivity to enhance the immersion aspect of the experience, but not in a way that would be too overwhelming.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-2.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: What sorts of technical innovations were involved in developing Human Within? Did you employ certain techniques or technologies that were especially unique?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Since it's live-action content and long-form, that was a big challenge. So Human Within uses a proprietary software called Vrex. It was initially developed by Signal Space Lab, and during the creation of the Afterlife project, but it's been improved upon during the development of Human Within.
 </p>
 <p>
  Vrex uses a user-friendly interface similar to timeline-bound editors like Final Cut or Premiere, but the technology allows for seamless branching interactivity that immediately reacts to the user's choices across various stimuli like eye direction, screen interaction, or even sound.
 </p>
 <p>
  It also enables the development of experiences that include live-action footage like Human Within. Without Vrex, fitting a long-form narrative onto a device with limited data capacity would be impossible.
 </p>
 <p>
  Vrex allows us to solve this problem in a way that offers greater content quality while also saving space. It considerably reduces the video size needed to render the content while maximizing the resolution of the media to provide a perceived higher resolution.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Do you think Vrex will play a role in future projects?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Absolutely. I think it very much could. There's definitely room for more projects that are long-form narrative, and this, technology that we've developed would certainly allow for long-form content and high data content to be standalone on a device, rather than being tethered to your computer. This is very important since being tied to an umbilical cord to your computer is not always the best experience.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-6" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-6.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Where do you distinguish between interactive fiction and games? Do you feel that projects like Human Within are starting to blur that line?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Yes, absolutely. Interactive fiction immerses users in a story in a way that traditional gaming can only do to a certain extent. Human Within puts you directly in the story with VR, where you aren't simply a passive observer of the story like in traditional audiences as a fly on the wall. You're in the story with the characters, and VR is the only way to do that.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  I also think that Human Within is blurring that line. However, when we were working on the project, whether the project fit into some specific category–like interactive fiction or video games–was never relevant. For us, it was always about telling this story with the opportunities that fit the story and the project. If it comes from the gaming world, great. We just focused on the story and what we could get out of it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-human-within-makes-player-choices-meaningful">
  How Human Within Makes Player Choices Meaningful
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: It's important for players to feel that their choices matter. How does Human Within achieve that goal in its approach to interactive storytelling?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  I agree, choice definitely matters. I'm not a fan of choice gameplay mechanics with little to no impact on the story's outcome. Choices for the sake of choice but with no real meaning–is it really a choice? Not really, at least not in a significant way.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Human Within is a long-form interactive experience in the VR sense, it's not a 15-to-20-hour experience. It's about an hour to an hour and a half per playthrough. The time can vary depending on how long it takes you to solve puzzles, which scenes you watch, and what ending you get.
 </p>
 <p>
  Because of the duration of Human Within, we have to be very selective regarding the choice opportunities in the story and the fact that it's live-action. That all impacts the shooting schedule and production process. Filming a branching narrative in live action is a huge endeavor, so we are very selective about the opportunities. As a result, your choices significantly influence which ending you ultimately get.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  Players' decisions don't only affect the outcome of the story, they also define the past. I found that quite interesting. Depending on the choice you make, the flashbacks you get differ significantly. You alter the backstory you experience, and I think from a story perspective, this really impacts the information you have as a player when you make your decisions.
 </p>
 <p>
  I think it also influences how you perceive the characters around you. Even the choices out of the backstory influence the choices you make for the future of the characters and the technology, so that was a super interesting part of the story,
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-9" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-9.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Human Within features 5 endings. What was your approach to writing for multiple end states? Do you anticipate one might be regarded as the "true ending"?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Every player wants to feel like their ending is the end [laughs]. It was important for each of our five endings to feel different. Originally, we had planned for eight endings, but when it came to writing them, we quickly realized that the differences between them were starting to bleed into each other and were losing their impact.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shooting eight endings in live-action with limited production schedules and budgets would be even more challenging. We had to make some cuts somewhere, but reducing the endings was a reduction for the better. Each ending is distinct, and no ending is perceived as the true ending. The ending you experience is 100% based on the choices you make in the story.
 </p>
 <p>
  For you, the ending is the end, but playing the story again and making different choices allows you to not only see the different endings play out but also allows you to gain some additional insight into certain character motivations. Is this character really as bad as he's being made out to be or is something else going on?
 </p>
 <p>
  You may or may not find that out depending on your choices.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: How will players weigh each of their decisions in Human Within? For example, are choices somewhat divided between good and evil?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Not good versus evil, it's not quite like that. Everyone in the world is unique and makes choices in their life based on a variety of circumstances. The choices in Human Within are based on selfish versus compassionate options.
 </p>
 <p>
  While these choices impact the events that follow their underlying themes, they also reflect the choices that are made behind the advancements of technology. “Is technology always created for the betterment of humanity, or are there sometimes ulterior motives behind their development?”
 </p>
 <p>
  That's one of the themes.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-3.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Human Within touches on some important ethical and technological questions. What do you hope players will be thinking about as they experience it? Do you have an overall message?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  From a filmmaker's perspective, what excited me the most about Human Within was the chance to explore these questions. Avi mentioned that when you're playing, you're not just watching someone else deal with these dilemmas; you are making the choices as Linh and experiencing the consequences firsthand.
 </p>
 <p>
  I think Human Within doesn't give you answers, though. Instead, it creates a space for players to explore someone else's perspective and reflect on how their actions shape the story and affect the characters around them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Technology can be both amazing and scary. Many advancements have certainly helped speed things up–like allowing illnesses to be detected earlier than before. At the same time, we still have yet to discover the impact smartphones have on us.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even autonomous self-driving cars sound exciting, but they carry some risks. They're so new and very few cities have them, but we have yet to see what kind of impact it will have on society, city infrastructures, and the flow of human foot traffic.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's good and bad in everything, and the fictional technology in Human Within straddles that line between being unbelievably dangerous and profoundly helpful. Ultimately, it comes down to how the technology is used.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of my favorite quotes regarding the advancements of technology is from the original Jurassic Park, when Ian Malcolm says, “Your scientists were so preoccupied with whether or not they could, they didn't stop to think if they should.” The movie’s over 30 years old now, and that quote is still as relevant today as it was back then for the fictional technology in Jurassic Park.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="screenshot-5" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/screenshot-5.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Do you have any last thoughts you’d like to share?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Earlier we discussed making an experience about using technology, and it's quite fitting that the development and filming of this project were at the tail end of the pandemic. All our communication between team members and the film production was done through video calls.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite the fact that we were physically separated in the making of this experience, it's amazing how well it came together. The narrative, production quality, directing, and acting are fantastic and it was all done through the amazing use of technology.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  Since this project was so different from what I've done previously, we had to work quite closely together. I thought it was quite fun, too. I tried something new, and looking back on it, it was totally worth it. I hope they’ll excuse my 100,000 questions, but we discussed this for hours and hours and we never actually saw each other.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  Throughout my career, I've always worked on projects that introduce a new game development challenge. I started working on kids games and I went on to some platformers and then stealth mechanics with Thief. From there, I dealt with branching mechanics in Deus Ex: Mankind Divided, and then multiplayer co-op gameplay in Gears of War 5, and then onto VR.
 </p>
 <p>
  Every project I worked on has always introduced something new. I learned a lot from Anne, and hopefully she learned a lot from me. It’s been a very interesting production, and it's been a long time that we've been working on this–longer for me than Anne because I was involved with the conceptual design, script writing, and prototyping.
 </p>
 <p>
  The mixture of 360 live-action, the internet space, and point cloud sequences was a new concept, as well as the long-form narrative in VR. it was so new that we had to make a fully playable prototype using 3D animatic storyboards.
 </p>
 <p>
  I'm excited for people to experience it and ask themselves the ethical questions behind technology. I'm also excited to see what kind of choices people end up making based on the options they have. I'm super excited after seeing the game grow since its conception; it's very special to be at this stage where we're able to talk about the game and have interviews and promote it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Weigel:
  </strong>
  As a director coming into a new project, it was amazing because we had the right partners. The people at Signal Space Lab have so much experience. Then on the German production side, Actrio has much experience shooting VR. Even my art department head has shot big VR projects, and he's the only one I know in Europe that I’d say could bring that experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  We had to build all the lights into the VR set design because there's no space to hide traditional lighting rigs and they're important in pre-production. This project came alive thanks to our partners and I'm really thankful for them.
 </p>
 <p>
  I’m also thankful for the actors and that we could convince them to try what we’re doing here. There used to be traditional scripts, and when we sent that big one, we really had to explain what we were doing. Avi did the prototype and that helped them understand what we were planning. It sounded totally abstract to some of them–like they couldn't do anything with it.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Winkler:
  </strong>
  It's a very unique project in the way that it's presented and the way it's filmed. It was a big challenge to find a director like Anne and a partnership with a film production studio like Actrio to get involved. At first, a lot of studios were like, “Oh, this is too ambitious. It can't be done.” There are naysayers, but if you find the right partner that embraces the vision, you end up making something really special.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   [END]
  </strong>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims 4: Realm Of Magic - Ultimate Familiar Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-sims-4-realm-of-magic-ultimate-familiar-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Familiars introduced in The Sims 4: Realm of Magic offer unique advantages for Spellcasters.
     </li>
     <li>
      Prices vary for familiars, from common like Fairy and Raven to rare like Skull and Phoenix.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can also bind regular cats and dogs as familiars, adding a personal touch to the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sims 4: Realm Of Magic
   </em>
  </strong>
  , familiars are finally here. Fans of the supernatural genre in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  , in particular, will be guaranteed to enjoy this game pack, which features not just these magical pets with special buffs and advantages, but also a whole host of new spells and potions to learn.
 </p>
 <p>
  A new life state, Spellcaster, was also introduced into the game, as well as a brand-new dimension that can be accessed from Glimmerbrook's special portal. While Spellcasters should focus most of their energy on learning new incantations, familiars are a great bonus to speed up the process. Here's all that players need to know about Realm of Magic's familiars, including their prices and detailed descriptions.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on January 11, 2024 by Stephanie Harris:
   </strong>
   Since the release of Realm of Magic, a few more animal companions have been added to the game in the form of the Horse Ranch pack. Nonetheless, familiars remain a fun addition to the game, and the only supernatural animal companions so far. Realm of Magic may not have been all fans had hoped it would be, but it certainly remains a unique pack when compared with the many much more realistic ones on offer.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  To make the life of Spellcasters easier, each familiar's price is now highlighted and the advantages of owning one are explained before jumping into the description of each familiar. Familiars come in three different price tiers, and have different appearances, despite all doing exactly the same thing.
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-do-familiars-do-in-realm-of-magic">
  What Do Familiars Do In Realm Of Magic?
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Realm of Magic Owl Familiar" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Realm-of-Magic-Owl-Familiar.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Familiars are magical creatures players can purchase at Juan's Wonderful One-Stop Wand Warehouse located in Caster Alley. Make sure to check the shop regularly, as the inventory changes constantly. If players are lucky, there is also the chance of randomly finding their summoning orbs by searching for magical tomes in the bookshelves in Magic Realm HQ or by dueling someone for one. Regular cats and dogs can also be bound as familiars. Players can bind as many familiars as they want, but only one can be summoned at a time.
 </p>
 <p>
  A familiar's presence will give a Spellcaster Sim an extra confident moodlet. Familiars are also able to protect the Sim from death. Each familiar comes with a unique personality, and they'll occasionally comment encouragingly on the Sim's progress as a magic-user. The best part about them, however, is that they will boost a Sim's experience gain whenever they perform activities that give them Spellcaster experience. Some familiars are more or less common than others.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fairy">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Fairy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-common-familiar">
  A Common Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Fairy" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Fairy.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   100 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Any fans of
  <em>
   The
  </em>
  <em>
   Legend of Zelda
  </em>
  will recognize this creature's appearance right away. The fairy is summoned using a blue summoning orb and appears as a small hovering glowing ball with deep blue butterfly wings.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Fairy is described as a non-physical being and only appears as a glowing concentration of energy suspended within its wings. It is said that when near a fairy, an almost electric, light spark can be felt.
 </p>
 <h2 id="raven">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Raven
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-common-familiar">
  A Common Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Raven" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Raven.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   100 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A classic familiar for any traditional witch or wizard out there, the Raven is a great option for players practicing magic. Its appearance is a deep shade of purple and black in color, with brightly glowing yellow eyes. In terms of looks, it's one of the more Halloween and spooky-themed familiars out there, perfect for any evil Spellcasters.
 </p>
 <p>
  While some might consider the Raven a bringer of bad news or misfortune, it's considered a particularly loyal familiar to any Spellcaster it's bound to and will take a deep liking to them.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sixam-owl">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Sixam Owl
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-common-familiar">
  A Common Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Sixam Owl" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Sixam-Owl.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   100 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  For those unsure what a Sixam is, it's the alien planet that becomes available for a Sim in the
  <em>
   Get To Work
  </em>
  expansion pack once they reach the maximum level in their scientist career. It's also Maxis spelled backward!
 </p>
 <p>
  It's safe to assume this creature hails from that far-away planet; therefore, it is no wonder that the Sixam Owl is said to have a deep connection with the moon. Blue and glowing with star-like details, it's the ideal choice for any Pufferheads, and could well be a reference to the beloved Harry Potter franchise.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bunnerfly">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Bunnerfly
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-common-familiar">
  A Common Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Bunnerfly" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Bunnerfly.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   250 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Those who have wondered what a bunny with butterfly wings would look like, look no further. Despite its adorable name and somewhat adorable appearance, the Bunnerfly has an oddly demonic feel to it. The familiar has red-glowing eyes and crimson butterfly wings that keep its black, fuzzy self suspended in the air.
 </p>
 <p>
  Its description states that the Bunnerfly's true nature is actually unknown, with the familiar being considered a bit of an anomaly in both magic and biology. It's also the only Common familiar with a price well above the 100 simoleon mark.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-uncommon-familiar">
  An Uncommon Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Dragon" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Dragon.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   250 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The selection of familiars really wouldn't be complete without a Dragon. Classic, and known as a fearsome creature capable of incredible devastation, it is the go-to familiar for anyone who values power over anything else. Nobody messes with the Dragon and his allies, his loyalty to his Spellcaster is completely unmatched.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Dragon appears like a baby of its kind, purple in color with yellow-glowing eyes and two horns on top of its head. Since it's an Uncommon familiar, players will need to pay more for it, but given its retro-style appearance that reminds players of Spyro the Dragon, it's a pretty fair price.
 </p>
 <h2 id="glowfrog">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Glowfrog
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-uncommon-familiar">
  An Uncommon Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Glowfrog" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Glowfrog.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   250 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Don't be fooled by the Glowfrog's silly appearance, as, apparently, staring into those blank eyes can spell trouble for an unsuspecting Sim. By nature, Glowfrog's are mischievous beings and won't hesitate to play games when given a chance to.
 </p>
 <p>
  As players might suspect, Glowfrogs appear as green hovering frogs with small wings and a tail with a brightly glowing yellow orb at its end. Frogs are another traditional choice for many Spellcasters, being commonly related to witches and Halloween for that matter.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="snub-nosed-leaf-bat">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Snub-Nosed Leaf Bat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-uncommon-familiar">
  An Uncommon Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Snub-Nosed Leaf Bat" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Snub-Nosed-Leaf-Bat.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   250 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When thinking about the words "unexpectedly cute," a hybrid between a baby pig, a bat, and a plant isn't the first thing that comes to mind; at least, until players actually see a Snub-Nosed Leaf Bat.
 </p>
 <p>
  Insanely adorable, this variation of the classic bat - which is a form that vampires take in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  - has a pink nose, stubby green legs, a fluffy white body, and brightly glowing green leaf-like wings. It's definitely one of the more unique familiars, with nothing quite like it in any other game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hex-doll">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Hex Doll
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-uncommon-familiar">
  An Uncommon Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Hex Doll" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Hex-Doll.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   250 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Who could forget about the art of voodoo when it comes to magic? For any believers in this ancient craft, the Hex Doll just might be the perfect pick. He's described as quite the silent familiar, but that doesn't take away from his supernatural charm.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Hex Doll looks like a brown voodoo doll, with a glowing heart on its chest and various patches on its body, as well as pins sticking from its head. While he looks perpetually angry, the Hex Doll is a steadfast follower.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="phoenix">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Phoenix
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rare-familiar">
  A Rare Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Phoenix" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Phoenix.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   500 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The symbol of rebirth and power, the Phoenix is among the rarest and most highly-coveted familiars in the
  <em>
   Realm of Magic
  </em>
  . Who isn't fascinated by this mystical, regal creature? His appearance is similar to the Raven, but his body glows like hot embers, with black spots on its head and wings and a glowing backside.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="related-single">
   RELATED: The Sims 4: The Best (And Worst) Romances
  </span>
 </p>
 <p>
  There are also two small horns protruding from its head and a pair of yellow glowing eyes that keep a watch on his favorite Spellcaster. Given how majestic it looks, it's no wonder it's considered a Rare familiar with a hefty price tag of 500 simoleons.
 </p>
 <h2 id="skull">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Skull
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rare-familiar">
  A Rare Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Skull" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Skull.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   500 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Skulls are obviously associated with death, and sometimes even darkness and evil. Only the most fearsome Spellcasters will welcome the presence of this creepy symbol, either to make it clear they're not to be messed with, or to make their enemies shake with fear in a duel.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Skull is ancient and faded on the surface, with cracks and scars carved into its bone. However, it emanates a strange greenish glow that seems to keep it suspended in the air. Despite its cartoon-like appearance, it's a great pick for any evil Spellcasters who prefer to stick to the spooky, Halloween theme of the pack.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="velid">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Velid
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rare-familiar">
  A Rare Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Velid" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Velid.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Price:
   </strong>
   777 simoleons
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Fans of Voidcritters will be excited to find out that one creature, in particular, makes an appearance in the
  <em>
   Realm of Magic
  </em>
  , proving his existence. Velid is said to have an extensive knowledge of space, which makes sense considering he's a visitor from a faraway land.
 </p>
 <p>
  He is always hovering on a small cloud of smoke and has a goat-like skull for a head, brown horns and large red eyes, with a blue body. Velid is the most expensive of all familiars, sold at the shop for 777 simoleons. That price is not an accident, either, and most likely has some type of hidden symbolism baked into it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cats-and-dogs">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Cats And Dogs
  </span>
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sims 4 Cat Familiar" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Sims-4-Cat-Familiar.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If none of the prior mystical beings tickle the player's fancy, rest assured that any Sim's previously lazy house cat or brand-new puppy can also become a familiar. All the player needs to do is click on them, select "Magic" and then "Bind As Familiar."
 </p>
 <p>
  Once a pet is summoned as a familiar, they'll be differentiated by a cute sparkle that surrounds them. They can go on adventures on their own to fetch magical items for the Sim. It's the perfect opportunity for players to get their very own black cat named Salem.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Gen 1 Pokemon Line Deserves Its Happy Ending in Gen 10</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-cubone-marowak-gen-10-regional-form-fake-happy-backstory/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  approaching the three-year mark without a main series iteration, fans are left wondering what the 10th generation of games might have in store for them. One thing that Game Freak has become fond of in recent games is giving more attention to fan-favorite creatures from previous games. With that in mind,
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  ’s Generation 10 presents the perfect opportunity to finally give a Generation 1 Pokemon a lighter outlook.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  ’s first generation is a favorite among many fans, and Game Freak has taken notice. Recent games have begun introducing new evolutions, regional forms, and now convergent forms of past creatures, most commonly from the series' earliest entries. These new forms give Game Freak a chance to expand on the lore behind some Pokemon or give them a power boost that they’ve been lacking. It doesn’t seem like this practice will be ending any time soon, so when considering which monsters deserve more love, one first-generation Pokemon immediately springs to mind. Cubone has always had a tragic story, and a new form could give it a new lease on life. Some adore Cubone because of its tragedy, and others have crafted theories about Cubone’s parentage, but in all of this attention, it remains the result of tragedy. Generation 10 would be the perfect time to finally reverse fate in Cubone’s favor.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-a-new-form-could-lift-cubone-rsquo-s-spirit">
  How a New Form Could Lift Cubone’s Spirit
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-311608489" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-311608489" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-311608489" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-311608489" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-311608489-img" id="article-gallery-1-311608489">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-311608489" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-691081791">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Beginning as early as gen 2, Game Freak decided that certain Pokemon deserved a glow-up. The likes of Golbat, Seadra, and Tangela have all been given new evolutions that help them stand out and make them more powerful at the same time. This is likely the thought process behind regional forms and evolutions as well. Even Cubone’s evolution, Marowak, received a fire-type Alolan form in Generation 7. A new evolution, regional form, or convergent form would be the ideal way to add more positive lore to the Cubone line, giving it the catharsis that it so desperately desires.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-new-cubone-evolution">
  A New Cubone Evolution
 </h3>
 <p>
  One route Game Freak might take in order to help Cubone out of its rut is to give it a new evolution. Some fans have already imagined what an evolution of Marowak might look like. It’s even believed that the Cubone line was intended to be a three-stage evolution line from the very beginning, leading to the theory that Kangaskhan may be the mother whose skull Cubone is wearing. A third evolution in the line could see Marowak discard its mother’s skull as a sign of inner growth and acceptance, turning Cubone’s story into one of recovering from loss rather than being destroyed by it.
 </p>
 <h3 id="cubone-rsquo-s-convergent-mirror-image">
  Cubone’s Convergent Mirror Image
 </h3>
 <p>
  After the introduction of convergent evolutions in Generation 9, some fans believe that the next generation may feature more, and Cubone could be a prime candidate. Many Pokemon could benefit from a convergent evolution line, but Cubone presents an opportunity for an ironic twist on the idea. The idea behind convergent Pokemon is that, just like in real life, sometimes creatures look similar, but don’t actually have any familial relationship. There’s no better way to show that idea than introducing a Pokemon who looks like Cubone, but has a backstory that’s as wholesome as Cubone’s is sad. In some ways, it would feel like adding insult to injury for Cubone, but creating a Pokemon to act as a mirror image could lead to some interesting interactions between the two.
 </p>
 <h3 id="something-entirely-new">
  Something Entirely New
 </h3>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  series has been in an era of experimentation lately, beginning with the introduction of battle gimmicks like mega evolution in gen 6. Each generation after has had some new form of battle-related boost, often linked to certain Pokemon, as well as to the game’s story.
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  Gen 10 is likely to receive its own gimmick, so perhaps Cubone could receive a new power or form due to the events in the next generation’s story. With so many possibilities, it would be a shame if the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  games continued to let Cubone suffer its unfortunate fate, so hopefully a new era will dawn for it in Gen 10.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
