<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Concept Combines Varesa With Honkai's Firefly</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-concept-varesa-honkai-star-rail-firefly/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fans merge Genshin Impact's Varesa with Honkai's Firefly in a popular concept post.
     </li>
     <li>
      Firefly was a powerful character in Honkai: Star Rail, ultimately leading to calls for nerfs.
     </li>
     <li>
      Varesa's kit in Genshin Impact leaks suggest a focus on Plunging Attacks and synergy with Natlan characters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A talented artist has created a character concept that combines
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  's Varesa with Firefly from
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  . Both
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  are known for their dedication to character design, so it is not surprising that fans often create their own concepts inspired by existing playable units.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's safe to say that
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  remains HoYoverse's most popular title, even though it was released back in 2020. However, since
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's launch, this turn-based RPG has surpassed
  <em>
   Genshin
  </em>
  in monthly revenue on multiple occasions.
 </p>
 <p>
  A Reddit user named vlilacc has shared an impressive concept in which they merged
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's upcoming five-star character, Varesa, with the fan-favorite Firefly from
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  . The Redditor took Varesa's model and equipped her with Firefly's recognizable outfit. The new costume features Firefly's signature brown tones with shades of blue and green. The post showcases three different concepts, each similar to the other, with the main differences being the inclusion of horns and variations in hair length. The post gained significant attention, gathering over 2.7k upvotes, with many fans claiming they would not mind if HoYoverse released this version of Varesa in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  Version 5.5.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-fan-made-concept-combines-varesa-with-honkai-39-s-firefly">
  Genshin Impact Fan-made Concept Combines Varesa With Honkai's Firefly
 </h2>
 <p>
  Since her release, Firefly has been one of the most popular characters in
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  . This is not surprising, considering she was a must-have character in the Break and Super Break meta. Many players have even suggested that HoYoverse should have nerfed Firefly, as her stacked kit made her seem unfair compared to other characters. Another similarity between Firefly and Varesa is that both are DPS characters, at least according to recent
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  leaks.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1714541152" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1714541152" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1714541152" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1714541152" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1714541152-img" id="article-gallery-1-1714541152">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1714541152" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1340275373">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  According to previous beta footage, Varesa will be a new five-star character whose kit revolves around Plunging Attacks, which are not too common among
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  characters. Similar to many recently released characters, Varesa will benefit from having
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's Natlan characters in her party, as her Passive Talents gain bonus effects when a Nightsoul Elemental Burst is activated. While Varesa's strong synergy with other Natlan characters makes sense lore-wise, many players dislike this recently introduced trend, as it limits the character's flexibility.
 </p>
 <p>
  Regarding Varesa's release date, the fact that she is the only new five-star character suggests that she will debut in the first banner cycle of Version 5.5. While HoYoverse has yet to officially confirm the update's release date, based on its usual update schedule, players can expect
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  Version 5.5 to arrive around March 26.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Leak Reveals a New Skin for Black Panther</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-leak-black-panther-skin-thrice-cursed-king/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      RivalsInfo has leaked a new skin for Black Panther called Thrice-Cursed King.
     </li>
     <li>
      Black Panther is a formidable Duelist in Marvel Rivals, with a strong melee focus and the ability to summon a spectral version of Bast.
     </li>
     <li>
      Images of the Thrice-Cursed King costume suggest Black Panther may have been turned into a vampire by the villain Dracula.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A prominent
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  leaker has shared gameplay footage of an upcoming skin for the hero Black Panther called Thrice-Cursed King. While there's no official release date for Season 2 of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , many fans are already discussing which characters may come to the game next, with Blade and Emma Frost being popular choices within the community.
 </p>
 <p>
  Black Panther is one of the most dangerous Duelists in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , as his superior movement and melee focus allow him to get in and out of fights with great speed. His ultimate attack gives him the ability to summon a spectral version of Bast, dealing significant damage to nearby enemies and refreshing the hero's cooldowns. While he did receive cosmetics within the battle pass for Season 0, many players have been eagerly awaiting more costumes for the popular hero.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent post on Twitter, prominent leaker RivalsInfo shared gameplay footage of a new skin for
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Black Panther titled Thrice-Cursed King. The costume shows the character wearing thick, gleaming silver armor with bat-like pauldrons that feature a crimson glow. This outfit doesn't include a mask, which allows players to see Black Panther's pointy ears and fangs, indicating that he may have been turned into a vampire by the villain Dracula. The skin was teased earlier in Season 1 when a Midnight Features quest rewarded gamers with a gallery card that included the hero donning the sinister outfit.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-leaker-showcases-the-lsquo-thrice-cursed-king-rsquo-skin-for-black-panther">
  Marvel Rivals Leaker Showcases the ‘Thrice-Cursed King’ Skin for Black Panther
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1026476002" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1026476002" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1026476002" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1026476002" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1026476002-img" id="article-gallery-1-1026476002">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1026476002" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-116316953">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  RivalsInfo also revealed that the Steam Power skin for Iron Man in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  may be returning to the game soon, which has many fans feeling excited. The steampunk-inspired cosmetic hasn't been seen since the title's previous beta tests, and some gamers have been clamoring to get their hands on it once again. According to X0X_LEAK, the bundles for Black Panther and Iron Man are scheduled to release on March 21 and will cost 1,600 Units each. As with all leaks, it's best to take these claims with a grain of salt. The developers could change their plans at any time, or the information itself could be inaccurate.
 </p>
 <p>
  NetEase Games recently revealed gameplay for two new skins coming to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  for the heroes Storm and Loki. The Goddess of Thunder costume gives Storm an Asgardian makeover as she dons armor and wields a hammer called Stormcaster. Meanwhile, the god Loki takes on a more earthly appearance with his Presidential Attire costume, which shows him wearing a green suit and golden crown. Both skins and their bundles will release on March 13 at 7 PM PDT. With so many new cosmetics to enjoy and a wealth of content just around the corner, many players are feeling optimistic about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Neil Is the Character to Watch in Death Stranding 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/death-stranding-2-neil-important-metal-gear-antagonist/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Neil's resemblance to Solid Snake hints at Kojima's meta connections between franchises.
     </li>
     <li>
      Neil may be an antagonist in Death Stranding 2, but Kojima is known for subverting expectations.
     </li>
     <li>
      Neil is expected to play a pivotal role in Death Stranding 2, possibly as a character development device.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Hideo Kojima just continues to show what he is capable of when the sky's the limit for game development, as he has released yet another 10-minute trailer for the highly anticipated sequel to 2019's
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
   </strong>
  </em>
  . The trailer offers an extended look at
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , showcasing what appears to be an incredibly emotional story, but the characters, both new and old, are arguably the highlight of the trailer.
 </p>
 <p>
  While it is certainly nice to see familiar characters like Sam and Fragile back for another round, one of the new characters revealed in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's pre-order trailer is Neil, a mysterious individual who appears to have a painful past fueling a vengeful future. While next to nothing has been firmly disclosed about his character arc, the trailer makes one thing clear: Neil is the character to watch in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-fans-should-keep-a-close-eye-on-neil-in-death-stranding-2">
  Why Fans Should Keep a Close Eye on Neil in Death Stranding 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-889210803" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-889210803" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-889210803" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-889210803" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-889210803-img" id="article-gallery-1-889210803">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-889210803" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-236663316">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="neil-39-s-resemblance-to-solid-snake-opens-the-door-to-death-stranding-2-meta-conversation">
  Neil's Resemblance to Solid Snake Opens the Door to Death Stranding 2 Meta Conversation
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's pre-order trailer hasn't been live for very long, and plenty of fans have already pointed out how much Neil resembles Solid Snake, the protagonist from another of Hideo Kojima's franchises,
  <em>
   Metal Gear Solid
  </em>
  . Of course, this is to be expected of Kojima, as he is known for including references to his past games in his works. In fact,
  <em>
   Metal Gear Solid
  </em>
  is a great example of this in action, which has multiple nods to
  <em>
   Snatcher
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Policenauts
  </em>
  , two of Kojima's earlier adventure games. Even the first
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  has a reference to
  <em>
   Metal Gear Solid
  </em>
  when Sam says, "Kept you waiting, huh?," as it mirrors Snake's famous phrase.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     While next to nothing has been firmly disclosed about his character arc, the trailer makes one thing clear: Neil is the character to watch in
     <em>
      Death Stranding 2
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  In light of that, it could be that Neil's resemblance to Solid Snake is nothing more than a subtle nod to one of Kojima's biggest franchises. At the same time, although Kojima has never outright confirmed it, the idea of a "Kojima-verse" has been tossed around for quite some time. Even if a Kojima-verse doesn't actually exist, though, Neil's resemblance to Solid Snake still blurs the lines between the developer's franchises, offering a meta-commentary that really enriches the overall experience. This may not be the most important reason fans should keep their eye on Neil in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , but it's at least enough for followers of Kojima's work to make an immediate connection with the sequel.
 </p>
 <h3 id="neil-may-be-an-antagonist-in-death-stranding-2-but-might-be-too-obvious">
  Neil May Be an Antagonist in Death Stranding 2, But Might Be Too Obvious
 </h3>
 <p>
  The main reason Neil is the character to watch in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  is his currently mysterious role in the game's story. Based on what is shown in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's pre-order trailer, Neil looks like he could be an antagonist in the narrative. However, that may be too obvious, especially when considering Kojima's reputation for subverting expectations. For example,
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  's Cliff Unger was originally portrayed as an antagonist, but he was eventually revealed to be a tragic anti-hero.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The latest trailer for
     <em>
      Death Stranding 2
     </em>
     actually implies that Neil could have a similar arc to Cliff's, though that would likely turn out to be a divisive move and be criticized for being too repetitive.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Nevertheless, Neil is clearly going to play a pivotal role in the story, even if he doesn't turn out to be the overarching antagonist of the story. Perhaps, like Cliff did in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , Neil will be used in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  as a character development device for Sam. Based on Kojima's history, it's entirely possible (and even highly likely) he is using Neil's prominence in the recent trailer as a form of misdirection, hiding the identity of the true antagonist. Whatever he turns out to be, though, Neil is the one fans should watch as
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  's June release date draws nearer.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have You Heard of Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders?</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/have-you-heard-of-lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Have you Heard of Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders? The skiing game that sees you racing, strolling, or hanging out, as you traverse down a snowcapped mountain.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Kitty Island Adventure: How To Survive The Mansion</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hello-kitty-island-adventure-how-to-beat-survive-mansion/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hello Kitty Island Adventure
   </strong>
  </em>
  has a whole biome that is perfect for Kumori called
  <strong>
   Spooky Swamp.
  </strong>
  In this location on the island, players will discover just how creepy it is, with rundown cabins, pumpkins with pumpkin spiders running around, a witch's hut, and also
  <strong>
   a haunted mansion.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players will be required to try and
  <strong>
   survive the haunted house
  </strong>
  with Kumori and solve its puzzles to finish t
  <strong>
   he "Survive The Mansion" quest.
  </strong>
  This quest is important for helping Kumori get the place ready so she can open up her poison shop and for players to unlock the Green Power Crystal, which will start up the Ghost Ride, and will also reveal a secret cave. This guide will explain
  <strong>
   how to survive the
   <em>
    Hello Kitty Island Adventure
   </em>
   haunted mansion in Spooky Swamp.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-survive-the-haunted-mansion-in-hello-kitty-island-adventure">
  How to Survive the Haunted Mansion in Hello Kitty Island Adventure
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1874770692" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1874770692" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1874770692" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1874770692" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1874770692-img" id="article-gallery-1-1874770692">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1874770692" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1919461746">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In order to survive the haunted mansion, players will have to make it through a total of 10 different rooms, solving the puzzles to be able to make it to the end to get the Green Power Crystal that the quest requires. However, with each room comes a brand-new puzzle that the player will have to solve. Sometimes, players will be able to call on Kumorii to help solve the puzzles that players get stuck on. In this guide, we will be breaking down each room and explaining how to complete them without needing Kumori to help solve puzzles for the player instead. Below is a chart detailing how to complete each puzzle:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Room Number
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Puzzle
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        How To Complete
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       A maze where players need to make it to the other side and go through the second door.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players will need to make a right turn at the entrance to the room. After running past the purple chairs, players will need to take the bottom path and head through the door.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 2
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Disappearing floors that the player can fall through. They have to cross over them to make it to the door at the end.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players can look across the floor and see that some of the flooring pieces are raised above the normal ground level. If players step on them, they will teleport back to the beginning of the room. Go around and through the door at the end.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Invisible mirrors will appear once the player walks into them, blocking their way to the door.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players will need to go to the right, walk past the table, and then move onto the middle pathway and go to the doorway.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       The room has a total of 11 doors, each one taking players to another door to confuse them. Only one door is the correct one.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       In order to find the correct door, players will need to travel to the second door on their left. It will be found on the left side of the purple mirror.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This puzzle is a room full of levers that players will have to pull until the green light turns on, letting the player know they did it correctly. The next part will require players to press colored buttons.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       To complete the first part of the puzzle, players will need to turn each lever counterclockwise to get each light above them to green. Next, players will need to press the red and green buttons by stepping on them.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This room will also feature levers but will be a little bit easier than the fifth room.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players will need to activate two levers on opposite corners of each other. This means activating the first lever of the top row and the last lever of the last row.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 7
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This time, players will be greeted with more levers and a maze that they will need to solve.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Once at the entrance, walk forward and then turn right. Continue walking forward, then turn right and keep going. Once players see the My Melody painting, pull that lever and head back. At the second bookshelf, go left, then right, and activate the lever found there. Lastly, head through the opening, then go up a little bit and turn right. Now, follow the path to the lever, pull it, and go through the door.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 8
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       The eighth room will go back to the disappearing floor panels that were in the earlier rooms.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players will want to go straight from the far left side, walking up until the character is next to the window, and then make a sharp right. Now, players will want to stop once they get to the door and go up slightly. Walk up to the clock and then go over to the left until they can go through the door.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 9
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This room features levers and three different paths that players will have to reveal with the levers.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Use the left lever to use the path to the next part of the puzzle. Now, the player can go to the right path and head toward the door.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Room 10
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This room holds another maze with disappearing paths that are based on which lever the player pulls.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Run straight up and pull the lever, then go back to the entrance and go down the right path to pull that lever. Now, a third path will open up for the player. Go down that path and pull the next lever found there. Head through the small gap and turn right, moving along the wall until you get to the fourth lever. Go back to the lever in the center, go to the bottom, and activate it. Now run along the long path to the door and exit the final room.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Escape The Mansion
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       The end of the mansion will feature a Green Power Crystal.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Players will need to get this Green Power Crystal to then use it for the Ghost Tour Ride, which will be a part of finishing the quest.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  After completing these steps, players will have successfully survived the Haunted Mansion. Now, players can complete their quest by heading to the Kumori-marked spot on their map. Activate the Ghost Ride, and players will need to go through a chat with the whole group. Players will then be able to go on the ride and turn on different lamps to
 </p>
 <p>
  complete the "Survive the Mansion" quest in
  <em>
   Hello Kitty Island Adventure
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
