<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>New Angry Birds Toys in the Works Thanks to Rovio, The Loyal Subjects Partnership</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/angry-birds-new-toys-rovio-the-loyal-subjects-partnership/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Rovio is partnering with The Loyal Subjects for a new line of Angry Birds toys and collectibles in 2026.
     </li>
     <li>
      The collaboration will include a nostalgic aesthetic and fan-favorite characters.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans can look forward to high-quality, innovative products in the future, according to Rovio and TLS.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Fans of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Angry Birds
   </em>
  </strong>
  have plenty to look forward to on the horizon, as Rovio is partnering with The Loyal Subjects for a new line of high-quality toys and collectibles based on the franchise. This collaboration is slated to kick off with “a mind-blowing suite” of
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  -themed products that will hit retailers in 2026.
 </p>
 <p>
  Few franchises have left their mark in gaming history like
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  . Since its debut in 2009, Rovio’s iconic IP has become one of the most ubiquitous names in mobile gaming and has further cemented its place in pop culture by branching out into other forms of media such as film and TV. Amid all of this, there have been loads of
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  merchandise for fans to get their hands on, and now there’s good news for those who haven’t yet had their fill.
 </p>
 <p>
  Rovio and leading toy brand The Loyal Subjects have announced a partnership to create a new line of
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  toys, collectibles, and more. In teasing this new line, TLS stated that it will recreate the aesthetic of the earlier
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  games, and that consumers can expect to see fan-favorite birds represented. What’s more, TLS is also working on a toy line to tie into the third film in the
  <em>
   Angry Birds Movie
  </em>
  series, which was confirmed to be in production last year.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="rovio-and-the-loyal-subjects-announce-new-angry-birds-toy-line">
  Rovio and The Loyal Subjects Announce New Angry Birds Toy Line
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1656207157" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1656207157" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1656207157" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1656207157" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1656207157-img" id="article-gallery-1-1656207157">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1656207157" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1888042672">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The first collection of
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  toys, collectibles, and plushes from The Loyal Subjects will arrive sometime in 2026, though fans will get their first look at the lineup later this year. Describing the partnership with Rovio, TLS stated how both companies value inspiring imagination and play in kids and adults alike. “The TLS team is soaring with excitement for
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  ,” said brand CEO Jonathan Cathey, who expressed confidence in TLS’ ability to carry the torch for the franchise. Similarly, Rovio VP of Transmedia Hanna Valkeapaa-Nokkala expressed excitement at having TLS on board, saying, “We can’t wait for fans to experience these high-quality, innovative, and exciting toy lines firsthand!”
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s clear from the announcement that the two companies are eager to take part in this partnership, with Cathey describing both as “sharing a North Star” promoting fun and a desire to create memorable products that fans of
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  will love. Between said products and the upcoming release of
  <em>
   The Angry Birds Movie 3
  </em>
  , there will be plenty to look forward to in the near future.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Loyal Subjects has a lengthy history of partnerships under its belt, having created products for a wide range of popular brands including Marvel, Nickelodeon, and WWE. With this expertise, fans should expect quality merchandise when TLS’
  <em>
   Angry Birds
  </em>
  line drops into retailers next year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Offline Mobile Simulation Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-offline-mobile-simulation-games-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Simulation games provide fun &amp; entertaining experiences on various topics with varying levels of accuracy.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some best offline mobile simulation games are SimCity BuildIt, Depotism 3K, WorldBox - God Simulator.
     </li>
     <li>
      Titles like Stardew Valley &amp; Mega Mall Story offer complete and engaging simulation experiences on different platforms.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   Simulation
  </strong>
  games have been around for almost as long as gaming. Ever since the days of dial-up Internet, simulation games have provided players with tons of fun and entertaining experiences, regardless of the topic they cover. Some are extremely accurate, whereas others sacrifice some accuracy to make gameplay more fun.
 </p>
 <p>
  Platforms like Steam have great free simulation titles in their library. However, a lot of them require an active Internet connection, which can be inconvenient for players who want to have a good time while they're on the road. Here are some of the
  <strong>
   best offline mobile simulation games
  </strong>
  out there.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="simcity-buildit">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   SimCity BuildIt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-decently-fun-city-building-title">
  A Decently Fun City-Building Title
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1804655619" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1804655619" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1804655619" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1804655619" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1804655619-img" id="article-gallery-1-1804655619">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1804655619" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1424552581">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The game features residential areas, as well as commercial and industrial buildings
  </li>
  <li>
   Players must solve some of the most common real-life issues of a large city
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  With so many simulation games out there, the possibilities for different topics are almost endless. Some great titles in this genre are not part of a franchise. However, this is not the case for
  <strong>
   <em>
    SimCity BuildIt
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which is part of the SimCity catalog. Throughout the game, players will have to solve real-life situations including traffic, pollution and sewage, as well as other public issues that typically affect large cities.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game's main concept is for it to be a freemium. However, it does have some annoying pop-up ads and in-game purchases, which is how the developers make money.
  <em>
   SimCity BuildIt
  </em>
  features commercial and industrial buildings which produce items, as well as residential zones which require constant upgrades. All in all, while the game has received mixed reviews, it certainly provides decent fun for what it offers. It should be noted that, while
  <em>
   SimCity BuildIt
  </em>
  can be played offline, players will be asked to connect to the Internet after a certain period.
 </p>
 <h2 id="depotism-3k">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Depotism 3K
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="when-ai-takes-over-the-fun-begins">
  When AI Takes Over, The Fun Begins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1480168894" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1480168894" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1480168894" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1480168894" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1480168894-img" id="article-gallery-2-1480168894">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1480168894" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-51205679">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platform(s):
   </strong>
   Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Windows, Linux, Xbox One, Mac operating systems, Android, iOS
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   November 08, 2018
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer(s):
   </strong>
   Konfa Games, Gameplay First LLC
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genre(s):
   </strong>
   Strategy Video Game, Simulation Game, Indie Game
  </li>
  <li>
   Players take on the role of AI overlords
  </li>
  <li>
   Preventing exhaustion and hunger in humans is key
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Anyone concerned about the possibility of AI enslaving humanity in the near future should probably skip this title, as it could be a little triggering for them. On a more serious note, though,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Depotism 3k
   </em>
  </strong>
  presents players with a scenario where they can be the AI overlord and exploit humans to generate power and build an empire.
 </p>
 <p>
  This title involves a ton of resource management as players will have to make sure that their human workers do not succumb to hunger or fatigue, which is sometimes easier said than done. This title is not only packed with simulation mechanics but also includes a few rogue-lite elements that complement it greatly. It's honestly surprising that
  <em>
   Depotism 3k
  </em>
  isn't more popular, as it could be argued that it is one of the best mobile simulation games out there.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="worldbox---god-simulator">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   WorldBox - God Simulator
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-game-that-puts-control-of-the-world-in-players-39-hands">
  A Game That Puts Control Of The World In Players' Hands
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2126849864" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2126849864" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2126849864" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2126849864" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2126849864-img" id="article-gallery-3-2126849864">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2126849864" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1332282331">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platform(s):
   </strong>
   Android, iOS, Windows, macOS, Linux
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   September 24, 2012
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer(s):
   </strong>
   Maxim Karpenko
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genre(s):
   </strong>
   Simulation Video Game, Sandbox
  </li>
  <li>
   Players have godlike powers and can choose to intervene in the events of their world
  </li>
  <li>
   Four different races that fight for power and conquest
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  God simulators are extremely popular, and with good reason, as they typically feature fun game mechanics that put control and power in players’ hands. In
  <strong>
   <em>
    WorldBox - God Simulator
   </em>
  </strong>
  , players will have the chance to use many powers in their toolbox as they look after the creatures in their world, which include innocent animals in search of food, and greedy kings pushing to expand their territory.
 </p>
 <p>
  This title also features four different civilized races, including orcs, elves, dwarves, and humans. Each one will try to expand their kingdom through colonization as players create more continents. Players will also have the choice to either intervene in the comings and goings of the creatures in their land or just sit back and watch what happens. All in all,
  <em>
   WorldBox - God Simulator
  </em>
  is definitely one of the best 2D simulation games out there.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mega-mall-story">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Mega Mall Story
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="managing-expanding-and-maintaining-massive-malls-has-never-been-more-fun">
  Managing, Expanding, And Maintaining Massive Malls Has Never Been More Fun
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-943642301" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-943642301" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-943642301" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-943642301" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-943642301-img" id="article-gallery-4-943642301">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-943642301" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1726250783">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platform(s):
   </strong>
   Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series X/S, Windows, Xbox One, Android, iOS
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   August 09, 2011
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer(s):
   </strong>
   Kairosoft
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genre(s):
   </strong>
   Simulation Video Game, Casual Game, Strategy Video Game, Indie Game
  </li>
  <li>
   Players can invest in developments around their mall to attract more customers
  </li>
  <li>
   Customers can become a store's regular if they like its quality
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While some simulation games are exclusive to PC, this is not the case for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mega Mall Story
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which is available throughout various platforms, so many players can enjoy it. Managing a huge mall and ensuring that customers keep coming through the doors isn't everyone's cup of tea, but for those who want the challenge and are looking for a distraction for a long trip, this title is ideal.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Mega Mall Story
  </em>
  features very interesting game mechanics, such as customers becoming regulars of a specific store when they're satisfied with its quality. As players go up in rank, so will their mall, and the more stars they get (up to 5), the more employees and advertising methods they'll gain access to. It's also possible to make investments to attract apartment complexes, office buildings and other developments that can bring in more people.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="stardew-valley">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Stardew Valley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ultimate-farm-simulation-experience">
  The Ultimate Farm Simulation Experience
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-48177430" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-48177430" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-48177430" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-48177430" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-48177430-img" id="article-gallery-5-48177430">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-48177430" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-2088547072">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Cooking, foraging and fishing are key game mechanics
  </li>
  <li>
   Players must manage their resources wisely
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Lastly, there's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Stardew Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  , a title that has garnered a huge fan base since it was first released, and with good reason, as it offers tons of possibilities for players to explore. The story begins when players inherit their grandfather's farm plot in the quiet, yet friendly populace of Stardew Valley.
 </p>
 <p>
  Throughout the game, players will have to collect various resources, including tools, hats, weapons, bait, and more. Fishing, foraging and cooking are key mechanics of this title and must be done often to progress.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  is, without a doubt, one of the most comforting farming simulation games out there, and also one of the most complete and complex. Players looking for a gaming experience that will both allow them to sit back and relax as their farm plot grows, while also being tasked with gathering and managing resources, will certainly love this title and everything around it.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Time: How to Unlock the Friends Quest</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/roblox-ninja-time-how-unlock-friends-quest/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Each shinobi in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Time
   </em>
  </strong>
  can learn different techniques to become the strongest. Though some can be unlocked simply by increasing stats, others require the completion of quests, and the Friends quest is no exception to this.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Unlike other quests, this one is blocked for most players of this
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  RPG. This is because the NPC will only offer you the quest if you fulfill secret conditions not mentioned anywhere. For those unsure about how to do so, here's
  <strong>
   how to unlock the Friends quest in
   <em>
    Ninja Time
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-renegade-prisoner-in-ninja-time">
  Where to Find Renegade Prisoner in Ninja Time
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-4a78e7c0dd2bfee6" id="emaki-video-player-4a78e7c0dd2bfee6">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before you can start the Friends quest in
  <em>
   Ninja Time
  </em>
  , you need to find a certain NPC, namely Renegade Prisoner. This character is not marked on the map, which makes him very easy to miss. Luckily, if you know where to look, you can get to him quite easily.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ninja Time village" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  You need to move southeast from Konoha until you reach the
  <strong>
   Uchiha village
  </strong>
  . There, players should visit a building similar to a police station with cells for criminals. Inside one of the cells, you will find Renegade Prisoner.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-unlock-the-friends-quest-in-ninja-time">
  How to Unlock the Friends Quest in Ninja Time
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Ninja Time Renegade Prisoner" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friends-quest-ninja-time-2-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although Renegade Prisoner does not say so, players must fulfill an important condition: obtain a certain skill mode called
  <strong>
   Crimson Inferno
  </strong>
  before starting the Friends quest.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players should note that it is only available to members of the Red Eyes clan. To unlock it, you need to
     <strong>
      upgrade your Eyes skill tree
     </strong>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  When you finally unlock this skill, you must use it to enter Crimson Inferno mode. It doesn't affect your character visually, but while it is active, you can talk to Renegade Prisoner and start the Friends quest in
  <em>
   Ninja Time
  </em>
  . To complete it, you need to
  <strong>
   kill 5 friends
  </strong>
  . You can even kill one friend 5 times to complete the quest, and you do not need to be a member of the same party to do this.
 </p>
 <p>
  After that, players need to visit the Uchiha Shelter building and take turns standing on the blue squares behind the counter. One of them is a hidden passage to the underground floor, where there is an ancient stone tablet. Interact with it to unlock Susanoo, one of the most powerful techniques of the Red Eyes. And depending on your Red Eyes clan, your Susanoo skill will be different in this
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet: Best Dragon Types In The Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-scarlet-violet-best-dragon-types/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Dragon-type Pokemon like Haxorus, Latios, and Kommo-o are powerful additions for competitive play.
     </li>
     <li>
      Legendary Dragon-types like Reshiram, Zekrom, and Rayquaza are available to capture in Pokemon Scarlet and Violet.
     </li>
     <li>
      Unique Dragon-type Pokemon like Roaring Moon, Archaludon, and Baxcalibur offer diverse and powerful options for players.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  franchise is known to have a variety of powerful Pokemon with numerous type combinations, from the simple Fire and Water to ones like Psychic or Fairy. Arguably one of the strongest types in the franchise's long history has been
  <strong>
   Dragon-types
  </strong>
  , which were originally introduced in the first generation games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Game Freak continues to create interesting dragon-type Pokemon for players to catch. With so many new additions to the franchise, as well as plenty of old favorites, these are by far the
  <strong>
   strongest Dragon-type Pokemon
  </strong>
  players should try capturing while exploring Paldea in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated March 2, 2025, by Blaise Santi:
   </strong>
  </em>
  It's been an exciting week for Pokemon fans now that footage of
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends Z-A
  </em>
  has finally been revealed. This follow-up to
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends Arceus
  </em>
  will likely introduce some new Dragon-type Pokemon, particularly as new forms of older Pokemon, to the mainline series, which will certainly be used a lot in future generations' competitive scenes. However,
  <em>
   Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  users who haven't picked the game up in a while may not know that some of the strongest Dragon-type Pokemon are now obtainable in the Gen 9 games thanks to functionality of Pokemon HOME as well as special Event Raids. Take a look at this updated list of the best Dragon-types in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , including some iconic mascots from the series' past!
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="haxorus">
  <span class="item-num">
   30
  </span>
  <span>
   Haxorus
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-axe-jaw-pokemon">
  The Axe Jaw Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1758127000" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1758127000" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1758127000" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1758127000" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1758127000-img" id="article-gallery-1-1758127000">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1758127000" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1419559784">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Rivalry, Mold Breaker, Unnerve
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Breaking Swipe, Outrage, Dragon Pulse, Crunch, Giga Impact
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tera Raid Battles
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       This Pokémon nests in caves and abandoned mines. It is docile, but it will become incredibly angry if its tusks are touched, so beware.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  In terms of Gen 5 Pokemon, Haxorus often gets the short end of the stick by not being a pseudo legendary. However, it's a fairly straight-forward pure-Dragon-type with a staggering physical Attack base stat. Paired with decent speed and the useful Ability, Mold Breaker, Haxorus can make for a big threat in the competitive scene with the right movepool.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from its learned moves, Haxorus gains incredible coverage with access to Earthquake and Poison Jab, which will both counter its biggest weaknesses. It can strengthen these moves with Terastallization, though some players may prefer keeping Haxorus' Tera-type as Dragon in order to make its physical STAB moves even more painful.
 </p>
 <h2 id="latios-amp-latias">
  <span class="item-num">
   29
  </span>
  <span>
   Latios &amp; Latias
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-eon-pokemon">
  The Eon Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-651000423" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-651000423" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-651000423" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-651000423" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-651000423-img" id="article-gallery-2-651000423">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-651000423" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-83530106">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Psychic
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Levitate
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Breath, Dragon Pulse, Zen Headbutt, Luster Purge (Latios), Mist Ball (Latias), Tailwind, Memento (Latios), Charm (Latias), Recover
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Area Two (Latios), Area Four (Latias)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Latios: It is a highly intelligent Pokémon. By folding back its forelegs in flight, it can overtake jet planes. Latias: Its body is covered with a down that can refract light in such a way that it becomes invisible.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Latios and Latias are grouped together here simply because they share a lot of similar qualities, and not just in terms of their design. Stats-wise, the only major difference between Latios and Latias is Latios' preference for Attack and Special Attack compared to Latias' Defense and Special Defense, but even their movepools are remarkably similar.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even in competitive play, they serve similar functions as potential Choice Specs sweepers, utilizing their equivalent speeds to become powerful special attackers. They're both also capable of getting mileage out of the unique item Soul Dew, which boosts Latios and Latias' Dragon and Psychic-type STAB attacks. With their unique type combinations, they're very underrated.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kommo-o">
  <span class="item-num">
   28
  </span>
  <span>
   Kommo-o
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-scaly-pokemon">
  The Scaly Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-575150608" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-575150608" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-575150608" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-575150608" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-575150608-img" id="article-gallery-3-575150608">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-575150608" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-552001340">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Fighting
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Bulletproof, Soundproof, Overcoat
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Clanging Scales, Clangorous Soul, Close Combat, Iron Defense, Boomburst
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tera Raid Battles
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It bashes its scales to test its opponents' mettle. The sound of struck Kommo-o scales frightens weaker foes and sends them running.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Kommo-o was introduced in
  <em>
   Pokemon Sun &amp; Moon
  </em>
  , but as of
  <em>
   The Hidden Treasure of Area Zero
  </em>
  , it can appear in Tera Raid Battles in
  <em>
   Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , or transferred over from
  <em>
   Pokemon HOME
  </em>
  . Prior to Koraidon, Kommo-o's Dragon/Fighting-typing was unique, allowing it to boast incredible Attack and Defense stats that can be quite rare for other Dragon-type Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  As of the previous generation, there's one particular item that's simply made for Kommo-o: Throat Spray. This consumable held item will boost a Pokemon's Special Attack after using a sound move, of which Kommo-o has many. It also makes for a strong Physical Attacker in Doubles matches, so don't underestimate this Pokemon just because Koraidon exists.
 </p>
 <h2 id="gouging-fire">
  <span class="item-num">
   27
  </span>
  <span>
   Gouging Fire
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-paradox-pokemon">
  The Paradox Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1306935643" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1306935643" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1306935643" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1306935643" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1306935643-img" id="article-gallery-4-1306935643">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1306935643" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-365232107">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fire/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Protosynthesis
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Burning Bulwark, Raging Fury, Dragon Rush, Outrage, Bite, Double Kick, Ancient Power, Crush Claw
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Area Zero (
       <em>
        Pokemon Scarlet: The Indigo Disk
       </em>
       )
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It resembles an eerie Pokémon once shown in a paranormal magazine. That Pokémon was said to be an Entei regenerated from a fossil.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Alongside the Raikou-reminiscent Raging Bolt, Gouging Fire is a brand-new Paradox Pokemon introduced in
  <em>
   The Indigo Disk
  </em>
  . This Fire/Dragon-type appears to be an ancestor of the Gen 2 Legendary Pokemon Entei, sporting a golden crest on its head. Unlike Entei, Gouging Fire learns some pretty powerful Dragon-type moves, like Dragon Rush and Outrage.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, Gouging Fire's biggest positive is the unique move Burning Bulwark, which only it can learn. The move works similarly to Protect, but for opponents who make direct contact with the shield, they are burned.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="walking-wake">
  <span class="item-num">
   26
  </span>
  <span>
   Walking Wake
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-paradox-pokemon">
  The Paradox Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1348339785" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1348339785" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1348339785" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1348339785" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1348339785-img" id="article-gallery-5-1348339785">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1348339785" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1669700950">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Water/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Protosynthesis
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Hydro Steam, Aqua Jet, Breaking Swipe, Dragon Breath, Flamethrower, Bite, Noble Roar
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Event distribution
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It resembles an illustration published in a paranormal magazine, said to be a depiction of a super-ancient Suicune.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rounding out the Paradox forms of Gen 2's Legendary beasts is the Water/Dragon-type Walking Wake, which resembles a prehistoric form of Suicune. It also learns the unique signature move Hydro Steam, which receives an attack boost when used in harsh sunlight. This pairs extremely well with Walking Wake's ability Protosynthesis, which it shares with other past Paradox Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Protosynthesis, a Pokemon's highest base stat will be boosted in harsh sunlight (or when holding a Booster Energy). Since Walking Wake's highest stat is already Special Attack, the special move Hydro Steam will be even more powerful in harsh sunlight than it already would be.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragonite">
  <span class="item-num">
   25
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragonite
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-dragon-pokemon">
  The Dragon Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1845690812" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1845690812" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1845690812" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1845690812" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1845690812-img" id="article-gallery-6-1845690812">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1845690812" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-647439970">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Flying
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Inner Focus, Multiscale
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Tail, Outrage, Hurricane, Roost, Fire Punch, Thunder Wave, Rain Dance, Agility, Extreme Speed
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Casseroya Lake
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It is said that somewhere in the ocean lies an island where these gather. Only they live there.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's simply hard to find much wrong with Dragonite, other than the fact it only evolves from Dragonair at the extremely-late level 55. This Dragon/Flying-type and its evolutionary line are notably one of the first Dragon-types in the entire franchise, a status it held until the addition of only Kingdra in Gen 2. Nevertheless, Dragonite has remained a top-tier Pokemon for many generations.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a lot of positives to Dragonite, competitively speaking, from its Hidden Ability Multiscale, which reduces damages at full HP, its incredibly diverse movepool, including moves like Aqua Tail, Fire Punch, and Stomping Tantrum, and its incredibly high stats, especially Attack. For the very first pseudo-legendary, Dragonite is about as nearly-legendary as it gets.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="goodra">
  <span class="item-num">
   24
  </span>
  <span>
   Goodra
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-dragon-amp-shell-bunker-pokemon">
  The Dragon &amp; Shell Bunker Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-565130294" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-565130294" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-565130294" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-565130294" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-565130294-img" id="article-gallery-7-565130294">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-565130294" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1222980371">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon, Dragon/Steel (Hisuian form)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Sap Sipper, Hydration, Gooey, Shell Armor (Hisuian form)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Breath, Dragon Pulse, Iron Head (Hisuian form), Shelter (Hisuian form), Muddy Water, Absorb, Acid Spray, Curse, Body Slam
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Evolve Sliggoo, Tera Raid Battles, Pokemon HOME (Hisuian form)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It loves the rain. This mellow Pokémon can be seen walking around on the plains and in the mountains on rainy days.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Speaking of pseudo-legendaries, Goodra is perhaps one of the more underrated pseudo-legendary evolutionary lines. Introduced in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon X &amp; Y
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the pure Dragon-type was notable for access to useful Abilities like Sap Sipper and Gooey, as well as its movepool including a solid selection of Water-type, Grass-type, and Poison-type moves.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it was
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Legends: Arceus
   </em>
  </strong>
  that really boosted Goodra's favor with hardcore
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans. The Hisui region introduced a regional form of Goodra that is Dragon/Steel, with moves to complement its new STAB capabilities and increased Defense at the cost of some Speed, making it a bulkier and, frankly, much more appealing Pokemon for any team.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tatsugiri">
  <span class="item-num">
   23
  </span>
  <span>
   Tatsugiri
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-mimicry-pokemon">
  The Mimicry Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-425187304" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-425187304" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-425187304" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-425187304" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-425187304-img" id="article-gallery-8-425187304">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-425187304" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1741785507">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Water
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Commander, Storm Drain
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Pulse, Water Pulse, Muddy Water, Nasty Plot, Mirror Coat, Helping Hand
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Casseroya Lake
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       This is a small dragon Pokémon. It lives inside the mouth of Dondozo to protect itself from enemies on the outside.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's surprising to think that this small fish that replicates the look of a piece of Sushi is a Dragon-type Pokemon. However, it is exactly that. Tatsugiri may appear as one of the weakest Dragon-types in the game, but they are also incredibly intelligent. They call upon the aid of Dondozo to help them in not only battle but also to get food.
 </p>
 <p>
  While taking part in two vs. two battles, Tatsugiri may use its signature ability of Commander, which allows it to hop into the mouth of an ally Dondozo that is on the field. While in this match-up, Tatsugiri is unable to be hit.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragalge">
  <span class="item-num">
   22
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragalge
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-mock-kelp-pokemon">
  The Mock Kelp Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-889894521" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-889894521" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-889894521" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-889894521" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-889894521-img" id="article-gallery-9-889894521">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-889894521" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-925804955">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Poison/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Poison Point, Poison Touch, Adaptability
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Sludge Bomb, Acid, Dragon Pulse, Outrage, Aqua Tail, Double Team
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       North Paldean Sea
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Using a liquid poison, Dragalge indiscriminately attacks anything that wanders into its territory. This poison can corrode the undersides of boats.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Dragalge is an incredible Dragon/Poison-Type Pokemon. It is not only a great choice for those looking for a Dragon for their roster but also for those looking for an incredibly powerful Poison-type. With Special Defense being one of its highest stats, Dragalge is also sure to stay alive in various battles, as it can also hit hard.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some Pokemon in
  <em>
   Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  are version exclusives, and Dragalge can only be found in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet
  </em>
  . Thankfully, players who own
  <em>
   Pokemon Violet
  </em>
  can still get their hands on this Mock Kelp Pokemon by trading with a player who has the other version of the game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="altaria">
  <span class="item-num">
   21
  </span>
  <span>
   Altaria
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-humming-pokemon">
  The Humming Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1765448973" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1765448973" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1765448973" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1765448973" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1765448973-img" id="article-gallery-10-1765448973">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1765448973" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-946066950">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Flying
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Natural Cure, Cloud Nine
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Breath, Dragon Pulse, Pluck, Sky Attack, Moonblast, Cotton Guard, Mist, Perish Song
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Casseroya Lake
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       If it bonds with a person, it will gently envelop the friend with its soft wings, then hum.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although Altaria doesn't look like a typical Dragon-type Pokemon, it has earned itself a place as one of the best Dragon-types a player may wish to consider. Players can either find Altaria flying around in the wild or capture a Swablu and evolve it at around level 35.
 </p>
 <p>
  As its fluffy cloud-like wings that wrap around its body suggest, Altaria is also a Flying-type Pokemon. This typing may have become less useful in recent games since players can fast-travel around the map freely, but Altaria continues to be a powerful member of any player's team.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="appletun">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Appletun
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-apple-nectar-pokemon">
  The Apple Nectar Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-506734083" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-506734083" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-506734083" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-506734083" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-506734083-img" id="article-gallery-11-506734083">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-506734083" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-966651677">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Grass/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ripen, Gluttony, Thick Fat
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Apple Acid, Energy Ball, Dragon Pulse, Astonish, Iron Defense, Withdraw, Stomp
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Mossfell Confluence
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It feeds mainly on sweet apples. It will also eat small bug Pokémon that are attracted by its sweet nectar.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Appeltun is another interesting Pokemon that players will likely want on their teams, not only for its adorable appearance but also for its powerful Dragon and Grass-type attacks. Appletun evolves from Applin once given a Sweet Apple. If given a Tart Apple instead, Applin becomes Flapple, which is another great Dragon-type that players should consider.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition to the usual Dragon-type moves available to the Pokemon, Appletun is also the only monster that can learn the move Apple Acid. This Grass-Type move deals substantial damage while also lowering the target's Special Defense. This benefits Appletun greatly, as its best stats involve its Special Attack.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cyclizar">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Cyclizar
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-mount-pokemon">
  The Mount Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-909488574" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-909488574" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-909488574" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-909488574" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-909488574-img" id="article-gallery-12-909488574">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-909488574" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1753527280">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Normal
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shed Skin, Regenerator
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Claw, Dragon Rush, Shed Tail, Double-Edge, Shift Gear, U-Turn, Bite
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       East Province Area One, Two, Asado Desert
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Apparently Cyclizar has been allowing people to ride on its back since ancient times. Depictions of this have been found in 10,000-year-old murals.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Cyclizar may be considered quite basic compared to its futuristic relative Miraidon and its ancient ancestor Koraidon. However, this doesn't stop Cyclizar from being an exciting choice early in the game until players can use their own legendary in battle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combining Dragon with Normal may not seem that special, but this does mean that players have a Pokemon that can confidentially go up against a Ghost-type Pokemon without worrying about its move set. Besides, Cyclizar is an adorable Pokemon to have on the team; it's just unfortunate that players can't use them as a vehicle like the other NPCs can.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="noivern">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Noivern
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-sound-wave-pokemon">
  The Sound Wave Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-2020382106" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-2020382106" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-2020382106" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-2020382106" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-2020382106-img" id="article-gallery-13-2020382106">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-2020382106" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-710473556">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Flying/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Frisk, Infiltrator, Telepathy
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Hurricane, Air Slash, Dragon Pulse, Moonlight, Bite, Absorb, Boomburst
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       North Province Area One, Two
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       In the dark, even Hydreigon are terrified of this Pokémon. But in the light, Noivern is the one that avoids battle.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Stepping away from the newest Pokemon added with
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  , players may also remember this Dragon-type from
  <em>
   Pokemon X &amp; Y
  </em>
  , the bat Pokemon, Noivern. Evolving from Noibat, some players may think Noivern would be a combination of Dark/Dragon, but it is actually Flying/Dragon-typed. Players would first need to evolve Noibat if they wish to have this dragon bat.
 </p>
 <p>
  One mustn't be fooled by its adorable design, as Noivern has been known to be incredibly cruel to Pokemon in the dark and incredibly timid in the light. Luckily, many players will find this Pokemon exploring the outdoors, instead of a damp cave.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hydrapple">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Hydrapple
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-incredibly-powerful-evolution-of-applin">
  An Incredibly Powerful Evolution Of Applin
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-150470706" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-150470706" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-150470706" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-150470706" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-150470706-img" id="article-gallery-14-150470706">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-150470706" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-218815296">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Grass/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Supersweet Syrup, Regenerator, Sticky Hold
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Syrup Bomb, Bullet Seed, Fickle Beam, Dragon Breath, Infestation, Withdraw, Astonish, Recover
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Evolve Dipplin
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       These capricious syrpents have banded together. On the rare occasion that their moods align, their true power is unleashed.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Applin is a Pokemon that already has multiple different evolutions depending on the sort of apple it gets from the player. This has led to two brand-new evolution paths in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  . When Applin is given a Syrupy Apple, it evolves into Dipplin, but unlike Flapple or Appletun, this evolutionary line doesn't stop there.
 </p>
 <p>
  This Pokemon can evolve a step further into Hydrapple if the player levels it up while knowing the Dragon Cheer move, causing it to become an even more powerful Grass and Dragon-type Pokemon, with a fierce special attack. Hydrapple is also the only Pokemon to know the ability Supersweet Syrup, which lowers the evasion of a target.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="raging-bolt">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Raging Bolt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-paradox-pokemon">
  The Paradox Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-2141836040" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-2141836040" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-2141836040" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-2141836040" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-2141836040-img" id="article-gallery-15-2141836040">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-2141836040" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-369118972">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Electric/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Protosynthesis
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Rising Voltage, Zap Cannon, Dragon Hammer, Twister, Sunny Day, Body Press, Calm Mind, Ancient Power, Stomp
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Area Zero (
       <em>
        Pokemon Scarlet: The Indigo Disk
       </em>
       )
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It bears resemblance to a Pokémon that became a hot topic for a short while after a paranormal magazine touted it as Raikou's ancestor.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players may find Paradox Pokemon from
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  to look quite familiar, such as Raging Bolt. That's because this Paradox Pokemon appears to be an ancient relative of the legendary Electric-type Pokemon Raikou that players are likely to have encountered during the second generation of the franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  With this in mind, Raging Bolt combines these legendary Electric-type moves with the Dragon-type to create an incredibly deadly force against other trainers. With an even more incredible Special Attack, the electricity that is created from its fur is sure to trample the competition.
 </p>
 <h2 id="giratina">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Giratina
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-renegade-pokemon">
  The Renegade Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1095207313" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1095207313" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1095207313" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1095207313" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1095207313-img" id="article-gallery-16-1095207313">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1095207313" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1692517330">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ghost/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Pressure, Telepathy, Levitate (Origin form)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shadow Force, Destiny Bond, Dragon Breath, Dragon Claw, Ancient Power, Earth Power, Aura Sphere, Defog, Pain Split
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Pokemon HOME, Event
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       A Pokémon that is said to live in a world on the reverse side of ours. It appears in an ancient cemetery.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Giratina is one of the few Legendary Pokemon unobtainable by regular means in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , though post-DLC, it's possible to transfer it over from
  <em>
   Pokemon HOME.
  </em>
  That means that players who were fortunate enough to catch Giratina in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Arceus
  </em>
  (or have even kept their Legendary Pokemon around since
  <em>
   Pokemon Platinum
  </em>
  ) can use it in-game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Competitively, Giratina is one of the best Legendary Pokemon out there, with the incredibly useful Ghost/Dragon type making it immune to Normal and Fighting-type moves. It can utilize Terastallization to become Fairy-type and have coverage against its Fairy and Dark-type weaknesses.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="reshiram">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Reshiram
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-vast-white-pokemon">
  The Vast White Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-449683032" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-449683032" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-449683032" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-449683032" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-449683032-img" id="article-gallery-17-449683032">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-449683032" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-1594524886">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Fire
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Turboblaze
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Pulse, Outrage, Flamethrower, Blue Flare, Ancient Power, Extrasensory, Crunch, Hyper Voice
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Area One (East Province), after receiving the Reshiram Treat from Snacksworth at Blueberry Academy
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       This legendary Pokémon can scorch the world with fire. It helps those who want to build a world of truth.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The mascot legendary for
  <em>
   Pokemon Black
  </em>
  is surprisingly obtainable in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , though it requires players to have the DLC expansion
  <em>
   The Indigo Disk
  </em>
  . For completing solo quests in Blueberry Academy, an NPC named Snacksworth will reward players with a "treat" corresponding to Legendary Pokemon, allowing them to be caught in various spots around Paldea.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reshiram, however, is exclusive to
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet
  </em>
  , meaning
  <em>
   Pokemon Violet
  </em>
  users will have to trade or utilize
  <em>
   Pokemon HOME
  </em>
  to acquire their own. Competitively, Reshiram has impeccable stats and a great movepool. Its Fairy-type and Ice-type weaknesses are neutralized by its dual-typing with Fire, making it only weak to Ground, Rock, and Dragon-type moves.
 </p>
 <h2 id="zekrom">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Zekrom
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-deep-black-pokemon">
  The Deep Black Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-294713499" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-294713499" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-294713499" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-294713499" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-294713499-img" id="article-gallery-18-294713499">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-294713499" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-1187005403">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Electric
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Teravolt
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon Claw, Outrage, Fusion Bolt, Bolt Strike, Ancient Power, Zen Headbutt, Crunch, Slash
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Area Five (South Province), after receiving the Zekrom Treat from Snacksworth at Blueberry Academy
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       This legendary Pokémon can scorch the world with lightning. It assists those who want to build an ideal world.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Reshiram's counterpart, Zekrom, is similarly obtainable from Snacksworth exclusively for players of
  <em>
   Pokemon Violet
  </em>
  . After completing 100 solo quests at Blueberry Academy, Snackworth will give the player a Zekrom Treat. This will allow them to encounter and potentially catch this Dragon/Electric-type Pokemon from
  <em>
   Pokemon White
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  As an Uber-tiered Pokemon in the competitive scene, Zekrom pairs well with a moveset that has high-powered STAB moves like Bolt Strike and Dragon Claw. Lots of players also pair Zekrom with Dragon Dance, boosting its already-incredible physical Attack as well as its surprisingly disappointing Speed stat, making it a sweeping powerhouse on any team.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rayquaza">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Rayquaza
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-sky-high-pokemon">
  The Sky High Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1715583090" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1715583090" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1715583090" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1715583090" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1715583090-img" id="article-gallery-19-1715583090">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1715583090" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-1349488851">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dragon/Flying
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Air Lock, Delta Stream (Mega Rayquaza)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Twister, Dragon Pulse, Dragon Ascent, Hurricane, Ancient Power, Rest, Crunch, Extreme Speed
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Event, Great Crater of Paldea, after receiving the Rayquaza Treat from Snacksworth at Blueberry Academy
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       A Pokémon that flies endlessly in the ozone layer. It is said it would descend to the ground if Kyogre and Groudon were to fight.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sadly, Mega Evolution isn't an option in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , meaning the overpowered Mega Rayquaza can't join a team. Nevertheless, groups of players can team up to complete group quests at Blueberry Academy, eventually rewarding them with a Rayquaza Treat. This will allow players to encounter a Rayquaza in the Great Crater of Paldea.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, some lucky players had the chance to catch a shiny Rayquaza in a special Event raid in December 2024, with the Dragon Tera type. Sadly, it ended in January 2025, meaning most
  <em>
   Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  players just missed their chances. Nevertheless, maybe scouring online trade forums is a great way to obtain this special Rayquaza.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dialga">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Dialga
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-temporal-pokemon">
  The Temporal Pokemon
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-294381185" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-294381185" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-294381185" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-294381185" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-294381185-img" id="article-gallery-20-294381185">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-294381185" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-255850749">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Steel/Dragon
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Abilities
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Pressure, Telepathy
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Learned Moves
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Flash Cannon, Iron Tail, Dragon Breath, Roar of Time, Power Gem, Earth Power, Aura Sphere, Slash
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Catch Locations
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Pokemon HOME, Event
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Pokedex Entry
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       It has the power to control time. It appears in Sinnoh-region myths as an ancient deity.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Dialga has always been one of the best-designed Legendary Pokemon, but thanks to
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends Arceus
  </em>
  , it's even more special. This Gen 4 mascot cannot be caught under ordinary means in
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet &amp; Violet.
  </em>
  Players must either transfer it from
  <em>
   Pokemon HOME
  </em>
  or wait for another Dialga Tera raid to hit the Gen 9 titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, if players manage to acquire a Dialga in
  <em>
   Scarlet &amp; Violet
  </em>
  , there's an additional item they should locate: the Adamant Crystal. This can be bought at the Porto Marinada auction, but only if players currently own a Dialga. In its Origin Forme, Dialga trades some of its physical Attack stats for some increased Special Defense, which is handy for players with a Special Attack-focused Dialga set.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rune Slayer: How to Get the Assassin Set</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/roblox-rune-slayer-how-get-assassin-set/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Rune Slayer
   </em>
  </strong>
  , players can craft or buy different pieces of equipment, and some sets can significantly boost one's character. The Assassin set is one such example, and players would do well to acquire it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This armor is one of the best that you can find in this
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  RPG. It is great for Agility characters, especially the Thief class, but players will need to prepared to spend quite a lot of time getting the whole set. Here's a rundown on
  <strong>
   how to get the Assassin set in
   <em>
    Rune Slayer
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-find-the-assassin-set-in-rune-slayer">
  How to Find the Assassin Set in Rune Slayer
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Rune Slayer forest" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike other gear, the pieces of the Assassin set in
  <em>
   Rune Slayer
  </em>
  can only be obtained by
  <strong>
   completing quests for the Thieves Guild
  </strong>
  . But as befits such a Guild, they are quite well hidden and do not offer work to anyone.
 </p>
 <p>
  To get the Assassin set in
  <em>
   Rune Slayer
  </em>
  , you must complete a series of quests for
  <strong>
   Saegar
  </strong>
  . This NPC is initially located in the Goblin Caves, so you can visit him by following the quests of the Adventurer's Guild. He will ask you to kill James, who is in Pinewood Thickets. Upon doing so, you need to return to him for a reward.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     It is important to note that, after this quest, the Saegar NPC will move to the Thieves Guild. So, to find him, move northeast from Ashenshire until you reach a huge mountain. On one of its sides, players can find a small door leading to the Guild.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  At the Thieves Guild, Saegar will give you contracts to kill certain people. If you succeed, you will receive good rewards, including armor. But of course, you will not be given the entire set at once; each quest will reward you with a piece of Assassin set.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Saegar's Contract 2
   </strong>
   - Kill Krogar to get Assassin's Boots
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Saegar's Contract 3
   </strong>
   - Kill Silas to get Assassin's Hood
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Saegar's Contract 4
   </strong>
   - Kill Vaelion to get Assassin's Cloak
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="rune-slayer---assassin-set-stats">
  Rune Slayer - Assassin Set Stats
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Rune Slayer player" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/assassin-set-rune-slayer-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Assassin set offers players high bonuses to Agility. So, if your build is based on this stat, this armor will suit you perfectly. However, to wear it,
  <strong>
   you need to be at least level 25
  </strong>
  . If you meet this condition, you will get the following stat bonuses while wearing the entire Assassin set in
  <em>
   Rune Slayer
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Armor Piece
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Stats
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Assassin's Hood
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Armor: 220
       </li>
       <li>
        Agility: +8
       </li>
       <li>
        Spirit: +2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Assassin's Cloak
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Armor: 425
       </li>
       <li>
        Agility: +16
       </li>
       <li>
        Spirit: +4
       </li>
       <li>
        Crit Chance: +2%
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Assassin's Boots
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        Armor: 220
       </li>
       <li>
        Agility: +8
       </li>
       <li>
        Spirit: +2
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
