<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch 2 Extends 6v6 Playtest</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/overwatch-2-6v6-playtest-duration-extended-how-long/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Overwatch 2's 6v6 playtest has been extended due to high player interest.
     </li>
     <li>
      The role queue mode will transition to an open queue format with 1-3 heroes of each class sometime around the middle of the season.
     </li>
     <li>
      The 6v6 mode could become a permanent addition in the future.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The limited-time 6v6 game mode playtest in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Overwatch 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  has been extended beyond its planned end date of January 6, with Game Director Aaron Keller confirming that the mode will remain available until the middle of the season before transitioning into an open queue format. This is thanks to the tremendous popularity that the 6v6 format has seen since returning to
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  , with many fans holding onto hope that the mode will become a permanent addition to the game later down the line.
 </p>
 <p>
  With 6v6 first making its appearance in the sequel
  <em>
  </em>
  throughout November last year in the Overwatch Classic event, Blizzard quickly realized fans' love for the 6v6 game mode in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  . The mode's initial run only lasted a few weeks, but quickly proved itself to be among the game's most played modes. It didn't take long before 6v6 found its way back into
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  shortly after the start of its 14th season, with the second 6v6 role queue playtest originally intended to run from December 17 to January 6, though without featuring the return of some antique hero abilities like in the Overwatch Classic event.
 </p>
 <p>
  Due to strong continued player interest in the mode,
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  director Aaron Keller recently shared on his personal Twitter account that the team has decided to extend the duration of the 6v6 mode's second round of playtesting. Fans of
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  will be able to continue jumping into 12-player matches for a long while yet, and while it hasn't been confirmed precisely when the playtest is now set to end, it is known that the 6v6 experimental mode will be moved into the Arcade section very soon. The mode will remain as-is until the middle of the current season, after which it will transition from a role queue mode to an open queue mode with each team requiring a minimum of 1 and a maximum of 3 heroes of each class.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-case-for-overwatch-2-39-s-6v6-mode-to-return-permanently">
  The Case For Overwatch 2's 6v6 Mode to Return Permanently
 </h2>
 <p>
  The persistent success of
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  's 6v6 mode may not come as a surprise to many players, with the return of 6-player teams consistently remaining one of the most highly-requested features since the sequel's release in 2022. The transition to 5v5 matches stood out as one of the boldest and most significant departures from the original
  <em>
   Overwatch
  </em>
  , bringing with it a profound effect on general gameplay which resonates differently with different players.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1722372751" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1722372751" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1722372751" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1722372751" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1722372751-img" id="article-gallery-1-1722372751">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1722372751" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2069699453">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Still, fans of 6v6 have more hope now than ever before that the mode will make its return to
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  as a permanent addition, at some point or another. Many fans hope that it will become an option in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  's competitive playlist as well, something which could well become a possibility once the mode's general playtests in the sequel have concluded.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect From the KOTOR Remake in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kotor-remake-2025-news-reveals-updates-development/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Few games have had a development cycle as turbulent as the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic Remake
   </em>
  </strong>
  . It was announced in 2021 with an intended 2022 release date. A teaser trailer was also released, which was later delisted from YouTube. The
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  was then announced as canceled, and then in 2022 it was revealed to have been moved to another developer. Word of progress made on the game has since been mostly silent, with longtime fans waiting patiently each year for an update.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Unfortunately, 2025 is likely to be no different from any of the other years in terms of news for the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  . After changing developers, the game is still likely to be in early development, with an optimistic hope for news of a release date or an update towards the end of 2025. With the
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi
  </em>
  franchise approaching its conclusion, there's now a gap for a single-player
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  game, and the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  would be perfect for
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi
  </em>
  players new to
  <em>
   KOTOR
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-kotor-remake-rsquo-s-development-is-apparently-still-progressing">
  The KOTOR Remake’s Development is Apparently Still Progressing
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-930872341" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-930872341" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-930872341" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-930872341" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-930872341-img" id="article-gallery-1-930872341">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-930872341" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1763267212">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Most recently, it was reported that the game had switched hands to Aspyr's parent company, Saber Interactive, and the studio then confirmed in a report in 2024 that the
     <em>
      KOTOR Remake
     </em>
     is still in active development.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="players-have-been-waiting-for-years-for-news">
  Players Have Been Waiting For Years For News
 </h3>
 <p>
  The report that the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  is still in development was the first news about the game fans had in years, and it was the last anyone had heard about it. That the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  is still in development at Saber Interactive is a good sign, but it is frustrating that there haven't been any official announcements made about its progress, and fans instead have to closely follow industry movements to get any sort of insight about it. The
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  's development cycle means that it's likely still in the early stages of development, with any significant news still likely at least a year away.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-kotor-remake-39-s-future-is-impossible-to-predict">
  The KOTOR Remake's Future is Impossible to Predict
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1563267313" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1563267313" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1563267313" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1563267313" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1563267313-img" id="article-gallery-2-1563267313">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1563267313" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-505653270">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There likely won't be a significant update for the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  for a while yet. For many fans, though, the fact that it's still happening is good news.
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  is considered by many to be one of the greatest RPGs and
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  games ever made, with some of the most iconic and compelling characters, stories, and settings in
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  . Seeing it come to life in a modern engine would be a dream come true for many. At the same time, some are also wary of their most beloved game and characters being mishandled.
 </p>
 <p>
  The lack of news about the
  <em>
   KOTOR Remake
  </em>
  's development hopefully indicates that Saber Interactive is giving the project the time and care it deserves to give fans the experience they're expecting. In the meantime, there's no way of knowing how the remake may take shape until fans see more of the game, and 2025 may be fairly silent still regarding any news or updates.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Hitman Knows Best!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-hitman-knows-best/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player eliminates an entire squad and more wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Complete - How to Level Up Quickly</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-how-level-up-quickly/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Farm Experience
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Tips for Leveling Up Fast
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Amenities
       </li>
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Giving Snacks
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Animal Requests Tips
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        What Should You Give?
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlocking more animals requires you to raise your Camp Manager Level in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Complete
   </em>
  </strong>
  . By level 76, you should have every animal in-game except for the animals locked to Villager Maps. Leveling up gets trickier as your level grows, so you'll want to be consistent with requests and speak to visitors at your campsite/cabin to farm as many friendship points as you can. Another motivator for leveling is its perks, as it's a surefire way to obtain Leaf Tokens and expand your inventory space.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-farm-experience">
  How to Farm Experience
 </h2>
 <h3 id="tips-for-leveling-up-fast">
  Tips for Leveling Up Fast
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="animal crossing pocket camp complete friendship level" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-friendship-level.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When you speak to an animal that appears on the map, you'll gain +2 friendship points. Animals that appear will always have
  <strong>
   requests
  </strong>
  for you to complete. Completing these, speaking to animals, giving gifts, and changing their outfits will all give experience to the respective animal's friendship level.
  <strong>
   When an animal levels, you gain experience towards your Camp Manager level
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Animals won't stay on the map forever. Every three hours, they'll swap out with another animal. When this happens, you'll also have new requests. Be sure to speak with everyone before the next three hours.
 </p>
 <p>
  If you have an animal at your campsite/cabin, then they'll stay there until you kick them out. If you warp to your campsite/cabin during the three-hour cycle, you'll receive
  <strong>
   a list of visiting animals that want to speak with you
  </strong>
  . This is an opportunity to farm some more friendship points. Choosing "Tell me a story!" will sometimes prompt you to select furniture/clothing as a gift for another animal. Each animal has their own style, but you'll still receive +6 friendship points even if they don't like the gift.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     It's important to know that friendship points can only be earned if you're
     <strong>
      selecting the dialogue options in red
     </strong>
     . For example, choosing "Change outfit!" when it's highlighted will give you +2 points. If you speak to the animal again, you'll notice "Change outfit!" will be written in regular text. This means you can't get friendship points by choosing the same option twice in a row.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="amenities">
  Amenities
 </h3>
 <p>
  You can also earn friendship points from multiple animals at once by constructing
  <strong>
   amenities
  </strong>
  . Each amenity has its own type, and if an animal's type matches the amenity, they'll gain more experience over those that do not. The animals that are chosen are randomized, but if there's someone you're trying to level, you should make sure they're at your campsite before the amenity finishes construction.
 </p>
 <p>
  Amenities can take days to craft, however, but once you have one on your campsite, you can level it up with Bells and materials to keep earning friendship points. When an amenity is at level 4, you can upgrade it to level 5/max level. Doing so will put it under construction for 3-4 days, so keep this in mind.
 </p>
 <h3 id="giving-snacks">
  Giving Snacks
 </h3>
 <p>
  Snacks are items you collect that can be given to animals ("Have a snack!" option). Each snack has its own type, so to get the most out of giving gifts, you should choose a snack that matches the animal's type. For example, a Plain Waffle is a natural-themed snack, so you'll get more points giving it to a natural-themed animal, such as Goldie, than you would a non-natural animal, such as Agnes.
 </p>
 <p>
  If you use Gulliver's Ship, you can unlock Villager Maps from
  <strong>
   golden islands
  </strong>
  . Villager Maps can then be used at Blathers's Treasure Trek to collect Bronze Treats, Silver Treats, and Gold Treats. Obtaining all souvenirs from a golden/villager island will earn you x20 Gold Treats. If you already have every Villager Map, then you can get Bronze/Silver/Gold Treats from doing Requests or completing Isles of Style. Unlike regular snacks, Bronze/Silver/Gold Treats are liked by everyone and are "generic" type. They will always give +3, +10, and +25 friendship points respectively.
 </p>
 <h2 id="animal-requests-tips">
  Animal Requests Tips
 </h2>
 <h3 id="what-should-you-give">
  What Should You Give?
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="animal crossing pocket camp complete fish" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete-fish.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  You can complete requests in bulk by choosing
  <strong>
   Pete's Parcel Service
  </strong>
  . As long as you have the items, you can send them off and earn friendship points without having to speak directly to the animals themselves. Most requests require you to deliver collected items, such as fruit or bugs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Other times, you'll see a request asking for one fruit, bug, or fish. These requests allow you to choose which item to give. While it may be tempting to just give them common items, you may want to choose something of
  <strong>
   higher value
  </strong>
  . Higher-quality gifts will sometimes give you bonus rewards and extra experience. You'll also receive 1500 Bells for giving rarer items. Some recommended items to give animals:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Perfect Fruit (excluding non-local)
  </li>
  <li>
   Snow crab
  </li>
  <li>
   Splendid alfonsino
  </li>
  <li>
   Amberjack
  </li>
  <li>
   R. Brooke's birdwing
  </li>
  <li>
   Luna moth
  </li>
  <li>
   White scarab beetle
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  When an animal reaches level 10 (or 15 for some), you can accept their Special Request. This unlocks furniture that you'll need to craft in order to complete the request. Special Request furniture usually costs 9000+ bells to make along with the required materials, and 10+ hours to craft. Completing Special Requests take longer, but it's another way to earn a lot of friendship points.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Reveals New Shadow Raid Day Plans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-shadow-raid-day-january-2025-plans-ho-oh/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Shadow Raid Day on January 19 features Ho-Oh, giving players a chance at the powerful Fire-type Pokemon.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can get up to 7 free Raid Passes by spinning gyms, and they can teach Shadow Ho-Oh the move Sacred Fire.
     </li>
     <li>
      A $5 ticket boosts the Raid Pass limit to 15.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has announced a new Shadow Raid Day featuring Ho-Oh for January 19. This will be the first event of its kind held by
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  in 2025 and will give trainers a new chance to capture one of the best Fire-type Pokemon available in the augmented reality game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shadow Raids were introduced in 2023, giving
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players a new way to get those variants after defeating Team GO Rocket. Last year there was no shortage of events to keep the community engaged, such as the return of Shadow Moltres in January and Shadow Mewtwo in August. The Legendary Bird of Kanto was added in 2020, while Shadow Mewtwo was added at Pokemon GO Fest in the same year. This time players should mark their calendars, as another powerful critter is soon returning to the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shadow Ho-Oh will be featured in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  's upcoming Shadow Raid Day, which will take place on January 19 from 2 pm to 5 pm local time. During this period, the pocket monster will appear in five-star raids, with increased chances of a shiny Shadow Ho-Oh appearing in one of these battles. Players will get up to five free
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Raid Passes by spinning gyms, increasing the limit to seven. They'll also be able to use a Charged TM to teach Johto's Legendary the Charged Attack Sacred Fire, an ability with 130 power in trainer battles, and 120 power in raids and gyms.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-brings-ho-oh-back-for-upcoming-shadow-raid-day">
  Pokemon GO Brings Ho-Oh Back for Upcoming Shadow Raid Day
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-797927206" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-797927206" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-797927206" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-797927206" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-797927206-img" id="article-gallery-1-797927206">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-797927206" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-306139939">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   When: Sunday, January 19, 2025, from 2 pm to 5 pm local time
  </li>
  <li>
   Featured Pokemon: Shadow Oh-Oh
  </li>
  <li>
   Using Charged TM will teach it Charged Attack Sacred Fire
  </li>
  <li>
   A new $5 ticket and a $4.99 Ultra Ticket Box will be available
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  To boost players' progress during Ho-Oh's Shadow Raid Day, Niantic will make available a $5 ticket that increases the limit of Raid Passes obtained from gyms to 15. The chances of obtaining Rare Candy XL will be higher, making it a good time to farm this essential
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  item for level 40 monsters. Purchasing the ticket will also give 50% more XP and 2x more Stardust from raid battles, with all benefits available until 10 pm local time on January 19. The Pokemon GO Web Store will sell an Ultra Ticket Box for $4.99 with an event ticket and a bonus Premium Battle Pass.
 </p>
 <p>
  The year has only begun, but the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  calendar already has several activities to keep the community engaged. Community Day featuring Sprigatito took place on January 5, and until January 7 players can catch Fidough, one of the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  debuts in 2025. The community is still waiting for details of other anticipated events, including the Community Day Classic (January 25) and the Lunar New Year event, which will run from January 29 to February 2.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
