<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Rebirth Of Souls: 8 Season Pass Character Predictions</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/bleach-rebirth-of-souls-season-pass-character-predictions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Lille Barro could be a slow but strong ranged combatant in the game with devastating sniping skills.
     </li>
     <li>
      Giselle's ability to create zombies could result in unique gameplay mechanics like puppet characters from Naruto Storm games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Bambietta might be included as a lethal zoner due to her ability to create dangerous explosives with her Reishi.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Ever since the game was first announced,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Bleach
   </strong>
  </em>
  fans have been wondering who exactly will be included in the roster of the new game,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bleach: Rebirth of Souls
   </em>
  </strong>
  , considering the sheer amount of characters featured in the original series. With the latest mechanics trailer also came confirmation that the season pass will be entirely focused on Thousand-Year Blood War combatants, referring to the final arc of the series.
 </p>
 <p>
  Considering these characters would likely be released around the same time as Cour 4 of the TYBW anime, it makes sense that individuals from this particular saga of the story would be the ones focused on in order to be a part of the hype, but who exactly could make the cut? Not every Quincy and Soul Reaper from the final arc will be able to join in the action considering there are only four spots up for grabs, so it's time to see who the most likely candidates are, and what they could potentially bring to the table.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="lille-barro">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Lille Barro
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="lille-barro-39-s-opponents-would-have-a-tricky-time-getting-past-his-expert-sniping-skills">
  Lille Barro's Opponents Would Have A Tricky Time Getting Past His Expert Sniping Skills
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1141115857" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1141115857" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1141115857" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1141115857" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1141115857-img" id="article-gallery-1-1141115857">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1141115857" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1173513770">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Lille Barro, if he was brought into the game as DLC, would be one, if not the very best ranged combatant in the game. Considering the devastating power of his sniper rifle, and how he is able to always hit his mark thanks to his Schrift ability, it could end up making Lille Barro a slow but strong character who can dish out tons of damage, while also taking a little while to set up his own attacks, which would help balance him out a little.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the same time, Lille also has quite a few forms that he could cycle through in a match, including his 'Messenger of God' transformation, where he is capable of firing enormous rays of light towards anyone who tries to mock him or his god. Lille proved to be a real problem for the Soul Reapers during the final few chapters of the story, so if
  <em>
   Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  is aiming to have all the very strongest members of the cast included, Lille Barro needs to be there.
 </p>
 <h2 id="giselle-gewelle">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Giselle Gewelle
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="giselle-39-s-ability-to-create-zombies-could-result-in-a-pretty-unique-and-creative-fighting-style">
  Giselle's Ability To Create Zombies Could Result In A Pretty Unique And Creative Fighting Style
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-88690843" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-88690843" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-88690843" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-88690843" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-88690843-img" id="article-gallery-2-88690843">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-88690843" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1030457608">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though Giselle isn't exactly a hand-to-hand fighter in the traditional sense, their true power lies in their Schrift, The Zombie, which allows them to turn people into submissive zombies after spilling some blood onto them. Considering Giselle was able to create an entire army of zombies in the story in barely any time at all, this could open up some interesting gameplay mechanics. For example, Giselle could call in zombies from off-screen to attack them, or they could even summon them and order them around the stage, similar to puppet characters from the
  <em>
   Naruto Storm
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <p>
  If she were able to control her subordinates, this would make her a kind of glass cannon who can throw out plenty of damage, while also being extremely vulnerable to it if the enemy manages to close the gap.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bambietta-basterbine">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Bambietta Basterbine
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bambietta-39-s-reishi-bombs-could-make-her-a-lethal-zoner">
  Bambietta's Reishi Bombs Could Make Her A Lethal Zoner
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-66081277" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-66081277" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-66081277" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-66081277" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-66081277-img" id="article-gallery-3-66081277">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-66081277" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1780561238">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite only getting a brief amount of screen time in the show compared to the other Sternritter, at least in her human form, that is, Bambietta still remains a fan-favorite of the group thanks to her stylish design and infectious charisma. This would already support a case for her being included as DLC later down the line, but she would also suit the game perfectly due to her Schrift, the Explode.
 </p>
 <p>
  Simply put, Bambietta can create all kinds of dangerous explosives with her own Reishi, which would make her a formidable zoner who could excel at keeping her opponents at bay while blasting them with a barrage of bombs from afar. Including her zombie skin would also be a nice extra addition for fans who have read or watched the final arc in the series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="retsu-unohana">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Retsu Unohana
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="unohana-39-s-deadly-kenpachi-form-would-be-a-ton-of-fun-to-play-as">
  Unohana's Deadly Kenpachi Form Would Be A Ton Of Fun To Play As
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-718308686" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-718308686" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-718308686" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-718308686" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-718308686-img" id="article-gallery-4-718308686">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-718308686" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-773708130">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This is specifically referring to Unohana as she appears in the final arc after having revealed her true identity as a Kenpachi. The
  <em>
   Rebirth of Souls
  </em>
  roster may already be stacked full of skilled swordsmen and women, but it simply wouldn't be complete without Unohana, the most ruthless killer in all the Soul Society.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unohana's incredible mobility and explosive attacks would make her an absolute blast to play as, especially when activating her Bankai, Minazuki, which allows her to manipulate blood at will. Rather than giving Unohana this iteration as a power-up mid-game, it would be more enjoyable to start off in her sinister Kenpachi mode, before then becoming more sadistic and bloodthirsty as the match goes on.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bazz-b">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Bazz-B
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bazz-gets-a-lot-of-time-to-shine-in-the-final-arc-and-as-so-is-more-than-deserving-of-a-character-slot">
  Bazz Gets A Lot Of Time To Shine In The Final Arc, And As So, Is More Than Deserving Of A Character Slot
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1009136440" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1009136440" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1009136440" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1009136440" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1009136440-img" id="article-gallery-5-1009136440">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1009136440" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1057170038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bazz-B, the loudmouthed and hot-headed Sternritter of the bunch, goes through quite an ordeal during the final arc. After managing to hold his own against Hitsugaya, Bazz then faces off against a few other Soul Reapers, before finally turning on his friend, Haschwalt, whose stubborn loyalty to Yhwach drives a wedge between the two longtime friends. Needless to say, he's a key player in the last saga of the story, so it only seems right that he would be included here, especially given how incredible his unique abilities would look in-game.
 </p>
 <p>
  If Bazz-B were made to be a little slower than the other fighters, it would help make his Burner Finger attacks feel even more destructive if they land. Seeing him whip out his ultimate technique, Burning Full Fingers, with the gorgeous cell-shaded art style in place would be a real feast for the eyes, and just one of his many attacks that would be a ton of fun to use in the middle of a match.
 </p>
 <h2 id="askin-nakk-le-var">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Askin Nakk Le Var
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="askin-39-s-death-dealing-ability-would-make-him-a-nightmare-to-face-for-the-opponent">
  Askin's Death Dealing Ability Would Make Him A Nightmare To Face For The Opponent
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-831741965" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-831741965" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-831741965" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-831741965" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-831741965-img" id="article-gallery-6-831741965">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-831741965" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-113674168">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Askin may be the most carefree and childish of the Sternritter, but there's a reason he was appointed as a member of the Schutzstaffel, and that's because he can obliterate his enemies in little to no time when he starts taking a fight seriously. The developers could play around with these two sides of Askin in the game, potentially making him appear more serious and determined the longer a battle goes on, especially once he starts assuming his Hasshein form.
 </p>
 <p>
  Askin wouldn't be a complete character though without his Death Dealing ability, which could see him manipulating his opponent's health, just like poison. Additionally, his Gift Bad power would undoubtedly be used as an AOE debuff, considering that's essentially how it works in the series, and who could forget his Gift Balls, which would be a handy projectile for him to use when trying to keep a safe distance.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ichibei-hyosube">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Ichibei Hyosube
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-quirky-but-formidable-member-of-squad-0-could-end-up-being-a-very-experimental-character-with-his-ink-powers">
  The Quirky But Formidable Member Of Squad 0 Could End Up Being A Very Experimental Character With His Ink Powers
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1134958493" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1134958493" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1134958493" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1134958493" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1134958493-img" id="article-gallery-7-1134958493">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1134958493" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1152613754">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though all of Squad 0 have something unique they can bring to the table if introduced as DLC characters, Ichibei is by far the most recognizable, and arguably powerful, of the lot. Since Ichibei's whole gimmick is that he can throw black ink onto his opponents to give him an edge in battle, this would become a key gameplay mechanic that could see Ichibei become stronger or unlock extra moves the more that he manages to spill.
 </p>
 <p>
  While he obviously wouldn't be able to erase words as he can in the original story, he could possibly cause a slow effect on the opponent instead, as he does with Yhwach after making his arm twice as heavy. This is a character who the developers could take a lot of creative liberties with, and if Ichibei does end up making it, there's no doubt he will be one of the most experimental members of the cast.
 </p>
 <h2 id="yhwach">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Yhwach
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-quincy-king-has-several-powerful-forms-he-can-cycle-through-during-a-match">
  The Quincy King Has Several Powerful Forms He Can Cycle Through During A Match
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1491262133" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1491262133" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1491262133" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1491262133" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1491262133-img" id="article-gallery-8-1491262133">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1491262133" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-3960490">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It seems more than likely Yhwach, the main villain of the final arc in the series, will be stepping into the roster considering how popular he is among the fanbase, alongside his relevance to the overall story. Yhwach possesses plenty of unique abilities that he could release throughout a match, including The Almighty, which allows him to see into the future, potentially allowing him to teleport around a stage or even to parry an opponent's oncoming attack.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, there's also his Soul King form, where he acquires an immense surge of power and a black mask full of eyes. Though this form might seem a little too strong to be included, considering that Aizen has already been shown with his Hogyoku modes, there's no reason for the developers to hold back with Yhwach either, especially since it would allow these two specifically to have some truly epic battles in-game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gears of War: E-Day Should Prioritize One Type of Halo Crossover, if Any</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/gears-war-e-day-halo-crossover-pvp-new-weapons-equipment/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Gears of War
   </strong>
  </em>
  franchise is no stranger to the world of pop-culture crossovers. Dom and Marcus made their first cross-franchise journey back in 2010 with a little trip to
  <em>
   Lost Planet 2
  </em>
  's icy E.D.N. III. Years later,
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  's Armadillo appeared in the Xbox One version of
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  . General Raam appeared as a fighter in
  <em>
   Killer Instinct
  </em>
  Season 3. And Marcus and Kait showed up as skins in both
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fall Guys
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While most of
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  's crossovers have occurred on foreign soil, the franchise has hosted a few collaborations of its own, such as
  <em>
   Terminator: Dark Fate
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  . It's currently unclear if the upcoming
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  is going to add any more crossovers to the franchise's slowly growing catalog, but if it does, and if
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  rears its head again, the crossover should prioritize one type of content above all else.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="gears-of-war-e-day-should-go-above-and-beyond-with-any-halo-crossovers">
  Gears of War: E-Day Should Go Above and Beyond With Any Halo Crossovers
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-600860786" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-600860786" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-600860786" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-600860786" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-600860786-img" id="article-gallery-1-600860786">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-600860786" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1140164989">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="gears-of-war-e-day-should-continue-what-gears-5-started">
  Gears of War: E-Day Should Continue What Gears 5 Started
 </h3>
 <p>
  A month before its September 2019 launch,
  <em>
   Gears 5
  </em>
  announced that those who purchased the Ultimate Edition of the game (and those subscribed to Xbox Game Pass Ultimate) would receive DLC inspired by
  <em>
   Halo: Reach
  </em>
  , a beloved entry that released almost a decade prior. This DLC pack contained two new playable characters, modeled after Spartans Emile-A239 and Kat-B320, both of whom were voiced by their original
  <em>
   Halo: Reach
  </em>
  actors.
 </p>
 <p>
  Along with unique voice lines,
  <em>
   Gears 5
  </em>
  's Kat and Emile came with unique ultimate abilities based on their
  <em>
   Halo: Reach
  </em>
  in-game equipment. Emile could deploy a Drop Shield to protect allies, while Kat could use a Hologram to distract enemies. This crossover DLC also came with a handful of themed cosmetics, such as weapon skins and a Noble Team-inspired banner.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-gears-of-war-e-day-x-halo-crossover-should-add-new-pvp-content">
  A Gears of War: E-Day x Halo Crossover Should Add New PvP Content
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Gears 5
  </em>
  's
  <em>
   Halo: Reach
  </em>
  crossover DLC was a really great collaboration, adding a decent amount of content to both the game's PvP and Horde modes. But
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  could go even further with its
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  crossover content, providing it might have some after release.
 </p>
 <p>
  For a start, a hypothetical
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  x
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  crossover should add more characters to the game's PvP and Horde modes, bringing iconic
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  heroes like the Master Chief and the Arbiter to the
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  franchise. This crossover should then bring a small arsenal of
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  -themed weapons to the game. While some weapons might need tweaking to fit
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  's particular brand of cover-based third-person shooting, it would be great to see
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  's Energy Sword, Gravity Hammer, Needler, Battle Rifle, Magnum, and more come to
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  , even if it was only for a limited-time event.
 </p>
 <p>
  Those weapons could even be accompanied by some iconic
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  equipment, again, tweaked slightly to fit with
  <em>
   Gears
  </em>
  ' multiplayer formula. Plasma grenades, Active Camo, Bubble Shields, and Deployable Covers could all work surprisingly well in
  <em>
   Gears of War
  </em>
  . Of course, none of this theoretical gameplay-affecting crossover content should come to
  <em>
   Gears of War: E-Day
  </em>
  's story mode, but it would be fun to see it in multiplayer and PvE modes like Horde, if the mode is featured in the prequel.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur's Gate 3: How to Romance Shadowheart</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-shadowheart-how-romance-guide-act-1-2-3-approval-selune-shar-bg3/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Baldur's Gate 3: Shadowheart Romance Guide
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Shadowheart Romance in Bladur's Gate 3: What to Avoid
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Shadowheart
  </strong>
  is a possible companion in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  , and players can pursue a
  <strong>
   romantic relationship
  </strong>
  with her. To do this, a fan needs to increase Shadowheart's opinion of their character by taking certain actions. This guide is here to provide details on those actions, and it will help players learn
  <strong>
   how to
  </strong>
  <strong>
   romance Shadowheart in
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
   .
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  To note, explaining the
  <strong>
   path to romancing Shadowheart
  </strong>
  requires delving into the territory of spoilers, particularly when looking toward
  <strong>
   Act 2
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   Act 3
  </strong>
  . As such, fans that are attempting to avoid spoilers, especially those connected to Shadowheart's companion quest, may want to stop reading after the
  <strong>
   Act 1
  </strong>
  section that is below and attempt to maintain the relationship without further guidance.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated January 17, 2025, by Christopher Norman Worcester:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   As we enter the early months of 2025, it is clear that Baldur's Gate 3 will maintain its incredibly well-deserved level of popularity. This guide focuses on just one of the many reasons for the game's success:
   <strong>
    romancing Shadowheart
   </strong>
   . As one of the game's most popular characters, pursuing a
   <strong>
    romantic relationship with Shadowheart
   </strong>
   remains a very popular topic. In this update, we'll ensure that our
   <strong>
    Shadowheart romance guide for Act 1, Act 2,
   </strong>
   and
   <strong>
    Act 3 in BG3
   </strong>
   is up-to-date, and presented in the best way possible. To that end, we will also be adding a new video guide for those players who prefer that medium.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3-shadowheart-romance-guide">
  Baldur's Gate 3: Shadowheart Romance Guide
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Baldur's Gate 3 Shadowheart toasting camp cutscene" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/09/baldur-s-gate-3-shadowheart-toasting-camp-cutscene.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As previously noted, players that want to develop a
  <strong>
   romance with Shadowheart in
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  must take actions of which she approves. Here is a list of the types of actions that align with her interests, and fans should pursue them whenever it is possible to do so:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Attempt to resolve situations without violence, using Deception and Persuasion when opportunities arise.
  </li>
  <li>
   Show kindness to animals, children, and the oppressed.
  </li>
  <li>
   Respect privacy, allowing Shadowheart to offer information in her own time rather than pressing hard for it.
  </li>
  <li>
   Pass Insight and Religions checks.
  </li>
  <li>
   Agree with Shadowheart and disagree with Lae'zel.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A player that follows these general guidelines should find that Shadowheart's
  <strong>
   approval
  </strong>
  of their character will quickly become
  <strong>
   High
  </strong>
  , at which point they will be able to start pursuing a romantic relationship. Fans can check their approval rating with Shadowheart at any time by looking to her character sheet, and they should take these actions to see the romance unfold:
 </p>
 <h3 id="shadowheart-romance-act-1">
  Shadowheart Romance Act 1:
 </h3>
 <p>
  Players that want to know
  <strong>
   how to
  </strong>
  <strong>
   romance Shadowheart during Act 1
  </strong>
  should look for the following dialogue option when
  <strong>
   speaking with her in camp
  </strong>
  : "I can't help but feel like you and I might have missed a chance to connect. Truly connect." This option should appear upon reaching High approval with the Cleric, even if that happens prior to rescuing Halsin in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , and players should see an option to connect with Shadowheart the next time that they interact with their
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="545209" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/08/bg3-bedroll.png"/>
   Bedroll
  </span>
  in camp.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="bg3 shadowheart romance guide" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bg3-shadowheart-swim.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="shadowheart-romance-act-2">
  Shadowheart Romance Act 2
 </h3>
 <p>
  The game's second act features some important moments for Shadowheart, and the way that a player chooses to approach them will affect how the romantic relationship evolves. More specifically, fans can take actions within
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's Gauntlet of Shar that will push Shadowheart toward or away from her chosen deity, and here are details on how that is done:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Selune Route
   </strong>
   : Do not pray to the Statue of Shar. Do not kill the Nightsong.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Shar Route:
   </strong>
   Pray to the Statue of Shar. Kill the Nightsong.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players that pursue the
  <strong>
   Selune route
  </strong>
  should speak with Shadowheart after exiting the Mausoleum and indicate that she is "not alone." These fans should then wait for Shadowheart to "change her look," tell her that they "love it" during a conversion in camp, indicate that they want to talk about their relationship, and then ask for a
  <strong>
   kiss
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Fans that have instead opted for the
  <strong>
   Shar route
  </strong>
  must indicate that it is time to "feast" during a cutscene that centers around a Statue of Selune. This cutscene can seemingly occur when performing a Long Rest after agreeing to make "sand castles" with Shadowheart, and
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  players may need to rest several times before it triggers.
 </p>
 <h3 id="shadowheart-romance-act-3">
  Shadowheart Romance Act 3
 </h3>
 <p>
  Players that have led Shadowheart down the
  <strong>
   Selune
  </strong>
  path will have one last opportunity for
  <strong>
   romance in Act 3
  </strong>
  . This opportunity will manifest as a late night
  <strong>
   swim
  </strong>
  , and players should receive an invitation to join Shadowheart simply by maintaining high approval in the opening hours of this final act.
 </p>
 <h2 id="shadowheart-romance-in-bladur-39-s-gate-3-what-to-avoid">
  Shadowheart Romance in Bladur's Gate 3: What to Avoid
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="wholesome shadowheart interaction in Baldur's Gate 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/untitled-design-47.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you have established a
  <strong>
   romantic relationship with Shadowheart in
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  , it is possible to maintain it through
  <strong>
   Act 1
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Act 2
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Act 3
  </strong>
  . However, Shadowheart can be slightly unpredictable in certain situations. If you want to stay with Shadowheart throughout the game, avoid these situations:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Multiple Relationships:
   </strong>
   Shadowheart may claim she's open-minded, but she will be quick to leave you if you spread yourself too thin for too long. Shadowheart will confront you, and even leave the relationship, if she feels you are growing too close to other companions. She is actually remarkably level-headed about it.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Maintain Her Quests:
   </strong>
   If you
   <strong>
    romance Shadowheart in Act I
   </strong>
   , then forget to continue her storyline, Shadowheart could go so far as to permanently leave your party. As obvious as it sounds, if you plan on sticking with a
   <strong>
    Shadowheart romance through Act 3,
   </strong>
   make sure to complete her quest as early as you can. This will help maintain her High approval rating throughout Act 2.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_24">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <strong>
      Shadowheart
     </strong>
     will actually be OK with you romancing the
     <strong>
      Drow Twins
     </strong>
     in Act 3, as long you
     <strong>
      ask her to join
     </strong>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Rules on TikTok Ban</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/tiktok-ban-upheld-supreme-court/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Supreme Court has confirmed that TikTok will be banned on January 19, 2025.
     </li>
     <li>
      The only way the ban can be avoided is if TikTok sells to a U.S. owner.
     </li>
     <li>
      Rednote, a TikTok clone, has seen a massive surge in downloads.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Supreme Court has rejected an appeal filed by
  <strong>
   TikTok
  </strong>
  over its proposed ban, letting the restriction go into effect on January 19, 2025. Parent company ByteDance has faced countless challenges since the proposed ban was first announced, taking the case up through several court levels, but its efforts have been in vain. Unless TikTok sells to a U.S. owner, companies could face legal consequences for supporting or distributing the app in the country starting this week.
 </p>
 <p>
  Congress first voted to ban TikTok in March 2024, with several states suing the app over child privacy concerns soon after. The company appealed the decision, claiming the ban violated the First Amendment, and the case eventually worked its way up to the Supreme Court. Now, just days before the restriction is set to take effect, the Supreme Court has agreed with previous rulings.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Supreme Court announced its unanimous decision on January 17, saying TikTok's "susceptibility to foreign adversary control" makes it too big of a security risk to justify its value as a free speech platform. According to the court, it's not strictly the app's data collection that makes it a threat, but rather the fact it's subject to Chinese law that could give the Chinese government access to said data. Many companies today collect information on their users, and security issues are common —
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2's
  </em>
  developer confirmed a data breach as recently as January 6 — but the Supreme Court decision states TikTok's case is unique. On top of collecting so much data on its users, the app is legally required to surrender it to Chinese authorities upon request, which the court sees as a potential threat to national security.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="supreme-court-upholds-january-19-ban-on-tiktok">
  Supreme Court Upholds January 19 Ban on TikTok
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2105430734" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2105430734" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2105430734" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2105430734" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2105430734-img" id="article-gallery-1-2105430734">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2105430734" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1186339616">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the Supreme Court's decision is a landmark one, it's not necessarily a surprise. Many users saw this coming, causing downloads of TikTok clone Rednote to skyrocket in the U.S. Interestingly, Rednote is also a Chinese-owned app, but the ban doesn't name it or its parent company, so it may escape legal action, at least for the time being. Another TikTok alternative, Lemon8, is owned by ByteDance, so it may not be as lucky. Of course, the ban could also extend to Rednote if the app garners enough attention from U.S. users and regulators alike.
 </p>
 <p>
  There is still a chance that TikTok's U.S. operations could survive. President-elect Trump has reversed his stance on the app, so he may pause the ban through executive action. The company could also sell its U.S. operations to an American-owned business, although ByteDance has expressed hesitancy to do so in the past. If no such action takes place, the U.S. wouldn't be the first country to restrict the app. In late 2024, Australia banned TikTok and other social media apps for children under 16. The incoming U.S. ban, though, would restrict it for all users, regardless of age.
 </p>
 <h2 id="">
 </h2>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Halo Element in Forza Horizon 5 So Far</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/halo-every-forza-horizon-5-crossover-warthog-event-lab-props-music/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Halo
   </strong>
  </em>
  has experienced more than its fair share of crossovers in the last two decades or so.
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  's very first cross-game collaboration came in 2005 with the release of
  <em>
   Dead or Alive 4
  </em>
  , which featured Spartan-458 as a playable fighter. From that point on, the floodgates remained open.
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  added a range of
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  skins some years later. The Arbiter appeared in
  <em>
   Killer Instinct
  </em>
  Season 3. The Xbox One version of
  <em>
   Super Bomberman R
  </em>
  included Master Chief, Arbiter, and Grunt playable characters.
  <em>
   Gears 5
  </em>
  had cameos from
  <em>
   Halo: Reach
  </em>
  's Kat and Emile. And
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Fall Guys
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Brawlhalla
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Rainbow Six Siege
  </em>
  have all added
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  -themed cosmetics in the last few years.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The vast majority of
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  's crossovers have been one-and-done, meaning that games usually only collaborate with the Sci-Fi series once. But that's not the case for
  <em>
   Forza Horzion
  </em>
  , a racing series that's dipped its toes into
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  's waters time and time again, including for the latest entry in the series,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="every-forza-horizon-5-x-halo-crossover-so-far">
  Every Forza Horizon 5 x Halo Crossover So Far
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1173438939" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1173438939" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1173438939" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1173438939" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1173438939-img" id="article-gallery-1-1173438939">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1173438939" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1098237326">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="forza-horizon-5-added-a-drivable-warthog-in-2021">
  Forza Horizon 5 Added a Drivable Warthog in 2021
 </h3>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Forza
  </em>
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  series has a long history of collaborating with
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  , with the very first instance occurring back in 2016. A month after its release,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 3
  </em>
  added a fully-drivable 2554 AMG Transport Dynamics M12S Warthog CST to the game, initially being exclusive to those who owned
  <em>
   Halo 5: Guardians
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Halo: The Master Chief Collection
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The Warthog made another appearance in
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </em>
  , where it was accompanied by an impressively themed
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  racetrack. Imitating the iconic "Warthog Run" from
  <em>
   Halo 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </em>
  's
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  track had players gunning it down a beach in a Warthog while Pelican dropships flew overhead and Jen Taylor's Cortana told them to speed up.
 </p>
 <p>
  For the third entry in a row, the Warthog cropped up again in
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  . Classes as a legendary vehicle,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  's Warthog cost 850,000 in-game credits, and quickly became one of the game's most popular off-road vehicles.
 </p>
 <h3 id="forza-horizon-5-added-over-70-halo-props-in-november-2024">
  Forza Horizon 5 Added Over 70 Halo Props in November 2024
 </h3>
 <p>
  To celebrate
  <em>
   Halo 2
  </em>
  's 20th anniversary and
  <em>
   Halo: The Master Chief Collection
  </em>
  's 10th back in November 2024,
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  added 71 individual
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  -themed props to the game's EventLab map creator. While some of these assets were brought forward from
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 4
  </em>
  's
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  racetrack, most came directly from
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  's own Forge mode.
 </p>
 <p>
  By far the biggest
  <em>
   Forza
  </em>
  x
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  crossover to date, this EventLab pack brought a bevy of iconic
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  objects to
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  . From Covenant deployable shields and drop pods, to a range of Forerunner structures and light bridges, to UNSC weapons crates, to stationary Warthogs and Pelicans, to the stone rings shown in
  <em>
   Halo Infinite
  </em>
  's memorable reveal trailer, fans were given a wealth of items that let them create the
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  racetracks of their dreams.
 </p>
 <p>
  These props were also accompanied by two new
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  -themed sky boxes, both depicting the titular array in the sky, one during the day and one during the night. A handful of
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  themes were also added to
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  's radio stations, including the
  <em>
   Halo 2: Anniversary
  </em>
  theme, the
  <em>
   Halo
  </em>
  'Gungir Mix',
  <em>
   Halo: Combat Evolved
  </em>
  's 'Installation 04', and
  <em>
   Halo 5: Guardians
  </em>
  ' 'The Trials.'
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
