<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Jones and the Great Circle Teases Update 3 Features</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-update-3-features-tease/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Update 3 for Indiana Jones and the Great Circle will fix bugs and include new graphical features, coming in February.
     </li>
     <li>
      The update will offer support for NVIDIA's latest Blackwell GPUs, improving the gameplay experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      MachineGames won its first award for the game and Disney may be interested in developing more Indiana Jones games.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
   </em>
  </strong>
  will get a new update in February, according to developer MachineGames. Despite
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  ’s amazing reception, the game had some bugs at launch, so this update will address some known glitches and more.
 </p>
 <p>
  Released in December 2024,
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  gained positive reviews, achieving an average score of 87 on OpenCritic. The game marked the return of the
  <em>
   Indiana Jones
  </em>
  franchise to video games after over a decade and was widely considered a very successful take on the character due to its gameplay and style.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, MachineGames has revealed on Steam that Update 3 for Indiana
  <em>
   Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  will be released in February. According to the developers, the update will be available for PC and Xbox, and it will fix several bugs based on feedback provided by players. Notably, the patch will fix a major bug that prevented some players from achieving 100% in the game due to problems climbing vines in Sukhothai. Update 3 will also bring new graphical features and options, and it will include support for NVIDIA’s latest Blackwell GPUs for PC. Unfortunately, the exact date for the update is still unknown, but considering it’s being teased, it’s likely that it will happen early in February.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="machinegames-teases-indiana-jones-and-the-great-circle-update-3">
  MachineGames Teases Indiana Jones and the Great Circle Update 3
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1806634522" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1806634522" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1806634522" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1806634522" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1806634522-img" id="article-gallery-1-1806634522">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1806634522" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-581320718">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since its release,
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  has been a very popular title, but it was released too late to participate in The Game Awards. Earlier this month,
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  gained its first award for the performance of Troy Baker as Indy in the 14th Annual New York Game Awards.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game was so successful that rumors indicate that Disney wants more
  <em>
   Indiana Jones
  </em>
  games, according to journalist Jez Corden. While official sales numbers for the game are yet to be disclosed, it seems that more games in the franchise may be developed in the future.
 </p>
 <p>
  In any case, it remains to be seen whether these upcoming games will be devised by MachineGames or other developers. Recent reports indicate that MachineGames may be working on several new games, but none of them has been officially announced yet. Right now, the two most popular theories include either a sequel for
  <em>
   Indiana Jones and the Great Circle
  </em>
  or maybe a new entry in the
  <em>
   Wolfenstein
  </em>
  franchise, as over six years have passed since the release of
  <em>
   Wolfenstein: Youngblood
  </em>
  , the latest entry in the universe.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: The Sims 1 and 2 Re-Releases Release Date Leaked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sims-1-2-re-release-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Sims 1 and 2 re-releases are expected to launch on Friday, January 31 at 10:00am CST.
     </li>
     <li>
      The games are only expected to release on PC.
     </li>
     <li>
      EA has yet to make the official announcement, but it has teased that the re-releases are real.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It seems as though the re-releases for
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Sims
   </em>
  </strong>
  and
  <em>
   The Sims 2
  </em>
  will both drop on Friday, January 31, if a recent leak is to be believed. The original
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  was a massive success at the time of its release, with both it and its sequel often hailed as two of the best video games ever made. Unfortunately, the evolution of PC hardware and operating systems has left the original
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  games in the dust, making it difficult to play the classics on modern rigs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Because of this, franchise fans have long called for EA to re-release the original
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  games, giving longtime fans the opportunity to take a trip down memory lane and those who may only be familiar with the newer titles the chance to see what made the classic games so special. EA recently teased that it was finally going to re-release the first two
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  games, and now a fresh leak has indicated exactly when that might be happening.
 </p>
 <p>
  According to Anadius on Twitter,
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Sims 2
  </em>
  will re-release for Windows 10 and 11 operating systems on Friday, January 31 at 10:00am CST. Pricing information for the re-releases has yet to be revealed. While fans are always cautioned to take leaks with a grain of salt, EA itself has teased that the re-releases are real, so it's just a matter if this leaked release date is accurate or not. Luckily, January 31 is only a few days away, so
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  fans will have their answers sooner rather than later.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="when-are-the-sims-1-and-2-re-releases-coming-out">
  When Are The Sims 1 and 2 Re-Releases Coming Out?
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Rumored Release Date: Friday, January 31 at 10:00am CST
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  What makes these classic
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  re-releases so exciting is that they will reportedly come with
  <em>
   all
  </em>
  the post-release expansions intact. For the original
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  , this includes Livin' Large, House Party, Hot Date, Vacation, Unleashed, Superstar, and Makin' Magic. For
  <em>
   The Sims 2
  </em>
  , the expansions include University, Nightlife, Open for Business, Pets, Seasons, Bon Voyage, FreeTime, and Apartment Life. These
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  expansions add significant new gameplay features and should ensure that the re-releases offer significant value, no matter how much they may cost.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-690416530" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-690416530" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-690416530" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-690416530" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-690416530-img" id="article-gallery-1-690416530">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-690416530" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1894187345">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  So far,
  <em>
   The Sims 1
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Sims 2
  </em>
  re-releases are only expected to launch on PC. The console versions of
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Sims 2
  </em>
  were significantly different from their PC counterparts, but perhaps those versions of the game could get re-releases at some point down the line as well. Based on the reaction to the leaks, there's clearly an appetite for classic
  <em>
   Sims
  </em>
  games to make a comeback, so here's hoping
  <em>
   The Sims
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Sims 2
  </em>
  re-releases are just the tip of the iceberg.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Orion Can't Afford to Walk Back Cyberpunk 2077's Smaller Post-Launch Changes</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cyberpunk-2077-project-orion-smaller-changes-customization-details-launch/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Few games in recent history have inspired as much fervent discussion as
  <strong>
   <em>
    Cyberpunk 2077
   </em>
  </strong>
  . First revealed back in 2013, its extensive and prolonged marketing period was characterized by seemingly endless hype, with CD Projekt Red coasting off the good will engendered by
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  , which elevated its reputation to astronomical heights. But
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  wound up communicating a terrible reality: no studio's reputation can be impeccable forever.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In the case of CD Projekt Red, its identity was marred by the historically disastrous launch of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  in late 2020. To say that the game failed to live up to its lofty expectations would be a massive understatement: it was virtually unplayable on last-gen consoles, and just about every version of the game was rife with bugs and performance issues, not to mention the lack of many core features. Five years and a handful of lawsuits later, CD Projekt Red has managed to scrape back much of the strong reputation that was lost in the course of the
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  rollout thanks to numerous patches, free content drops, and the well-received
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  DLC. And with a sequel, codenamed
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , on the way, the studio ought to learn valuable lessons from its recent past, and not just on the macro scale.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="project-orion-needs-to-heed-cyberpunk-2077-39-s-smaller-post-launch-changes">
  Project Orion Needs to Heed Cyberpunk 2077's Smaller Post-Launch Changes
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1689697326" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1689697326" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1689697326" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1689697326" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1689697326-img" id="article-gallery-1-1689697326">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1689697326" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-851326547">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="cyberpunk-2077-39-s-redemption-is-resultant-from-more-than-just-the-big-ticket-items">
  Cyberpunk 2077's Redemption Is Resultant from More Than Just the Big-Ticket Items
 </h3>
 <p>
  Naturally, huge overhauls to the
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  experience, like the massive technical improvements and ambitious
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  expansion, get the most attention from both audiences and media outlets. It's true that these significant and obvious changes were instrumental in making
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  the well-received game that it is today, but they are held up by countless smaller updates. Taken cumulatively, these smaller changes are just as important as the headline-defining overhauls.
 </p>
 <p>
  Quality-of-life features like being able to purchase vehicles from an in-game terminal rather than driving to their locations manually, or fun, frivolous details like the option to customize a car's color, have gone a long way toward making
  <em>
   Cyberpunk
  </em>
  a better game. It's far more feature-rich now, with a more reactive and interactive world for players to get stuck into. Here are just a few of the best, potentially overlooked changes to
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  since its launch:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The option to listen to the radio while on-foot
  </li>
  <li>
   More in-depth NPC background conversations
  </li>
  <li>
   Greater crowd density
  </li>
  <li>
   The option to invite romanceable NPCs to V's apartment
  </li>
  <li>
   The Night City Metro System
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved character models, especially Johnny Silverhand
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="project-orion-needs-to-learn-from-cyberpunk-2077-39-s-approach-to-nuanced-features-and-systems">
  Project Orion Needs To Learn from Cyberpunk 2077's Approach to Nuanced Features and Systems
 </h3>
 <p>
  It would definitely be surprising if some or all of the aforementioned features were absent in
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  . For example, if the sequel lacks the option to customize car colors, that would be a significant, easily avoidable step backward. In other words, it's highly likely that
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  will carry such minor features over from its predecessor. But it would behoove CD Projekt Red to remember why such features are so important in the first place.
 </p>
 <p>
  Something like being able to eavesdrop on interesting, but ultimately inconsequential, Night City NPC dialog isn't exactly a selling point of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  , but it makes the world feel far more alive and believable. The same can be said for something like the Metro System, even if it doesn't have any function beyond what the already-existing fast travel options offer. These post-launch features represent a strong attention to detail, which is essential for creating a vivid and alluring game world. Plus, many of these smaller features, like the option to change car color or listen to the radio on-the-go, simply make the game more fun.
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  shouldn't make audiences wait for similar inclusions.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Ammo In Sniper Elite Resistance</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/how-to-get-refill-ammo-bullets-in-sniper-elite-resistance/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get More Ammo in Sniper Elite Resistance
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   <strong>
    Sniper Elite Resistance
   </strong>
  </em>
  , players will be relying on their weapons more than melee combat to deal with Nazis. Each location is infested with a ton of enemies, and there are so many Nazis you can take out before running out of ammo. Ammo supply can be scarce depending on the difficulty you're playing the game at. So, here are all the ways you can resupply your ammo to avoid running out at a crucial moment.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-more-ammo-in-sniper-elite-resistance">
  How to Get More Ammo in Sniper Elite Resistance
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-326792127" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-326792127" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-326792127" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-326792127" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-326792127-img" id="article-gallery-1-326792127">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-326792127" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1208954416">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are three main ways players can restock ammo in
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  . These ammo sources should be kept in mind while you're exploring each location so you always have bullets for your preferred weapon.
 </p>
 <h3 id="ammo-boxes-amp-supply-pouches">
  Ammo Boxes &amp; Supply Pouches
 </h3>
 <p>
  Players will find
  <strong>
   ammo boxes
  </strong>
  scattered around a map that provide a particular type of ammo for a weapon. They're mainly found near major locations where you'll also encounter a lot of enemies roaming around. These provide regular, as well as, special ammo for your rifles and sidearms. You'll also have an opportunity to swap one type of ammo with another based on your requirements.
 </p>
 <p>
  On the other hand,
  <strong>
   supply pouches
  </strong>
  don't display what kind of ammo they have. Every time you loot a supply pouch, you'll get a random type of ammo. Similar to ammo boxes, players can find supply pouches both inside buildings and out in the open.
 </p>
 <h3 id="getting-ammo-by-looting-bodies">
  Getting Ammo by Looting Bodies
 </h3>
 <p>
  Whether you take out an enemy lethally or non-lethally, you'll have an opportunity to
  <strong>
   search their bodies for loot
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  . Although you're not guaranteed to always find ammo while looting bodies, there's a high chance you'll get random rounds for your weapons.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Higher difficulties will decrease the chances of ammo being found by looting bodies, and vice versa for lower difficulties.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="taking-ammo-from-found-weapons">
  Taking Ammo from Found Weapons
 </h3>
 <p>
  While exploring a location or taking out enemies, players can pick up weapons from the ground and use them temporarily. However, if you prefer using your own arsenal,
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  lets you
  <strong>
   take the ammo from a found weapon
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  After taking the ammo from a found weapon, Hawker will drop the weapon and use the ammo for his own weapons. This is also a great way to loot ammo, as the ammo will belong to the same weapon type it was looted from.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Elite Resistance Best PC Settings</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sniper-elite-resistance-best-pc-graphics-settings/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Sniper Elite Resistance
   </strong>
  </em>
  pulls players into the world of a Nazi-hunting sniper, who travels from one visually stunning vista to another. Despite the lack of upscaling features like DLSS or FSR, it surprisingly runs well on PCs with native resolution. However, the developers have added some graphics settings for players to tweak. So, we'll be showcasing the best PC settings for
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  , which will strike a nice balance between visuals and high performance.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="best-settings-for-sniper-elite-resistance-on-pc">
  Best Settings for Sniper Elite Resistance on PC
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1410722563" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1410722563" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1410722563" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1410722563" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1410722563-img" id="article-gallery-1-1410722563">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1410722563" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1507818121">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  has grouped up both the
  <strong>
   display and graphics settings
  </strong>
  into a simple, easy-to-use menu. The graphical changes also take place in real-time, so players won't have to restart the game every time they tweak a setting or two. That said, some settings do have a large impact on performance compared to others with minimal visual impact.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here are all the best PC settings for
  <em>
   Sniper Elite Resistance
  </em>
  that will balance great performance and visuals.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Setting Type
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Setting Name
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Preset
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Note
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="1" rowspan="8">
      <p>
       Display
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Display Mode
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Borderless Fullscreen
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Works just as well as Exclusive Fullscreen.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Resolution
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Native
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Vsync
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Off
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Introduces slight input lag. Best that it's turned off.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Render Scale
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100%
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Lowering it will improve performance but will make textures blurry.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Brightness
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Personal Preference
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       HDR
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       If supported
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Async Compute
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Although this is meant for weaker CPUs, turning it off can result in texture flickering. Players can turn it off later when it's working as intended to get an FPS boost.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reduce Mouse Lag
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Helps reduce latency if you're playing on a mouse and keyboard.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td colspan="1" rowspan="11">
      <p>
       Graphics
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Graphics Detail
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Custom
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       We'll tweak individual settings, so no need to set a pre-determined graphical preset.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Anti-Aliasing
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High/Ultra
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ultra looks the sharpest but introduces prominent aliasing around textures. High reduces jagged edges but textures can look blurry at certain angles. The performance difference is minimal.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shadow Detail
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Medium
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Turning shadows down to medium gives a major FPS boost while maintaining a solid shadow quality.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reflection Detail
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reflective surfaces are mostly indoors, so reflections won't be tanking your FPS that much. If they are, feel free to drop this to medium.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Draw Distance
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ultra
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This is an important setting that renders objects and characters from afar and allows you to scope out an area or get some kills before arriving there. There is an above-average performance impact, however. High preset is second best for draw distance.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Texture Detail
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4GB VRAM: Medium, 6GB VRAM: High, 8GB+ VRAM: Ultra (follow this legend to set textures according to your hardware.)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Water Detail
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       This mainly manages the water surfaces of streams and canals, which are mostly at the exterior of the play area. Turning it up won't affect performance much either.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ambient Occlusion
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Motion Blur
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Although motion blur can be a distraction,
       <em>
        Sniper Elite Resistance's
       </em>
       implementation of it is pretty decent.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Tessellation
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       On
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Improves the loot of terrain and other objects that are part of the environment with additional textures. Performance impact is minimal.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Obscurance Fields
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Off
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Although this isn't a very demanding setting, considering it adds Ray-Traced shadows, the effect is only centered around the player or other characters. When there are a lot of characters on-screen, the FPS will take a hit.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sniper Elite Resistance is a breath of fresh air when it comes to a game's optimization on launch. Most of the settings can be cranked without compromising on that 60 FPS smooth experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  The best PC settings for Sniper Elite Resistance were tested on a laptop with an
  <strong>
   i7-11800H CPU, Nvidia RTX 3070 GPU, and 32GB RAM
  </strong>
  . The average FPS was around 75-80 with 1% lows hitting 60 FPS. The game will only get better with performance patches and bug fixes down the line, so you can look forward to cranking up some settings down the line.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
