<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Snapshot Update Adds 6 New Features to the Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/minecraft-snapshot-25w02a-new-features-pig-variants-patch-notes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Minecraft Java Edition
   </em>
  </strong>
  has released snapshot 25w02a, which adds six new features to the game, including two new pig variants. This is the first
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  snapshot released in 2025, and it brings players a range of fresh features, bug fixes, and adjustments.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Snapshots allow players of Mojang's sandbox to test features before they are introduced to the game. Last year, for example,
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  reintroduced bundles with snapshot 24w33a, increasing the storage space for players on their adventures. The bundle was first tested in 2020 and had been shelved until then. Snapshot 23w11a, also released in 2024, introduced the mace, a powerful new weapon. With it, players hit enemies to inflict damage and knockback them, and if they use the mace while falling from a height, the fall damage is negated. Now, players can try out some new features to start 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  With snapshot 25w02a,
  <em>
   Minecraft Java Edition
  </em>
  players can try six new features, including two pig variants. One of them is the cold pig, a variant of the classic
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  mob that lives in colder biomes and is protected by fluffy, darker fur. The warm pig, on the other hand, can be found in biomes, such as savannahs and jungles, and its coat has a rusty-brown tone. Several general changes have been introduced, including a new crafting recipe players can find in Ruined Portals, farm animals that now spawn in Badlands, and the possibility of uploading Hardcore single-player worlds in Realms.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1515802222" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1515802222" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1515802222" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1515802222" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1515802222-img" id="article-gallery-1-1515802222">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1515802222" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-827907511">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The snapshot also includes ambient changes to make players' experience even more immersive, like leaves falling from the trees available in the game. Finally updating
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  's flowers, Mojang is introducing wildflowers, a new type that grows in birch forests, meadows, and old growth birch forests. With leaves now falling from trees, another feature is the decorative leaf litter block that makes a sound when players step on it and is found in forests, dark forests, and wooded badlands. The Pale Garden, the sandbox's most recent biome, has gained some tweaks, such as occupying a larger area, which didn't happen before.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Minecraft Java Edition
  </em>
  players can already test the features and adjustments introduced by snapshot 25w02a,
  <em>
   Bedrock Edition
  </em>
  owners are waiting for the update to drop. It's worth noting that one of the highlights is the new pigs, something that has existed in other
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  games but hasn't yet been introduced to the main title. The leaf litter blocks and wildflowers are also two interesting additions, with a high potential to further inspire the well-known creativity of
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  players.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="minecraft-snapshot-25w02a-patch-notes">
  Minecraft Snapshot 25w02a Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <p>
  <strong>
   New Features
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added new falling leaves particles to Leave blocks without particles
  </li>
  <li>
   Added cold and warm variants for the Pig
  </li>
  <li>
   Added Wildflowers block
  </li>
  <li>
   Added Leaf Litter block
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Leaves block particles
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   All Leaves blocks now have chance of spawning falling leaf particles
  </li>
  <li>
   These blocks are affected by this change:
  </li>
  <li>
   Oak Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Jungle Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Acacia Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Dark Oak Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Spruce Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Mangrove Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Birch Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Azalea Leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Flowering Azalea Leaves
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pig Variants
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   New Pig variants have been added, the variant is determined by the biome they spawn in
  </li>
  <li>
   Temperate Pig - The Pig we are all familiar with
   <ul>
    <li>
     Spawns by default where the cold and warm Pig variants do not spawn
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Cold Pig - A variant that spawns in the following biomes:
   <ul>
    <li>
     Old Growth Pine Taiga
    </li>
    <li>
     Old Growth Spruce Taiga
    </li>
    <li>
     Taiga
    </li>
    <li>
     Snowy Taiga
    </li>
    <li>
     Windswept Hills
    </li>
    <li>
     Windswept Gravelly Hills
    </li>
    <li>
     Windswept Forest
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Warm Pig - A variant that spawns in the following biomes:
   <ul>
    <li>
     Savanna
    </li>
    <li>
     Savanna Plateau
    </li>
    <li>
     Windswept Savanna
    </li>
    <li>
     Jungle
    </li>
    <li>
     Sparse Jungle
    </li>
    <li>
     Bamboo Jungle
    </li>
    <li>
     Eroded Badlands
    </li>
    <li>
     Wooded Badlands
    </li>
    <li>
     Badlands
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   When bred by a player, a baby Pig variant will not be chosen by the current biome, but instead randomly selected from one of the parents' variants
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Wildflowers
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Wildflowers are a new type of flower which grow in Birch Forests, Old Growth Birch Forests and Meadows
  </li>
  <li>
   Wildflowers can have different amounts of flowers in one block space
   <ul>
    <li>
     Up to four Wildflowers can be placed in the same block space
    </li>
    <li>
     Placing a Wildflower into an already placed Wildflowers block increases the amount of flowers
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Using Bone Meal on Wildflowers will produce more Wildflowers
  </li>
  <li>
   Wildflowers can be placed in four orientations
  </li>
  <li>
   Wildflowers can be crafted into Yellow Dye
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter is a new type of decorative block which can be found in the Forests, Dark Forests and Wooded Badlands
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter can have different amounts of leaves in one block space
  </li>
  <li>
   Up to four Leaf Litter pieces can be placed in the same block space
  </li>
  <li>
   Placing a Leaf Litter into an already placed Leaf Litter block increases the amount of leaves
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter can be placed in four orientations
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter can be created by smelting any type of Leaves block
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter can be used as fuel for smelting
  </li>
  <li>
   Leaf Litter has unique block sounds
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Changes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Lodestones have a new crafting recipe and can now be found in Ruined Portals
  </li>
  <li>
   Added new break, place, step, fall and hit sounds for Iron Blocks, Iron Bars, Iron Trapdoors, Iron Doors and Heavy Weighted Pressure Plates
  </li>
  <li>
   Zombified Piglins now need to be killed by a Player to drop the Player-specific loot
   <ul>
    <li>
     This makes them consistent with all other mobs in the game
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Chunks loaded by a portal will now be re-loaded again automatically when the world is reopened
  </li>
  <li>
   Farm animals can now spawn in Badlands
  </li>
  <li>
   Short Grass now generates slightly sparser in Meadows
  </li>
  <li>
   The volume of the narrator is now affected by the game's configured volume in the 'Voice' category
  </li>
  <li>
   Uploading a world to Realms will now enable Command Blocks by default
  </li>
  <li>
   It is now possible to upload Hardcore singleplayer worlds to Realms
  </li>
  <li>
   Bubble columns produce less particles and sounds when entities that are unaffected by them are inside them
  </li>
  <li>
   If the game detects that the last startup did not complete normally, the fullscreen option will now be reset
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Garden Awakens Changes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Pale Garden biome now occupies more space that was previously taken by Dark Forest
  </li>
  <li>
   Woodland Mansions can now generate in Pale Garden biome
  </li>
  <li>
   Pale Oak Leaves and Pale Oak Saplings have an updated map color
  </li>
  <li>
   Creakings can now be named using Name Tags
   <ul>
    <li>
     Named Creaking will persist through the day
     <ul>
      <li>
       However, it will still be torn down if stuck with a player or if it is too far from its Heart
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     Named Creakings are still resistant to all damage, and can communicate with their Hearts via particles
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Creaking Hearts correctly placed between Logs have a new dormant texture during the day
   <ul>
    <li>
     Dormant Creaking Hearts cannot spawn new Creakings and Resin
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Transition between the awake and dormant states for Creaking Hearts and transition of Eye Blossoms is now based on the fixed day time
   <ul>
    <li>
     All these behaviors are no longer affected by weather or dimension brightness
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Lodestone Changes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The Lodestone is now crafted from 1 Iron Ingot surrounded by 8 Chiseled Stone Bricks
  </li>
  <li>
   Lodestones can now be found as loot at Ruined Portals in the Overworld or Nether
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Technical Changes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The Data Pack version is now 62
  </li>
  <li>
   The Resource Pack version is now 47
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Data Pack Version 62
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Changes to commands
  </li>
  <li>
   Updated data format of Text Components
  </li>
  <li>
   structure_block in the load mode has now a new option: Strict Placement
   <ul>
    <li>
     If set to false, the blocks in the placed structure will not trigger block updates, block entity side effects, or shape updates
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   The Owner field of tamed animals is no longer restricted to referencing Players
  </li>
  <li>
   Updated data format of equipment drop chances in entity data
  </li>
  <li>
   Added data-driven registry for pig variants
  </li>
  <li>
   Added pig entity sub-predicate for matching pig variants
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Commands
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Text Components in commands such as /tellraw or /title are now specified with SNBT instead of JSON
  </li>
  <li>
   Text Style in the /scoreboard command when specifying the styled number format is also now specified with SNBT instead of JSON
  </li>
  <li>
   The behavior of setblock and fill commands have changed in how they handle block entity data:
   <ul>
    <li>
     If the block entity data is not specified, and the existing block has data, the block entity data will be preserved
    </li>
    <li>
     If the block entity data is specified, the block entity data will be set to the specified value
    </li>
    <li>
     To clear the block entity data explicitly, you must now specify the block entity data as {}
    </li>
    <li>
     The operation is now successful if either the block state changed or the block entity data changed
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   fill, clone, setblock and place template accept a new option: strict
  </li>
  <li>
   If specified, the command will place blocks as-is without triggering block updates and shape updates
  </li>
  <li>
   The replace option in the fill command is no longer terminal, and can be followed with additional options
  </li>
  <li>
   New syntax for commands to use the new strict option, and more flexible use of replace:
   <ul>
    <li>
     fill &lt;from&gt; &lt;to&gt; &lt;block&gt; keep
    </li>
    <li>
     fill &lt;from&gt; &lt;to&gt; &lt;block&gt; [replace &lt;filter&gt;]? [strict|destroy|hollow|outline]?
    </li>
    <li>
     clone [from &lt;sourceDimension&gt;]? &lt;begin&gt; &lt;end&gt; [to &lt;targetDimension&gt;]? &lt;destination&gt; [strict]? [[replace|masked|filtered &lt;filter&gt;] [force|move|normal]?]?
    </li>
    <li>
     setblock &lt;pos&gt; &lt;block&gt; [destroy|keep|replace|strict]?
    </li>
    <li>
     place template &lt;template&gt; [&lt;pos&gt; [&lt;rotation&gt; [&lt;mirror&gt; [&lt;integrity&gt; [&lt;seed&gt; [strict]?]?]?]?]?]?
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Text Component Data Format
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Text Components are no longer stored as JSON wrapped by a string
  </li>
  <li>
   The format itself is the same as before, but inlined directly into the outer structure
  </li>
  <li>
   For example, the item component minecraft:custom_name="{"text":"Renamed item"}" will become minecraft:custom_name={text:'Renamed item'}
  </li>
  <li>
   This includes Text Components passed as arguments to commands such as /tellraw or /title
   <ul>
    <li>
     For example, /tellraw @s ""text":"Hello world"" may become /tellraw @s {text:'Hello world'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Note: in the case where Text Components are embedded in NBT, no distinction exists between boolean and integer types
   <ul>
    <li>
     To pass boolean arguments to translations, you must use the string form
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   For Text Components with the nbt type and interpret set to true, Text Components will be parsed from the given NBT directly rather than converting to string and parsing as JSON
  </li>
  <li>
   The format of hover and click events has been updated
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Hover Events
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The hoverEvent field has been renamed to hover_event
  </li>
  <li>
   The legacy value field (which was parsed from a rendered text component) is no longer supported
  </li>
  <li>
   For the show_text action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     contents field has been renamed to text
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'show_text',contents:'Hello world'} becomes {action:'show_text',text:'Hello world'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   For the show_item action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The contents field has been inlined
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'show_item',contents:{id:'minecraft:stick',count:2}} becomes {action:'show_item',id:'minecraft:stick',count:2}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   If contents was specified only as an item id, it is replaced with the full format and inlined
  </li>
  <li>
   e.g. {action:'show_item',contents:'minecraft:stick'} becomes {action:'show_item',id:'minecraft:stick'}
  </li>
  <li>
   For the show_entity action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The contents field has been inlined
    </li>
    <li>
     The id field has been renamed to uuid
    </li>
    <li>
     The type field has been renamed to id
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'show_entity',contents:{id:[I;0,0,0,0],type:'minecraft:pig'}} becomes {action:'show_entity',uuid:[I;0,0,0,0],id:'minecraft:pig'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Click Events
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The clickEvent field has been renamed to click_event
  </li>
  <li>
   For the open_url action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The value field has been renamed to url
    </li>
    <li>
     The click event will no longer parse if not a valid URI with either https:// or http:// schemes, instead of simply not working
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'open_url',value:'https://minecraft.net'} becomes {action:'open_url',url:'https://minecraft.net'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   For the run_command action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The value field has been renamed to command
    </li>
    <li>
     The click event will no longer parse if the command contains disallowed characters, instead of simply not working
    </li>
    <li>
     It is no longer required that the specified command field has a / prefix
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'run_command',value:'/say Hi'} becomes {action:'run_command',command:'/say Hi'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   For the suggest_command action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The value field has been renamed to command
    </li>
    <li>
     The click event will no longer parse if the command contains disallowed characters, instead of simply not working
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'suggest_command',value:'/help'} becomes {action:'suggest_command',command:'/help'}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   For the change_page action:
   <ul>
    <li>
     The value field has been renamed to page
    </li>
    <li>
     The page value now requires a positive integer instead of a string
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. {action:'change_page',value:'1'} becomes {action:'change_page',page:1}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   The copy_to_clipboard format is unchanged
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Tags
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Block Tags
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added #replaceable_by_mushrooms - exhaustive list of all bocks that can be replaced as a mushroom is placed or grows
  </li>
  <li>
   Added #sword_instantly_mines - blocks that are instantly mined by Swords
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Item Tags
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added #book_cloning_target - item that can be crafted together with a Written Book to clone it
  </li>
  <li>
   Biome Tags
  </li>
  <li>
   Added #spawns_cold_variant_farm_animals - all biomes where cold variant of farm animals spawn
  </li>
  <li>
   Added #spawns_warm_variant_farm_animals - all biomes where warm variants of farm animals spawn
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Entity Data
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The ArmorDropChances, HandDropChances, and body_armor_drop_chance fields have been merged into a drop_chances field
   <ul>
    <li>
     Format: map between equipment slot type and chance value
     <ul>
      <li>
       Valid equipment slots: head, chest, legs, feet, mainhand, offhand, body
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   If not specified or removed, chances will be assumed as default (0.085f)
  </li>
  <li>
   e.g. drop_chances:{chest:0.1,feet:1.0}
  </li>
  <li>
   Drop chances with a default value will no longer be stored, and the drop_chances field is removed entirely if all defaults
  </li>
  <li>
   Area Effect Clouds have a new field: potion_duration_scale (float)
   <ul>
    <li>
     If not specified, defaults to 1.0
    </li>
    <li>
     The duration of the potion effect applied is scaled by this factor
    </li>
    <li>
     Area Effect Clouds created by Lingering Potions will have a scale of 0.25
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Pig Variants
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Pig variants can be data-driven by adding entries to data/&lt;namespace&gt;/pig_variant/&lt;id&gt;.json
  </li>
  <li>
   This feature is experimental
  </li>
  <li>
   Fields in file:
   <ul>
    <li>
     model - one of: normal, cold
    </li>
    <li>
     texture - texture id for this variant, resolves to assets/&lt;namespace&gt;/textures/&lt;path&gt;.png
    </li>
    <li>
     biome - single entry, list or a tag describing biomes in which this variant natually spawns
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   If not specified, this variant will only be selected if no other variant matches the current biome
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Recipes
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   crafting_transmute Recipe Type
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The result field now supports specifying a count and a components patch to apply to the result
  </li>
  <li>
   The components patch is applied to the final transmuted item
  </li>
  <li>
   The new format is an object with fields:
   <ul>
    <li>
     id - item id
    </li>
    <li>
     count - positive integer (default: 1)
    </li>
    <li>
     components - a component patch object (default: empty)
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. "result": {"id": "minecraft:stick", "count": 3, "components": {"!minecraft:damage": {}, "minecraft:enchantment_glint_override": {}}}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   The field can still be defined as before as an inline item id (e.g. "result": "minecraft:stick")
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Item Components
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   New weapon component
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   When present, the 'Item Used' statistic will be incremented for each attack with the item
  </li>
  <li>
   The specified amount of damage can be done to the item with each attack
  </li>
  <li>
   Format: object with fields:
   <ul>
    <li>
     damage_per_attack - non-negative integer (default: 1)
     <ul>
      <li>
       The amount to damage the weapon for each attack performed
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     can_disable_blocking - boolean (default: false)
     <ul>
      <li>
       If true, will disable a blocking Shield on successful attack
      </li>
      <p>
      </p>
     </ul>
    </li>
    <li>
     e.g. weapon={damage_per_attack:2}
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   New potion_duration_scale component
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   When present, for items that have the potion_contents component, the duration of the applied effects will be scaled by this factor
  </li>
  <li>
   This also applies to custom_effects in the potion_contents component, unlike the previous hardcoded scaling factor
  </li>
  <li>
   If not specified, defaults to 1.0
  </li>
  <li>
   Format: non-negative float
   <ul>
    <li>
     e.g. potion_duration_scale=0.25
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   tool Component
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added new optional field: can_destroy_blocks_in_creative (bool)
   <ul>
    <li>
     If false, players cannot break blocks while holding this tool in Creative Mode
    </li>
    <li>
     If not specified, defaults to true
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Resource Pack Version 47
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added textures for new falling leaves particles
  </li>
  <li>
   New and updated Pig textures
  </li>
  <li>
   Added textures for new Wildflowers block
  </li>
  <li>
   Added break, place, step, fall and hit sounds for Iron Blocks, Iron Bars, Iron Trapdoors, Iron Doors and Heavy Weighted Pressure Plates
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   New and updated Pig textures
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Added new textures for Pig variants:
   <ul>
    <li>
     cold_pig
    </li>
    <li>
     warm_pig
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Changed the size of pig texture
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Fixed bugs in 25w02a
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   MC-7697 - Tridents or arrows shot through lava sometimes don't catch fire
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-55800 - Successful "/fill air destroy" commands give error message and return 0 for result/success
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-56653 - Zombified Piglins drop XP and rare drops if killed by anything while in angered state
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-90212 - You cannot hang on to climbable blocks while gliding with elytra
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-93185 - The exit portal in the end generates at highest block at 0 0 which can make it generate incomplete
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-97244 - The "minecraft:enchant.thorns.hit" sound event doesn't play when non-player entities are damaged by the thorns enchantment
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-113878 - Attribute modifiers description for chest is misleading / "When on body" instead of "When on chest"
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-118053 - Wolves with the Owner of a non-player are spawned sitting
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-118092 - Crafting recipe unlock toast says "New Recipes Unlocked!" even when only one recipe was unlocked
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-118470 - Narrator plays at full volume when volume is off
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-128079 - Statistic for using shears doesn't increase when mining certain blocks
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-135192 - Boats are immediately sunken if there is a string on the surface of the water
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-141297 - You cannot set lit state of redstone torches using setblock, debug stick and BlockStateTag, to be to opposite of the situation it would be in
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-165421 - Bubble columns have the opposite effect on tridents and wind charges
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-167125 - Rounding error on fall damage
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-183329 - Nether portal teleport overlay does not show up if the player has the nausea effect
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-183623 - Hardcore worlds in the world menu have a comma after the red exclamation mark
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-184681 - Customized worlds still say "Buffet world customization" since 20w21a
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-202226 - /recipe give or take for one recipe says "recipes"
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-220672 - Inconsistent pluralization in customize world preset heading source string
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-222876 - "Buffet world customization" is incorrectly capitalized
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-226772 - Shulker box opening / closing subtitle shows "Shulker"
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-241951 - Player momentum on X and Z axis are cancelled separately at low values
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-248099 - Mob pathfinding breaks after falling into water accidentally while walking
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-253721 - Wrong logs when running /op @a
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-260440 - Players can no longer activate swimming mode in water while flying with elytra
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-261385 - Bubble columns act differently at the surface depending on non-air blocks
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-262928 - The "minecraft:entity.player.hurt" sound is no longer played when players receive thorns damage from guardians or elder guardians
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-262939 - Changing dimensions or respawning with nausea effect active displays nether portal overlay
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-265514 - HRTF stuck on even when directional audio is set to off in update 1.20.2
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-267221 - "value" within "change_page" clickEvent json looks for a string instead of an integer
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-267323 - Items fields with old boolean JSON formatting are cleared upon world update
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-270220 - Granting all advancements results in prolonged, disruptive and loud audio spam
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-271065 - Diagonal movement is not normalized when crouching or using certain items
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-272790 - Shulker boxes and other blocks in the end exit portal when it changes state are not dropped as items
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-273338 - Flying boat glitch using string and rising bubble columns
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-274187 - The sweeping attack from a sword enchanted with Fire Aspect can ignite other players with PVP disabled
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-275994 - Having the pie chart open while the window is unfocused spams the logs
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277403 - Flaming arrows and tridents still don't extinguish when water is placed in their location
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277537 - Pale moss carpets sometimes generate disjointed
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277780 - Minecraft resaves all maps with every autosave even after the 1st patch
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277807 - Teleporting the player's mount causes rotation de-sync, previously did not
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277865 - The animation of boats in bubble columns breaks when over a certain "Time" in level.dat
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-277922 - Boats in 1 block high downward bubble column will continue to rock back and forth
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278040 - Creaking swim pathfinding breaks after being submerged
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278096 - "Fabulous!" graphics and clouds disabled causes all particles to linger in frame buffer for one frame
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278164 - Click sound is played twice when you click a setting button and there's a slider under the mouse in the next screen
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278204 - Blaze fireballs now cause TNT minecarts to explode instantly
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278249 - Experience orb positions desync severely and abruptly correct themselves
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278375 - Feeding wheat or hay bale to llama or trader llama with maximum Temper causes item stack to be desynced
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278376 - Arrows and tridents act weirdly in one block deep bubble columns
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278422 - Reloading the world after removing Owner tag from a sitting tamed wolf with /data remove makes the wolf moving and sitting at the same time
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278493 - Tamed wolves which are angry at creakings remain angry when said creakings despawn
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278502 - Weeping and twisting vines disconnect
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278552 - minecraft:entity.player.big_fall no longer plays the sound when falling from great height
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278585 - Players can get stuck when landing on the edge of powder snow
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278591 - Ender dragon spawn egg is no longer given when using pick block on the ender dragon entity
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278615 - Reinforcement zombified piglins are angry at you even if you killed the "caller" in one hit
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278621 - Client/server desync when placing powder snow while landing in it
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278627 - Players wearing leather boots will take fall damage when landing on the edge of powder snow
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278634 - Trying to /setblock a 'waterlogged=true' state on (glow_lichen, resin_clump, sculk_vein, etc.) produces an error
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278659 - Attacking a natural stationary creaking does not trigger sculk sensors
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278683 - Mobs spawned from spawners or /summon never drop their equipment
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278708 - Throwing ender pearls while mounted only dismounts you, without teleporting
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278728 - smithing_transform recipes can't set an item's components back to default
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278733 - Breaking a double resin brick slab block only returns a single slab
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278734 - Sheep's heads stutter when they look up or down
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278755 - Teleporting far away while riding an entity softlocks the game
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278801 - The closed eyeblossom to gray dye recipe is not grouped with the other gray dye recipe
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-278841 - Powder snow no longer slows down the player falling from a high place
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-279145 - Shulker bullets are no longer affected by bubble columns
  </li>
  <li>
   MC-279152 - Shulker bullets can't teleport through nether or end portals, end gateways
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Square Enix Games Only Available On The PS2, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-square-enix-games-only-available-ps2-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Many top Square Enix games are exclusive to the PS2, limiting accessibility for players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Unique titles like Musashi: Samurai Legend and Radiata Stories are gems stuck on the console.
     </li>
     <li>
      Front Mission 5 and Valkyrie Profile 2 are rewarding, challenging games held back by PS2 exclusivity.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   Square Enix
  </strong>
  is one of the most notable video game companies of all time. This merger occurred around the time when the sixth generation of gaming was in its infancy, means that the bulk of its games were developed with the PS2 in mind. After all, it wasn't until the next generation arrived that Square Enix would start releasing games for both PlayStation and Xbox consoles.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a result, some of the best Square Enix games are PS2 exclusives that are stuck on this console. Unfortunately, this makes it hard for players to check out these interesting titles for themselves.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="musashi-samurai-legend">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Musashi: Samurai Legend
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-obscure-sequel-to-brave-fencer-musashi">
  An Obscure Sequel To Brave Fencer Musashi
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1739034917" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1739034917" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1739034917" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1739034917" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1739034917-img" id="article-gallery-1-1739034917">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1739034917" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1623995625">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Most fans of SquareSoft are aware of
  <em>
   Brave Fencer Musashi
  </em>
  , a unique action RPG that flew under the radar for many in the wider gaming sphere. Fans of this title will be surprised to know that this title received a sequel that was somehow even more obscure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most people have no idea that
  <em>
   Musashi: Samurai Legend
  </em>
  exists, which is a shame since Nomura's designs and the fun combat make it a PS2 gem that is stuck on this console. Players who want to check out a charming action RPG will love what
  <em>
   Musashi: Samurai Legend
  </em>
  brings to the table.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dawn-of-mana">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Dawn Of Mana
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-underrated-entry-in-the-mana-series">
  An Underrated Entry In The Mana Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-846947932" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-846947932" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-846947932" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-846947932" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-846947932-img" id="article-gallery-2-846947932">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-846947932" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1126378510">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dawn of Mana
  </em>
  is one of the most important games in the
  <em>
   Mana
  </em>
  series, so it's puzzling that this title is stuck on the PS2. It was the first game in the series to be set in a 3D environment, and abandoned the co-op gameplay that had become a staple of the series at one point.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Dawn of Mana
  </em>
  had its fans, the story and leveling system were criticized for bogging down the experience. Perhaps this is why the game was never ported to other consoles, with Square Enix focusing on other priorities instead.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="radiata-stories">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Radiata Stories
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-unique-jrpg-with-a-ridiculous-number-of-recruitable-npcs">
  A Unique JRPG With A Ridiculous Number Of Recruitable NPCs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-108186328" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-108186328" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-108186328" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-108186328" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-108186328-img" id="article-gallery-3-108186328">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-108186328" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1665702636">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite being one of the most unique PS2 JRPGs, this one can be a tough title to get into.
  <em>
   Radiata Stories
  </em>
  boasts a great script and simple combat that would seem to make it easily accessible. It's not until players go through the game that they realize how overwhelming it can be to recruit NPCs for their journey.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can recruit more than a hundred characters to use in battle, which helps make up for the simplicity of the combat itself. This can make
  <em>
   Radiata Stories
  </em>
  a daunting game to get into, but its cult classic reputation makes it clear that players will have a great time if the experience clicks with them.
 </p>
 <h2 id="front-mission-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Front Mission 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-challenging-tactical-rpg-with-mech-combat">
  A Challenging Tactical RPG With Mech Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1877376315" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1877376315" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1877376315" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1877376315" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1877376315-img" id="article-gallery-4-1877376315">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1877376315" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1938476224">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the most underrated tactical RPG franchises players can sink their teeth into, most
  <em>
   Front Mission
  </em>
  games are engaging enough for fans to stick with these games for the long haul.
  <em>
   Front Mission 4
  </em>
  is no exception here, forcing players to adjust to its difficulty or die trying.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game had its flaws and can be a bit boring at times, but the tactical gameplay more than makes up for any issues. It's a shame that
  <em>
   Front Mission
  </em>
  fans can only check out this title on the PS2. Many fans agree that a re-release on modern consoles is long overdue.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="grandia-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Grandia 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-best-battle-systems-in-any-jrpg">
  One Of The Best Battle Systems In Any JRPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-229750513" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-229750513" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-229750513" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-229750513" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-229750513-img" id="article-gallery-5-229750513">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-229750513" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-521765905">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If players want a JRPG with a unique story, then
  <em>
   Grandia 3
  </em>
  may not be the best game for them. However, the real strength of this title is a hybrid combat system, which still looks amazing to this day.
 </p>
 <p>
  Anyone who owns a PS2 and wants to check out Square Enix's history should play through
  <em>
   Grandia 3
  </em>
  . Some of its elements may be generic, but the engaging battles that players can engage in more than make up for this.
 </p>
 <h2 id="front-mission-5-scars-of-the-war">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Front Mission 5: Scars Of The War
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="easily-the-best-front-mission-game-on-the-ps2">
  Easily The Best Front Mission Game On The PS2
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-974247141" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-974247141" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-974247141" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-974247141" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-974247141-img" id="article-gallery-6-974247141">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-974247141" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1635369977">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Front Mission 5: Scars of the War
  </em>
  is an excellent title in the series, and it tests a player's knowledge of the battle system. It's advised that players have a basic idea of the combat system from previous games before trying to jump into this title, which makes no effort to hide its difficulty.
 </p>
 <p>
  Every victory feels rewarding as players enjoy a cinematic story that is surprisingly well-told and engaging for its time. This game is a no-brainer for fans of the
  <em>
  </em>
  series who are attached to previous games in the series and want to see how far
  <em>
   Front Mission
  </em>
  pushes things without getting too frustrating.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="drakengard">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Drakengard
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="yoko-taro-39-s-genius-is-on-full-display">
  Yoko Taro's Genius Is On Full Display
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-2139489414" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-2139489414" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-2139489414" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-2139489414" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-2139489414-img" id="article-gallery-7-2139489414">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-2139489414" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1554188002">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Yoko Taro has become a household name at this point, but there was a time when his name wasn't all that prominent in the video game industry. His work on
  <em>
   Drakengard
  </em>
  was exemplary in regard to the ambitious narrative, though the story was bogged down by unimaginative gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, players who can deal with some of the game's shakier gameplay systems will be drawn into the story in no time. As one would expect, the title boasts multiple endings that are equally riveting and worth unlocking for players who love Yoko Taro's eccentric work.
 </p>
 <h2 id="valkyrie-profile-2-silmeria">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Valkyrie Profile 2: Silmeria
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-hard-yet-rewarding-jrpg-that-is-highly-underrated">
  A Hard Yet Rewarding JRPG That Is Highly Underrated
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-468520234" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-468520234" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-468520234" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-468520234" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-468520234-img" id="article-gallery-8-468520234">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-468520234" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1684327121">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the most beautiful yet complex JRPGs on the PS2, it's a crying shame that
  <em>
   Valkyrie Profile 2: Silmeria
  </em>
  hasn't been ported to other consoles yet. If there's one game that deserves this treatment, it's the amazing sequel to
  <em>
   Valkyrie Profile
  </em>
  that rewards players for mastering a fast-paced combat system that can get challenging at times.
 </p>
 <p>
  Everything from the visuals to the soundtrack boasts immense quality, and fans can't get enough of the combat system that rewards players for beating a foe that has been giving them a tough time. It's a wonderful JRPG with an epic story perfect for fans seeking a unique JRPG to invest a ton of hours in.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - A Sign To Remember!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-a-sign-to-remember/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player flips onto an awning on accident and more funny accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Most Idealistic Final Fantasy Characters, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-most-idealistic-characters-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sabin Rene Figaro pursued individual freedom over royal duty.
     </li>
     <li>
      Adelbert Steiner sees the world's hierarchy as inherently just.
     </li>
     <li>
      Tidus from Dream Zanarkand inspires others to break through despair.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Fantasy is, in a certain way, the idealization of life, history, and the human experience. While there is plenty of dark fantasy with grimdark edgelord characters to feast upon, fantasy with an optimistic perspective will likely always garner favor, even in an often-cynical medium like video games, which tends to focus on violence, conflict, and competition.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Final Fantasy
   </strong>
  </em>
  series has carried beacons of idealism in its characters throughout its long and thematically-varied lifespan. These figures have an idea of the world that they think should be realized for the betterment of everyone, although not all of their visions for a better world are the same. Ideally, those who have not played the following games should beware of spoilers ahead.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="sabin-rene-figaro---final-fantasy-6">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Sabin Rene Figaro - Final Fantasy 6
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="absconding-rotalty-for-an-authentic-life">
  Absconding Rotalty For An Authentic Life
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2096874036" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2096874036" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2096874036" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2096874036" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2096874036-img" id="article-gallery-1-2096874036">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2096874036" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1893953856">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sabin Rene Figaro was first in line to the throne of Figaro Castle, but as he came of age, he gambled away the position with his twin brother over a coin toss. However, as events unfold in Final Fantasy 6, it is revealed that Edgar intentionally made the flip with a two-headed coin, ensuring his brother's freedom.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sabin left the duties of the throne to pursue an authentic life of individual freedom. He trained under a martial arts master to perfect his body and mind. However, when the call came to defend his brother and his home, Sabin reasoned that using his abilities to defend the innocent and bring about peace would be the best use for his skills.
 </p>
 <h2 id="adelbert-steiner---final-fantasy-9">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Adelbert Steiner - Final Fantasy 9
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-blind-trust-in-power-and-the-throne">
  A Blind Trust In Power And The Throne
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1446717492" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1446717492" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1446717492" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1446717492" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1446717492-img" id="article-gallery-2-1446717492">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1446717492" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1438976743">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Not all idealists believe that the world should change or have an issue with power and a wish to see more equality in the world. Case in point Final Fantasy 9's Adelbert Steiner, the leader of the Knights of Pluto and devout soldier for Alexandria and Queen Brahne. Steiner sees the world and its feudal hierarchies as being inherently just, believing that everyone deserves and belongs in their place.
 </p>
 <p>
  Being of the narrow-minded lawful good variety, his tendency to blindly trust and admire those in high places puts him in awkward positions when his charge, Princess Garnet, puts herself at odds with the queen. Eventually, the "good" of his "lawful good" temperament comes through as he adjusts his perspective, but even in doing so, he loses exactly none of his ideas about justice and righteousness.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tidus---final-fantasy-10">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Tidus - Final Fantasy 10
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="literally-from-a-dream-maintained-utopia">
  Literally From A Dream-Maintained Utopia
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-232477825" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-232477825" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-232477825" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-232477825" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-232477825-img" id="article-gallery-3-232477825">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-232477825" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-160145950">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Idealists are often accused of wanting to live in a utopia, or, in other words, a place that does not and cannot exist. However, in the case of this peppy blitzball superstar, utopia is exactly where he came from. Tidus comes from Dream Zanarkand, a magical replica of the real city that existed in Spira more than 1,000 years before Yuna's pilgrimage in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  In this idealized reimagining, Tidus grew up adored by fans, knowing no other life than that of a superstar. His ejection from this world puts him at odds with the party and many of the citizens of contemporary Spira, who have only ever experienced hardship, unjust suffering, and tragic fates. However, to others, Tidus' attitude is a refreshing and inspirational breath of fresh air, helping them break through the despair brought about by Sin's eternal punishment.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hope-estheim---final-fantasy-13">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Hope Estheim - Final Fantasy 13
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="it-39-s-even-in-his-name">
  It's Even In His Name
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1916380287" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1916380287" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1916380287" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1916380287" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1916380287-img" id="article-gallery-4-1916380287">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1916380287" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-798476227">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hope Estheim begins his journey as a young, grief-stricken boy consumed by loss and anger. Over time, and with experience, he transforms into a champion of optimism and belief for a better future. Throughout Final Fantasy XIII, Hope struggles with his feelings of powerlessness in a cruel and unforgiving world but grows into someone who can inspire others to act with conviction.
 </p>
 <p>
  By the time of Final Fantasy XIII-2 and Lightning Returns, Hope becomes a visionary leader and a steadfast force of hope. He strives to rebuild a world worth living in, with an aim to prove that even the most broken spirits can ascend to something beautiful.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="barret-wallace---final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Barret Wallace - Final Fantasy 7
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-headstrong-idealist-with-questionable-methods">
  The Headstrong Idealist With Questionable Methods
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1269143418" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1269143418" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1269143418" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1269143418" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1269143418-img" id="article-gallery-5-1269143418">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1269143418" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1234585327">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Like many real-life activists, in his passion to restore health to the world to protect it for the existence of future generations and life itself, Barret often takes a non-nuanced view of his enemy, the Shinra Electric Company. He denies any of the conveniences and modern trappings brought about by their parasitical leaching of the planet's energy, possibly as a way to help him carry out the work of unseating them from their positions of power.
 </p>
 <p>
  His willingness to use violence, going so far as blowing up one of the reactors in Midgar in the opening act of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  , disregarding the potential for collateral damage, may make him seem cynical. However, especially when put in contrast to a mercenary like Cloud, his beliefs about doing the right thing for the planet and for the sake of all children (including his own) show him to be idealistic regardless of his methods.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rinoa-heartilly---final-fantasy-8">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Rinoa Heartilly - Final Fantasy 8
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fighting-for-freedom-justice-and-love">
  Fighting For Freedom, Justice, And Love
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-2100124143" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-2100124143" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-2100124143" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-2100124143" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-2100124143-img" id="article-gallery-6-2100124143">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-2100124143" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2012542112">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As the only non-SeeD fighter, Rinoa immediately sets herself apart from the rest of the party by outlining her idealistic dream of freeing her home of Timber and ridding it of its oppressors. It isn't just her status as a non-child soldier that makes her seem idealistic, or her willingness to put her life on the line in her rebellion for liberation. Although her picture of a better world is unlikely to manifest, she still works towards it with everything she has.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is revealed later in the story that Rinoa's beliefs go so deep that she is willing to even fight against her own father, the head of the Galbadian military. Rinoa also believes in the goodness and kindness of the human heart and often clashes with Squall and Quistis when she perceives their lack of compassion, even during missions that involve violence and destruction.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="zidane-tribal---final-fantasy-9">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Zidane Tribal - Final Fantasy 9
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="altruism-for-altruism-39-s-sake">
  Altruism For Altruism's Sake
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-878499269" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-878499269" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-878499269" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-878499269" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-878499269-img" id="article-gallery-7-878499269">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-878499269" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1180773206">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Zidane's quote that he "doesn't need a reason to help people" is an emblematic line that sums this cheeky, monkey-tailed rascal up the best. Zidane comes from a gang of thieves, which makes him savvy and street-wise.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, this never dampens his enthusiasm to do the right thing and help raise others to the greatness he sees in them, as he demonstrates in his relationships with Vivi and Garnet. It is easy to lose idealism when surrounded by hardship, but Zidane proves that a vision for a better world can be found just about anywhere.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Creates Demonic Variant of Cloyster</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-demonic-variant-cloyster/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon fan artist designs demonic evolution for Cloyster, following a popular demonic Shellder creation.
     </li>
     <li>
      Official Pokemon variants like regional forms inspire fans to create unique fanart pieces.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans react positively to Cauldroyster design, appreciating attention for classic Pokemon like Shellder and Cloyster.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A prolific
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan artist has shared their unique version of Cloyster that gives the Pokemon a demonic makeover. The unique version is a follow-up to a demonic Shellder from the same artist that made waves in the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  community prior.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fan-made Pokemon have been popular since the series' inception, but as the franchise has grown, so have the official variants of Pokemon and their evolutions. With regional variants, branched evolutions, and some Pokemon having multiple forms, it's helped to spur even more ideas in the community, resulting in neat pieces of fanart like this.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan and Reddit user Matratzfratz shared one of their latest creations, a hellish version of Cloyster that's an evolution of their prior demonic Shellder fanart. Shellder is included in their post, so fans can see how the unique forms tie in to each other. The hellish version of Shellder, called Hellder, is effectively undead, and evolves into Cauldroyster, a Dark/Poison-type. Cauldroyster looks very interesting, with a horned shell, and a cauldron-like base, which is where the name originates from. The description of the Pokemon amusingly notes that while the Pokemon looks like it's up to no good, it's actually taking a bath in its own cauldron.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fans-react-to-unique-cloyster">
  Pokemon Fans React to Unique Cloyster
 </h2>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans seem to be quite fond of the demonic Cauldroyster, with several expressing that they like the design and are happy to see Cloyster get some attention. It's an understandable position to take. Although Shellder and Cloyster play a role in some unique evolutions that Slowpoke can undergo, the Bivalve Pokemon haven't received any special variants or new evolutions themselves since they premiered in
  <em>
   Pokemon Red and Blue
  </em>
  . Some fans may feel that these two Pokemon getting some attention is long overdue.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1255230646" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1255230646" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1255230646" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1255230646" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1255230646-img" id="article-gallery-1-1255230646">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1255230646" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-479149686">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With that said, some weren't thrilled about the idea Matratzfratz had of how Hellder would evolve into Cauldroyster. The description states that in order to turn into Cauldroyster, Hellder needs to use Energy Root, Berry Juice, Pretty Feather, and Sacred Ash all in the same fight. This is not only a bit difficult, since it would mean keeping Hellder alive for long enough to use all of these items, but Sacred Ash is extremely rare. However, others felt that it was fine, and liked the idea of some Pokemon having more complex methods of evolution, and it would give Sacred Ash a use within battles, as it's typically only usable outside of them. As a fan design, it's ultimately up to the artist to decide how the Pokemon would work, whether or not it would be practical in an actual game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
