<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - All Chenyek's Guild Test Answers</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-all-chenyeks-guild-test-answers/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       All Chenyek's Guild Test Answers In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When players first arrive in Kuttenberg in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Katherine will send them to a dodgy tavern called The Hole in the Wall. Here they will meet members of the so-called
  <strong>
   Kutternburg Guild
  </strong>
  , including Chenyek, who will send Henry after a fellow called Goatskin as part of the main quest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Either immediately or after finding Goatskin, players can
  <strong>
   inquire about helping the band of thieves
  </strong>
  . To be accepted, Henry must first
  <strong>
   answer three questions
  </strong>
  , with the last one being the most important. While Henry doesn't have to get all of Chenyek's guild questions right in
  <em>
   KCD2
  </em>
  , it will improve his reputation with the group.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="all-chenyek-39-s-guild-test-answers-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  All Chenyek's Guild Test Answers In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Kingdom Come Deliverance 2 - Chenyek Test - Wycliffe's First Thesis" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/02/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-chenyek-test-wycliffe-s-first-thesis.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As the patrons of the Hole in the Wall appear to be a
  <strong>
   band of ruffians
  </strong>
  , players may be taken aback by Chenyek's questions. These
  <strong>
   questions are hard
  </strong>
  , and players can be excused for having little clue about the correct guild answers
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-is-wycliffe-39-s-first-thesis">
  What Is Wycliffe's First Thesis?
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Answer:
   </strong>
   Repentance
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   John Wycliffe was an English theologian
  </strong>
  who lived in the
  <strong>
   14th century
  </strong>
  and is often seen as an
  <strong>
   early proponent of Protestantism
  </strong>
  . His writing had an impact on
  <strong>
   Jan Hus, the Czech reformer
  </strong>
  who was mentioned many times during the first game, and
  <strong>
   for whom the Hussites were named
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="which-estate-has-the-greatest-reformatory-potential">
  Which Estate Has The Greatest Reformatory Potential?
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Answer:
   </strong>
   The Commoners!
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Chenyek will agree with Henry and state that the
  <strong>
   reformation must start from the bottom
  </strong>
  . By answering differently, such as the Church, he will agree that these other estates need to change the most, but that they have no desire to.
 </p>
 <h3 id="who-is-the-rightful-king-of-bohemia">
  Who Is The Rightful King Of Bohemia?
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Answer:
   </strong>
   Wenceslas!
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  If players have been paying attention to the story, then this should be an
  <strong>
   easy one for Henry to answer honestly
  </strong>
  . There is an argument for saying Sigismund, as
  <strong>
   Henry does not know where the loyalty of the Kuttenberg guild lies
  </strong>
  . It's safe to say, however, that Chenyek will be more than happy to have met a fellow Wenceslas loyalist.
 </p>
 <h3 id="unlocking-the-feast-for-the-poor-quest">
  Unlocking The Feast For The Poor Quest
 </h3>
 <p>
  Upon answering these questions correctly, Henry will be
  <strong>
   offered his first task
  </strong>
  with the group, unlocking and starting the side quest known as
  <strong>
   Feast for the Poor
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This involves stealing fine sausages from Sigismund's supplies and handing them out to the poor. Chenyek will now ask Henry one last question.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_19">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Chenyek will ask other conversational questions, giving Henry more dialogue options, but these don't matter as much.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="what-should-you-leave-in-place-of-the-fine-sausages">
  What Should You Leave In Place Of The Fine Sausages?
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Answer:
   </strong>
   A Cabbage
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Chenyek previously stated that he and the rest of the people often had
  <strong>
   naught to eat but cabbage
  </strong>
  , so placing a single
  <strong>
   cabbage in place of sausages
  </strong>
  feels like a fitting statement. Players can
  <strong>
   buy one from a grocer
  </strong>
  before they set out on the quest.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry We're Closed - Official Console Announcement Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/sorry-were-closed-official-console-announcement-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The nostalgic survival horror game Sorry We're Closed is heading to Xbox, PlayStation, and Switch. Watch the official console announcement trailer here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Man’s Sky Releases New Experimental Branch for February 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/no-mans-sky-experimental-branch-february-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      No Man's Sky's Experimental Branch receives a February 2025 update with fixes and improvements.
     </li>
     <li>
      Hello Games allows players to test upcoming patches to help vet solutions for various issues.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new branch includes a bug fix that causes ships to lose their custom name, and several fixes allowing the Exocraft scanners to locate buildings.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    No Man’s Sky
   </strong>
  </em>
  developer Hello Games has released another Experimental Branch update for February 2025, supplying more fixes to the popular action-adventure game.
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  ’s Experimental Branches allow players to test fixes scheduled to deploy in upcoming patches, serving as volunteers for Hello Games to vet different solutions for a myriad of problems. For players to enter Experimental mode, they need only right-click on the game’s Steam library page, navigate to the “BETAS” tab under Properties, and enter “3xperimental” in the textbox, followed by pressing “CHECK CODE” and selecting the beta from the list.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  first debuted in August 2016, and gameplay is built around four core pillars: exploration, survival, combat, and trading. Players have access to a procedurally generated open world harboring 18 quintillion planets, and each planet has its own ecosystem, flora and fauna, and alien species to encounter and interact with. Joining the game’s latest Experimental Branch,
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  also received a new hotfix update in February 2025, designed to fix crashes and solve ongoing issues.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
  </em>
  Experimental Branch for February 2025 fixes a long list of issues, following
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  ’s Experimental Branch for January 2025 that addressed bugs attacking flora, minerals, and creature models, and crashes in multiplayer and networking. Some of the main takeaways from the branch include a bug fix that causes ships to lose their custom name after an expedition, several fixes targeting issues that prevented the Exocraft scanners from locating buildings, and a PC fix regarding a graphics problem that occured when changing options in PCVR.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1410519201" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1410519201" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1410519201" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1410519201" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1410519201-img" id="article-gallery-1-1410519201">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1410519201" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1433090835">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While players are collectively pleased to receive another Experimental Branch, highlighting that the update works seamlessly alongside praise for the devs’ hard work, some
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  explorers are frustrated by the new Titan expedition. Featuring gas giants with hazardous environments, some players find it difficult to escape the tornado that sweeps them away from their starting point.
 </p>
 <p>
  Space enthusiasts are spoiled for choice when it comes to Hello Games’ action-adventure, considering the steady stream of updates the game receives, and
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  fans may also be treated to a Nintendo Switch 2 port if the rumors are true. The Japanese publisher finally announced the successor console back in January 2025, and the industry has since been speculating what games will grace the catalog.
  <em>
   No Man’s Sky
  </em>
  is a strong contender because of the survival project’s success, and the title may even get improved graphics should the port receive the green light.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="no-man-39-s-sky-experimental-branch-february-2025-patch-notes">
  No Man's Sky Experimental Branch February 2025 Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue with the Hazard Pay milestone in the Titan expedition that could notification messages to flicker.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that prevented an underwater crashed freighter from spawning at the second rendezvous point in the Titan expedition.
  </li>
  <li>
   Implemented a recovery for players who have lost their hyperdrive in the Titan expedition.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a number of issues that could prevent Exocraft scanners from locating buildings.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that could cause Specialist Polo to repeat some dialogue in the In Stellar Multitudes mission.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that prevented the In Stellar Multitudes mission from detecting nearby dissonant planets while aboard the Space Anomaly.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a rare issue which could prevent the In Stellar Multitudes mission from restoring the first purple star system.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that caused ships to lose their custom name when brought back from an expedition.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that caused Multi-Tools to lose their custom name when brought back from an expedition.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a UI issue that could cause inconsistencies in the hold-to-confirm time for popups if the popup button overlapped a button beneath the popup.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that could cause a mismatch between the colour of a dialogue box title and the race of the speaker.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that could cause a significant dip in framerate when practising alien language.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that prevented the Surge Battery recipe from being learnt in Abandoned Mode.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue that could cause the game to hang when changing graphics options in PCVR.
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case For and Against Assassin’s Creed Establishing a New Ezio</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/assassins-creed-ezio-auditore-multiple-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A recurring protagonist like Ezio would allow for stronger character development, offering depth and evolution over multiple games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Consistency in world-building and mechanics could be maintained with a recurring protagonist in Assassin's Creed.
     </li>
     <li>
      However, there's a risk of stagnation and overstaying their welcome if the series introduces a new recurring protagonist.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Over the course of its lifespan of nearly two decades, the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Assassin's Creed
   </em>
  </strong>
  series has seen a great number of interesting protagonists, but none have left such a lasting mark as
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed 2
  </em>
  's Ezio Auditore. Unlike Altair who came before him, Ezio Auditore was charismatic, emotional, and relatable, allowing players to more personally attach themselves to him and to more readily grow fond of him. In turn, this moved Ubisoft to create two more games featuring the beloved protagonist (
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed: Brotherhood
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed: Revelations
  </em>
  ) to finish out his story and give fans more time with him.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  gave Ezio more time in its universe, no other protagonist has been given the same treatment. This isn't necessarily due to
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  's Ezio experiment being a failed one, but that doesn't necessarily mean the series should do something like that again. As such, there remains a case both for and against
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  establishing a new "Ezio" by introducing a recurring protagonist once again.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-case-for-a-new-ezio-in-assassin-39-s-creed">
  The Case for a New Ezio in Assassin's Creed
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1404297267" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1404297267" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1404297267" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1404297267" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1404297267-img" id="article-gallery-1-1404297267">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1404297267" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-289847453">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="a-recurring-protagonist-would-allow-for-stronger-character-development">
  A Recurring Protagonist Would Allow for Stronger Character Development
 </h3>
 <p>
  The most apparent benefit to
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  featuring a recurring protagonist like Ezio again is the opportunity it would allow for stronger development of said character. Ezio's multi-game arc allowed for a richer and more fulfilling evolution of his character, from a reckless noble to a wise and experienced mentor. A new recurring protagonist in the
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  series would likely offer the same depth, letting players grow alongside them rather than wiping the slate clean with each game.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-recurring-protagonist-would-allow-for-consistency-in-world-building-and-mechanics">
  A Recurring Protagonist Would Allow for Consistency in World-Building and Mechanics
 </h3>
 <p>
  Something else that another recurring protagonist could do for the
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  series is it would potentially allow for consistency in both world-building and mechanics. While the fundamental mechanics of each
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  game largely remain the same, some other, more significant changes tend to make everything feel new again. Freshness in gameplay design isn't inherently a bad thing, but a recurring protagonist would allow
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  to only temporarily moderately refine mechanics between the protagonist's games.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Mechanics that only slightly differ from a previous
     <em>
      Assassin's Creed
     </em>
     are a great way to mature the recurring protagonist as well.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Additionally, while
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  's overarching narrative is fairly consistent throughout the series (when it's mentioned), the world-building that occurs in each game is significantly different, on account of the constant changes in time periods, settings, and protagonists. Another recurring protagonist like Ezio would, therefore, allow multiple games to be more consistent in their world-building, allowing players the opportunity to become more attached to the world in turn.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-case-against-a-new-ezio-in-assassin-39-s-creed">
  The Case Against a New Ezio in Assassin's Creed
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1640423493" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1640423493" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1640423493" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1640423493" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1640423493-img" id="article-gallery-2-1640423493">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1640423493" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-708247015">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="a-recurring-protagonist-would-be-at-risk-of-stagnation">
  A Recurring Protagonist Would Be at Risk of Stagnation
 </h3>
 <p>
  On the flip side, something another recurring
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  protagonist would be prone to is stagnation. One of
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  's strengths is its ability to reinvent itself in each installment with new historical settings and characters. As such, a new recurring protagonist could limit creative freedom, forcing the series to find ways to keep the same character relevant and interesting across multiple games. This really only worked for
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed 2
  </em>
  's Ezio because he was such an interesting character, so simply forcing a protagonist's recurrence "just because" wouldn't be enough of a reason to do so.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-recurring-protagonist-could-easily-overstay-their-welcome">
  A Recurring Protagonist Could Easily Overstay Their Welcome
 </h3>
 <p>
  A recurring protagonist like Ezio could also easily overstay their welcome if the series wasn't careful with how it handled said character. Ezio's trilogy in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  really only worked because his story had a clear arc and conclusion. If
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  overstayed its welcome with a new recurring protagonist, it would risk diminishing the impact of that protagonist on the franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately, while the idea of a new recurring protagonist in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  has strong potential for deeper character development and a more cohesive narrative, it also risks compromising the franchise's versatility. The success of Ezio's trilogy stemmed from both the strength of his character and the way his story unfolded, rather than a forced attempt at repeated appearances. If
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  were to reintroduce a protagonist across multiple installments, they would need to do so in a balanced way — ensuring the character is compelling without restricting the series' ability to reinvent itself.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - How to beat the Grandmaster in The Best For Last</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-best-for-last-quest-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Where To Find The Grandmaster In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Beat The Grandmaster In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Should You Accept The Grandmaster's Offer For A Drink And Healing Or Part Ways?
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  , players can participate in a series of brawl fights from Zhelejov to Lower Semine, and after beating a total of six contenders, the Grandmaster will be the final challenge for those aiming to be the best boxers in the Trosky region.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But the Grandmaster, a reclusive master of the brawling arts, is a tough foe to beat. In this guide, players will find useful advice on where to find this mysterious character, as well as how to defeat him in a fair fight.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-the-grandmaster-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  Where To Find The Grandmaster In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-887360537" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-887360537" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-887360537" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-887360537" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-887360537-img" id="article-gallery-1-887360537">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-887360537" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1794183557">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  You will find Barnaby, the Herbalist north of Trosky Castle, in a retired hut in the middle of the forest. After talking to him by day, he will accept Henry's challenge and a fight will immediately begin.
 </p>
 <p>
  While approaching him won't cause any trouble, try to not have a 'Wanted' status when you go meet him because a Bailiff might be waiting around the area and this could cause Barnaby to become immediately hostile towards Henry, automatically failing the mission.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-beat-the-grandmaster-in-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  How to Beat The Grandmaster In Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-9cb254000e03f2af" id="emaki-video-player-9cb254000e03f2af">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Barnaby the Grandmaster is tough as nails. He has the highest HP pool of all brawlers in the game and fights really defensively. Players will often find themselves countered by his skills, and if they try to counter themselves, they might get into a clinch and receive a beatdown before they realize what is going on.
 </p>
 <p>
  If players have practiced Master Strikes with Tomcat they will know that the best way to avoid losing a counter-parry is with a master strike. Thankfully, this can be done barehanded as well, and it is the best approach to beat this fight without too many issues.
 </p>
 <p>
  On the other hand, here's a recommended set of Perks to make this fight a little bit easier:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Belligerent Brawler
   </strong>
   : After the first strike in combat, subsequent unarmed attacks will cost you 20 % less stamina and will be 10 % stronger. The effect lasts for 30 seconds. This perk will also activate after performing a stealth takedown.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Battering Ram
   </strong>
   : You've never tried it, but you feel like you could punch through a city gate if it came down to it. If you successfully execute an unarmed combo, your opponent will be badly shaken and their stamina will recover 50% slower, making them much more vulnerable.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Start Me Up
   </strong>
   : A good fight can get you really fired up, and combined with your fighting skills, it makes you a truly tireless opponent. After executing a combo or master strike in unarmed combat, you immediately regain some of your stamina back.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  With these three Perks, it will be possible to play to counter by doing successive small jabs combos and master strikes to prevent Barnaby from recovering and getting him against the ropes. Well, there are no ropes there, only the orchard's fence, but that will have to do.
 </p>
 <p>
  After beating Barnaby, players will receive some extra Unarmed and Strength Experience and will learn the
  <strong>
   Elbow Blow combo
  </strong>
  , which is great for breaking enemies' defenses during a tough brawl.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="should-you-accept-the-grandmaster-39-s-offer-for-a-drink-and-healing-or-part-ways">
  Should You Accept The Grandmaster's Offer For A Drink And Healing Or Part Ways?
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1441218822" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1441218822" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1441218822" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1441218822" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1441218822-img" id="article-gallery-2-1441218822">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1441218822" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1866936770">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If players accept The Grandmaster's Offer and choose to be healed and drink with him, they will have a chance to talk about Barnaby's past. If they make a successful Charisma check (Moderate Difficulty) they can convince him to reveal the truth as to why he lives in exile in the wild.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is a pretty sad story, and it is recommended that players accept his proposal, as they will also be able to learn some Alchemy and Survival from Barnaby as an extra reward for winning the fight.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is not recommended to press aggressively for the truth, because it is a Hard Difficulty check, and if players fail, they will be locked out from receiving the extra rewards.
 </p>
 <p>
  The other option is to reject Barnaby's offer and miss some important dialogue. But if the fight ends late and players are badly hurt after the fight, they might be ambushed by bandits on their way back and that would end poorly. So, it is in their best interest to accept the Grandmaster's Offer.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
