<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Companions To Use In Freedom Wars Remastered</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/freedom-wars-remastered-best-companions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Choose between a million-year prison sentence or fighting in deadly missions for freedom in "Freedom Wars Remastered."
     </li>
     <li>
      Companions in the game are essential for survival, all bringing unique strengths and skills to aid the player.
     </li>
     <li>
      Select from a diverse cast of companions with different abilities and backgrounds, each influencing gameplay in their own way.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Freedom Wars Remastered
   </strong>
  </em>
  plunges players into a harrowing prison sentence lasting a whopping million years and offers them a simple choice: surrender and die incarcerated, or get out there on the battlefield and fight for their lives.
 </p>
 <p>
  Set in a dystopian future,
  <em>
   Freedom Wars Remastered
  </em>
  lore punishes the player for simply being alive, deeming it the ultimate sin and for any hope of survival and eventual freedom, companions are not an option; they are a necessity. It is entirely the players' choice as to who they bring along with them, with each companion being more valuable in one area than the next.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wolf">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Wolf
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="kai-silva">
  Kai Silva
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2006230473" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2006230473" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2006230473" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2006230473" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2006230473-img" id="article-gallery-1-2006230473">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2006230473" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2024956782">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Wolf, real name Kai Silva, is a Healing Thorn Type and carries the EZ Falke II and SR-42/LA melee and accessory weapons, respectively. Nicknamed Wolf due to Kai being
  <em>
   Freedom Wars: Remastered
  </em>
  's lone wolf although, ironically, Wolf is considered to be an excellent companion by many players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kai and Nina are both old friends of the leading protagonist in the game, and the latter first meets Kai at a party. Wolf is invaluable in giving secrets, hints, and other tips and tricks to the player should they decide to choose him as a companion.
 </p>
 <h2 id="leopard">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Leopard
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="billy-koller">
  Billy Koller
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1651238347" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1651238347" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1651238347" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1651238347" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1651238347-img" id="article-gallery-2-1651238347">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1651238347" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1023801759">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Leopard is one of the more energetic and lively sinners in the game and players often like to choose Leopard to join in the adventure due to his witty quips and stylish attire.
 </p>
 <p>
  Leopard, real name Billy Koller, is a Shield Thorn Type and even better, has a heavy melee strength, meaning players who choose Leopard to accompany them benefit twice over from having him around.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="charm">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Charm
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ann-vittoz">
  Ann Vittoz
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1651029020" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1651029020" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1651029020" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1651029020" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1651029020-img" id="article-gallery-3-1651029020">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1651029020" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-499592671">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With medium melee strength and a strong Healer Thorn Type, Charm (real name Ann Vittoz) is definitely one of the favorites among all the companions in the game. Exceedingly open and friendly, she contrasts directly with Wolf and when the player chooses to pair them together, Charm tends to draw Wolf away from his inherent introverted persona.
 </p>
 <p>
  Charm and her brother, Hal, have weapons that are integral to the players' mission once they reach CODE 5 and as such, she is a popular choice for a companion to the protagonist.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lilium">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Lilium
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="beatrice-anastassi">
  Beatrice Anastassi
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1296229232" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1296229232" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1296229232" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1296229232" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1296229232-img" id="article-gallery-4-1296229232">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1296229232" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-2029674570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Beatrice Anastasi, commonly known as Lilium, became a Sinner in a different way from most of the other possible companions players can choose. When she was searching for her father, while still living in On High, the fair-skinned, childlike Lilum came across the life of Sinners and quickly became one. Choosing Lilium as a companion to the protagonist will greatly aid players when they venture into the Hourai Panopticon. The Casket that resides there needs Lilium's Will-O energy to open.
 </p>
 <p>
  With a light touch melee strength and a proud Healer Thorn Type, Lilium is perpetually on a search for her father, Cesare. When players choose her as a companion, Lilium will assist as much as possible, but will still always favor looking for clues as to Cesare's whereabouts at the same time.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sakamoto">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Sakamoto
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="elfriede-cabrera">
  Elfriede Cabrera
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2096028791" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2096028791" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2096028791" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2096028791" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2096028791-img" id="article-gallery-5-2096028791">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2096028791" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1444858795">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Elfriede "Sakamoto" Cabrera has an impressive heavy melee strength and a Shield Thorn Type. As an Attack Sinner, Sakamoto is the daughter of another potential companion, Uwe, and due to her close connection to her mother, is definitely the most mature character.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both she and her father use a style of weapon, gauntlets, which are as of yet inaccessible to the player, but the latter can utilize the flare knife. Sakamoto, along with Natalie, Carlos, Beatrice, Uwe, and Mattias, cannot be created with the player's Character Editor, so pick her as a companion or lose out!
 </p>
 <h2 id="alma">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Alma
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="marie-milan">
  Marie Milan
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1381399840" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1381399840" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1381399840" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1381399840" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1381399840-img" id="article-gallery-6-1381399840">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1381399840" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-13524771">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Marie Milan, otherwise known as Alma, is of medium melee strength and a Shield Thorn Type. Friendly but introverted, Alma is fascinated by battle weapons and when the player chooses her as one of their companions, upgrades seem to come more easily.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although there are many advantages to choosing Alma to accompany the protagonist, overarchingly she helps players to discard a particular command. When players need to either retrieve citizens from, or escort citizens to, the Extraction Point, bringing along Alma will negate the need for the Protect Citizens command. Unlike other potential companions, Marie Milan can be recreated using the Character Editor and interestingly, the character is voiced throughout the series by Shiina Natsukawa.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="regina">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Regina
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="nina-diaz">
  Nina Diaz
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1028843325" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1028843325" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1028843325" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1028843325" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1028843325-img" id="article-gallery-7-1028843325">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1028843325" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1460461675">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With a Binding Thorn Type and a light melee strength, Nina "Regina" Diaz is a Sinner of attack class standard. Maintaining an optimistic persona, even when the protagonist is in a tricky spot, Nina enjoys bonding with other characters and is in complete contrast to Kai.
 </p>
 <p>
  Where Regina really stands out is when it comes to battles, as she shines in close-combat struggles. It would also be worth highlighting that, should players choose Regina as one of their companions, she will always try and revive them wherever possible.
 </p>
 <h2 id="leo">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Leo
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="mattias-bruno">
  Mattias Bruno
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-187677894" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-187677894" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-187677894" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-187677894" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-187677894-img" id="article-gallery-8-187677894">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-187677894" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-551173165">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Easily the most popular choice, both due to his weapon of heavy melee strength and his Healer Thorn Type, Leo (otherwise known as Mattias Bruno) is an excellent companion in
  <em>
   Freedom Wars: Remastered
  </em>
  . Full of bounding energy, Leo is a fairly new Sinner and simultaneously acts as a friend and a foe to the player's protagonist. While living their lives as CODE 2 sinners, Leo learns a rumor of a ghost girl trapped in the Cell Garden on Level 2. This, coupled with his deeper and more confronting relationship with the protagonist, makes Mattias Bruno the most popular choice for companion of them all.
 </p>
 <p>
  Choosing Leo as one of the protagonist's closest confidants will result in the ability to modify weapons more efficiently and a quicker infiltration of the Cell Garden. Additionally, should players be looking for assistance in the final challenge before CODE 3 promotion, bringing Leo along will heighten the Panoticon-based retribution.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hogwarts Legacy 2 Should Reward Gryffindors with a Nostalgic House-Exclusive Quest Item</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hogwarts-legacy-gryffindor-sword-house-exclusive-quest-why-lore/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  By the time that it finally and truly allows players to explore with each spell and feature that they’ll need for open-world progression unlocked,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hogwarts Legacy
   </em>
  </strong>
  proves itself to be a gargantuan feat for anyone hoping to claim full, 100% completion—not just Field Guide challenge completion but combing each nook and cranny to fill out every collection catalog, too. This collection hunt turns a decently long action-RPG into a massive time sink if players wish for it to be; meanwhile, players have enough on their plates if they embark on every side quest and companion quest in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Besides the back-burned quest for Ravenclaw’s Amit Thakkar, companion quests are thorough explorations of a particular character from Hogwarts’ Slytherin, Gryffindor, and Hufflepuff houses. Sebastian Sallow’s is objectively richer than the others as it presents players with the three Unforgivable Curses to learn, though, and it becomes far more immersive if players have already met Sebastian and his best friend, Ominis Gaunt, as a Slytherin student themselves. That said, while house-exclusive Richard Jackdaw quests create a fun incentive to choose another house in different playthroughs, a Gryffindor-exclusive quest in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  ’s sequel could be extraordinary with one iconic weapon: the sword of Godric Gryffindor.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="hogwarts-legacy-rsquo-s-house-exclusive-quests-are-an-example-of-good-concept-poor-execution">
  Hogwarts Legacy’s House-Exclusive Quests are an Example of Good Concept, Poor Execution
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1017535094" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1017535094" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1017535094" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1017535094" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1017535094-img" id="article-gallery-1-1017535094">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1017535094" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1746979131">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  House-exclusive quests in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  were a great idea because they could encourage players to want to enroll their protagonist as either a Gryffindor, Slytherin, Hufflepuff, or Ravenclaw and see what activity each one has them embark on. Rather, because of how short-lived and inconsequential they all are, house-exclusive quests are fairly unmemorable and will hopefully be more expansive in a sequel to
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  if the concept is returned to.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players are taken to Azkaban and see Dementors in Huffepuff’s house-exclusive quest, which is easily the most thrilling and remarkable detour of them all in
     <em>
      Hogwarts Legacy
     </em>
     despite only lasting a few minutes.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="hogwarts-legacy-2-has-an-opportunity-to-let-players-feel-like-worthy-gryffindors">
  Hogwarts Legacy 2 Has an Opportunity to Let Players Feel Like Worthy Gryffindors
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1761540137" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1761540137" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1761540137" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1761540137" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1761540137-img" id="article-gallery-2-1761540137">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1761540137" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-940172704">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Harry Potter
  </em>
  , the sword of Godric Gryffindor appears to a worthy Gryffindor, whether that’s been Harry Potter who wielded it to kill the basilisk in the eponymous Chamber of Secrets or Neville Longbottom who wielded it to kill Nagini during the Battle of Hogwarts in
  <em>
   the Deathly Hallows
  </em>
  . As such, it could be fantastic if a sequel to
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  has a Gryffindor-exclusive quest where Godric Gryffindor’s glistening and bejeweled sword is summoned to the player in a time of need, perhaps as a boss fight ensues with players wielding the sword instead of their wand.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Batman: Arkham City
     </em>
     achieved this by having Batman wield Talia al Ghul’s sword against the game’s final boss, Clayface.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  This would not only be terrific because it would give Gryffindors unique gameplay that other houses would lack but also because it could mean that Gryffindors encounter a fearsome creature not seen elsewhere in the game. Having that be a basilisk would be too transparent of an homage to
  <em>
   the Chamber of Secrets
  </em>
  , surely, though the wizarding world is full of terrifying beasts that had not graced
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  and could appear in the sequel. The sword would be relinquished after this boss fight, but if the house-exclusive quest had an appropriate length it might be rewarding all the same.
 </p>
 <p>
  Further, it could be clever to have players choose to fight whatever creature lies in wait and thus grant them the sword due to their demonstrated bravery. Slytherin, Hufflepuff, and Ravenclaw could and should all have their own house-exclusive quests be as fulfilling as possible, and wielding the sword of Gryffindor would be the most significant and faithful way of honoring one of Hogwarts’ most popular houses.
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth: Every Knuckles Ability Tifa Can Learn, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-7-ff7-rebirth-tifa-best-knuckles-abilities-weapons/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Tifa in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
   </em>
  </strong>
  is kind of like the Monk of the group. She uses gloves as her weapons to augment her fists which she honed as a child studying under the mighty Zangan. Every glove, of the seven that she can acquire in the game, will have an accompanying ability attached to it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Using these abilities in battle will unlock them to use with other gloves down the line. It’s a good way to build Tifa’s ability list in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  , so let’s go through them all and decide which among them reigns king. There will be spoilers for locations, but the story won’t have many mentions.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on February 2, 2025 by Joshua Leeds:
   </strong>
   There are multiple abilities available for Tifa, who is arguably one of the best party members in the game. This article has been updated to further clarify where each weapon can be obtained and a general idea of what the ability does in combat along with its ATB cost.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="overpower-kaiser-knuckles">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Overpower (Kaiser Knuckles)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="under-pressure">
  Under Pressure
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Kaiser Knuckles weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kaiser-knuckles-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   More efficiently pressure enemies with your basic attacks or other abilities.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: In Chapter 5 aboard the Shinra-8 while following Barret you'll reach Cargo Hold 1F; you'll enter a small clearing where a scene will show and a hooded man get attacked by one of the mysterious enemies. After defeating the enemies, look along the left side of the room to a small platform you can climb up to find a purple chest with the knuckles within.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  There is a big story change in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  after Junon as the cargo ship from the original was changed to a cruise liner. It’s called The Shinra-8 and this is where players can obtain Tifa’s Kaiser Knuckles. It’s just in a chest and not tied to the Queen’s Blood tournament that is being held onboard.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kaiser Knuckle can unlock the Overpower ability for Tifa which is more of a charge than an attack. It’s not her best move but it will help put enemies in a Pressured state. Getting Pressured in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth means
  </em>
  that it will go into a Staggered state more easily, which will immobilize an enemy and weaken its defenses.
 </p>
 <h2 id="divekick-leather-gloves">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Divekick (Leather Gloves)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bring-flying-enemies-down">
  Bring Flying Enemies Down
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Leather Gloves weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/leather-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Jump up before launching down onto an enemy.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: The Leather Gloves are Tifa's starting weapon.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Leather Gloves are Tifa’s default weapon, so players don’t have to go far to find them. They can unlock the Divekick ability which should not be confused with the fighting game of the same name. Tifa will hop up into the air and then bring her foot down on an enemy.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is a good attack to use on flying enemies because if timed right, Tifa can bring them down. It can deal some damage but it’s more of a strategic ability than anything else.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="reverse-gale-sylph-gloves">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Reverse Gale (Sylph Gloves)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="get-over-here">
  Get Over Here!
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Sylph Gloves weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sylph-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Knocks enemies up into the air or down to the ground.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: in the Mythril Mines during Chapter 3 when controlling Cloud, Tifa, and Aerith. Climb down the stairs to reach the excavation site right after getting separated to find the gloves in a purple chest along the back wall of the excavation site.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Sylph Gloves can be obtained in the Mythril Mine during Chapter 3 of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  . Tifa can learn the Reverse Gale ability from them which will conjure gusts of wind on the battlefield. This can be beneficial in three ways if players get their aiming down.
 </p>
 <p>
  They can launch enemies into the air if they are hit by it, which will leave them vulnerable. Reverse Gale can also bring flying enemies down like Divekick. Finally, a gust of wind from this attack can bring an enemy toward Tifa as if she were Scorpion yelling, “Get Over Here!” in the
  <em>
   Mortal Kombat
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="chi-trap-tiger-fangs">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Chi Trap (Tiger Fangs)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="trapping-the-battlefield">
  Trapping The Battlefield
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Tiger Fangs weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tiger-fangs-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Creates an orb of Chi that damages any enemy it touches.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: During Chapter 9 when you head to the Gongaga Reactor when playing as Tifa, Aerith, and Yuffie. In Reactor B3 will be a flooded tunnel, swim to the far end of the tunnel before looking back to find a grappling spot, followed by another one in the same direction higher up. After the second grapple, turn around to see a purple chest on the next section up that can also be grappled to, with the Tiger Fangs inside.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Most unique moves in the game power up characters, or attack enemies directly. There are a few moves from characters that can place traps on the battlefield though. Tifa is one of those characters and her Chi Trap can be learned through the Tiger Fangs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Tiger Fangs can be obtained in the Gongaga Reactor during Tifa’s segment of Chapter 9 in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  . Tifa will channel a big orb when using Chi Trap in front of her. If an enemy runs into it, they will be dealt a massive blow but sometimes the AI is good about avoiding traps like these.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="starshower-dragon-claws">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Starshower (Dragon Claws)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="become-an-unblinking-star">
  Become An Unblinking Star
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Dragon Claws weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dragon-claws-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   A flurry of attacks and a strengthened next command.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: Obtained by completing Rank 3 of Desert Rush found in the Dustbowl.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Starshower is a great attack tied to one of the hardest weapons for Tifa to obtain in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  , the Dragon Claws. These gloves are hidden in the Dustbowl region of Corel which used to be called the Corel Prison in the original game. Cloud can participate in a mini-game down there called Desert Rush.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s kind of like the box-breaking Moogle mini-game from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake
  </em>
  except with special electrical boxes thrown in to make it more challenging. Obtainment method aside, Starshower starts with a pause as if Tifa is psyching herself up. Then she proceeds to dart around an enemy in an unblinking motion of attacks. It hits multiple times and makes her invincible during the animation thus making the trial of this mini-game in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  worth it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="unfettered-fury-crystal-gloves">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Unfettered Fury (Crystal Gloves)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stagger-enemies-into-dust">
  Stagger Enemies Into Dust
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Crystal Gloves weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/crystal-gloves-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Adds non-elemental magic to your basic attacks.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: On your way north out of Nibelheim on your way to the reactor, you'll cross a bridge with a building just on the other side with a truck parked out front. The Crystal Gloves around found to the left of the building in a purple chest.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Tifa will begin the game with a power-up ability called Unbridled Strength. This will raise her attack power on normal attacks and raise her Chi level too. Tifa has two Chi levels and they change what the triangle button does on the PS5 controller. If players use Unbridled Strength once, they can use Omnistrike and if they do it twice in a row, Rise and Fall will appear.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unfettered Fury is a move that can be learned through the Crystal Gloves and they can be found in the Nibel Region aka Tifa’s home turf. Unfettered Fury is like a more powerful version of Unbridled Strength and it will raise those Chi levels as well. Players can combo these two power-ups together to create some devastating results.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="true-strike-jarngreipr">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   True Strike (Jarngreipr)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="summon-up-the-power-of-the-god-hand">
  Summon Up The Power Of The God Hand
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Jarngreipr weapon in Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/jarngreipr-weapon-in-final-fantasy-7-rebirth.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Delivers a powerful close-range attack.
  </li>
  <li>
   ATB - 1
  </li>
  <li>
   Location: In Chapter 13 in The Temple Of The Ancients in the Hall Of Life - Second Tier. You'll initially find this place during the story when playing as Cloud, Tifa, and Barret, after defeating the riot troopers and jumping over the fallen pillar. Off to the left from the direction the gust of lifestream comes from will be a purple chest, just time your interaction with it between gusts.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  True Strike is not only Tifa’s strongest attack but it is one of the strongest character abilities in the game. It’s attached to the hard-to-pronounce gloves called Jarngreipr. It is hidden in the Temple of the Ancients which is the last dungeon in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Tifa will focus her energy into one punch and then deal a deadly blow to her opponent with True Strike. If powered up with Unbridled Strength or Unfettered Fury, this move will be even deadlier. It would be interesting to see how True Strike would stand against a normal punch from One Punch Man which is a crossover fight fans of the anime and
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  would probably love to see.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur’s Gate 3 Player Notices Hidden Detail About Popular Item</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-mask-of-the-shapeshifter-face-change-race/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Baldur's Gate 3's Mask of the Shapeshifter changes based on race, adding depth to gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      The item was originally from Divinity: Original Sin 2, surprising some BG3 players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Baldur's Gate 3's attention to detail keeps players discovering new things long after launch.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An eagle-eyed
  <em>
   <strong>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </strong>
  </em>
  player online has noticed an extremely well-hidden detail about a popular item in the game. This
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  detail may seem obvious with the benefit of hindsight, but most agreed that they'd never realized this before.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Larian's extraordinary attention to detail in
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  was immediately obvious at launch, it has only been in the time since that gamers have discovered the actual extent of it. Over a year after launch, there was one
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  player who found a strange detail that added tons of combat complexity, and there have been plenty of others, too. It's games like this that tend to live on far beyond their initial release, and the signs are there that
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  will be one such title where players will be finding new things for years to come.
 </p>
 <p>
  Redditor The-Crafty pointed out that the Mask of the Shapeshifter's appearance will actually change based on the race that players are pretending to be. The item is only available as part of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's Digital Deluxe Edition, but is a convenient option for players who want to disguise their character for a unique playthrough experience. In hindsight, it seems fairly obvious that the Mask of the Shapeshifter would have this trait, but plenty of players in the thread were shocked to discover this for themselves, with one even claiming it slipped them by after hundreds of hours of gameplay.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3-39-s-mask-of-the-shapeshifter-changes-face-depending-on-chosen-disguise">
  Baldur's Gate 3's Mask of the Shapeshifter Changes Face Depending on Chosen Disguise
 </h2>
 <p>
  Some were even shocked to find out the item existed in the game at all. This is because
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's Mask of the Shapeshifter was originally featured as a key tool for the character Fane in Larian's previous game,
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </em>
  , and some players were not aware that it made the jump to the newer title, too. One user in the thread even confirmed that the changing face detail depending on race was also present in
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2052391071" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2052391071" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2052391071" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2052391071" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2052391071-img" id="article-gallery-1-2052391071">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2052391071" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2035706192">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The upcoming Patch 8 for
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  will seemingly mark Larian's last major update for its critically acclaimed CRPG. While the studio has yet to reveal exactly when players will be able to get their hands on Patch 8, stress tests are currently ongoing for the massive update, which will see Photo Mode, cross-play, and 12 new subclasses be added to
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  . It should be a fitting send-off as Larian prepares to go full steam ahead on its next projects.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 RPGs With The Best Ranged Combat, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/rpgs-with-best-ranged-combat-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Best RPGs should offer engaging ranged combat to keep players invested with a variety of options.
     </li>
     <li>
      Deus Ex excels in role-playing with mastered ranged combat skills enhancing gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fallout 4 impresses with improved combat resembling modern shooters for an engaging experience.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players love role-playing games for letting them build a character in their image, letting them tackle the game's challenging scenarios in whatever manner they see fit. Most of these games focus on combat, given that it's the easiest way to engage players.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is why the best RPGs feature some form of ranged combat that will keep fans coming back for more. Taking out enemies from a distance utilizing a suite of impressive weaponry is a huge part of what makes these games such a joy to play through.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_4">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Games will be ranked based on the overall quality of their ranged combat and the variety of options at their behest.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="deus-ex">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Deus Ex
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ranged-combat-is-heavily-governed-by-jc-39-s-skills">
  The Ranged Combat Is Heavily Governed By JC's Skills
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-454661072" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-454661072" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-454661072" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-454661072" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-454661072-img" id="article-gallery-1-454661072">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-454661072" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1757327181">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the dated nature of
  <em>
   Deus Ex
  </em>
  makes its gameplay a bit harder to get into than most other RPGs, it excels in other ways that leave other titles in the dust. At the start of the game, players who haven't invested in JC's ranged combat skills will witness firsthand how incompetent he is when aiming a weapon.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's not until players invest some points and train themselves in using a litany of weapon types that players can reduce weapon sway and reload time while also increasing damage and accuracy. In terms of role-playing, most games don't get ranged combat right quite like
  <em>
   Deus Ex
  </em>
  , with masters of a particular weapon type loving how easy it is to pick enemies off from a distance without missing shots.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="bethesda-made-major-strides-to-improve-this-game-39-s-combat">
  Bethesda Made Major Strides To Improve This Game's Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1768507908" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1768507908" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1768507908" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1768507908" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1768507908-img" id="article-gallery-2-1768507908">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1768507908" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1921841998">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  's attempts to appeal to a casual player base didn't sit right with many, the title was a huge improvement over its predecessor in terms of combat. Bethesda made a notable effort to help this gameplay like most modern shooters with impressive results.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will love using the weapon of their choice, running and gunning in each encounter to take out enemies as quickly as possible. Both monsters and humans are fun to deal with as players acquire powerful legendary weapons to take out their foes in no time.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="mass-effect-andromeda">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Mass Effect: Andromeda
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-game-falters-in-many-departments-but-the-combat-is-easily-mass-effect-at-its-very-best">
  The Game Falters In Many Departments, But The Combat Is Easily Mass Effect At Its Very Best
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-123322687" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-123322687" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-123322687" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-123322687" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-123322687-img" id="article-gallery-3-123322687">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-123322687" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-607650726">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There's no denying that
  <em>
   Mass Effect: Andromeda
  </em>
  faltered in many areas, which prevented it from being a worthy entry in this beloved series. However, even its biggest detractors have to agree that the combat is vastly improved from the Commander Shepard trilogy.
 </p>
 <p>
  The jetpack adds more verticality to combat and makes shootouts more exciting than ever. Players will love zipping around the battlefield and flanking foes, punishing them for being behind cover for too long without making an active effort to change their position.
 </p>
 <h2 id="stalker-call-of-pripyat">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   STALKER: Call Of Pripyat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-best-game-in-the-series-for-many-with-the-gameplay-to-match">
  The Best Game In The Series For Many With The Gameplay To Match
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1311470035" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1311470035" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1311470035" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1311470035" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1311470035-img" id="article-gallery-4-1311470035">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1311470035" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-968322174">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Many people consider
  <em>
   Call of Pripyat
  </em>
  to be the best
  <em>
   STALKER
  </em>
  game players can get their hands on. It takes its lessons from the previous two games to let players enjoy an excellent experience as players explore the hostile Chernobyl Exclusion Zone once again.
 </p>
 <p>
  With its fair share of intense firefights and survival-horror gameplay, players will be left breathless after the end of a grueling encounter they survived by the skin of their teeth. It's the perfect game for new fans to check out if they don't have time to check out all three games in the trilogy.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="borderlands-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Borderlands 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-gameplay-is-better-than-ever-before-with-the-looter-shooter-goodness-being-quite-captivating">
  The Gameplay Is Better Than Ever Before, With The Looter-Shooter Goodness Being Quite Captivating
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1141130087" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1141130087" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1141130087" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1141130087" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1141130087-img" id="article-gallery-5-1141130087">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1141130087" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-2110605486">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The story of
  <em>
   Borderlands 3
  </em>
  disappointed many fans, even if the gameplay was a huge step up from its beloved predecessor. Players loved how engaging the looter shooter gameplay was, with players relishing the idea of getting their hands on a powerful weapon that could even the playing field against stronger opponents.
 </p>
 <p>
  Taking out bosses and waves of enemies with a vast array of weaponry is a huge part of what makes
  <em>
   Borderlands 3
  </em>
  so special. The gunplay is the best part of the game that will compel players to see this title to the very end, even if the game's other elements may not reach the heights that fans want.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hogwarts-legacy">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="combining-spells-to-combo-opponents-is-a-blast-every-single-time">
  Combining Spells To Combo Opponents Is A Blast Every Single Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-2093295096" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-2093295096" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-2093295096" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-2093295096" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-2093295096-img" id="article-gallery-6-2093295096">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-2093295096" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1664604667">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fans were elated at the opportunity to explore Hogwarts in the 1800s, with
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  wowing everyone with the detailed school of Hogwarts and its surroundings. Players had high expectations from the combat, and
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  didn't falter in this department.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players were treated to fun action combat where the fifth-year students employed everything they'd learned against their foes. Combining multiple spells to enhance the damage dealt and take out numerous foes in style is a huge part of what makes this title such a blast to play through.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="v-can-become-a-blur-in-combat-as-they-use-a-wide-variety-of-firearms-to-obliterate-their-opponents">
  V Can Become A Blur In Combat As They Use A Wide Variety Of Firearms To Obliterate Their Opponents
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-520865067" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-520865067" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-520865067" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-520865067" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-520865067-img" id="article-gallery-7-520865067">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-520865067" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-942184579">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  went through the wringer back when it launched, with many fans rightfully criticizing the title for failing to live up to its lofty expectations. However, once CD Projekt Red ironed out all the bugs and added more content for fans to enjoy, they realized that this title was brimming with quality storytelling and memorable characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  The combat has been tweaked numerous times, with Update 2.0 completely changing how gear works. Every iconic weapon is viable in the long run as players select the loadout that suits their version of V and take out opponents in style.
 </p>
 <h2 id="horizon-forbidden-west">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ranged-gameplay-is-better-than-ever-before-in-this-sequel">
  The Ranged Gameplay Is Better Than Ever Before In This Sequel
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1253275219" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1253275219" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1253275219" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1253275219" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1253275219-img" id="article-gallery-8-1253275219">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1253275219" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1030118393">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </em>
  is a game that splits fans down the middle. Some people enjoyed the newest chapter in Aloy's adventures, while other people felt that the title was a bit too uninspired when it came to open-world design.
 </p>
 <p>
  What fans agreed on was that
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  's combat was an improvement over its predecessor that gave Aloy more options to choose from in combat. The game's main focus is on ranged combat, with players using special arrows and other unique ranged weapons to target enemy weaknesses, shred their armor, and annihilate any robotic threat standing in Aloy's way.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
