<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <item>
         <title>Outer Wilds Releases New Update</title>
         <link>https://gamerant.com/outer-wilds-april-2024-update/</link>
         <description>HighlightsThe new Outer Wilds Switch update improves visuals and fixes bugs, enhancing the gaming experience for fans.Changes include better graphics for water, murals, holograms, and performance upgrades for stability during long play sessions.The update also addressed various frustrating bugs like infinite load screens and collisions issues, keeping players immersed in the game.The Switch edition ofOuter Wildshas received a new update that adds performance improvements, visual upgrades, and bug fixes. This isOuter Wilds' second update on the Switch since the game launched.Following the reveal ofOuter Wildscoming to Switchback in November, the acclaimed game generated plenty of excitement among Nintendo fans. However, its Switch release came with some drawbacks, most notably its graphical downgrades. While this did not come as a surprise to many fans due toOuter Wilds' expansive nature and the Switch's hardware limitations, some were still disappointed with the game's look on the Nintendo platform. Fortunately for these fans, the game's newest update improved its graphics in certain ways, although the changes don't seem to be too major.Related8 Mistakes Everyone Makes While Playing Outer WildsOuter Wilds doesn't hold players hands, which can often lead to silly little mistakes that end up wasting a lot of time. Here's how to avoid them.Outer Wilds' April 22 Switch update applies visual improvements to six aspects of the game, including the water on Giant's Deep, the murals in the Old Settlement, holograms on Giant's Deep and the Vessel, and the resolution of lights in the fog of Dark Bramble. The update also fixed a variety of frustrating bugs, like one that caused an infinite load screen while quitting out ofEchoes of the Eyeand another that caused areas to appear white and lose all item collision while playing the same DLC.Outer Wildson Switch also received stability improvements during long play sessions and various performance improvements, although these upgrades were not explained in more detail.TheOuter Wildsupdate included plenty more bug fixes that should help users stay immersed in one of themost atmospheric indie gamesavailable. The fixed bugs include the Nomai shuttle floating away after recalling it on Ember Twin, incorrect music playing during certain sequences in Echoes of the Eye, lighting flickering when taking pictures near Dark Bramble, users getting stuck while viewing slide reels, and more.CloseDeveloper Mobius Digital Games has not confirmed when fans can expect the next Switch update forOuter Wilds, but in the meantime, users can check out some ofOuter Wilds' best-kept secretsspread around its universe. These range from a hidden satellite based on Voyager 1 to a giant, digital cat that purrs.In terms of spicing the game up, fans who ownOuter Wildson PC are especially in luck.Outer Wildsfeatures an assortment of mods that add major gameplay improvements or features, as well as minor quality-of-life upgrades. Unfortunately, these are not available to Xbox, PlayStation, or Switch users.Outer Wilds Patch Notes for April 22 UpdateGameplayFixed incorrect music playing during certain dark sequences in Echoes of the EyeFix for getting stuck while viewing slide reels when button prompts are disabled via the Options menu in Echoes of the EyeThe Nomai shuttle no longer floats away when recalling it on Ember TwinIt is no longer possible to take a scout photo of a certain character before meeting themFixed some out of order slide reel images in Echoes of the EyeVarious fixes to collisionsArt &amp; VisualsImproved the animation of a hologram on Giant's DeepFixed a hologram in the Orbital Probe CanonFixed certain environmental animations in Echoes of the EyeImproved the resolution of a certain easter eggImproved the look of water on Giant's DeepImproved the resolution of the murals in the Old SettlementImproved resolution of a hologram in the VesselIncreased the resolution of lights in the fog of Dark BrambleLighting no longer flickers while taking pictures when the Scout is inside Dark Bramble but the player is notFixed damage effect visuals on ship cockpit so they look more like cracksThe color of certain glowing Nomai platforms are now the correct color when viewed from a distanceMore fixes for assets appearing where they shouldn'tVarious fixes for LODs so they match better with their high resolution versions and reduced noticeable LOD poppingVarious fixes for incorrect, misaligned or missing textures and materialsVarious lighting adjustments and fixesFixes for various minor visual issuesTechImproved loading and unloading of assets throughout the game, but primarily in Echoes of the Eye, fixing the issue where sometimes areas would appear white and may not have collisionsQuitting to the main menu while playing Echoes of the Eye no longer causes an infinite loadFixed an image that appeared frozen for too long at the end of Echoes of the EyeVarious stability improvements for long play sessionsVarious performance improvementsUIFixed a rare issue where the Scout's photos stop being displayed</description>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>MLB The Show 24 Releases Update 6</title>
         <link>https://gamerant.com/mlb-the-show-24-update-6-patch-notes/</link>
         <description>HighlightsGame Update 6 for MLB The Show 24 brings new content and bug fixes, including City Connect uniforms for the Mets.No gameplay changes in recent patches; updates focus on fixing crashes, player name display issues, and adding missing elements.MLB The Show 24 continues to improve with each update, ensuring a smooth gaming experience for players on all platforms.Game Update 6 forMLB The Show 24has just been released, bringing new content and several bug fixes to the baseball title. The most recent patches for the Major League Baseball game have not made any gameplay changes.Players ofMLB The Show 24encountered a variety of technical problems immediately following the game's March 19 launch, including freezes and server issues, among other things. Since then, developer San Diego Studio has released several patches for its baseball title, which is the 19th installment in the long-runningMLB The Showseries. The latest update forMLB The Show 24introduced new content and addressed a number of game bugs.RelatedMLB The Show 24: Best Teams To RebuildRebuilding a team in MLB The Show 24 takes time and patience, but taking over these teams offer general managers with a bright future to look out for.The first change to be mentioned in the notes for Game Update 6 is the addition of the City Connect uniform for the New York Mets, which is among thebest teams inMLB The Show 24for starting pitchers. The April 23 patch fixed several issues too, including one that caused a crash whenever a player tried to select a team in the Daily Lineups on Jackie Robinson Day, and another that resulted in player names being displayed incorrectly on the backs of jerseys.The changelog for Game Update 6 noted that there were various fixes to presentation and audio as well, but those were not specified. Much like the most recent patch,MLB The Show 24's Game Update 5also made presentation tweaks. Additionally, it added missing UI elements to the defeat screen in Showdown and allowed postseason patches to be displayed on a team's hats should they be in the Franchise mode's playoffs.CloseGame Updates 4, 5, and 6 featured no gameplay or live content balance changes forMLB The Show 24. Past updates did rebalance the game, such as the one that came out on March 29, whichnerfed San Diego Padres pitcher Matt Waldron inMLB The Show 24. Players had discovered that it was difficult to hit against Waldron in the game, so San Diego Studio increased the velocity of the pitcher's knuckleball and slightly decreased his break to make the throw less difficult to bat against.The Game Update 6 build ofMLB The Show 24will appear as version 1.06 for the Sony PlayStation 4 and Nintendo Switch, 1.006 for the PlayStation 5, and 1.0.0.73 for Microsoft's Xbox One and Series consoles. As all the games in theMLB: The Showseries have only been available on console, it is highly unlikely for the latest installment to receive a PC port. Othergreat video games about baseballthat are notMLB: The Showentries can still be played on Windows, however, like the titles in theOut of the Park Baseballfranchise.MLB The Show 24 Game Update 6 Patch NotesGENERAL:New York Mets City Connect uniform has been added.Fixed an issue with Dynamic Difficulty while player locked.Fixed a crash that could occur when selecting a team in Daily Lineups on Jackie Robinson Day.ONLINE HEAD-TO-HEAD:Fixed a crash that could occur after attempting to throw out a baserunner after a walk.ROAD TO THE SHOW:The simulation screen will now match the game scenario in extra innings.FRANCHISE AND MARCH TO OCTOBER:Teams will now wear their City Connect uniforms for the correct home games during the season.Fixed a crash that could occur when entering Franchise or March to October.MISCELLANEOUS:Fixed an issue causing some player names to display incorrectly on the back of jerseys.Various fixes to presentation and audio.DEVELOPER NOTESThere are no gameplay or live content balance changes at this time.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Destiny 2 Releases Update 7.3.6.2</title>
         <link>https://gamerant.com/destiny-2-onslaught-update-patch-notes/</link>
         <description>HighlightsDestiny 2's Update 7.3.6.2 brings fixes for Crucible, Warlord's Ruin dungeon, and improvements to the Onslaught mode for more rewarding gameplay.The update finally adds weapon drops for finishing all 50 waves, as well as the potential for another one to drop throughout the game mode.The Crucible also saw changes to the Elimination game mode, as well as Competitive, where special ammo wasn't always respawning correctly.Bungie releases Update 7.3.6.2 forDestiny 2, adding new fixes and gameplay changes as well as tweaks to activities like the Crucible and Onslaught wave defense. Thanks in large part to the Into the Light update,Destiny 2has seen a renaissance of sorts, with the player base returning and community positivity restored after a dark period of time the past few months. Into The Light has added one of the more popular activities Destiny 2 has seen in a long time with Onslaught, a horde style wave defense mode as well as 12 returning fan favorite guns like The Mountaintop and Recluse.WhileDestiny 2Into The Light got the ball rolling, Bungie has continued the trend with new reveals for the upcoming Final Shape expansion. Earlier in April, the studio revealed a ton of new information on the expansion, including anall-new subclass for Destiny 2 called Prismatic, which essentially lets players customize their abilities from the preexisting Light and Dark subclasses. However, asDestiny 2rapidly approaches the final showdown with The Witness, Bungie continues to keep the core game updated as the studio has just released the latest patch.RelatedDestiny 2 Fan Spots Clever Prismatic Subclass Teaser That Was Hiding in Plain SightAs The Final Shape draws closer, one Destiny 2 fan finds a cleverly hidden teaser for the highly anticipated Prismatic subclass.Alongside the typicalDestiny 2Weekly Update, Bungie also released a new patch which addresses a number of issues impacting various activities in the game. In terms of the Crucible, the Elimination mode had an issue where one player would be unable to spawn every other round when on the Burnout map. Competitive playlists now do not feature Mercy rules and Special ammo crates should now respawn correctly on the Wormhaven map.CloseTheWarlord's Ruin dungeonalso had a frustrating issue for solo players, who could get lockout out of completing the dungeon due to blocked doors at the imprisoned puzzle following the first encounter. Kingsfall also received a fix for an issue that resulted in two players getting the Unstable Light debuff at the same time during the Golgoroth boss fight. The update also addresses four general issuesDestiny 2players have been running across, including picking up a New Light Kit overriding existing abilities in saved loadouts.However, one of the biggest pieces to Update 7.3.6.2 involves Onslaught, which added Bungie's recent change tomaking all 50 waves more rewarding forDestiny 2players. In addition, six issues were fixed, all potentially having a negative impact during gameplay, from being unable to leave the Pyramid space to crashing the game mode outright. The Recluse submachine gun was also tweaked so that the reticle bounce behavior now aligns closer with the original version of the gun.Destiny 2 Update 7.3.6.2 Patch NotesCRUCIBLEEliminationFixed an issue where a single player would be unable to spawn every-other round on Burnout in the Elimination playlists.CompetitiveFixed an issue where Mercy ruling was present in Competitive playlists.Fixed an issue where Special ammo crates were not respawning on Wormhaven in 3v3 Clash Competitive playlists.RAIDS AND DUNGEONSWarlord’s RuinFixed issue where solo players were unable to complete Warlord’s Ruin due to blocked doors at the imprisoned puzzle after the first encounter is completed.KingsfallFixed an issue where two players could receive the Unstable Light debuff at the same time during the Golgoroth encounter.ONSLAUGHTAdjusted reward drops to ensure a guaranteed weapon drop within a 50-wave run and an additional bonus weapon drop upon completion of wave 50 in any difficulty.Fixed an issue where the portal out of the Pyramid arena would occasionally not spawn.Fixed an issue where the activity would end after looting the default reward chest in wave 50 instead waiting for all chests to be looted.Fixed an issue where players could access unintended locations in the Pyramid arena boss encounter.Fixed an issue where players could duplicate batteries using class abilities.Fixed a crash caused by environmental objects.Fixed an issue where repeatable Onslaught bounties would take up two quest slots and only allowed players to abandon one of them.GAMEPLAY AND INVESTMENTWEAPONSUpdated the reticle bounce behavior on the BRAVE Recluse to more closely match the behavior on the original Recluse.GENERALFixed an issue where the Gilded Cage ornament was missing spikes on one side of the barrel.Fixed an issue where jumping and interacting with a vendor would not display the vendor screen correctly.Fixed an issue where picking up a New Light Kit would override existing abilities for that subclass in saved loadouts.Fixed issue where the Vanguard node was locked for New Light players after completing the Tower tutorial.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Destiny 2 Shows New Traveler Destination Coming in Final Shape DLC</title>
         <link>https://gamerant.com/destiny-2-final-shape-pale-heart-preview/</link>
         <description>HighlightsThe Pale Heart, a new destination in Destiny 2's Final Shape DLC, is the world within the Traveler created by its own consciousness.Players will explore familiar locations from past Destiny games within the shifting landscape of the Pale Heart as they fight against the Witness.The Final Shape will see Guardians facing the Witness inside the Pale Heart, and should answer long-standing questions about the Traveler.A new trailer forDestiny 2's upcomingFinal ShapeDLC shares a little more information about the mysterious Pale Heart destination that players will get to explore for themselves once the expansion drops in just a couple of months. This wondrous new place within theDestiny 2universe appears to be the world within the Traveler itself, and while previous trailers, gameplay previews, and developer documentaries have given fans a little insight into what this realm is and what to expect from it, plenty of unanswered questions yet remain.Fans got their first glimpse at this new destination when it was shown duringThe Final Shape's reveal trailer, though mention of the Traveler's &quot;Pale Heart&quot; has been made long before the destination's reveal. Guardians watched the Witness travel through the gateway to this mysterious domain at the end ofDestiny 2's previousLightfallcampaign, and while the Vanguard's efforts to follow have so far proven fruitless, the game's most recent Season of the Wish tasks players with striking a bargain with the Ahamkara, Riven, in the hopes of this paracausal wish-granting dragon allowing them to discover a method of safely pursuing the Witness.RelatedDestiny 2: 5 Tips And Tricks For OnslaughtOnslaught is the new activity introduced in Destiny 2's Into the Light update. Here are a few helpful tricks to survive the game's new horde mode.Destiny 2's Pale Heart is perplexing, to say the least, though Bungie have explained that this new destination exists as a world within the Traveler that has been created by its own consciousness. A new trailer for the expansion gives fans a slightly better look at the destination, with the returning Hunter Vanguard Cayde-6 telling Guardians about his own experiences in this place and how it's being corrupted by the presence of the Witness and its forces of Darkness. This elusive being has technically been the primary antagonist throughout the entire history of theDestinyseries, and Guardians must fight their way through the Pale Heart before the Witness is able to enact the Final Shape there.Destiny 2's Pale Heart Will See Players Retracing the Steps of a Decade-Long JourneyCloseThe creators ofDestiny 2have described the Pale Heart as a shifting landscape that reacts to the presence of the beings within it, and based on what players have seen from previews so far, the Pale Heart manifests the memories of the many locations Guardians have visited over the past decade. While these are somewhat vague, altered variations of such locations, players will nonetheless find themselves revisiting familiar places as they traverse the Pale Heart, including the original Tower that veteranplayers called home back in the firstDestiny.Getting to see what's essentially the inside of the Traveler is a big deal. Even afternearly a decade ofDestiny, some of the most fundamental questions regarding the Traveler remain unanswered, and players have been imagining what the inside of it really looks like since the original game came out. Still, one way or another, Guardians will finish their long fight against the Witness onceThe Final Shapereleases on June 4.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>New Game is Lord of the Rings Meets Stardew Valley</title>
         <link>https://gamerant.com/games-like-stardew-valley-tales-of-the-shire-lotr/</link>
         <description>HighlightsTales of the Shire offers a unique life-sim experience for Lord of the Rings fans, focusing on hobbit village life over combat.Players can create and personalize a hobbit character in a cozy setting, engaging in activities like farming and fishing.The game hints at appearances from major LOTR characters and will be available on all current consoles and PC, with no official release date.Tales of the Shire: A The Lord of the Rings Gamehas recently shared its first trailer, unveiling some of its gameplay. This upcomingLord of the Ringsgame will be a good pick forStardew Valleyfans, as it ditches the traditional combat-focused experience of mostLotRtitles and concentrates on the life-sim aspects of a hobbit village in the Shire.Developed by Wētā Workshop and published by Private Division,Tales of the Shirewas originally announced last year as a cozy spin on theLord of the Ring’s Middle-earth.Tales of the Shirewas teaseda few days ago, and now the first trailer showing its gameplay has been officially unveiled.RelatedNew Life Sim Game Looks Like 3D Stardew Valley Set in a CityAn upcoming 3D life sim game that mixes strong Stardew Valley vibes with a cozy Japanese countryside location releases a demo.In the upcomingTales of the Shire, gamers will take on the role of a hobbit living in the small village of Bywater. The new trailer depicts the game’s idyllic setting and some of the activities that will be available to players. InTales of the Shire, gamers will be able to create and personalize a hobbit and their home, as well as engage in activities such as farming, fishing, and getting to know the region and its inhabitants well. It was also hinted that somemajorLord of the Ringscharactersmay appear in the game, but their names are not confirmed yet. At the moment,Tales of the Shiredoes not have an official release date, but it’s confirmed for all current consoles and PC.Tales of the Shire Announcement TrailerTales of the Shireseems to be part of a larger movement to create more diverse games inspired byLord of the Rings. Last year, Embracer Group confirmed thata new wave ofLord of the Ringsgameswould be coming up in the future. Hopefully, the game will fare better thanThe Lord of the Rings: Gollum, which was the last game to try out something different in Middle-earth but ultimately failed in this regard.CloseCreative spins on theStardew Valleyformula are nothing new, too. Last year, for example, anewStardew Valley-like game calledMirthwoodwas announced. InMirthwood, gamers build a farm in a fantasy world and manage it, harvesting crops and taking care of their animals, but with a twist. They play as refugees from a land torn by war and the game has combat and exploration mechanics, mixing the farming sim style with some RPG elements.</description>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
