<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Crossing: New Horizons Player Finds Hilarious Spot for T-Rex Fossil</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/animal-crossing-new-horizons-t-rex-funny-eat-peach/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Player creatively aligns T-Rex fossil with fruit tree in Animal Crossing
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans celebrate fan's clever placement of the T-Rex fossil on social media
     </li>
     <li>
      Community continues to showcase ingenuity with various creative ideas in the game
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An
  <em>
   <strong>
    Animal Crossing: New Horizons
   </strong>
  </em>
  player has found a hilarious spot for their T-Rex fossil, aligning it perfectly with a particular object on their island.
  <em>
   Animal Crossing: New Horizons
  </em>
  players continue to celebrate the game, even though the support for the title has come to an end.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Animal Crossing: New Horizons
  </em>
  is one of the most successful games to launch in recent years. While the discontinuation of its support despite its overwhelming success disappointed fans, the ingenuity of players and the build tools available to them in the game have helped to maintain an active playerbase regardless.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, a player going by Popendo on Reddit has shared their perfect placement of their T-Rex fossil, amusing fans in the community. The player's post notes that they noticed that the T-Rex lined up perfectly with the fruit trees in the game, and that gave them an idea. The result is an image of their
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  character looking alarmed as the T-Rex fossil stands nearby, with its jaws closing around a peach still hanging on its tree. The placement is funny, especially since the T-Rex looks like it's broken out of the museum from its exhibit to eat a peach.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="animal-crossing-new-horizons-love-clever-t-rex-idea">
  Animal Crossing: New Horizons Love Clever T-Rex Idea
 </h2>
 <p>
  Fans have shared their amusement at the scene and appreciation of the fan for sharing it with them. Some have pointed out that it's possible to trigger the
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  dinosaur so that it closes its mouth, which could make an even more effective image of the T-Rex actively eating the peach. Others have joked about it, pointing out that the poor T-Rex would just have the peach fall through it, since it lacks internal organs.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1418611623" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1418611623" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1418611623" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1418611623" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1418611623-img" id="article-gallery-1-1418611623">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1418611623" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1765093693">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Outside of the dinosaur's encounter with a peach, fans have continued to share clever ideas in and around
  <em>
   Animal Crossing: New Horizons
  </em>
  . Fans have recently made waves for recreating things like Twin Peaks in
  <em>
   Animal Crossing: New Horizons
  </em>
  , as a tribute to the late writer, David Lynch, while others have built medieval structures or recreated classic memes. Some have even taken their love for
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  outside of the game, with one player converting the series' iconic villagers into real, edible food. While the height of the obsession with
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  has diminished since the game first released, there are fans who will likely keep coming up with clever ideas in and around the game until a new
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  game launches, and perhaps even past that point.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkey Kong Bananza is a Logical Progression From Nintendo Switch Online's Offering</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/donkey-kong-bananza-nintendo-switch-online-movie-setup/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Donkey Kong
   </strong>
  </em>
  franchise is finally making its long-awaited return on the Nintendo Switch 2. During the latest Nintendo Direct centered around the Nintendo Switch 2, the publisher announced the release of
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Bananza
  </em>
  , a new 3D platformer centered around Donkey Kong. This is the first wholly new
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game in over a decade, following the release of 2014’s
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Country: Tropical Freeze
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Most interestingly, this is the first 3D
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game since 1999’s
  <em>
   Donkey Kong 64
  </em>
  . It also comes after years of rumors surrounding the existence of such a game, along with reports of a canceled 3D
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game being developed by Vicarious Visions. A new
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game feels like a logical progression for Nintendo’s recent treatment of the franchise, especially considering its Nintendo Switch Online offerings.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="donkey-kong-bananza-comes-amidst-major-donkey-kong-hype">
  Donkey Kong Bananza Comes Amidst Major Donkey Kong Hype
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1129131538" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1129131538" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1129131538" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1129131538" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1129131538-img" id="article-gallery-1-1129131538">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1129131538" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-557457693">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="nintendo-switch-online-has-been-a-haven-for-donkey-kong">
  Nintendo Switch Online Has Been A Haven For Donkey Kong
 </h3>
 <p>
  Before the announcement of
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Bananza
  </em>
  , Nintendo kept itself pretty busy, releasing several
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  games on Nintendo Switch Online. Near the end of 2024, the publisher released the
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Land
  </em>
  trilogy on Nintendo Switch Online as part of its collection of Game Boy and Game Boy Color games. That wasn’t all the
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  love on the service, as the Game Boy
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game referred to by fans as
  <em>
   Donkey Kong ’94
  </em>
  was added to the service in March.
 </p>
 <p>
  Given that Nintendo has been putting so much love into releasing
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  games on Nintendo Switch Online, it only seemed right for Nintendo to put out a new game to boost the franchise’s hype. These newly released titles arrive alongside the arcade
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  trilogy and the Super Nintendo Entertainment System’s
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Country
  </em>
  trilogy on Nintendo Switch Online. With fans now able to experience
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  ’s classic lineage, it only makes sense for Nintendo to capitalize with something wholly new.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-new-donkey-kong-game-has-been-a-long-time-coming">
  A New Donkey Kong Game Has Been A Long Time Coming
 </h3>
 <p>
  Obviously, a fresh game in the
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  series has been a long time coming. While the Retro Studios
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Country
  </em>
  duology has been re-released on the Nintendo Switch, the franchise has not received a new game since
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Country: Tropical Freeze
  </em>
  in 2014. Considering the myriad of rumors and speculation regarding a new
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game on the Switch, a new game feels long overdue for Nintendo’s iconic orangutan.
 </p>
 <p>
  As previously mentioned, this is also the first 3D
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game to be released since
  <em>
   Donkey Kong 64
  </em>
  in 1999. Despite being a solid commercial success during its initial run on the Nintendo 64, that game's reputation has taken a hit in recent years thanks to its tedious collect-a-thon elements and over-reliance on backtracking. A new 3D
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game has a great opportunity to improve upon
  <em>
   Donkey Kong 64
  </em>
  ’s downsides for a much smoother and more interesting 3D platformer.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Given that Nintendo has been putting so much love into releasing classic
     <em>
      Donkey Kong
     </em>
     games on Nintendo Switch Online, it only seemed right for Nintendo to put out a new game to boost the franchise’s hype.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="the-super-mario-bros-movie-has-some-big-influence-on-donkey-kong">
  The Super Mario Bros. Movie Has Some Big Influence On Donkey Kong
 </h3>
 <p>
  A new
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game also feels apt given the jump in popularity of the character in the wake of
  <em>
   The Super Mario Bros. Movie
  </em>
  . Donkey Kong received a new design in the film that also influenced his appearance in the games, as evidenced by his redesign in the upcoming
  <em>
   Mario Kart World
  </em>
  . The film’s incredible popularity has no doubt oozed into other elements of the
  <em>
   Mario
  </em>
  series, and
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  can absolutely take advantage of that with a new game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nintendo has certainly taken its time releasing the next new
  <em>
   Donkey Kong
  </em>
  game, but it’s certainly made sure to keep the franchise relevant through re-releases and Nintendo Switch Online offerings. Now, the publisher finally has the chance to take the series in an exciting new direction with
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Bananza
  </em>
  . Here’s hoping this new title breaks out as one of the many must-own titles on the Nintendo Switch 2.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inZOI: How to Get and Drink a Protein Shake</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/inzoi-how-get-drink-protein-shake/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    inZOI
   </em>
  </strong>
  offers the players a realistic life simulation experience with a variety of activities that they can carry out throughout the game. The game allows the players to choose their traits, values, ambitions, and preferences, which then affect how Zoi’s life plays out as the game progresses. All the decisions they make, tasks they complete, or people they bond with depend on the characteristics each player can make individually for their Zois.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Another interesting mechanic in the game is Urges, which are the players' temporary wishes. These urges are similar to impulses that people feel and only last for a limited time in the game. Completing these Urges on time allows the players to earn free Meow Coins and several other attributes in the game. However, some Urges are more complicated to complete than others. Drinking a protein shake can be a confusing urge to complete since the game doesn’t give any clear direction on how to get a protein shake in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-and-drink-a-protein-shake">
  How to Get and Drink a Protein Shake
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="vending machine inzoi" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/vending-machine-inzoi.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are several types of urges in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  . These urges can be caused by your Zoi’s attributes, such as values, traits, or ambitions. While urges like cleaning the house sanitizing the bed, or cooking any specific dish might be easy to complete, some might seem confusing to players. Drinking a Protein Shake is one such urge, which many players can find confusing, especially if players don’t know how to make or get the Protein Shake in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  . The urge to drink a protein shake comes from your Zoi’s safety value; they want a healthy and comfortable lifestyle.
 </p>
 <p>
  As of the writing of this guide, there is no way to make protein shakes using blenders in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  . However, considering the game is still in early access, there might be some recipes for making a protein shake in the future. However, players must rely on other techniques to get the Protein Shake to complete such urges.
 </p>
 <p>
  Protein Shake in
  <em>
   inZOI
  </em>
  can only be found in vending machines placed across all the maps in various locations. However, not all vending machines have protein shakes; only the glass-door beverage vending machines do. Look at their colors to differentiate between the usual vending machines and beverage vending machines. Regular vending machines are orange, while the beverage vending machines are blue.
 </p>
 <p>
  If you are playing on the Bliss Bay map, you can find a glass-door beverage vending machine inside the basketball court in Muscle Beach or the amusement park’s restaurant. Moreover, you can also buy a glass-door beverage vending machine for yourself from the Build Menu and place it inside your home if you have enough Meow Coins to do it. Each protein shake costs only 4 Meow Coins, and you can drink as many protein shakes as you want. Completing the urge to drink a protein shake will reward you with Meow Coins and make you tranquil.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour Mini-Games Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-welcome-tour-mini-games-revealed/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Hands-on reveals mini-games showcasing Switch 2 graphical capabilities.
     </li>
     <li>
      New Switch 2 game demos frame rate guessing and 4K Mario.
     </li>
     <li>
      Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour expected to be informative.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
   </strong>
  </em>
  has had some of its mini-games detailed courtesy of a hands-on experience. The unexpected game left some expectant
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </em>
  fans scratching their heads, so further details may help gamers determine if
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  is for them.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Nintendo Switch 2 Direct revealed a lot of details about the console, including its interesting social features, camera, and launch period games. However, one thing that stood out, for better or worse, was the new
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  game. The game was briefly demonstrated, with one of the developers exploring the inside of a Nintendo Switch 2 and gaining information about how the system works in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, VideoGamesChronicle has shared its experience going hands-on with
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  , with a couple of mini-game reveals. The two games are designed to demonstrate how the system's new graphical capabilities work. The first, called Guess the Frame Rate, does what the title implies, showing gamers a ball moving at different frame rates, which they have to guess. The second is
  <em>
   Super Mario Bros
  </em>
  4K Demo, which is set on World 1-1 of the original NES
  <em>
   Super Mario Bros
  </em>
  . Here, the game starts at its original NES resolution of 256×240, taking up only a small portion of the screen, before gradually expanding to reveal that the entirety of the World 1-1 map can fit on a 4K resolution display.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="nintendo-switch-2-welcome-tour-highlights-console-39-s-benefits">
  Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour Highlights Console's Benefits
 </h2>
 <p>
  For those who have never used a game system that can play titles at a higher frame rate, or those who don't know just how impressive a 4K display can be for gaming, these two mini-games might be informative and interesting. However, it doesn't seem like something most established gamers would need to experience. Those who own newer consoles, like the Xbox Series or PlayStation 5, or gaming PCs, are familiar with the differences between frame rates and how good 4K can look versus 1080p. These two
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  experiences seem like they would work well as a kiosk hands-on experience with the Nintendo Switch 2, rather than as a full release for the system.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1328122655" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1328122655" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1328122655" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1328122655" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1328122655-img" id="article-gallery-1-1328122655">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1328122655" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-639841882">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Nintendo fans have expressed confusion and curiosity at the
  <em>
   Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour
  </em>
  being a paid experience. It's not unheard of for game systems to include tutorials that help users get accustomed to what a system can do, but they're typically not sold separately. There's still a lot of questions about it, as not even the price has been revealed outside of Japan, where it will cost roughly $6 USD. Nintendo will likely announce more in the coming months in the lead-up to the console's release.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Builds LEGO Versions of Gen 3 Starters</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-lego-gen-3-starters-torchic-treecko-mudkip/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      LEGO versions of Gen 3 starters have been designed by a fan, replicating the looks of Torchic, Treecko, and Mudkip in brick form.
     </li>
     <li>
      The announcement of official Pokemon-themed LEGO sets in 2026 has excited fans.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon
   </em>
  </strong>
  fan has designed LEGO versions of the Gen 3 starters, imagining what Torchic, Mudkip, and Treecko would look like in a blockier form. With none of the upcoming official LEGO sets based on the franchise fully revealed yet,
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans have taken it upon themselves to create buildable versions of popular creatures, achieving some impressive results.
 </p>
 <p>
  On March 18, fans received the exciting news that official sets based on
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  would be released in 2026. While only a brief teaser featuring a Pikachu tail was shared, the news made waves in the fandom. Over the years, many fans have wanted The Pokemon Company to collaborate with LEGO to create official sets. The demand for
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  -themed LEGO products is understandable, given the popularity of the franchise and the numerous pocket monsters available to draw on for inspiration.
 </p>
 <p>
  Following the announcement of future LEGO sets, one
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan known as eyemcantoeknees has shared their own interpretation of what the Gen 3 starters from the Hoenn region could look like in this form. Using various bricks, they managed to match the likeness of the creatures. Treecko was made predominantly of green pieces and featured a long tail. Meanwhile, Torchic had its iconic orange coloration, with the builder giving the starter a flame-like crest on top of its head. Mudkip contrasted these bright colors with a design made mostly of blue and white bricks. The Reddit user even replicated the large fins of the Water-type Pokemon and gave it orange gills.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-fan-designs-lego-versions-of-treecko-mudkip-and-torchic">
  Pokemon Fan Designs LEGO Versions of Treecko, Mudkip, and Torchic
 </h2>
 <p>
  These custom LEGO designs have been popular with Reddit users, earning hundreds of upvotes. In addition, they continue the trend of fan-made creations shared with the community. On their Reddit page, eyemcantoeknees has posted many other Pokemon designs, including blocky forms of Mew, the Charmander evolution line, Absol, and more. Other fans have also gotten in on the hobby, with one builder creating impressive LEGO versions of the Eeveelutions.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-189035733" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-189035733" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-189035733" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-189035733" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-189035733-img" id="article-gallery-1-189035733">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-189035733" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-370987531">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hopefully, these fan-made LEGO designs will make the wait for official sets in 2026 more bearable for the community. Fortunately, many other things to be excited about in the world of
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  are coming this year. For example,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  will be released in 2025, offering a new adventure in the Kalos region. While a specific release date has yet to be revealed, fans know the game will bring back Mega evolutions. In addition, Game Freak has shared that the starters for
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  will be a mix of different generations: Chikorita and Totodile from Gen 2 and Tepig from Gen 5.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
