<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Honkai: Star Rail Leak Hints at New Weekly Boss</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/honkai-star-rail-leak-new-weekly-boss-version-3-3/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Leaks from Honkai: Star Rail are teasing the release of the next Weekly Boss set to come to the sci-fi RPG.
     </li>
     <li>
      Honkai: Star Rail will reportedly add its next Weekly Boss for Amphoreus during the Version 3.3 update, though details about the boss were not confirmed.
     </li>
     <li>
      Version 3.3 will also welcome Hyacine and Cipher to the playable roster, with Phainon and the Fate/Stay Night crossover rumored for the following patch.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A recent leak from
  <strong>
   <em>
    Honkai: Star Rail
   </em>
  </strong>
  is hinting at the release window for the game's next Weekly Boss, set to debut within the next few updates. The sci-fi RPG from HoYoverse features a variety of different combat challenges for players to tackle, with plenty of exciting and useful rewards for helping to upgrade characters. Calyxes offer both EXP materials and resources used to improve a character's Traces, while Stagnant Shadows grant important materials for leveling and Ascending characters. However, one particular type of boss poses a greater challenge than the rest.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since the game's launch,
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  has introduced multiple different "Echo of War" bosses as the game's highest tier of enemies. Each Echo of War boss typically correlates to a major climactic moment in
  <em>
   Star Rail
  </em>
  's story, with only a limited amount of resources able to be acquired each week. The materials given by Echo of War bosses, however, are essential for maxing out characters, with the materials used to raise a character's Traces to their highest level. Now, a brand-new weekly boss is set to be introduced in the near future.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="honkai-star-rail-leak-teases-next-weekly-boss">
  Honkai: Star Rail Leak Teases Next Weekly Boss
 </h2>
 <p>
  A new leak shared by prominent HoYoverse leaker Sakura Haven is revealing the release window for
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's next Weekly Boss. According to Sakura Haven, the next Echo of War boss coming to
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  will be introduced during the Version 3.3 update, with no confirmation given on what the boss will be. The post also shares more information about the heavily-rumored refresh to
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's battle pass, suggesting that the changes will arrive in Version 3.4 rather than the 3.3 update.
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's Version 3.3 is currently expected to launch on May 20.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2018215699" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2018215699" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2018215699" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018215699" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018215699-img" id="article-gallery-1-2018215699">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2018215699" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-833848038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The addition of a new Weekly Boss to
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  comes during a period where the story of
  <em>
   Star Rail
  </em>
  's newest world is expected to reach its climax.
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's previous Trailblaze Missions for its new worlds have typically finished their initial arcs during the second or third post-launch update. The Version 2.2 update introduced the "Harmonious Choir" as Penacony's major Weekly Boss, while Version 2.3 saw the highly-anticipated addition of Firefly to the playable roster. Version 1.2 similarly added "Phantylia the Undying" as the Xianzhou Luofu's Weekly Boss.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  looks to have plenty of content on the way beyond Version 3.3's newest Weekly Boss. The update will add two new five-star characters to the game, with both Hyacine and Cipher confirmed to become playable during the patch. The following Version 3.4 update is also heavily rumored to be a big one for
  <em>
   Star Rail
  </em>
  , with Phainon rumored to be joining the roster alongside the long-awaited
  <em>
   Fate/Stay Night
  </em>
  crossover.
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  fans should have an exciting set of patches on the way from the sci-fi RPG.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel's Wolverine Receives Disappointing Update From Insomniac</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvels-wolverine-development-update-from-insomniac/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Insomniac Games once again responds to fans pleading for news on Marvel's Wolverine.
     </li>
     <li>
      The studio says it is "actively working" on Marvel's Wolverine for PS5 but won't share news until it is ready to do so.
     </li>
     <li>
      Marvel's Wolverine was announced in September 2021, with no official news having been shared since.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Insomniac Games, the development studio behind
  <em>
   Marvel's Spider-Man
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  ​​​​​​, has provided a somewhat disappointing update on the developer's next title,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Marvel's Wolverine
   </strong>
  </em>
  . The highly anticipated PlayStation 5 game was first revealed all the way back in September 2021, but very few details on
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  have been shared since, and it looks like it will remain that way for the time being.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Insomniac Games is well known among gamers for being the development team behind the likes of
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Spyro
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Resistance
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Sunset Overdrive
  </em>
  ​​​​​, recent years have seen the studio develop some of the best
  <em>
   Spider-Man
  </em>
  games since 2004's
  <em>
   Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  . As
  <em>
   Marvel's Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  recently debuted on PC
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   , with the help of Nixxes Software, fans are now eager to see more from the studio's next upcoming Marvel property.
  </span>
  Unfortunately, some fans appear to be becoming impatient, which has caused Insomniac to provide a somewhat disappointing update for those who won't stop asking about
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="insomniac-games-provides-update-on-marvel-39-s-wolverine">
  Insomniac Games Provides Update on Marvel's Wolverine
 </h2>
 <p>
  In response to a fan on Twitter, Insomniac Games has revealed that
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   the studio is "actively working on
   <em>
    Marvel's Wolverine
   </em>
   for PS5." While it's great to know that the project is still in
  </span>
  active development, the studio went on to state that it will share news when it is ready to do so. "We can't act on everything requested when things take time, resources, and the greenlight to share them," Insomniac Games explained. This isn't the first time that Insomniac has responded to the outcry from fans for more
  <em>
   Wolverine
  </em>
  news, as the studio took to Twitter back in May 2024 to simply state that it will "share news when the time is right." Almost one year later, it looks like the time still isn't right.
 </p>
 <p>
  After over three years of silence, many fans were beginning to wonder if the title was ever going to see the light of day. Although Insomniac has shared nothing on its next big Marvel property since its reveal in 2021, insiders have shared promising updates on
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  . Journalist and industry insider Jeff Grubb touched on the title last year, saying that the studio's track record with superhero games is a promising sign that it will meet player expectations when it does finally launch. Grubb also noted he believes the studio will show more soon, but these rumors have yet to come to fruition.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1267521275" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1267521275" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1267521275" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1267521275" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1267521275-img" id="article-gallery-1-1267521275">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1267521275" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-368313190">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's possible that the massive data breach Insomniac Games suffered back in 2023 has set the studio back in its development timeline, but that remains unverified as of now. The breach sadly saw private employee information leaked online, as well as a roadmap of the studio's future plans. But what also came as massively devastating was an early build of
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  making its way online. In response to the attack, Insomniac said it was "saddened and angered" and that the whole ordeal had been "extremely distressing." In regards to
  <em>
   Marvel's Wolverine
  </em>
  , the studio once again told fans that while it "appreciates everyone's enthusiasm," official information about the game will be shared when the time is right.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Highlights Switch 2's Exclusive Online Features</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-switch-2-online-exclusive-features-nso-list-gamecube-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Nintendo Switch Online will soon offer several features exclusive to the Switch 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new offerings include access to a limited catalog of GameCube titles, as well as free upgrade packs for the Switch 2 Editions of select games.
     </li>
     <li>
      NSO will also offer GameChat, which will be free for Switch 2 owners until March 31, 2026.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Switch 2
  </strong>
  version of Nintendo Switch Online will offer several exclusive features, including access to select GameCube games. Nintendo has highlighted these unique selling points as part of a recent product event meant to build anticipation for its upcoming console.
 </p>
 <p>
  The first Switch 2-focused Nintendo Direct took place on April 2, revealing a variety of new details about the device. Following up on that move, two Nintendo Treehouse: Live presentations were held on April 3 and 4, offering a showcase of many Switch 2 launch titles and some previously unconfirmed console features.
 </p>
 <p>
  Among other things, the April 4 event highlighted some Switch 2-exclusive features of Nintendo Switch Online, including access to GameCube titles. Around a dozen GameCube games have so far been confirmed to be coming to NSO, including
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Kirby Air Riders
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Super Mario Sunshine
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Fire Emblem: Path of Radiance
  </em>
  . Ditto for
  <em>
   Luigi's Mansion
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Pokemon XD: Gale of Darkness
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Super Mario Strikers
  </em>
  . Not every one of these titles may necessarily be available from day one, though all are expected to be added to the Nintendo Switch Online catalog before the end of 2025. The GameCube library will be an exclusive perk of the NSO + Expansion Pack tier of the service.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="switch-2-exclusive-nso-features">
  Switch 2-Exclusive NSO Features
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Nintendo Switch Online features Switch vs Switch 2 comparison" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg" decoding="async" height="1440" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/nintendo-switch-online-features-switch-vs-switch-2-comparison.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   GameChat (NSO)
  </li>
  <li>
   GameCube Games (NSO + Expansion Pack)
  </li>
  <li>
   Select Nintendo Switch 2 Edition upgrade packs (NSO + Expansion Pack)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Switch 2 owners who buy an NSO + Expansion Pack subscription will also get access to upgrade packs for select Switch 2 Edition games. The full list of these offerings has yet to be confirmed, although Nintendo did already mention several of them, including
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Tears of the Kingdom
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Metroid Prime 4 Beyond
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Mario Party Jamboree
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Kirby and the Forgotten Land
  </em>
  are also slated to receive Switch 2 edition upgrades, together with
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-531048571" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-531048571" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-531048571" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-531048571" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-531048571-img" id="article-gallery-1-531048571">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-531048571" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-167957214">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The final NSO feature exclusively available for Nintendo's upcoming console is GameChat, which is tied to the Switch 2's C button. The system allows a group of up to 12 people to chat while using their consoles, even if they are playing different games. Apart from voice chat, GameChat will also support screen sharing and work in both handheld and docked modes. The feature will be compatible with the console's built-in parental controls, although it's still unclear how granular its settings will actually be.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unlike the other two Switch 2-exclusive NSO features, GameChat will be treated to an extensive free trial period. Switch 2 owners will be able to access it at no cost between the console's June 5 launch and March 31, 2026. Afterward, GameChat will require a basic NSO membership, which starts at $19.99 per year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even If You’re Not a Fan, Switch 2’s Box Art Has One Undeniable Benefit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nintendo-witch-2s-box-art-positive-upside-different-clear/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The long-awaited reveal of the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  features and game lineup has finally arrived, and gamers everywhere are reacting to the first real look at Nintendo's next console/handheld hybrid. 2017’s Nintendo Switch launch kicked off the most successful era of the company's history, and it is riding that wave straight into the Nintendo Switch 2’s June 2025 release. While the launch lineup for the Nintendo Switch 2 looks small at the moment, many of the games announced for the system look very promising, especially the handful of first-party titles that Nintendo revealed at its April Direct.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Chief among those titles are
  <em>
   Mario Kart World
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Donkey Kong Bananza
  </em>
  , each of which Nintendo has given the spotlight. Both games will be out within the Nintendo Switch 2's launch window, and currently look like the main exclusives Nintendo will use to sell the console. Other titles, like
  <em>
   Hyrule Warriors: Age of Imprisonment
  </em>
  and the surprising
  <em>
   Kirby Air Riders
  </em>
  , will be joining them before the end of 2025, and Nintendo has already secured a strong third-party offering to support these games. Besides their increasingly steep price tags, the worst part of the Switch 2’s game library is how it will look on a shelf.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="people-aren-39-t-happy-about-the-nintendo-switch-2-39-s-boxes">
  People Aren't Happy About The Nintendo Switch 2's Boxes
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-764621148" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-764621148" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-764621148" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-764621148" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-764621148-img" id="article-gallery-1-764621148">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-764621148" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-83268507">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Heading online after the April 3 Nintendo Direct revealed a lot of extra information about the Switch 2, its games, and its pricing, among other things, but sorting through these mixed details, no one could have predicted that the Switch 2’s game cases would cause a stir. It turns out that the Nintendo Switch 2 uses a different box art template than the original Switch, and disagreements about its quality have already begun. Some don't mind the new design, and it’s evident that game art and logos aren't suffering because of it, but it still sticks out like a sore thumb.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-switch-2-cover-art-rubs-some-the-wrong-way">
  How Switch 2 Cover Art Rubs Some The Wrong Way
 </h3>
 <p>
  The main point of contention is that instead of the red and white Nintendo Switch logo occupying a small square at the top left, the red is now a case-wide banner with the Switch 2’s logo stuck in the middle. Furthermore, the game cases themselves may use red see-through plastic instead of the Switch 1’s light gray, meaning the right and bottom edges of the box art also sport a harsh red border. The borders may look more subdued when viewing an actual Switch 2 game case instead of a 2D render, but there's no ignoring the new banner.
 </p>
 <h2 id="nintendo-switch-2-box-banners-are-distracting-for-an-important-reason">
  Nintendo Switch 2 Box Banners Are Distracting For An Important Reason
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1320770465" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1320770465" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1320770465" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1320770465" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1320770465-img" id="article-gallery-2-1320770465">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1320770465" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1573192188">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="there-should-be-no-confusing-switch-1-and-2-boxes">
  There Should Be No Confusing Switch 1 and 2 Boxes
 </h3>
 <p>
  Universal case templates involving banners, whether on top of a cover like with most PlayStation systems or on one side like a Nintendo DS case, have been a common sight across gaming for decades, but the Switch 2’s box art stands out even among those. Never before has a game box banner contained so much unused space, looked like it was dominating and surrounding an individual game’s artwork, and been so brightly colored. Debates about the Switch 2’s cover art will likely rage for a while, but there is a silver lining that will aid the console in the long run.
 </p>
 <p>
  Because the Nintendo Switch 2’s banner looks so different from anything on Switch 1 boxes, and can potentially draw the eye away from a game’s own box art, not many people will mistake Nintendo Switch 2 game cases for their Switch 1 counterparts. Consumer confusion contributed to the rough transition from the Wii to the Wii U, and the two Switches have even more similar names and appearances. Keeping their boxes apart will help greatly, especially since not every game on one Switch is compatible with the other. It's unorthodox, but this move is in the
  <strong>
   Nintendo Switch 2
  </strong>
  's best interest.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roblox: GHOUL://RE Codes (April 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/roblox-ghoul-re-codes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       GHOUL://RE Codes
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Redeem Codes for GHOUL://RE
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Get More GHOUL RE CODES
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    GHOUL://RE
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one of many
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  games that were inspired by the popular manga and anime series
  <em>
   Tokyo Ghoul
  </em>
  . Unlike a lot of the others, it focuses mainly on PvP combat, helping to provide players with a unique and intense experience that few other games on the platform can match.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  players who are looking to gain an advantage can redeem
  <em>
   GHOUL://RE
  </em>
  codes to get free Ghoul Points and other great in-game rewards. The following guide contains a list of all of the latest codes for
  <em>
   GHOUL://RE
  </em>
  and will be updated whenever any new ones are added to the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated April 5, 2025, by Tom Bowen:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   Those who haven't already done so should redeem
   <strong>
    UpdateSoon
   </strong>
   , as there's a good chance that it will expire once the next update drops. They should also take a few moments to bookmark this page, as we're constantly searching for new codes for GHOUL://RE and will add any that we find to the list below.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="ghoul-re-codes">
  GHOUL://RE Codes
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ghoul-re-codes" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="all-working-ghoul-re-codes">
  All Working GHOUL RE Codes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    UpdateSoon
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 500 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MilestoneReached2
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 200 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MilestoneReached
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 200 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    UpdateOne
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 400 Ghoul Points
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Codes for
     <em>
      GHOUL://RE
     </em>
     tend to expire pretty quickly, so players should be sure to redeem the ones listed above as soon as possible.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="all-expired-ghoul-re-codes">
  All Expired GHOUL RE Codes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    EmergencySD
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 250 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Sorryfordelay
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 500 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    MACFIX
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 300 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    TY10K!
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 150 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    WeWantCodes
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 200 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    OrdinaryPumpkin
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 100 Ghoul Points
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    TYFOR20k
   </strong>
   - Redeem code for 150 Ghoul Points
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="how-to-redeem-codes-for-ghoul-re">
  How to Redeem Codes for GHOUL://RE
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ghoul-re-codes-redeem" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-codes-redeem.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The process for redeeming codes in
  <em>
   GHOUL://RE
  </em>
  is very similar to the ones found in other
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  games, so experienced players shouldn't have too much trouble figuring it out for themselves. However, for those who are new to the platform or anybody in need of a refresher, the following step-by-step instructions should help.
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Launch
   <em>
    GHOUL://RE
   </em>
   .
  </li>
  <li>
   Click on the &gt; button at the top of the screen.
  </li>
  <li>
   Type or paste one of the working
   <em>
    GHOUL://RE
   </em>
   from the list above into the gray box.
  </li>
  <li>
   Press enter or click the Confirm button to redeem the code.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-more-ghoul-re-codes">
  How to Get More GHOUL RE CODES
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ghoul-re-discord" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg" decoding="async" height="1920" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ghoul-re-discord.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The best place to find all of the latest
  <em>
   GHOUL://RE
  </em>
  codes is right here, as we'll update this guide whenever a new one becomes available. However, fans of the game may also want to join the official
  <em>
   GHOUL://RE
  </em>
  Discord server and become a member of the game's community group, as new
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  promo codes are sometimes revealed there first before appearing elsewhere.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GHOUL://RE Discord Server
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    GHOUL://RE Robvlox Community
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
