<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Comments on PlayStation Network Outage</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-playstation-network-psn-outage-comments-response/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Marvel Rivals team has apologized to fans for the fact that the game is currently unplayable on the PS5.
     </li>
     <li>
      Like every other online game for Sony's consoles, the hero shooter is currently down as a result of a PlayStation Network outage, which started on February 7.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Marvel Rivals team is currently in direct communication with Sony over the situation, but Sony itself isn't yet talking to fans about what's going on.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  developer and publisher NetEase Games has apologized to fans for any inconvenience resulting from the ongoing PlayStation Network outage. The interruption of service has rendered
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  and every other online game for Sony's consoles unplayable.
 </p>
 <p>
  The PSN servers went offline in the evening hours (ET) on Friday, February 7. Sony promptly said it was aware of the issue and investigating it, but hasn't provided a meaningful update on its efforts ever since. As of this writing on February 8, the PlayStation Network has already been unavailable for over 19 hours and counting.
 </p>
 <p>
  And while Sony's radio silence on the matter continues, the
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  team at NetEase has now issued its own statement on the situation. A representative for the group confirmed that the ongoing outage is the reason why the hit hero shooter is presently unplayable on the PS5. NetEase is in active communication with Sony over when and how the situation will be resolved, the statement reads.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-39-statement-on-the-psn-outage">
  Marvel Rivals' Statement on the PSN Outage
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fans-are-growing-frustrated-with-the-psn-outage">
  Fans Are Growing Frustrated With the PSN Outage
 </h3>
 <p>
  Although the
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  developer is currently communicating with Sony, the PS5 maker still isn't talking to fans about what's going on. The company's lack of updates on the PSN outage has agitated some PlayStation users, who have been taking to social media to voice their frustrations with the interruption of service since February 7. Some fans are already likening the situation to the 2011 PSN outage, which ended up lasting for nearly a full month and was the platform's longest interruption of service in history.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2098744547" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2098744547" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2098744547" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2098744547" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2098744547-img" id="article-gallery-1-2098744547">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2098744547" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-119495958">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Until whatever is presently plaguing the PlayStation Network is dealt with, no PS4 or PS5 games can be played online. The outage also affects other aspects of the service, preventing any account management actions and game streaming, among other activities. The web version of the PlayStation Store is currently accessible, but no purchases can be completed through it. Game Rant's testing suggests that even just logging into the PlayStation Store through a web browser isn't a possibility right now.
 </p>
 <p>
  PlayStation PC games with PSN account integration are affected by the ongoing outage as well. E.g., the multiplayer Legends mode in the Steam version of
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  is presently unavailable. Based on Sony's track record, the company is likely still in the process of investigating the situation, which would explain why it has yet to provide a meaningful status update. The duration of the ongoing outage and its sudden onset both suggest that the early February 2025 service interruption was caused by unforeseen circumstances.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur's Gate 3 Players Reveal Characters They Never Use</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/baldurs-gate-3-unused-companions-fan-discussion/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players can impact the story by selecting companions in Baldur's Gate 3 with unique questlines.
     </li>
     <li>
      Companions offer depth and replayability, requiring multiple playthroughs to see all content.
     </li>
     <li>
      Reddit discussions reveal players often leave latecomers behind due to party composition or personality preferences.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Baldur's Gate 3
   </em>
  </strong>
  fans online have been discussing which of the game's many companions they usually leave on the sidelines during their adventure. Players don't necessarily have to grab all the companions during
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , but doing so can greatly impact the story.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's companions were instantly hailed as a high point of the game upon its release in late 2023. Each character had their own distinct personality, with unique questlines that could see their adventure take different paths. Their fate during these personal questlines is often left to the player, and whether they would encourage them to become the best or worst versions of themselves. It's this kind of depth that makes
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  so replayable - it would take so many different playthroughs to see all the content every companion has to offer.
 </p>
 <p>
  A thread was started on Reddit by user PunchBeard, which questioned players about which
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  companions they usually leave behind on any given playthrough. Of course, there was a wide variety of answers, but some sentiments continued to pop up throughout. Many claimed to swap them out frequently, depending on which
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  companion quest they had coming up. This is a smart idea, as it allows players to get the most from their playthrough. Others were not fond of latecomers Jaheira, Halsin, and Minsc. The latter of the trio especially, given how late he appears in the game. At that point, players are naturally comfortable with their party, so it's difficult for a new character to break in.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3-fans-often-leave-latecomers-behind">
  Baldur's Gate 3 Fans Often Leave Latecomers Behind
 </h2>
 <p>
  Other more typically popular companions also got a few mentions, too. One player said they always leave Lae'zel behind "purely for the fact that she’s mean to me." Another gamer claims to find Shadowheart "immensely annoying," and so she spends a lot of time in camp for them. Some players in the thread were more focused on their
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  party composition rather than their preference for the personality of each companion. For example, some choose between Karlach and Lae'zel since they're so similar as a Barbarian and a Fighter respectively.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-556486173" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-556486173" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-556486173" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-556486173" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-556486173-img" id="article-gallery-1-556486173">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-556486173" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1556005216">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With the upcoming launch of
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  's Patch 8, Larian's period of post-launch support is coming to an end. With Photo Mode, crossplay, and 12 new subclasses on the way, it's set to be a fitting send-off for the epic CRPG. Stress testing for Patch 8 is currently underway, but the studio has yet to reveal exactly when it will be fully released. After this, Larian is expected to completely move on to its next unannounced project.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 Best 6-Player Co-Op Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-6-player-co-op-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Among Us is a universally popular game that anyone can play, making it a great choice for multiplayer gaming. With lobbies of up to 10 players, it's an engaging social deduction game that is best played with friends in a voice chat.
     </li>
     <li>
      Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Shredder's Revenge is a nostalgic beat-em-up game that appeals to fans of the retro TMNT games. With six playable characters and the option for six players, it's a fun throwback experience that captures the essence of the franchise.
     </li>
     <li>
      Destiny 2 is a free-to-play FPS with RPG and MMO elements, perfect for a group of friends looking for cooperative gameplay. While some modes only support up to 3 players, larger groups can join up for modes like Raid and Menagerie for an epic multiplayer experience.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In the modern world of multiplayer gaming, there can never be enough players allowed to get together to play a game. From massively multiplayer games to more intimate lobbies with just friends, there are a lot of ways to experience games today alongside other people.
 </p>
 <p>
  While three or four players might be a more common number to get playing together, there are a lot of games today that will support lobbies of a much larger size. It can be difficult to choose what type of game will be good for everybody to play together, but there are some marvelous options available that can include anybody, from veteran gamers to relative newcomers.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on February 8, 2025, by Chris Harkin:
   </strong>
   The gaming industry moved towards allowing larger groups of friends to play together a few years back, and it hasn't moved away from it since. Although single-player games are still common, many of the biggest successes in gaming today are coming from the varied world of multiplayer games that allow many players to team up and work together in some way. Stretching from puzzles to shooters and everything in between, the world of co-op goes from more traditional party games to those games with a much grander scale for serious gamers. It is unlikely that new games will step away from giving players the opportunity to grab a group of friends and bring them together anytime soon, so more entries will be added at later dates.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="team-fortress-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Team Fortress 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="classic-fps-chaotic-fun-in-groups">
  Classic FPS Chaotic Fun In Groups
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-622751248" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-622751248" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-622751248" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-622751248" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-622751248-img" id="article-gallery-1-622751248">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-622751248" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-532309910">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A game that spawned from a mod and was improved to become a long-lasting and beloved FPS game,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Team Fortress 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  has become iconic within the sphere of gaming. Players choose a team between Red and Blue and choose a character class, and then they are spawned into different game modes to fight for victory.
  <em>
   TF2
  </em>
  established some of the major concepts used today for gaming, and it still retains popularity among many players.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fortunately, for larger groups of players wanting to join together, the standard team size is 6, but some competitive modes allow more than this, making it a great choice for large groups of players. Although shooter games aren't for everyone, the style of
  <em>
   TF2
  </em>
  makes it feel a lot more friendly for groups of players with varied skill levels than some other shooter games.
 </p>
 <h2 id="jackbox-party-pack">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Jackbox Party Pack
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="various-games-for-many-players-all-in-one">
  Various Games For Many Players All In One
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1604756478" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1604756478" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1604756478" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1604756478" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1604756478-img" id="article-gallery-2-1604756478">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1604756478" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-458563916">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Jackbox Party Pack
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a fascinating series of games, all of which are easily played among either a group of friends or an entire chat's worth of Twitch viewers. These games are hilarious fun, and their variation with five games in each pack means that players aren't likely to get bored as quickly as they might with some other party games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Games like Quiplash, Trivia Murder Party, and Talking Points have helped turn
  <em>
   Jackbox
  </em>
  into a major hit among larger groups of gamers looking for something fun for an evening. This is the perfect answer to a group that features a mix of veteran gamers and more casual players.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="pico-park">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Pico Park
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-wonderfully-chaotic-puzzle-game-for-whole-groups">
  A Wonderfully Chaotic Puzzle Game For Whole Groups
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1093449809" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1093449809" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1093449809" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1093449809" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1093449809-img" id="article-gallery-3-1093449809">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1093449809" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-135960349">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pico Park
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the most unusual co-op games ever released. Supporting up to ten players in a single game, this puzzle title lets players work together as a larger group to try and find a key that will allow them to unlock the door at the end of the stage, permitting them to move on.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pico Park
  </em>
  comes with a huge variety of levels and game modes, making it a great party game for larger groups to play. The standard world mode comes with 48 different levels split into 12 different styles, while players can also play together locally or in battle/endless modes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="project-zomboid">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Project Zomboid
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fantastic-and-challenging-open-world-zombie-survival">
  Fantastic And Challenging Open-World Zombie Survival
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2050918223" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2050918223" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2050918223" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2050918223" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2050918223-img" id="article-gallery-4-2050918223">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2050918223" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-738769">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although there are a lot of survival games and zombie survival games, few allow so many players to come together and work to loot, build, and survive.
  <em>
   <strong>
    Project Zomboid
   </strong>
  </em>
  is special for this, and players have been hugely enjoying the isometric open-world aspect. Not just this, but also the many different elements of survival within this game, and of course, the co-op aspect.
 </p>
 <p>
  Being able to work alongside so many friends to try and survive the onslaught makes for a charming, but dangerous, time. Players get to live the simple life at times, crafting and fishing, and other times they have to grab loot where they can in deadly areas and try to take on hordes of zombies. The blend of simple base-building and tension-filled moments makes for a great experience alongside large groups of friends.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="valheim">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Valheim
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="norse-survival-in-barebones-fashion-made-easier-with-friends">
  Norse Survival In Barebones Fashion Made Easier With Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-729466505" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-729466505" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-729466505" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-729466505" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-729466505-img" id="article-gallery-5-729466505">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-729466505" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-560755078">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Valheim
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a game that can be incredibly difficult to get to grips with and to make progress in. This is definitely one of the more grind-filled survival games, set in a procedurally generated world that is inspired by Norse Mythology.
  <em>
   Valheim
  </em>
  is exciting but it takes a lot of work, and that becomes a lot easier with friends along for the ride.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a lot of excellent things to do in
  <em>
   Valheim
  </em>
  . Fights to be fought and builds to be created, but the most glaring thing that stands out to fans is the brutality.
  <em>
   Valheim
  </em>
  truly is a game that is great alone, but greatly improved with friends coming along for the ride.
 </p>
 <h2 id="human-fall-flat">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Human: Fall Flat
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-floating-dreamscape-party-platformer">
  A Floating Dreamscape Party Platformer
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-332017266" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-332017266" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-332017266" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-332017266" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-332017266-img" id="article-gallery-6-332017266">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-332017266" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1190892571">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the best party games for a group of gamers ever seen,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Human: Fall Flat
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a physics platformer that can be played by up to eight people online. It encourages players to work together to try and navigate puzzles and levels, many of which can be solved in a variety of different ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fun in
  <em>
   Human: Fall Flat
  </em>
  is the completely ridiculous physics and the openness of the levels, allowing players to find their own solutions creatively. Working together in a larger group makes the game even more fun, making this a perfect single-evening experience for a party of six.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="killing-floor-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Killing Floor 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-great-retro-styled-co-operative-shooter">
  A Great Retro-Styled Co-Operative Shooter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1641675513" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1641675513" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1641675513" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1641675513" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1641675513-img" id="article-gallery-7-1641675513">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1641675513" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-249787325">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another FPS game that is perfect for a group of six players,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Killing Floor 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  , was released in 2016. Set in a world overtaken by military clones that have spread across Europe following the events of the first game,
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  allows up to six players to work together in the campaign against hordes of zombie-like creatures, making it one of the best co-op zombie games on the market.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though there was some criticism leveled at the plot, the actual gameplay has been much praised, making
  <em>
   Killing Floor 2
  </em>
  another perfect party game for a group of players looking to relax and turn off their brains. Players can work together to try and survive each mission or compete for the most kills and points.
 </p>
 <h2 id="terraria">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Terraria
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="base-building-amp-sandbox-action-with-large-groups">
  Base-Building &amp; Sandbox Action With Large Groups
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1025849976" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1025849976" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1025849976" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1025849976" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1025849976-img" id="article-gallery-8-1025849976">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1025849976" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-511510656">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another game that allows a large group of players to enter a single world,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Terraria
   </strong>
  </em>
  has often been cited as having similarities to
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  but in two dimensions. There are a lot of things that make
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  unique, though, including the intricacy of the crafting system.
 </p>
 <p>
  This can be an overwhelming game to get into initially, but with a few friends along for the ride,
  <em>
   Terraria
  </em>
  is much easier to get to grips with quickly. As of version 1.4, up to 16 players can join a single server, making this a perfect cooperative experience with a lot of replayability for six players or more.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="minecraft">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Minecraft
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ultimate-co-op-game-for-all-adventures">
  The Ultimate Co-Op Game For All Adventures
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-124130872" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-124130872" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-124130872" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-124130872" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-124130872-img" id="article-gallery-9-124130872">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-124130872" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-638398312">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the greatest games of all time,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Minecraft
   </strong>
  </em>
  , has proven its popularity many times over the last decade by retaining player numbers almost unheard of over a lengthy time.
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  offers gamers many ways to play, and a group of friends can come together in an online server or Java realm to do anything from creative builds to attempting to defeat the Ender Dragon together.
 </p>
 <p>
  The wide range of capabilities available in
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  means that players can potentially keep engaging together in new projects endlessly. With such an active modding community and so many great multiplayer servers to try out,
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  is the ultimate party game for larger groups from six to ten or even smaller groups of friends.
 </p>
 <h2 id="don-39-t-starve-together">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Don't Starve Together
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="brutal-survival-game-made-for-co-op-play">
  Brutal Survival Game Made For Co-Op Play
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1807622287" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1807622287" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1807622287" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1807622287" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1807622287-img" id="article-gallery-10-1807622287">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1807622287" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1866380346">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A survival game with endless possibilities and a lot of stress to worry about,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Don't Starve
   </strong>
  </em>
  was infamous for being a challenge, but the sequel
  <em>
   <strong>
    Don't Starve Together
   </strong>
  </em>
  introduced co-op and made things even harder in some ways. This edition comes with a lot of survival meters to be kept track of, and even when working together, players will find a lot of struggles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite being one of the forerunners of the current survival genre's popularity, especially in co-op terms,
  <em>
   Don't Starve Together
  </em>
  is easy to learn but hard to master. Up to six gamers can play together, allowing for a hilarious and unique sort of evening.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-forest">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   The Forest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-island-filled-with-friends-building-amp-cannibals">
  An Island Filled With Friends, Building &amp; Cannibals
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1816829560" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1816829560" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1816829560" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1816829560" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1816829560-img" id="article-gallery-11-1816829560">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1816829560" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-650050070">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Forest
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the best survival games for a larger group of friends to engage in. Up to 8 players can join a multiplayer session on the same island, making for a much better experience, as much of the building and crafting in
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  becomes a lot easier alongside multiple friends.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  is about a man whose plane crash lands on an island, forcing him to try to survive and try to fight off the native cannibals while searching for his son. The absolute chaos involved in entering cave systems and fighting off monstrous cannibal creatures is perfect for a larger group of friends. Horror survival games such as
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  are perfect for groups of friends looking for a scary yet entertaining experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="among-us">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Among Us
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ultimate-co-op-game-of-deception-for-large-groups">
  The Ultimate Co-Op Game Of Deception For Large Groups
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-2040445126" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-2040445126" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-2040445126" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-2040445126" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-2040445126-img" id="article-gallery-12-2040445126">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-2040445126" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1547676752">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Among Us
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a great and simplistic game that anybody can play. The popularity of
  <em>
   Among Us
  </em>
  is universal, given the social deduction style that has been so popular in board games for years. Whether or not players have ever played a video game before, they will be able to quickly catch on to the style of
  <em>
   Among Us
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The lobbies support up to ten players, but playing online without friends in voice chat makes the game far less interesting. Six players or more can easily work together in their attempts to win the game and stop the impostors from murdering everybody.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-shredder-rsquo-s-revenge">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Shredder’s Revenge
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-modern-arcade-masterpiece-for-many-players">
  A Modern Arcade Masterpiece For Many Players
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1033202143" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1033202143" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1033202143" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1033202143" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1033202143-img" id="article-gallery-13-1033202143">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1033202143" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1401231427">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  classic arcade games made for some of the most memorable media in the franchise.
  <em>
   <strong>
    Shredder’s Revenge
   </strong>
  </em>
  was a unique update to this beat-em-up series, released in 2022 for a variety of consoles and filled with the familiar kind of classic beat-em-up aspects that fans of the retro games will fall in love with all over again.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even bringing back the 1987 animated
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  series voice actors, this game is a true throwback and love letter to the origins of the franchise. The pixilated art style and fun gameplay have helped drive a slight resurgence of the beat-em-up genre, and with April O’Neil and Master Splinter being playable, six players can jump into this game without a problem.
 </p>
 <h2 id="destiny-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Destiny 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-best-mmos-to-play-with-friends">
  One Of The Best MMOs To Play With Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-235388827" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-235388827" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-235388827" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-235388827" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-235388827-img" id="article-gallery-14-235388827">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-235388827" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-2097752666">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If a few friends are looking for something free-to-play to jump into,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Destiny 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  could be a great option. This online FPS game featuring RPG and MMO elements has become huge, with constant updates overhauling much of the gameplay to keep things changing, helping it become one of the best looter shooters of all time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite some match types in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  only featuring up to 3-player cooperation, up to six players are able to join together for modes such as Raid and the Menagerie. Either of these makes for a great option for a larger group of friends getting together, even working well for single players looking to meet a larger party for raids, as there are ways for a single extra to join as a fill for an already established party.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="stardew-valley">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Stardew Valley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="crafting-years-of-crops-amp-a-huge-farm-alongside-friends">
  Crafting Years Of Crops &amp; A Huge Farm Alongside Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1597732578" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1597732578" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1597732578" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1597732578" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1597732578-img" id="article-gallery-15-1597732578">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1597732578" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1912168513">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the most relaxing games on the market,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  , is a great way to chill out either alone or with a group of friends. While traditionally up to four players can join a single co-op game, there are a variety of ways in which players can get more friends onto a single server.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ever since
  <em>
   Stardew
  </em>
  was released on Beta nearly a decade ago, there have been ways to add more players to a server than what is supposedly allowed. This means that six-player games and even more are easily put together with the right know-how. This can be done through mods or even without them, making
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  a great option for a group of friends looking to chill out together.
 </p>
 <h2 id="factorio">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Factorio
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-best-construction-game-for-large-groups">
  The Best Construction Game For Large Groups
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1095659" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1095659" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1095659" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1095659" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1095659-img" id="article-gallery-16-1095659">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1095659" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-528410641">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the more complicated games available today,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Factorio
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a construction and management game that takes place in a 2D environment, where gamers are able to work together to create automated factories of varying complexity, continuing to get more complicated as time goes by.
 </p>
 <p>
  To create the best possible version of this game, the developers kept it in early access for four years, but it was worth it to produce the incredible final version they did. Technically, though it would be difficult to get near this number, around 65,000 players can be on one server. For a group of six, however,
  <em>
   Factorio
  </em>
  is a must-try.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="forza-horizon-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-ultimate-racing-experience-for-many-friends">
  The Ultimate Racing Experience For Many Friends
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1800738241" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1800738241" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1800738241" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1800738241" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1800738241-img" id="article-gallery-17-1800738241">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1800738241" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-1409972290">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A hugely loved racing game,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Forza Horizon 5
   </strong>
  </em>
  , has added a lot of options over the years for players looking to relax, drive, or race across the country. One of the most major updates introduced cooperative play, allowing up to six players to work alongside each other in a convoy. Co-op even allows players to complete campaign missions alongside their friends.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Forza Horizon 5
  </em>
  didn't start out as an amazing co-op adventure, it has evolved and has become even better through these additions, now offering chill and tense gaming experiences that can be played alone or with a whole group of friends.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 Games Every Lover Of High Fantasy Should Play</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/high-fantasy-game-recommendations-must-play/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      High fantasy settings in video games offer immersive worlds, rich lore, and a chance for players to take on epic roles as heroes, knights, and sorcerers.
     </li>
     <li>
      While post-apocalyptic and modern-day settings have become more common in recent years, there are still great games that embrace high fantasy concepts with swords, sorcery, elves, and witchcraft.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like Trials of Mana, Golden Axe, Final Fantasy 16, Kingdoms of Amalur, Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor, Chained Echoes, and Elden Ring offer diverse and captivating experiences in high fantasy settings that cater to different tastes and playstyles.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Video games that used a
  <strong>
   high fantasy
  </strong>
  setting as their backdrop were some of the most common in the industry. It is easy to see why game developers could look at
  <em>
   Dungeons &amp; Dragons
  </em>
  and J.R.R. Tolkien's
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  for inspiration for stories and settings.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, in recent years, high fantasy Tolkienesque settings have become less commonplace, with more developers preferring to use post-apocalyptic or even modern-day settings. But that does not mean fans lack a choice of great games that use a high fantasy concept. Some of the greatest games of the last two generations are still happy to use worlds steeped in swords, sorcery, elves, and witchcraft.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on February 8, 2025, by Michael Llewellyn:
   </strong>
   Whether it’s traditional Tolkienesque fantasy, whimsical adventures, or dark, gritty themes, the fantasy genre can cater to many tastes. This also applies to gaming genres from action RPGs to strategy games. This list is updated to include two more fantasy-based games and information tags for most titles.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="unicorn-overlord">
  <span class="item-num">
   26
  </span>
  <span>
   Unicorn Overlord
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-accessible-deep-and-fun-fantasy-strategy-game">
  An Accessible, Deep, And Fun Fantasy Strategy Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-389449488" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-389449488" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-389449488" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-389449488" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-389449488-img" id="article-gallery-1-389449488">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-389449488" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-433811893">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Unicorn Overlord
  </em>
  is an accessible and stunning tactical RPG from Vanillaware. It’s an accessible but rich game with tons of depth and a cast of terrific characters. Players take on the role of a prince tasked with reclaiming his family’s kingdom and getting revenge after his parents were betrayed.
 </p>
 <p>
  The prince must form alliances with humans, bestrals, elves, and more to increase his army to reclaim his land. The battles are played out automatically, but the compelling aspect of
  <em>
   Unicorn Overlord's
  </em>
  gameplay is the preparation before every battle and watching it unfold on the screen. The 2D characters are beautifully drawn, well-written, and acted.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings">
  <span class="item-num">
   25
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 2: Assassins Of Kings
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dark-fantasy-that-still-holds-up">
  Dark Fantasy That Still Holds Up
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1873038039" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1873038039" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1873038039" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1873038039" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1873038039-img" id="article-gallery-2-1873038039">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1873038039" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1169134706">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings
  </em>
  , the second entry in CD Projekt Red's dark fantasy action RPG series, offers players a darker experience in the high fantasy genre. It is based on the fantasy novels of the same name and explores a land of cruelty, prejudice, and war. It isn't as open as its successor,
  <em>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt,
  </em>
  but there are still wide open areas to explore with lots of detailed towns full of side quests.
 </p>
 <p>
  The combat isn't as polished, but it remains strategic with fluid action that is both challenging and satisfying. However, it does have more difficulty spikes compared to its successor, making it notably more challenging. This game serves as a great starting point for anyone looking to explore the rich world, lore, and characters of The Witcher series.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="metaphor-refantazio">
  <span class="item-num">
   24
  </span>
  <span>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-incredible-and-original-fantasy-world">
  An Incredible And Original Fantasy World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1685722096" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1685722096" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1685722096" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1685722096" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1685722096-img" id="article-gallery-3-1685722096">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1685722096" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1921143323">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players looking for a fantasy game that feels and looks unlike anything else in the genre should look no further than
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio.
  </em>
  Developed by Atlus, its gameplay is similar to the
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  series but manages to improve on the gameplay formula and tell a compelling story that improves as it develops.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Metaphor: ReFantazio's
  </em>
  fantasy element is distinguished by its inclusion of fairies and various races, yet it stands apart in the fantasy genre due to its unique character designs and Victorian-esque architecture. The nightmarish monster designs rank among the most bizarre, featuring grotesque and horrific creatures for players to battle. The turn-based battles are as stylish and tactical as the latest entries in the
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  series, but the combat is faster-paced and feels fresh again.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-9">
  <span class="item-num">
   23
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 9
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-beautiful-jrpg-that-ticks-all-the-right-boxes">
  A Beautiful JRPG That Ticks All The Right Boxes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1343460816" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1343460816" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1343460816" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1343460816" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1343460816-img" id="article-gallery-4-1343460816">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1343460816" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1742251537">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Final Fantasy 9
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the most high fantasy games in the mainline series. Where many entries combine science fiction and fantasy,
  <em>
   FF9
  </em>
  is a throwback to the early days of the iconic JRPG series. Even if players aren't swayed by nostalgia there is something magical about this entry, from the opening scenes with the flying ship to when players get their first glimpse of the little mage Vivi making his way through the crowds in Alexandria.
 </p>
 <p>
  While it contains emotional and darker moments,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 9
  </em>
  possesses a less somber tone compared to its predecessors on the PS1, featuring a light-heartedness that is more akin to games from the
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Mana
  </em>
  series.
  <em>
   FF9
  </em>
  leads players through a thrilling adventure where minor events gradually lead to a grand narrative. Additionally, once the world becomes accessible, it is filled with numerous secrets and side quests to uncover.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-39-s-dogma-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   22
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon's Dogma 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-stunning-world-filled-with-magic-and-mystery">
  A Stunning World Filled With Magic And Mystery
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-436254140" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-436254140" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-436254140" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-436254140" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-436254140-img" id="article-gallery-5-436254140">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-436254140" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1130653252">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dragon's Dogma 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  is an open-world action RPG set in a merciless fantasy realm teeming with creatures, monsters, and dragons, drawing inspiration from renowned fantasy works ranging from
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  to Harryhausen classics such as
  <em>
   Jason and the Argonauts
  </em>
  .
  <em>
  </em>
  The narrative is serviceable, but not as memorable as
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  series,
  <em>
  </em>
  even though it has improved considerably from the first game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma 2,
  </em>
  with its open-world gameplay, diverse classes—also referred to as vocations—and an impressive combat system provides a distinctive experience that seems customized for each player.
  <em>
   Dragon's Dogma 2
  </em>
  instills a sense of wonder that drives players to continue exploring. Additionally, battling massive creatures such as ogres, dragons, and the Cyclops is consistently exhilarating, and the magnitude and scale of the gigantic Talos are truly awe-inspiring.
 </p>
 <h2 id="trials-of-mana-2020">
  <span class="item-num">
   21
  </span>
  <span>
   Trials Of Mana (2020)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-whimsical-family-fantasy-adventure">
  A Whimsical Family Fantasy Adventure
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1234985204" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1234985204" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1234985204" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1234985204" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1234985204-img" id="article-gallery-6-1234985204">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1234985204" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1093816684">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Trials of Mana
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a remake of the Super Famicom (SNES) classic of the same name that launched in 1995. The 1995 version was translated, ported, and launched as part of the
  <em>
   Collection of Mana
  </em>
  in 2019, but this is a 3D remake of the sequel to the fan-favorite
  <em>
   Secret of Mana.
  </em>
  Players can select a lead and two party members from six selectable characters. The story is an entertaining
  <em>
   Dragon Quest-
  </em>
  style adventure in an immersive fantasy world that harks back to the innocence and simplicity of 16-bit era JRPGs. It's a solid introduction to the
  <em>
   Mana
  </em>
  series before the upcoming
  <em>
   Visions of Mana
  </em>
  launches in 2024.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="golden-axe-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Golden Axe (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-classic-side-scrolling-sword-amp-sorcery-fantasy-fighter-from-sega">
  A Classic Side Scrolling Sword &amp; Sorcery Fantasy Fighter From Sega
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-632265375" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-632265375" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-632265375" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-632265375" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-632265375-img" id="article-gallery-7-632265375">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-632265375" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-2101313863">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released
   </strong>
   : January 27, 1989 (first)
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developer
   </strong>
   : Sega
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms
   </strong>
   : PC, PlayStation 2, PlayStation Portable (in
   <em>
    Sega Genesis Collection
   </em>
   ), Sega Genesis/Megadrive, Sega Master System.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Golden Axe
   </strong>
  </em>
  series is a side-scrolling action series from Sega based on Sword &amp; Sworcery books and movies like
  <em>
   Conan
  </em>
  but implements elements of high fantasy into the characters, magic, and stories. Robert E. Howard's
  <em>
   Conan
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Kull
  </em>
  novels influence the barbarian and Amazonian characters, but the Tolkienesque races and villains like Death Adder are present. Ignoring
  <em>
   Beast Rider
  </em>
  on the PS3, fantasy fans will enjoy the original trilogy, which is available as part of the
  <em>
   Sega Genesis/Megadrive Collection.
  </em>
  Sega announced a new
  <em>
   Golden Axe
  </em>
  title in the works at the 2023 Game Awards.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-16">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 16
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dark-fantasy-with-an-incredible-soundtrack-and-kaiju-like-boss-fights">
  A Dark Fantasy With An Incredible Soundtrack And Kaiju-Like Boss Fights
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-2054740160" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-2054740160" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-2054740160" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-2054740160" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-2054740160-img" id="article-gallery-8-2054740160">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-2054740160" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1649219150">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Adopting a more action-based fighting system,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Final Fantasy 16
   </strong>
  </em>
  utilizes a
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  -style combat. However, it is still a
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  game with explorable maps, side quests, towns, and endearing characters. While the mechanics and focus on one character limit the scope of customization, the 2023 release feels like more of a
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  game than - the still enjoyable -
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 16
  </em>
  utilizes a dark medieval fantasy visually similar to the
  <em>
   Game of Thrones
  </em>
  TV show. The world is a bit drab, but there are many high-fantasy elements that fans will love. There is sorcery, dragoons, dragons, knights, magic, orcs, goblins, and more. Moreover, the Godzilla-like boss battles are some of the most epic in gaming.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kingdoms-of-amalur">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Kingdoms Of Amalur
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="epic-action-rpg-with-an-excellent-combat-system-and-intriguing-world">
  Epic Action RPG With An Excellent Combat System And intriguing World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1554963118" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1554963118" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1554963118" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1554963118" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1554963118-img" id="article-gallery-9-1554963118">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1554963118" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-972819856">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not held in the same regard as
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Kingdoms of Amalur
   </strong>
  </em>
  gained a cult following among RPG fans thanks to its dream-like fantasy world, lore, and flexible combat system that played like a hack-and-slash game. Created by a dream team of developers,
  <em>
   Kingdoms of Amalur
  </em>
  was overseen by
  <em>
   Spawn's
  </em>
  Todd McFarlane, fantasy writer R.A. Salvadore,
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  designer Ken Rolston, and composer Grant Kirkhope.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Kingdoms of Amalur: Re-Reckoning
  </em>
  was good news for fans as the now-classic RPG was remastered, and this version even received a new story expansion called
  <em>
   Fatesworn
  </em>
  . While not as dark or in-depth as
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Kingdom of Amalur
  </em>
  's world, characters, and excellent gameplay deserve praise.
 </p>
 <h2 id="middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Middle-earth: Shadow Of Mordor (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-open-world-action-rpg-set-in-the-lord-of-the-rings-universe">
  An Open World Action RPG Set In The Lord Of The Rings Universe
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1451238959" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1451238959" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1451238959" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1451238959" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1451238959-img" id="article-gallery-10-1451238959">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1451238959" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1128547075">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With franchises associated with high fantasy, few are more prominent than
  <em>
   Middle-earth
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  by J.R.R. Tolkien. Tolkienesque is associated with most fantasy settings, from
  <em>
   Dragon Age
  </em>
  to
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate
  </em>
  . However, it does not get more Tolkienesque than two quality titles set in the
  <em>
   LOTR
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  universe,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor
   </strong>
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Shadow of War.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  The games put players in the shoes of a ranger named Talion. He is killed in battle but revived with the powers of a Wraith and is hellbent on taking revenge on Sauron's armies of orcs. The story is set between
  <em>
   The Hobbit
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  and portrays a universe that satisfies fans of the movies and TV shows.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chained-echoes">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Chained Echoes
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="medieval-fantasy-and-mechs-merge-in-this-stunning-snes-inspired-rpg">
  Medieval Fantasy And Mechs Merge In This Stunning SNES-Inspired RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1593506615" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1593506615" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1593506615" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1593506615" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1593506615-img" id="article-gallery-11-1593506615">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1593506615" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1710333729">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Chained Echoes
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a retro-style fantasy RPG that is a love letter to classic 16 and 32-bit JRPGs like
  <em>
   Chrono Trigger
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Xenogears.
  </em>
  It was one of the best indie games of 2022, with its beautiful 2D visuals, strong narrative, world, and a cast of likable characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Chained Echoes
  </em>
  combines elements of the fantasy genre and even includes some science fiction using mechs and magical technology. It is an old-school JRPG that feels modern thanks to its refinements of the turn-based combat and skill system. Incredibly,
  <em>
   Chained Echoes
  </em>
  is a passion project created by one person with a stunning soundtrack by composer Eddie Marianukroh.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elden-ring">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Elden Ring
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-vast-explorable-dark-fantasy-world-with-layers-of-depth">
  A Vast Explorable Dark Fantasy World With Layers Of Depth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1814923242" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1814923242" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1814923242" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1814923242" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1814923242-img" id="article-gallery-12-1814923242">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1814923242" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-490836967">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Elden Ring
   </em>
  </strong>
  cemented its legacy as the Game of the Year Awards show winner in 2022. It
  <em>
  </em>
  is an easy recommendation for high fantasy lovers who like their fantasy setting dark and dangerous.
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  was developed by the same studio that created and popularised the Souls-like sub-genre.
 </p>
 <p>
  FromSoft's open-world RPG title will be familiar to fans of the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  series, except it has taken the evolutionary step of setting it in a vast open-world landscape. For fantasy lovers, there are dragons, trolls, dark knights, and many other creatures to tangle with.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-39-s-crown">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon's Crown
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-stunning-side-scrolling-fantasy-rpg-and-beat-em-up-hybrid">
  A Stunning Side Scrolling Fantasy RPG And Beat-Em-Up Hybrid
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-2074652154" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-2074652154" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-2074652154" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-2074652154" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-2074652154-img" id="article-gallery-13-2074652154">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-2074652154" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-754470311">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Originally released as a Vita title, Vanillaware's action RPG
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dragon's Crown
   </strong>
  </em>
  didn't get the audience it deserved upon its launch. However, thanks to the PS4 port, which features stunning HD 2D visuals, it can be experienced by more fans.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon's Crown
  </em>
  plays similarly to classic coin-op beat-em-ups like
  <em>
   Dungeons &amp; Dragons
  </em>
  and the
  <em>
   Golden Axe
  </em>
  franchise. However, it features RPG mechanics that will keep players returning for more. With a campaign set in a fantasy world and couch co-op gameplay,
  <em>
   Dragon's Crown
  </em>
  is a unique action RPG that can hook players in for hours.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-lord-of-the-rings-the-third-age">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   The Lord Of The Rings: The Third Age
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-turn-based-fantasy-rpg-set-in-peter-jackson-39-s-middle-earth">
  A Turn-Based Fantasy RPG Set In Peter Jackson's Middle-earth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-153966881" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-153966881" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-153966881" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-153966881" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-153966881-img" id="article-gallery-14-153966881">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-153966881" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-86998846">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Lord of the Rings: The Third Age
   </strong>
  </em>
  has become a forgotten classic. As a result of the best version never leaving the GameCube, PS2, and Xbox era, many modern gamers may miss out on what is one of the best games and RPGs set in Tolkien's universe. It borrowed several elements from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  with its turn-based combat and the execution of its narrative.
 </p>
 <p>
  Like
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  , it is a more linear experience when compared to Western-developed RPGs like
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls: Morrowind.
  </em>
  However, despite these shortcomings, it is an excellent way to be immersed in Peter Jackson's interpretation of the
  <em>
   Lord of the Rings
  </em>
  and meet familiar faces and voice performances from the trilogy.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="divinity-2-the-dragon-knight-saga">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Divinity 2: The Dragon Knight Saga
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-epic-open-world-rpg-set-in-the-divinity-universe">
  An Epic Open World RPG Set In The Divinity Universe
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1886264730" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1886264730" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1886264730" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1886264730" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1886264730-img" id="article-gallery-15-1886264730">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1886264730" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-727619973">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Not to be confused with the more recent
  <em>
   Divinity: Original Sin 2
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Divinity 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  is based in the game universe and features very different gameplay.
  <em>
   Divinity 2
  </em>
  is a third-person action RPG set in a fully 3D world.
  <em>
   Divinity 2
  </em>
  has a ton of depth, lore, and hours of gaming for fantasy fans to lose themselves in.
 </p>
 <p>
  The protagonist gains the ability to transform into a dragon to traverse the vast landscape using the same engine that created
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls: Oblivion.
  </em>
  The combat is a little janky, but the writing is superb, with lots of humor and connections to the more popular
  <em>
   Original Sin
  </em>
  series.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-age-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Age (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-rich-dark-fantasy-world-from-the-creators-of-the-original-baldur-39-s-gate-games">
  A Rich Dark Fantasy World From The Creators Of The Original Baldur's Gate Games
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-1752105665" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-1752105665" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-1752105665" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-1752105665" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-1752105665-img" id="article-gallery-16-1752105665">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-1752105665" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-549984959">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Origins
  </em>
  was the first entry in the series and BioWare’s first fantasy RPG since the incredible
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate
  </em>
  series. Unlike
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  the
  <em>
   Dragon Age
  </em>
  series was not set in the already established
  <em>
   Forgotten Realms -
  </em>
  <em>
   Dungeons &amp; Dragons
  </em>
  universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  BioWare had to create its universe from scratch. Thanks to their hard work, the franchise expanded into novels, board games, comics, and an anime movie. The universe is expansive, with a sequel in the works, and very Tolkienesque but has the dark tone and violence of the
  <em>
   Game of Thrones
  </em>
  novels.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-quest-11">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Quest 11
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-stunning-and-colorful-fantasy-rpg-suitable-for-the-family">
  A Stunning And Colorful Fantasy RPG Suitable For The Family
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1994149952" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1994149952" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1994149952" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1994149952" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1994149952-img" id="article-gallery-17-1994149952">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1994149952" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-416107061">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  series is a Japanese RPG launched on the NES in 1986. The series is a colorful and whimsical fantasy accessible to players of all ages—the most recent entry,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Dragon Quest 11
   </em>
  </strong>
  , may be the best entry in the series yet.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game can last a player up to a hundred hours and has arguably the best story next to
  <em>
   Dragon Quest 5
  </em>
  , with enough twists to surprise even the most hardened of RPG fans.
  <em>
   Dragon Quest 11
  </em>
  <em>
   S
  </em>
  is
  <em>
  </em>
  an updated ultimate edition of the game released on the Nintendo Switch, featuring new cutscenes, orchestral music, a classic 2D mode, and all the DLC released on the PS4 and Xbox One.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-legend-of-zelda-breath-of-the-wild">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   The Legend Of Zelda: Breath Of The Wild
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-massive-open-world-fantasy-rpg-from-one-of-the-greatest-series">
  A Massive Open World Fantasy RPG From One Of The Greatest Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1127788580" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1127788580" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1127788580" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1127788580" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1127788580-img" id="article-gallery-18-1127788580">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1127788580" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-886514982">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda
  </em>
  series is a Nintendo-exclusive action-adventure game that saw its first entry on the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES) in 1986. Since then, nearly every game in the series has become one of the most influential fantasy games ever created.
 </p>
 <p>
  Games like
  <em>
   The Legend of Zelda: Link’s Awakening
  </em>
  inspired the classic RPG
  <em>
   Alundra.
  </em>
  More recently,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Breath of the Wild
   </em>
  </strong>
  has inspired the likes of
  <em>
   Immortals: Fenix Rising
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . Link's latest adventure
  <em>
  </em>
  is one of the best fantasy adventure games available. It has a beautiful world to explore and lore to keep fantasy fans gripped.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="pillars-of-eternity-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Pillars Of Eternity (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dark-fantasy-crpg-inspired-by-the-baldur-39-s-gate-series">
  A Dark Fantasy CRPG Inspired By The Baldur's Gate Series
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-1928660890" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-1928660890" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-1928660890" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-1928660890" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-1928660890-img" id="article-gallery-19-1928660890">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-1928660890" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-12465633">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pillars of Eternity
   </strong>
  </em>
  series was a crowd-funded RPG series designed to pay tribute to the old school computer RPGs like
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate.
  </em>
  It was developed by Obsidian, who worked on games like
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic 2,
  </em>
  and the critically acclaimed
  <em>
   The Outer Worlds.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Not only is
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity
  </em>
  an incredible RPG experience, but it features some of the absolute best writing ever seen in a video game. Furthermore, despite being a game using an old-school isometric viewpoint, the art and high-resolution visuals are a treat for the eyes.
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity
  </em>
  was originally a PC game, but it has been adapted beautifully to consoles.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dark-souls-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Dark Souls (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-punishing-but-rewarding-dark-fantasy-rpg-trilogy">
  A Punishing But Rewarding Dark Fantasy RPG Trilogy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-217899534" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-217899534" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-217899534" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-217899534" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-217899534-img" id="article-gallery-20-217899534">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-217899534" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-1714512148">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Even though the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Dark Souls
   </strong>
  </em>
  series is a trilogy, the first game was a spiritual successor to the original
  <em>
   Demon's Souls.
  </em>
  All three games in the trilogy have now been released on current-generation systems,
  <em>
  </em>
  with the first two games getting remastered with improved visuals and frame rates. The
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  series and
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  have spawned their sub-genre of challenging action RPGs.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game is a dark medieval fantasy setting like nothing else, as the player is tasked to explore and fight through the post-apocalyptic lands of once-great kingdoms. Unlike most RPGs, the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  series relies on indirect environmental storytelling, allowing players to piece the lore together dynamically at their pace.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed: Black Flag Manga Sequel Gets A Physical Release</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/assassins-creed-black-flag-sequel-physical-release/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Assassin's Creed: Black Flag is a beloved game known for its great mechanics and story.
     </li>
     <li>
      Viz Media will release the sequel manga, Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple, in Fall 2025.
     </li>
     <li>
      The manga will follow Edward Kenway's search for Pieces of Eden in Southeast Asia and his descendant's modern storyline.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon has-sub-content">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       What Is Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple About?
       <span class="collapsible-quick-link">
       </span>
      </div>
      <ul class="table-content-sub-level is-collapse">
       <li class="table-content-element icon is-sub-level">
        Assassin's Creed Shadows Is Also Getting A Manga
       </li>
      </ul>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Assassin's Creed: Black Flag
   </em>
  </strong>
  is the sixth installment in the Assassin's Creed franchise. The game was released a decade ago but is enjoyed by fans to this day. Assassin's Creed: Black Flag follows the story of Edward Kenway, a Welsh pirate who lived during the Golden Age of Piracy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gamers who have played Assassin's Creed: Black Flag know that it is a phenomenal game with great mechanics and story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ubisoft gave fans a gift by releasing a sequel to Edward Kenway's story in Webtoon format. It has been available on the webtoon website for a while, but a physical edition was missing. Thankfully, Viz Media has finally announced that
  <strong>
   Assassin's Creed: Black Flag's sequel manga, Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple, will release in Fall 2025
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="what-is-assassin-39-s-creed-forgotten-temple-about">
  What Is Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple About?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="ac4 black flag remake" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/ac4-black-flag-whale.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple follows Edward Kenway as he searches for Pieces of Eden in Southeast Asia. The modern segment covers Noah Kim, Edward Kenway's descendant, who is kidnapped and forced to go through his ancestor's memories. The story for Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple has been written by ARC. Meanwhile, the story's adaptation is handled by three people:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   SHYTAN
  </li>
  <li>
   NOHT
  </li>
  <li>
   LEON
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The story is divided into two volumes, and the upcoming physical release will have both. While it's not necessary to read the manga, fans who enjoyed Edward Kenway's adventures in Assassin's Creed: Black Flag should give it a try.
 </p>
 <h3 id="assassin-39-s-creed-shadows-is-also-getting-a-manga">
  Assassin's Creed Shadows Is Also Getting A Manga
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1067835663" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1067835663" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1067835663" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1067835663" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1067835663-img" id="article-gallery-1-1067835663">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1067835663" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-15798394">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Aside from Black Flag's manga getting an English print release, it was recently confirmed that Assassin's Creed Shadows will get a manga of its own. The manga will be released in Japan on March 20, 2025, the same day as the game. Assassin's Creed Shadows' manga will serve as a prequel to the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Based on the official description, it will follow the story of a mysterious young assassin who fights against the Templars and their growing influence in Japan. A global release date for the manga has not been revealed, but the official X (formerly Twitter) account for the franchise has confirmed it will be released later in other regions.
 </p>
 <p>
  The news about Assassin's Creed Shadows getting a manga release has hyped fans further for the game's release. They are both excited and intrigued to read the manga and see how it will be connected to the main story of the game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_18">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Assassin's Creed: Forgotten Temple will be released in Fall 2025.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Source: X (formerly Twitter)
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
