<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Announces Road to Unova Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-road-to-unova-event-date-details/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO's Road to Unova event starts Feburary 24 with Unova starters, raids, and new eggs.
     </li>
     <li>
      Trainers can expect special Genesect raids and event bonuses.
     </li>
     <li>
      A new Pokemon GO Tour Pass unlocks rewards and encounters during the event.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has announced Road to Unova, an upcoming event that starts on February 24. This is yet another
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  announcement for the GO Tour 2025, the augmented reality game's annual event celebrating a specific region of the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  The event will have three stages, with in-person activities happening February 21, 22, and 23 for trainers in Los Angeles, U.S., and New Taipei, Taiwan. During this period, they will enjoy Pokemon spawns based on the seasons, Unown attracted by Incense, raids, and a selection of pocket monsters hatching from 2 km, 5 km, and 10 km eggs. March 1 and 2 will see the Pokemon GO Tour: Unova - Global, an event to keep worldwide players engaged with discounted trades and Unova-themed wild spawns, eggs, and raids. In anticipation of the global phase of this year's GO Fest, Niantic has good news for players.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  has announced the Road to Unova event, which will begin on February 24 at 10 am, and end on March 1 at 10 am local time. During this period, players will encounter the Unova starters in the wild and have the chance to see their intermediate evolutions. There will be one-, three-, and five-star raids, the latter taking place from February 24 to 28 with a selection of powerful Pokemon such as Reshiram, Zekrom, and the Genesect variants with special backgrounds. New 2 km egg spawns will be available, along with themed Timed Research and Field Research tasks, egg hatching distance halved, and a Remote Raid Pass limit set at 20.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-announces-new-go-tour-2025-themed-event">
  Pokemon GO Announces New GO Tour 2025-Themed Event
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2093405792" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2093405792" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2093405792" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2093405792" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2093405792-img" id="article-gallery-1-2093405792">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2093405792" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1366440072">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   When: Monday, February 24 from 10 am to Saturday, March 1, at 10 am local time
  </li>
  <li>
   New Pokemon: Shiny Meloetta
  </li>
  <li>
   Wild Encounters: Snivy, Tepig, and Oshawott. Chance of encounters with Servine, Pignite, and Dewott
  </li>
  <li>
   Eggs (2km): Roggenrola, Timburr, Karrablast, Shelmet, and Larvesta
  </li>
  <li>
   Players can use the new GO Tour Pass
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Added for the event
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Timed Research
  </li>
  <li>
   Field Research Tasks
  </li>
  <li>
   Avatar items and stickers
  </li>
  <li>
   Two $4.99 new tickets (one raid- and other hatch-focused)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Event Bonuses
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   1/2 Egg Hatch Distance when Eggs are placed in an Incubator during the event period.
  </li>
  <li>
   Remote Raid Pass limit increased to 20 from Monday, February 24 to Friday, February 28, 2025.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   One-Star Raids
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Snivy
  </li>
  <li>
   Tepig
  </li>
  <li>
   Oshawott
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Three-Star Raids
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Druddigon
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Five-Star Raids: Monday, February 24
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Genesect
  </li>
  <li>
   Genesect (Shock Drive)
  </li>
  <li>
   Genesect (Burn Drive)
  </li>
  <li>
   Genesect (Chill Drive)
  </li>
  <li>
   Genesect (Douse Drive)
   <ul>
    <li>
     Genesect encountered in raids will know the Normal-type Charged Attack Techno Blast.
    </li>
    <li>
     Genesect (Shock Drive) encountered in raids will know the Electric-type Charged Attack Techno Blast.
    </li>
    <li>
     Genesect (Burn Drive) encountered in raids will know the Fire-type Charged Attack Techno Blast.
    </li>
    <li>
     Genesect (Chill Drive) encountered in raids will know the Ice-type Charged Attack Techno Blast.
    </li>
    <li>
     Genesect (Douse Drive) encountered in raids will know the Water-type Charged Attack Techno Blast.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Five-Star Raids: Tuesday, February 25
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Cobalion
  </li>
  <li>
   Terrakion
  </li>
  <li>
   Virizion
   <ul>
    <li>
     Cobalion, Terrakion, and Virizion encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Sacred Sword.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Five-Star Raids: Wednesday, February 26
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Therian Forme Tornadus
  </li>
  <li>
   Therian Forme Thundurus
  </li>
  <li>
   Therian Forme Landorus
   <ul>
    <li>
     Tornadus encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Bleakwind Storm.
    </li>
    <li>
     Thundurus encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Wildbolt Storm.
    </li>
    <li>
     Landorus encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Sandsear Storm.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Five-Star Raids: Thursday, February 27
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Reshiram
   <ul>
    <li>
     Reshiram encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Fusion Flare.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Five-Star Raids: Friday, February 28
  </strong>
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Zekrom
   <ul>
    <li>
     Zekrom encountered in raids will know the Charged Attack Fusion Bolt.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  During Road to Unova, trainers can use the new Pokemon GO Tour Pass to unlock even more rewards. All trainers will receive a free pass, while the deluxe edition can be purchased for $14.99 and will reward buyers with a Victini encounter. A $4.99 ticket for Masterwork Research will mark shiny Meloetta's debut in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO.
  </em>
  Two other tickets will be available; each will cost $4.99, and one will give specific benefits for raids, the other for hatching Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players are waiting for the GO Tour of Unova, the augmented reality game has other active events. Legendary Flight, which added the Dynamax forms of Kantonian birds to the game, ends on February 9. Steeled Resolve, the debut of Corviknight and its evolutions in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , wraps on February 26. The Community Day Classic will be on January 25, while the Lunar New Year event will run from January 29 to February 2.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Saving The Rainbow!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-saving-the-rainbow/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players get accidental eliminations through walls and more in Rainbow Six Siege.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel’s Blade Should Watch Marvel Rivals Closely, and Not For The Reason You Think</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvels-blade-mcu-movie-lore-dracula-new-hero/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  NetEase and Marvel have been collaborating to add in-depth lore to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  that players may be unaware of. With Blade leaked as a character roster addition sometime in the future, NetEase and Marvel should consider fan response to some new Season 1 additions as they perfect the vampire hunter for
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  . While Marvel shouldn’t just look at fan response before perfecting Blade for
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , this info should be kept in mind as development for the MCU’s
  <em>
   Blade
  </em>
  continues.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  By every metric, Marvel Rivals Season 1’s additions have blown players away. With the expanded Battle Pass compared to Season 0, two new characters with more allegedly on the way, and plenty of new skins,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is maintaining its incredible momentum after taking the hero shooter genre by storm.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-39-lore-is-the-best-path-for-character-additions">
  Marvel Rivals' Lore is the Best Path for Character Additions
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-530303763" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-530303763" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-530303763" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-530303763" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-530303763-img" id="article-gallery-1-530303763">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-530303763" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-516048776">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the best parts of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  is also understandably overlooked. Sure, Invisible Woman and Mr. Fantastic are thrilling new additions to the shooter’s character roster, but they’ve also heavily expanded the game’s lore. The Season 1 release trailer and the game’s new main menu opening sequence both highlight the threats the Fantastic Four face and what drew them into the shooter in the first place. A villain to rival them all, Dracula is the main antagonist of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  Season 1.
 </p>
 <p>
  Of course, the best combatant against a vampire is a vampire hunter. Dracula could easily set up Blade’s addition to
  <em>
   Marvel Rival
  </em>
  ’s character roster, but NetEase and Marvel should watch how fans react to Dracula as a villain before committing to using him as a gateway for Blade. In fact, official artwork of Blade facing off against Dracula has already been revealed by
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , solidifying that the two may face off in the shooter’s lore sometime in the future.
 </p>
 <p>
  By navigating to “Heroes,” players can select a hero of their choosing and read one of the various stories centered on the character. These stories focus on
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ’ version of the character, giving players a clear view of how the hero differs from their MCU, film, television, or comic adaptations. These stories also mention other characters that have yet to be introduced to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ’ character roster. As Dracula’s story progresses throughout Season 1, perhaps Blade will be mentioned in the lore associated with other upcoming
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  heroes like the Thing or the Human Torch.
 </p>
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-could-change-the-mcu-39-s-blade">
  Marvel Rivals Could Change the MCU's Blade
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1956434242" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1956434242" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1956434242" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1956434242" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1956434242-img" id="article-gallery-2-1956434242">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1956434242" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-352435719">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Reactions from fans both to the Dracula versus Blade storyline and Blade as a
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  addition as a whole could alter the upcoming
  <em>
   Blade
  </em>
  film. The film’s production history has been a bit rocky to say the least, as filming for
  <em>
   Blade
  </em>
  was halted due to the WGA and SAG-AFTRA strikes in 2023. The lack of information about the film’s production and development over the last year led fans to believe that the project may be scrapped, but Kevin Feige has confirmed that Marvel is dedicated to completing the film.
 </p>
 <p>
  Story details for the film also have yet to be released in full. Though it's unlikely that the MCU
  <em>
   Blade
  </em>
  adaptation’s plot will be similar to his lore in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , the shooter would be a great opportunity for moviegoers to become acquainted with a new version of the character. While Wesley Snipes’ portrayal of the vampire hunter is iconic, modern audiences will likely associate the character with its most recent adaptation in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  . To prime the next generation for Blade, Marvel needs to consider how the character will shape
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  and, in turn, the MCU.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Genshin Impact Leak Teases New Artifact Sets for Version 5.5</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-new-artifact-sets-version-5-5-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      According to a leak, Version 5.5 of Genshin Impact may bring new Artifact Sets to Natlan.
     </li>
     <li>
      The update could introduce a second Artifact Domain in Natlan, shaping in-game strategies.
     </li>
     <li>
      New sets in Genshin Impact will likely complement upcoming characters' abilities.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A recent leak in the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Genshin Impact
   </strong>
  </em>
  community has revealed that Version 5.5 could introduce a second batch of Artifact Sets in Natlan, after a hiatus of four updates. While
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  is known for having a very strict schedule for content updates, there is an argument to be made that Natlan has been an exception in this regard. Version 5.2 launched with an Interlude instead of the final Act of Natlan's Archon Quest, while Version 5.3 and Version 5.4 have both skipped adding a map expansion to the new region.
 </p>
 <p>
  As a result, the tail end of Natlan is expected to be heavy in content, while the stretch of updates between Version 5.1 and Version 5.5 has been described as dry by the
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  community. While the Archon Quest was of equal length to Fontaine and Sumeru, and Ochkanatlan was well-received by fans, Natlan in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  will only have two zones and one Artifact Domain to work with seven months after launch.
 </p>
 <p>
  According to hxg_diluc via DK2, Version 5.5 will seemingly be the update to introduce the second Artifact Domain for Natlan, and there are several factors that point in this direction. Version 5.2 introduced the Flower-Feather Clan and the Masters of the Night-Wind, but the Collective of Plenty is still missing. Since Version 5.4 is set to launch without a new area, and Iansan is rumored for Version 5.5, adding two Artifact Sets in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  to the upcoming Natlan map expansion is a likely outcome.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-could-be-adding-new-artifact-sets-in-version-5-5">
  Genshin Impact Could Be Adding New Artifact Sets in Version 5.5
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1652616200" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1652616200" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1652616200" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1652616200" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1652616200-img" id="article-gallery-1-1652616200">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1652616200" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1805358768">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Given that Natlan supports prefer Scroll of the Hero of Cinder City, and Natlan hypercarries prefer Obsidian Codex, these new Artifact Sets would have to focus on a new niche entirely. While the leak doesn't mention the exact bonuses of the new Artifact Sets, it's important to remember that they tend to synergize with the ability kits of upcoming
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  characters. According to the list, Iansan, Varesa, Effie, and Ifa are all expected to launch between Version 5.5 and Version 5.6.
 </p>
 <p>
  Assuming both Iansan and Varesa are Electro characters in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  , then one of the sets could potentially be dedicated to the Overload or Superconduct playstyle, with the latter being extremely unlikely. Given the rise of Overload in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  a dedicated Artifact Set could provide further synergy beyond having Chevreuse in the team. On the other hand, the second half of Natlan will also see the release of several 5-Stars and 4-Stars not tied to the Nightsoul mechanic, such as Skirk and Dahlia. Whatever its effects end up being, they will almost certainly conform to the needs of these characters.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Operation Rainbow!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-operation-rainbow/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player makes an excellent grenade throw and more accidental wins in Rainbow Six Siege.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
