<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>New Pokemon TCG Pocket Event Adds New Promo Cards</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-pocket-solo-battles-cresselia-ex-drop-event-new-promo-cards/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon TCG Pocket's new event offers players the chance to collect promo cards like Cresselia ex.
     </li>
     <li>
      Promo cards may have different abilities and HP compared to regular cards, enhancing gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can obtain promo cards like Electivire and Turtwig by playing Solo Battles until February 16.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket
   </em>
  </strong>
  started the new Cresselia ex drop event on February 3, giving players the chance to earn five new promo cards.
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  players get new cards by opening booster packs, but it's through events that they pull promo cards, which are special additions to the collection.
 </p>
 <p>
  That's because
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  promo cards can feature changes in abilities and HP compared to their original counterparts. One example is the Eevee promo card, whose ability and illustration differ from the regular cards of the popular Normal-type. Blastoise is another case, as its regular cards have different illustrations and moves from the promo variant. This time, players will have the chance to get more promo cards related to the game's latest expansion.
 </p>
 <p>
  The new Solo Battle event Cresselia ex Drop began on February 2, through which players can grab the new Cresselia ex promo card. The event started at 10 pm PST and will end on February 16 at 9:59 pm PST. In addition to the card featuring the powerful Legendary Pokemon, players can add promo cards of Electivire, Misdreavus, Skarmory, and Turtwig to their collections. Similarly to previous events, players must play against the AI battles divided by difficulty levels, obtaining promo packs, hourglasses, stardust, and shop tickets as rewards.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-tcg-pocket-starts-new-cresselia-ex-drop-event">
  Pokemon TCG Pocket Starts New Cresselia ex Drop Event
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1114333431" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1114333431" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1114333431" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1114333431" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1114333431-img" id="article-gallery-1-1114333431">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1114333431" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-499858997">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   When: Now until February 17 at 9:59 pm PST
  </li>
  <li>
   New promo cards: Cresselia ex, Electivire, Misdreavus, Skarmory, and Turtwig
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  As a Psychic-type card, Cresselia ex's main weakness is Dark-type cards such as Ekans and Arbok, Koffing, and Weezing. According to ptcgpocket.gg, there is only a 12.66% chance of Cresselia ex dropping when opening promo packs, while Electivire has a 15.82% chance, and Turtwig, Misdreavus, and Skarmory have a 23.84% chance of appearing. Promo card packs, on the other hand, have a 51% chance of dropping at the Beginner level, and a 100% chance of coming at the Expert level. As such, a helpful
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  trick shared previously can greatly help players save time and make the most of the event's stamina.
 </p>
 <p>
  While taking part in the new Solo Battles to obtain new promotional cards, players can finally pull cards from the second
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  set. Named Space-Time Smackdown, the expansion has most of the cards focused on Sinnoh Pokemon, with Dialga and Palkia gracing the packs. The legendary duo received regular exes, immersive variants, and full art with a gold background, adding to the list of most desired cards. Additionally, players will find other Sinnoh cards such as the starters Piplup, Turtwig, and Chinchar, and 10 new ex cards such as Pachirisu and Gallade, colorful and shiny border variants.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Warcraft Patch 11.1 Has Some Big Surprises for Roleplayers</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/world-of-warcraft-patch-11-1-roleplay-emote-items-restrictions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      World of Warcraft Patch 11.1 is introducing items for unique animations like playing dead, holding food, and more.
     </li>
     <li>
      Consumables for roleplaying cost one gold and last 15 mins, but they are currently limited to the Low Blow zone.
     </li>
     <li>
      Additional items allow holding food and performing various animations across World of Warcraft.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    World of Warcraft
   </strong>
  </em>
  is adding some new items in Patch 11.1 that let characters use unique emotes and animations, including playing dead, taking a combat stance, and even holding different types of food and drink. Though some of these items have some pretty severe limitations, they will be a massive help for
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  roleplayers who want to increase their immersion.
 </p>
 <p>
  Patch 11.1, Undermined, is adding an expansive zone full of secrets, activities, and items for fans to find. Recently, players discovered several such surprises in the
  <em>
   WoW
  </em>
  update in the form of two height-adjusting potions, as well as Noggenfogger Select FRESH, which allows Goblin characters to lean against the wall when the consumable is drunk.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, several other consumables have been located on the Patch 11.1 Public Test Realm that let fans interact with the world in unique ways. The Low Blow – an underground fighting ring in a sewer grate found in Hovel Hill in Undermine – features a vendor named Brix the Bloody who sells a number of new consumables. According to screenshots taken by Wowhead writer Portergauge, these items let one perform unique animations, including adopting various combat stances, being knocked down, or playing dead. There are even some items that let players create a counter above their head, seemingly to track health, hits, or other roleplaying mechanics.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="roleplaying-emotes-in-world-of-warcraft-patch-11-1">
  Roleplaying Emotes in World of Warcraft Patch 11.1
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-84146232" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-84146232" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-84146232" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-84146232" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-84146232-img" id="article-gallery-1-84146232">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-84146232" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1471075431">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Consumable
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fighting Guide: Armed Combat
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Equipped weapon fighting stance
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fighting Guide: Unarmed Combat
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Racial unarmed fighting stance
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fighting Guide: Magical Combat
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Magical fighting stance
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       FIghting Guide: Grappling Combat
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Monk's unarmed fighting stance
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Scoring Guide: Start Counter
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Display with three red points above head
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Scoring Guide: Remove Point
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Remove one point from counter
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Scoring Guide: Add Point
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Add one point to counter
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Injury Guide: Stunned
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Stunned animation
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Injury Guide: Play Dead
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Knocked down animation
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Injury Guide: Knockdown
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Death animation
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Each of these items costs a single gold, and lasts for up to 15 minutes, making them affordable, easy ways to spice up roleplaying encounters with animations that are normally not freely accessible. Unfortunately, these items can presently only be used in the Low Blow within the
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  Patch 11.1 zone of Undermine, meaning their usefulness is currently quite limited.
 </p>
 <p>
  That said, there are several other items fans can get that have no such restrictions. Portergauge also found several consumables from vendors in Undermine that let a character hold various food items, including a hamburger, hotdog, pineapple cocktail, and a box of takeout. Like the Low Blow items, these consumables are cheap and last for 15 minutes, but can seemingly be used in areas other than Undermine in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  These aren’t the first such items to be added to the game – there are similar ones purchased from the Siren Isle in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  that let characters walk around with books, crates, and other objects. Between these and the bevy of emote consumables in Patch 11.1, it seems like
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  is giving roleplayers a lot to be excited about. Hopefully, the consumables locked to the Low Blow are just a test run and will eventually be usable elsewhere in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Times Connections Hints and Answers for #604 February 4, 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nyt-connections-hints-answers-604-february-4-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Connections
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a fun and engaging word game where you group sixteen words into four groups. It’s a mix of logic and creativity, and while some connections jump out right away, others can be a bit trickier. The challenge lies in spotting the subtle links that tie the words together.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  If you already know how to play
  <em>
   Connections
  </em>
  , but you need a little help to keep things moving, this hints and answers guide has got you covered. It’s here to offer gentle nudges and spoilers, making sure you can enjoy the puzzle without the frustration.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="words-in-the-nyt-connections-puzzle-604-for-february-4-2025">
  Words in the NYT Connections Puzzle #604 for February 4, 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="NYT-New-York-Times-Games-Connections-February-04-2025" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyt-new-york-times-games-connections-february-04-2025.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Connections
  </em>
  puzzle for today contains the words:
  <strong>
   File, Save, Butter, Chicken, Spread, Sand, Under, Store, Lady, Favorite, Sticky, Preserve, keep, Buff, Parlay,
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   Grind.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-is-the-definition-of-parlay">
  What is the Definition of Parlay?
 </h3>
 <p>
  Parlay is a word that is normally associated with gambling. It can mean "to bet or gamble the money you just won from a previous bet." It can used as a noun to describe that kind of bet or a verb. There is also a slang term that means "to use something that you have to achieve a goal."
 </p>
 <h2 id="hints-for-the-nyt-connections-puzzle">
  Hints for the NYT Connections Puzzle
 </h2>
 <p>
  If you are looking for a helpful hint or spoiler for this innovative puzzle game, you can find a whole bunch of them below. Open each of these sections with the "Read More" link underneath each of the different headers below.
 </p>
 <h3 id="some-general-hints-for-the-whole-connections-puzzle">
  Some General Hints for the Whole Connections Puzzle
 </h3>
 <h3 id="yellow-nyt-connections-category-hints">
  Yellow NYT Connections Category Hints
 </h3>
 <h3 id="yellow-connections-category-answer">
  Yellow Connections Category Answer
 </h3>
 <h3 id="yellow-connections-category-answer-and-all-four-words">
  Yellow Connections Category Answer and All Four Words
 </h3>
 <h3 id="green-nyt-connections-category-hints">
  Green NYT Connections Category Hints
 </h3>
 <h3 id="green-connections-category-answer">
  Green Connections Category Answer
 </h3>
 <h3 id="green-connections-category-answer-and-all-four-words">
  Green Connections Category Answer and All Four Words
 </h3>
 <h3 id="blue-nyt-connections-category-hints">
  Blue NYT Connections Category Hints
 </h3>
 <h3 id="blue-connections-category-answer">
  Blue Connections Category Answer
 </h3>
 <h3 id="blue-connections-category-answer-and-all-four-words">
  Blue Connections Category Answer and All Four Words
 </h3>
 <h3 id="purple-nyt-connections-category-hints">
  Purple NYT Connections Category Hints
 </h3>
 <h3 id="purple-connections-category-answer">
  Purple Connections Category Answer
 </h3>
 <h3 id="purple-connections-category-answer-and-all-four-words">
  Purple Connections Category Answer and All Four Words
 </h3>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="answers-for-today-39-s-nyt-connections-604-for-february-4-2025">
  Answers for Today's NYT Connections #604 for February 4, 2025
 </h2>
 <p>
  The full answer to today's
  <em>
   Connection
  </em>
  is in the section below. Inside are all the categories from the mobile puzzle game along with the words that go inside of each of those groups.
 </p>
 <p>
  Want to play? Check out the New York Times Games Connections website available on almost any device with a browser.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 - Minimum &amp; Recommended System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-kcd2-recommended-system-requirements/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       System Requirements For Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you're a fan of exploring medieval Europe, you won't want to miss
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Set in the 15th century, it's the sequel to Warhorse Studios' 2018 debut title. Unlike the first game, this installment is being released exclusively for newer-generation consoles and PC.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While console players don't have to worry about hardware being able to run the game or not, the same can't be said for PC players. Fortunately, the developers have provided detailed system requirements, and there are some interesting details to note.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="system-requirements-for-kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  System Requirements For Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-136899589" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-136899589" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-136899589" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-136899589" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-136899589-img" id="article-gallery-1-136899589">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-136899589" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1082860765">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       PC Specs
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Minimum
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Recommended 1080p
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Recommended 1440p
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Recommended 1080p
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Recommended 1440p
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Best
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Graphic Preset
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Low
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Medium
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Medium
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       High
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Best
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Average Performance
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1080 @ 30 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1080p @ 60 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1440p @ 60 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1080p @ 30 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1440p @ 60 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1440p @ 60 FPS 4K @ 30 FPS
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        CPU
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i5-8400 or AMD Ryzen 5 2600
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i5-13600K or AMD Ryzen 5 7600X
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i5-13600K or AMD Ryzen 5 7600X
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i5-12600K or AMD Ryzen 7 5800X
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i7-13700K or AMD Ryzen 7 7800X3D
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Intel Core i7-13700K or AMD Ryzen 7 7800X3D
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Memory
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       16 GB
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       24 GB
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       24 GB
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       32 GB
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       32 GB
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       32 GB
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        GPU
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 (6GB) or AMD Radeon RX 580
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3060 or AMD Radeon RX 6600 XT
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3060 Ti or AMD Radeon RX 6700 XT
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2060 SUPER or AMD Radeon RX 5700
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce RTX 4070 or AMD Radeon RX 7800 XT
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       NVIDIA GeForce RTX 4080 or AMD Radeon RX 7900 XT
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Storage
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100 GB SSD
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Like most modern AAA games,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  requires Windows 10 64-bit or higher to run — anything lower simply won't work. The game also demands 100 GB of free storage, which should be on an SSD. This isn't unusual, as most modern games now require an SSD instead of an HDD.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-72851614" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-72851614" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-72851614" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-72851614" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-72851614-img" id="article-gallery-2-72851614">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-72851614" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2099097654">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  What stands out is that the game can run on a GeForce GTX 1060 (6GB), though only at 1080p @ 30 FPS with Low Graphics Preset — and that's without any upscaling. The fact that such an old GPU can still handle the game is impressive. Additionally, 16 GB of RAM is required, but higher resolutions and graphics settings will push that requirement up to 32 GB.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     These requirements apply to native resolution, meaning no upscaling has been factored in. If you're using a weaker GPU, using upscaling techniques could help, especially at higher resolutions.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Fable Could Improve the Series' Hero-Villain Dichotomy</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fable-2025-hero-villain-dichotomy-improve-morality-antagonists/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fable needs to move beyond binary morality to offer more complex, contextual choices.
     </li>
     <li>
      Introducing factions with differing interpretations of right and wrong can challenge players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Including villains with relatable backstories can add depth and moral ambiguity to the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fable
   </strong>
  </em>
  series has long been a prime example of choice-driven gameplay, as its innovative morality system helped to pioneer similar mechanics in many of the RPGs that have since followed. Despite its influence, however,
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  's morality system has also proven over time to be rather limiting, as it ultimately boils complex moral decisions down to a binary fight between good and evil. Now, with the upcoming
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  reboot, Playground Games has a unique opportunity to evolve this system into something deeper, more nuanced, and truly reflective of the complexities of morality.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the clearest ways to help any choice-driven game be more morally complex is to ensure its choices offer more than just two distinct choices. For
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  , this would mean replacing its binary morality system with more ambiguous choices — options that make it difficult to tell black from white. However, that much is a given and often doesn't truly put players in a difficult spot when it comes to choices. Instead,
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  may need to go the extra mile with its choice-driven gameplay, perhaps by making morality more contextual and featuring villains that are more relatable.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-fable-can-bring-more-color-to-the-series-39-black-and-white-nature">
  How Fable Can Bring More Color to the Series' Black-and-White Nature
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-317013481" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-317013481" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-317013481" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-317013481" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-317013481-img" id="article-gallery-1-317013481">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-317013481" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1996880646">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="fable-could-make-morality-more-contextual">
  Fable Could Make Morality More Contextual
 </h3>
 <p>
  In addition to incorporating choices that are more complex than traditional binary morality,
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  could increase the difficulty of decisions made in the game by making morality more contextual than universal. Specifically, contextual morality would mean it is more based on the needs of the people involved or the immediate situation at hand, rather than relying on an overarching sense of good and evil. In past games in the
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  series, the player's actions were judged more universally as either good or evil, regardless of the context. The
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  reboot, on the other hand, could change that by introducing situations that aren't as clear as they might initially appear to be.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     <em>
      Fable
     </em>
     may need to go the extra mile with its choice-driven gameplay, perhaps by making morality more contextual and featuring villains that are more relatable.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  To do this,
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  will need to introduce scenarios where the morality of a situation depends more on who and what is directly involved in said situation. A great way to implement this would be to include unique factions or sub-regions in
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  's Albion that have their own interpretation of what is right and wrong, thereby challenging players to think differently. For example, perhaps players might encounter a group of people that feels oppressed by their leaders, even though the actions of the leaders are entirely justifiable. In a circumstance like that, it would then be more for players to decide which to side with, rather than the game simply telling them which is the better side.
 </p>
 <h3 id="fable-could-feature-villains-with-relatable-backstories-and-motivations">
  Fable Could Feature Villains With Relatable Backstories and Motivations
 </h3>
 <p>
  Another very significant move that
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  could make toward moral ambiguity is to feature villains that have more relatable backstories and motivations. Fortunately, based on what has been revealed so far, this might actually be the case for the reboot. According to one of its most recent trailers,
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  's Humphry has a history with who appears to be the game's antagonist. Whether she is the primary antagonist or not, however, it seems as though
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  's protagonist will interact with the character in such a way that could make her more relatable.
 </p>
 <p>
  What a more relatable villain would do for
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  is make their actions appear justifiable at times, which would ultimately complicate things for players when it comes to making choices to stand either for them or against them. This, in addition to making morality more contextual in
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  , would undoubtedly turn the series' binary choice system on its head and offer players an unprecedented degree of ambiguity. Hopefully, Playground Games has considered the criticism of
  <em>
   Fable
  </em>
  's binary morality system and has implemented something more complex than ever before.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
