<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Helldivers 2 CEO Comments On The Lack of a Content Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/helldivers-2-ceo-content-roadmap-arrowhead-game-studios/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Arrowhead Game Studios has continued to have close communication with the community. The newest update given from community communication is on the studios reluctance for a content roadmap. Arrowhead CEO, Shams Jorjani explained that this is because the team likes "not knowing what will happen next".
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 Missing Popular Feature</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/clair-obscur-expedition-33-no-mini-map/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 won't have a mini-map.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players will have access to a compass, with the developers urging free exploration.
     </li>
     <li>
      The title recently went gold and will be released on April 24 for PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series X/S.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The upcoming RPG
  <strong>
   <em>
    Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
   </em>
  </strong>
  won't feature a mini-map, with players being asked to instead rely exclusively on a compass as they explore the game's world. Quickly becoming one of the most highly anticipated titles of 2025,
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  promises to combine some of the best parts of the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Persona
  </em>
  franchises in an entirely new and novel IP.
 </p>
 <p>
  Developed by the French studio Sandfall Interactive, the dark fantasy RPG
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  will tell the story of a group of adventurers on a quest to stop the Paintress, who has the ability to kill everyone of a certain age by simply drawing the numbers on a massive monolith. Being made by a small team of 30 developers, the game has already found massive success ahead of its April release, with preorders for the
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  Collector's Edition selling out within its first few days on the market. More details regarding the title continue to pop up, with the game's producer now confirming that one common feature won't be making an appearance.
 </p>
 <p>
  Francois Meurisse, the COO of Sandfall Interactive and producer of
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  , has confirmed (via Eurogamer) that the game won't include a mini-map, as players are encouraged to explore. According to Meurisse, there is also a canonical reason why players won't be able to rely on a mini-map. "We want players to discover the world as the expedition does it. They don't have a map because every previous expedition failed. So yes, sometimes it can be difficult to find their way," he explained. Players will, however, be able to see an overview map of the entire game world, and will also be able to consult a compass as they try to get their bearings. Audiences are responding well to the game's unique style, with
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  recently going gold.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="clair-obscur-expedition-33-won-39-t-include-a-mini-map">
  Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 Won't Include a Mini Map
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1217150480" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1217150480" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1217150480" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1217150480" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1217150480-img" id="article-gallery-1-1217150480">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1217150480" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-521025627">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  According to Meurisse, the title will feature both linear and semi-open world portions to tell a more focused story. Despite its impressive graphics and flashy combat,
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  will be available for a price much lower than many expected, retailing for $49.99 at launch and promising to contain at least 30 hours of content. Developers at Sandfall Interactive aimed to make the game accessible to as many people as possible, stating that as an indie studio, the pricing made sense.
 </p>
 <p>
  In January, despite the game being months away from launch, it was announced that
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  was getting a live-action feature film adaptation, with the game's developers working closely with Story Kitchen on the project. Sandfall Interactive's first game is scheduled to be released on day one for Xbox Game Pass Ultimate and PC Game Pass on April 24, with the title also coming to PlayStation 5.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Assassin's Creed Shadows Encourages Cautious Gameplay More Than Any Other Entry</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/assassins-creed-shadows-stealth-cautious-gameplay-ai-overhaul/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      AC Shadows emphasizes cautious gameplay due to an AI overhaul.
     </li>
     <li>
      Enemies are more alert and responsive, increasing AC Shadows' challenge.
     </li>
     <li>
      Combat is unforgiving in AC Shadows, pushing players to strategic thinking.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  series has long been defined by its stealth mechanics, though they have been repeatedly adjusted throughout the franchise's history. In more recent entries,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  's stealth was dumbed down in favor of action-oriented gameplay that saw players directly overpowering their foes rather than strategically eliminating them from the cover of tall grass, walls, objects, and more. However,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Assassin's Creed Shadows
   </strong>
  </em>
  has taken the series' stealth system to a new degree of realism and challenge, encouraging more cautious gameplay than any other entry before it.
 </p>
 <p>
  With its AI overhaul and dual protagonist system,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  ensures that players are more likely to play cautiously when controlling Naoe, the game's stealth specialist. Whether they are infiltrating an enemy castle or trying to retrieve a well-guarded treasure chest, players are better off approaching each situation more carefully than the series has ever pushed them to before.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="players-need-to-play-cautiously-in-assassin-39-s-creed-shadows">
  Players Need to Play Cautiously in Assassin's Creed Shadows
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1100902561" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1100902561" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1100902561" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1100902561" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1100902561-img" id="article-gallery-1-1100902561">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1100902561" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1429330093">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="enemies-are-more-alert-than-ever-in-ac-shadows">
  Enemies Are More Alert Than Ever in AC Shadows
 </h3>
 <p>
  The primary way
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  encourages more cautious gameplay is through its extensive AI overhaul, which sees enemies behaving in unprecedented ways that ultimately increase the game's challenge. With
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  ' AI overhaul, enemies are more alert than they have ever been, even before seeing Naoe emerge from the shadows. Enemies in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  still have that iconic
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  AI flair to them, but they are more likely to notice even the slightest cues that Naoe is in the vicinity, and players can guarantee they will respond to those cues.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Yasuke can function in a stealth capacity as well, but there is little need for that, as he is intentionally designed to overpower enemies in direct confrontations.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Once enemies are alerted to Naoe's presence in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , whether they've stumbled on a dead body or spotted a suspicious figure moving through the area, it takes a considerable amount of time for them to reset to their normal position. Even then, from that point on, their awareness is heightened, and it's far more difficult to assassinate them without being detected. For example, should an enemy be investigating some bushes that players have chosen to hide in, attempting to assassinate them might do more harm than good, as enemies can now stop assassinations from happening if they are on high alert. This makes every engagement in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  one that requires plenty of thought before proceeding.
 </p>
 <h3 id="ac-shadows-ensures-naoe-can-be-easily-overpowered">
  AC Shadows Ensures Naoe Can Be Easily Overpowered
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  has really never been known for having challenging combat, and that's largely because the series has emphasized stealth and parkour elements more, which allow players to either quickly escape danger or avoid it altogether. In
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , however, combat is highly unforgiving, especially for Naoe. Players who move recklessly through an area are likely to be overwhelmed by enemies, and since it's difficult enough for Naoe to take on one enemy, attempting to take on multiple simultaneously is a recipe for disaster.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     The primary way
     <em>
      Assassin's Creed Shadows
     </em>
     encourages more cautious gameplay is through its extensive AI overhaul, which sees enemies behaving in unprecedented ways that ultimately increase the game's challenge.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  In light of that, players are far better off choosing to approach each situation cautiously in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  using the game's refined stealth mechanics. It's also better that they weight the outcome of a situation before engaging an enemy in
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , even if they are doing so from a stealth vantage point, as alerting nearby enemies can ruin a heist very quickly. Thankfully, as challenging as this may make the game, it also makes
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  ' stealth much more engaging and realistic, which is something the series has needed for some time now.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomfall: How To Get &amp; Use Signal Redirector</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/atomfall-find-signal-redirector-location-mechanics/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There are a handful of tools
  <strong>
   <em>
    Atomfall
   </em>
  </strong>
  players can collect that aren't used in combat. The Metal Detector is used to dig up buried stashes and hidden lunchbox collectibles, while the Flashlight is used to light up your surroundings and highlight items in the environment.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Signal Redirector in
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  is one of the most useful things to get early as it is used to redirect power on certain switches, which disables machinery, opens doors, and otherwise grants control over various electronics throughout the world. This guide explains how to get a Signal Redirector and how this useful, but somewhat confusing, tool works.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-signal-redirector-in-atomfall">
  How To Get Signal Redirector In Atomfall
 </h2>
 <h3 id="all-signal-redirector-locations">
  All Signal Redirector Locations
 </h3>
 <p>
  To find a Signal Redirector, you must make your way to Skethermoor, the easiest entrance to which can be found in the east of Wyndham Village. Here, there are two Signal Redirector locations
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  players can find: one in something called the
  <strong>
   Windfall Cache
  </strong>
  and one
  <strong>
   inside of the Skethermoor Prison
  </strong>
  , which was taken from Dr. Garrow upon her capture.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1002452164" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1002452164" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1002452164" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1002452164" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1002452164-img" id="article-gallery-1-1002452164">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1002452164" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-335023047">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   To
   <strong>
    open the Windfall Cache
   </strong>
   , you must
   <strong>
    first find the Windfall Key
   </strong>
   .
   <strong>
    Hug the northern border of Skethermoor as you enter from Wyndham Village to find a secret Protocol bunker
   </strong>
   hidden in the northern woods.
  </li>
  <li>
   Make your way through the complex, past the Protocol soldiers, until you
   <strong>
    find a bathroom. Squeeze past the stalls to find a secret room
   </strong>
   and a body that contains the Windfall Key.
  </li>
  <li>
   Then, go southeast to the Road Block, and continue past it until you find the
   <strong>
    Protocol Field Station at coordinates 41.3E, 74.9N,
   </strong>
   surrounded by fencing.
  </li>
  <li>
   The
   <strong>
    Windfall Cache can be found inside this bunker
   </strong>
   , but be warned – if you are not friendly with Protocol, you will be considered trespassing and will be shot on sight, which can make this method rather difficult.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-564364604" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-564364604" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-564364604" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-564364604" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-564364604-img" id="article-gallery-2-564364604">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-564364604" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1743427918">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The
   <strong>
    Protocol Skethermoor Prison is located in the far southwest of Skethermoor
   </strong>
   . To find the Signal Redirector location inside the prison, continue through until you reach the lower levels, where Dr. Garrow is being held in solitary.
   <ul>
    <li>
     You do not need to be friendly with Protocol and Captain Sims to enter this location, but it makes the task significantly easier.
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   Speak to Dr. Garrow in her cell, or ignore her, and look for the entrance to the Security wing on the bottom floor, to the right of Dr. Garrow as you face her.
  </li>
  <li>
   The
   <strong>
    Signal Redirector is on a shelf in a side room just to the right inside the Security area.
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Once acquired,
  <strong>
   equip the Signal Redirector with △ (Y) when the prompt appears in the bottom-left
  </strong>
  , or by selecting it directly from your backpack menu. Like the Metal Detector, the prompt will only appear if you are close to a signal that can be redirected with the Signal Redirector.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     There may be other methods to get a Signal Redirector
     <em>
      Atomfall
     </em>
     players can discover in this dense and interconnected Northern British landscape. This guide to how to find the Signal Redirector will be updated as we discover any additional locations.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="how-to-use-the-signal-redirector">
  How To Use The Signal Redirector
 </h2>
 <h3 id="signal-redirector-mechanics-explained">
  Signal Redirector Mechanics, Explained
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-882375546" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-882375546" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-882375546" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-882375546" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-882375546-img" id="article-gallery-3-882375546">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-882375546" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-372591788">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Atomfall
  </em>
  , Signal Redirector mechanics work much like the Metal Detector. When you are close to a signal you can redirect, a pop-up will appear in the bottom-left of the screen that prompts you to equip the Signal Redirector.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once equipped, you
  <strong>
   must point it directly at a power switch nodule while standing relatively close by
  </strong>
  . You do not need to be directly next to or under a Signal Redirector node, but you must be within a few feet to activate the tool.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_18">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Interestingly, you do not need to
     <em>
      see
     </em>
     a switch to change it with a Signal Redirector –
     <em>
      Atomfall
     </em>
     players can use the Signal Redirector through walls, as long as you are close enough to the power switch itself.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  As you look around an environment trying to find a signal box,
  <strong>
   look at the Signal Redirector's screen, and you will notice a small black bar that rises depending on where you look
  </strong>
  . When you
  <strong>
   get closer
  </strong>
  to the location of a signal, the
  <strong>
   black bar will go all the way to the right and make a high-pitched tone
  </strong>
  . This helps pinpoint switch box locations for your Signal Redirector when you cannot directly see them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you're close enough, and the
  <strong>
   switch is highlighted with a white box, press the R2 (RT) to activate the Signal Redirector
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  A satisfying beep sound effect will ring out as you switch the power, which swaps the lit bulb on the targeted signal box. Some signal boxes have two outputs, some have three, so be sure you redirect the power to whichever bulb is associated with the object you are trying to activate/deactivate.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Post-Apocalyptic Settings In Video Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-post-apocalyptic-settings-video-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      UNSIGHTED offers a unique war-torn sci-fi world with multiple playthroughs and engaging upgrade systems.
     </li>
     <li>
      Darkest Dungeon 2 presents a dismal dark age with improved turn-based combat and rogue-like elements.
     </li>
     <li>
      Sunset Overdrive provides a vibrant and colorful post-apocalypse with chaotic gameplay and unique exploration.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Post-apocalyptic settings have become somewhat cliched over the years. However, there remain a number of games that provide immersive, distinctive settings that take place in locations long past their prime.
 </p>
 <p>
  From the ruined kingdom of Hallownest to the open expanse of the Mojave wasteland, many video game post-apocalyptic settings are broad and varied. Furthermore, many of these titles feature wildly different gameplay opportunities from one another. For those looking to dive in, here are the
  <strong>
   best post-apocalyptic settings in games
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="unsighted">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   UNSIGHTED
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-war-torn-sci-fi-world">
  A War-Torn Sci-Fi World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-205993166" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-205993166" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-205993166" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-205993166" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-205993166-img" id="article-gallery-1-205993166">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-205993166" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1848906235">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Unsighted
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a combination of top-down action and Metroidvania gameplay, excelling with its crunchy pixel-art visuals and unique sci-fi setting. The game takes place in a war-torn future, a landscape populated by sentient robots slowly losing their minds after an apocalyptic battle with humanity.
 </p>
 <p>
  Waking amid this ruined world, players are tasked with regaining control and saving whoever they can along the way. The game's distinctive setting is particularly notable for its distinctive zones, and the constant sense of tension provided by the in-game timer makes for a unique tone.
 </p>
 <h2 id="darkest-dungeon-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Darkest Dungeon 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dismal-burning-dark-age">
  A Dismal, Burning Dark Age
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-193450355" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-193450355" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-193450355" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-193450355" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-193450355-img" id="article-gallery-2-193450355">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-193450355" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1794617469">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though technically
  <strong>
   <em>
    Darkest Dungeon 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  tasks players with averting the apocalypse, it's already in full swing by the time the player arrives. Catastrophic events have already happened, leaving players floundering in a burning dark age amid abandoned bastions, lost knowledge, and ruined homes.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a world populated by madmen, eldritch horrors, and nightmarish monsters,
  <em>
   Darkest Dungeon 2
  </em>
  presents a setting that synergizes perfectly with its harsh and unforgiving gameplay. Though its opportunities for world-building are somewhat limited by its roguelite structure,
  <em>
   Darkest Dungeon 2
  </em>
  manages to set the scene via evocative writing, stylish presentation, and a dramatic soundtrack.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sunset-overdrive">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Sunset Overdrive
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-vibrant-post-apocalypse">
  A Vibrant Post-Apocalypse
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-379720866" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-379720866" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-379720866" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-379720866" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-379720866-img" id="article-gallery-3-379720866">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-379720866" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-99247513">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sunset Overdrive
   </em>
  </strong>
  takes place in the vibrant, summery environments of Sunset City, a veritable playground for expressive movement and bombastic action. Despite its post-apocalyptic setting,
  <em>
   Sunset Overdrive
  </em>
  is bursting with color, offering a uniquely exuberant take on a typically dismal genre.
 </p>
 <p>
  This works in tandem with
  <em>
   Sunset Overdrive
  </em>
  's tongue-in-cheek tone and movement-based gameplay. The fluidity of movement also makes traversal a more engaging experience than is typical of open-world games, with the urban environments facilitating exciting exploration.
 </p>
 <h2 id="mutant-year-zero-road-to-eden">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Mutant Year Zero: Road To Eden
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="lush-greenery-amp-creative-character-designs">
  Lush Greenery &amp; Creative Character Designs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-80920644" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-80920644" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-80920644" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-80920644" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-80920644-img" id="article-gallery-4-80920644">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-80920644" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1879917801">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mutant Year Zero: Road To Eden
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a strategy RPG that takes place in a post-apocalyptic setting populated by quirky mutants. The creative character designs, overgrown environments, and abundance of greenery help tremendously in making the world a unique and interesting place to explore.
 </p>
 <p>
  This tactical title also features real-time exploration, allowing players to poke around the game's eerie environments with relative freedom. For fans of ruined and overgrown settings, the world of
  <em>
   Mutant Year Zero
  </em>
  is likely to appeal.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="caravan-sandwitch">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Caravan SandWitch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-surprisingly-hopeful-world">
  A Surprisingly Hopeful World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2074834068" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2074834068" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2074834068" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2074834068" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2074834068-img" id="article-gallery-5-2074834068">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2074834068" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1358375531">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Caravan SandWitch
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a conflict-free exploration game with a focus on relaxation and discovery. This exploration-heavy experience is elevated by the game's stylish visuals, charming characters, and unique post-apocalyptic setting.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though it takes place on an exploited and ruined planet,
  <em>
   Caravan SandWitch
  </em>
  remains a decidedly hopeful experience. The game's atmosphere is ultimately peaceful, supported by a harmonious population that exudes kindness over hatred.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-new-vegas">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="extreme-attention-to-detail-amp-unique-factions">
  Extreme Attention To Detail &amp; Unique Factions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1845552299" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1845552299" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1845552299" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1845552299" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1845552299-img" id="article-gallery-6-1845552299">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1845552299" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-632898467">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The post-nuclear world of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout: New Vegas
   </em>
  </strong>
  may at first appear as a typical wasteland. However, it remains a unique place to be thanks to creative location design and the incredible variety of NPCs that breathe life into its many towns and hidden nooks.
 </p>
 <p>
  The multitude of distinctive factions also helps to make
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  unique, supported by a cast of memorable creatures. More importantly,
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  is simply full of things to see and do, packed with points of interest both big and small that drive exploration and consistently pique curiosity.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bastion">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Bastion
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dream-like-fantasy-world">
  A Dream-Like Fantasy World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1276536774" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1276536774" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1276536774" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1276536774" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1276536774-img" id="article-gallery-7-1276536774">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1276536774" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-148426478">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though its action may be fairly typical, especially by today's standards,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bastion
   </em>
  </strong>
  remains a truly unique and memorable experience throughout, thanks in no small part to its setting. In the game, players battle through various hand-painted environments as they attempt to unravel the mysteries surrounding a catastrophe known as the Calamity.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game's visual style and dynamic presentation of each environment are certainly among
  <em>
   Bastion
  </em>
  's greatest strengths. However, the wild environments, creative character and enemy designs, and surreal imagery make
  <em>
   Bastion
  </em>
  's post-apocalyptic setting particularly distinct.
 </p>
 <h2 id="caves-of-qud">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Caves Of Qud
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-expansive-science-fantasy-setting">
  An Expansive Science-Fantasy Setting
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1637661896" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1637661896" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1637661896" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1637661896" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1637661896-img" id="article-gallery-8-1637661896">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1637661896" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-19331749">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Caves Of Qud
   </em>
  </strong>
  is an open-world RPG that takes place in a distinctive science-fantasy world built from an innovative combination of hand-crafted and procedural content. This allows players to explore meaningful locations while also encountering constant surprises, facilitating a frequent sense of discovery.
 </p>
 <p>
  The exotic environments of
  <em>
   Caves Of Qud
  </em>
  are made up of ancient ruins and untamed wilds, painting lost civilizations with a retro-futuristic eye. And although its old-school and minimalist visuals won't be for everyone, they only allow the music, writing, and ambiance of the game to shine all the brighter.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
