<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K25 is Missing 26 Wrestlers from 2K24</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wwe-2k25-missing-26-wrestlers-2k24-list/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      WWE 2K25 boasts the largest roster ever, with 300 playable characters, including legends and current Superstars.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some Superstars from WWE 2K24 won't return for WWE 2K25 due to contract issues or being let go by the company.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans are hopeful for a potential TNA DLC pack to bring back legends like Robert Roode and address missing characters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  26 wrestlers from
  <em>
   WWE 2K24
  </em>
  will not be returning for
  <em>
   <strong>
    WWE 2K25
   </strong>
  </em>
  . As the build-up to the release of
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  continues, more details about the game are coming out. This includes reveals about debuting modes, new features, and the much-awaited roster reveal. The developers try their best to come up with the best mix of current Superstars and legends so that the title can attract the attention of wrestling fans of all ages.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's full roster was revealed recently. With an impressive and massive count of 300 playable characters including wrestling legends, unique gimmicks, plus Raw, SmackDown, and NXT talents, the game will end up having the biggest roster to date. However, as with every yearly roster, some Superstars are bound to come and go. Whether the departure is due to being let go by the company or a contract expiration, some characters from previous years won't be part of the next game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user Makuraudo listed all Superstars from
  <em>
   WWE 2K24
  </em>
  who were not part of
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  's recent roster reveal. Characters from
  <em>
   WWE 2K24
  </em>
  's Pat McAfee DLC Pack were mostly expected to be one-off, especially because of the negative reception it received. Names like Edge, Bobby Lashley, and a few others left the company, so it's not surprising to see them being left out. However, the more shocking omissions would have to be Robert Roode, Big Boss Man, Jerry Lawler, and Ted DiBiase.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wwe-2k24-characters-who-aren-39-t-part-of-wwe-2k25">
  WWE 2K24 Characters Who Aren't Part of WWE 2K25
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   AJ Hawk
  </li>
  <li>
   Bad Bunny
  </li>
  <li>
   Beth Phoenix
  </li>
  <li>
   Big Boss Man
  </li>
  <li>
   Bobby Lashley
  </li>
  <li>
   Boston Connor
  </li>
  <li>
   Cameron Grimes
  </li>
  <li>
   Damon Kemp
  </li>
  <li>
   Darius Butler
  </li>
  <li>
   Dijak
  </li>
  <li>
   Drew Gulak
  </li>
  <li>
   Jerry Lawler
  </li>
  <li>
   Jinder Mahal
  </li>
  <li>
   Muhammad Ali
  </li>
  <li>
   MVP
  </li>
  <li>
   Post Malone
  </li>
  <li>
   Ricochet
  </li>
  <li>
   Robert Roode
  </li>
  <li>
   Ronda Rousey
  </li>
  <li>
   Sanga
  </li>
  <li>
   SCRYPTS
  </li>
  <li>
   Shane McMahon
  </li>
  <li>
   Ted DiBiase
  </li>
  <li>
   Ty Schmit
  </li>
  <li>
   Veer
  </li>
  <li>
   Xia Li
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Robert Roode's absence is a shock because most fans know that he is still employed by the WWE. Although Roode now acts as a producer for the company, the same could be said for Tyler Breeze, who works in a backstage role but is still part of the roster. The comments section speculates that there could have been some contract issues with Roode after shifting from a performer's contract. However, many fans are hopeful that the WWE and TNA partnership could add something new to the games. With much clamor for a TNA DLC pack, maybe the developers can bring back a Bobby Roode TNA character for The Glorious One.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1227145841" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1227145841" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1227145841" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1227145841" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1227145841-img" id="article-gallery-1-1227145841">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1227145841" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-165600477">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As for Boss Man, Lawler, and DiBiase, it's highly likely that their Legends deals could have expired, leading to their removal. Granted, it's still a surprise, especially since DiBiase and Lawler have made a few one-off appearances for the company recently. While it would likely receive negative press,
  <em>
   WWE 2K25
  </em>
  could add back these missing characters via DLC or MyFaction.
  <em>
   WWE 2K24's
  </em>
  WCW DLC Pack did this by bringing back updated and alternate versions of DDP, The Iron Sheik, Mr. Perfect, and Lex Luger, who have appeared in older games.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization 7’s DIsasters Are a Logical Progression from Civ 6’s</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/civilization-7-natural-disasters-civ-6-change-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Ever since its inception, the
  <em>
   Sid Meier's Civilization
  </em>
  franchise has attempted to emulate the real world. Not only has it taken real-world leaders and civilizations, but its gameplay loop has been built around actual history. With
  <em>
   Civ 6
  </em>
  , Firaxis chose to take it even further by also delivering a more realistic world with the inclusion of natural disasters and Climate Change. While
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sid Meier's Civilization 7
   </em>
  </strong>
  may not include Climate Change just yet, it has taken those disasters to the next level.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Sid Meier's Civilization 7
  </em>
  has taken
  <em>
   Civ 6's
  </em>
  disasters feature and fleshed them out to deliver something that feels far more lifelike. No longer are they only spurred on by a multi-tiered climate system, and instead, players must be prepared for the unpredictability of nature. If that was not enough, they have also become far more intimidating looking while also being easier to manage in the long run. And with updates, the feature will likely only grow.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="civilization-7-has-reworked-storms-for-the-better">
  Civilization 7 Has Reworked Storms for the Better
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1218363043" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1218363043" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1218363043" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1218363043" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1218363043-img" id="article-gallery-1-1218363043">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1218363043" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-262384640">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="civ-6-introduced-the-concept-of-natural-disasters">
  Civ 6 Introduced the Concept of Natural Disasters
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Sid Meier's Civilization
  </em>
  may have dabbled with weather in past games through random events, but
  <em>
   Civ 6
  </em>
  was the first game to introduce natural disasters as its own separate entity. Through the game's Gathering Storm DLC, Firaxis added a whole host of disasters for players to deal with. Floods could take out entire tiles, droughts and forest fires could devastate surrounding areas, and storms such as tornadoes or blizzards could impact players immensely. On top of that, they also had to constantly look out for volcanic eruptions and meteor showers.
 </p>
 <p>
  All of these disasters helped add to the realism of
  <em>
   Civ 6
  </em>
  's world while also giving players an extra challenge to deal with. As Climate Change got worse, these disasters would also get worse. Their range would increase, the damage they caused would worsen, and everything about these storms would become even more terrifying. Players would have to do everything they could to prevent this, or risk losing to nature itself. While that made for an interesting gameplay addition, some also felt like it was a bit too much. So,
  <em>
   Civ 7
  </em>
  has changed things a bit.
 </p>
 <h3 id="civ-7-has-taken-the-concept-to-the-next-level">
  Civ 7 Has Taken the Concept to the Next Level
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of the biggest changes that
  <em>
   Civ 7
  </em>
  has introduced to storms is that they are no longer tied to a Climate Change mechanic. It remains to be seen if that feature comes back at some point in the future, but as of now, storms are their own separate thing. Because of this, they feel far more random and sporadic as there is no Climate Change bar telling players what to expect. They can swoop in at a moment's notice, devastate some tiles, and disappear. Luckily, it seems like the frequency has been toned down from
  <em>
   Civ 6
  </em>
  , making them far easier to manage.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is not entirely clear just how often or when these disasters will occur, which makes them a bit more interesting. On top of that, the new designs Firaxis came up with for
  <em>
   Civ 7
  </em>
  really make them look and feel far more intimidating. There's just something spine-tingling about watching a hurricane slowly roll in or a tornado ripping up tiles near a city, which is really helped by the more realistic art style the studio has chosen.
 </p>
 <p>
  While some players may miss the Climate Change mechanic, this iteration of storms feels like a nice progression from what has come before. They are less frequent, more random, and they look terrifying. With post-launch updates and DLC for
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  , there's a chance that the studio adds even more into the mix. But for now, players will just have to keep a watchful eye on the weather as they attempt to conquer the world.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - My Treasure!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-my-treasure/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player steals a treasure chest with a harpoon in Sea of Thieves and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley: How to Make Chia Seed Bread</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/disney-dreamlight-valley-ddv-how-make-chia-seed-bread-recipe/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Chia Seed Bread Recipe in Dreamlight Valley
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Use Chia Seed Bread in Disney Dreamlight Valley
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Every new expansion in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Disney Dreamlight Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  adds new recipes, and Storybook Vale is no exception. This update brings about 100 new dishes, including tasty appetizers, entrees, and desserts. One of them is Chia Seed Bread, a three-star entree that you can easily make.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Chia Seed Bread only needs three ingredients, and the good news is they’re all pretty cheap. Once it’s ready, players can use it in different ways. Below, you will find a list of all the ingredients for Chia Seed Bread and their locations.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="chia-seed-bread-recipe-in-dreamlight-valley">
  Chia Seed Bread Recipe in Dreamlight Valley
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-316d0a35c6aea08f" id="emaki-video-player-316d0a35c6aea08f">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As we mentioned above, players will need three ingredients for Chia Seed Bread. Here’s the complete recipe:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   1 x Wheat
  </li>
  <li>
   1 x Shovel Bird Eggs
  </li>
  <li>
   1 x Chia Seeds.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <div style="list-style-type:disc">
 </div>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-wheat">
  How to Get Wheat
 </h3>
 <p>
  Wheat is the only ingredient for Chia Seed Bread that isn’t found in Storybook Vale. To get it,
  <em>
   DDV
  </em>
  players need to head back to Dreamlight Valley. You can buy wheat seeds from Goofy’s Stall in Peaceful Meadow and grow them yourself. If you don’t want to wait, you can sometimes buy fully grown wheat for three Star Coins, but keep in mind that it’s not always in stock.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-shovel-bird-eggs">
  How to Get Shovel Bird Eggs
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="goofy's stall in the bind ddv" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/goofy-s-stall-in-the-bind-ddv.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Shovel Bird Eggs are sold at Goofy’s Stall in The Bind, the first area of Storybook Vale. However, you won’t be able to buy them right away. They only become available after the second stall upgrade. Once you've upgraded the stall by interacting with Scrooge’s sign, you can buy Shovel Bird Eggs for 160 Star Coins. These eggs are also used in other Storybook Vale recipes, like Golden Apple Pie, Lightning Cake, and Cape Gooseberry Chia Pancakes.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-get-chia-seeds">
  How to Get Chia Seeds
 </h3>
 <p>
  You can also buy Chia Seeds from Goofy’s Stall in The Bind while you're there. They only cost five Star Coins and take five minutes to grow. And yes, you have the option to use Miracle Growth Elixir to speed up their growth.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-use-chia-seed-bread-in-disney-dreamlight-valley">
  How to Use Chia Seed Bread in Disney Dreamlight Valley
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="selling chia seed bread to goofy ddv" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/buying-shovel-bird-eggs-ddv.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you have all the ingredients, head to a cooking station to make your Chia Seed Bread. You can sell it for
  <strong>
   122 Star Coins or eat it to restore 478 energy
  </strong>
  , which is pretty decent for a three-star meal. Moreover, you can gift it to your friends like Jafar and Goofy, so be sure to check their favorite gifts for the day.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Creates Impressive LEGO Magikarp</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-lego-magikarp-fan-build/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A creative fan impresses with a LEGO Magikarp design.
     </li>
     <li>
      The LEGO builder replicated Magikarp's design impressively, earning praise from fans.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some fans are disappointed by Pokemon's partnership with Mega Bloks over LEGO, with high demand for official LEGO Pokemon sets.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A creative
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has impressed the community with their clever use of LEGO blocks to recreate the iconic Magikarp. The customized LEGO creation had fellow
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans comparing it to officially licensed block kits.
 </p>
 <p>
  When it comes to combining memorable creature design with marketability, there's almost nothing out there that compares to
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  . Over the years, The Pokemon Company has released hundreds of different creature designs through the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  games and anime, and in turn, fans all over the world have raced to express those designs in real life. One of the most well-loved of those designs is that of the humble Magikarp and its Gyarados evolution. Magikarp has appeared in nearly every
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  property, becoming a reliable presence throughout the series.
 </p>
 <p>
  One
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fan who goes by A_dude_named_Sue on Reddit expressed their Magikarp fandom through the medium of LEGO blocks. They used the versatile pieces to recreate a classical Magikarp design straight out of
  <em>
   Pokemon Red
  </em>
  . Like other impressive LEGO Pokemon recreations, their Magikarp captured the goofy creature's essence, winning praise from fellow fans.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fans-compare-custom-lego-magikarp-to-official-pokemon-nanoblock-sets">
  Fans Compare Custom LEGO Magikarp to Official Pokemon Nanoblock Sets
 </h2>
 <p>
  Fans were seriously impressed by the LEGO Magikarp, who hailed their ability to replicate the piscine Pokemon's smooth curves using the typically polygonal LEGO pieces alone. Some commenters even compared their Magikarp with the officially licensed
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  Magikarp Nanoblock set. The comparison saw the LEGO Magikarp come out ahead thanks to having additional detail and a better expression of its fishy form.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-308752501" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-308752501" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-308752501" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-308752501" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-308752501-img" id="article-gallery-1-308752501">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-308752501" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-988861578">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Praise for the customized LEGO Magikarp also led some fans to lament the fact that The Pokemon Company opted to partner with Mega Bloks for an official
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  Mega Bloks toy set over LEGO. They claimed that the more limited versatility of Mega Bloks compared to LEGO limited the building possibilities for
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  . The partnership also cut off the potential that could be wrung out of LEGO's recent turn towards themed sets in recent years, which has seen the company release new collectible playsets based on video games and cartoons, and even appear as a distinct mode in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The persistent recurrence of LEGO
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  creations shows the sheer creativity of experienced LEGO builders and the capacity of fans to express their love for their favorite characters even without official support. That said, it also shows that there's definitely pent-up demand brewing for LEGO to make an official partnership with
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  if such an opportunity were to present itself.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
