<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>17 Detective Games With Realistic Crime Solving</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-detective-games-realistic-crime-solving/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Realistic detective games like Sherlock Holmes: Crimes and Punishments use clue logging and skill checks to catch culprits authentically.
     </li>
     <li>
      In Return of the Obra Dinn, players must investigate closely, note clues, and deduct accurately to uncover the ship's mysterious events.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like The Painscreek Killings and Disco Elysium require players to explore, observe, and deduce in order to solve intricate mysteries.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Crime has been a key subject in gaming ever since Hiroshi Suzuki’s
  <em>
   Manbiki Shounen
  </em>
  used shoplifting as a basis for stealth gameplay. Though while committing crimes has worked wonderfully for
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto, Saints Row, Hitman,
  </em>
  and more, there are also a wide range of games dedicated to stopping crimes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Usually, this came via fisticuffs, like in
  <em>
   Streets of Rage
  </em>
  , while others included detective-style investigations
  <em>
   and
  </em>
  fisticuffs, like
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Asylum.
  </em>
  That said, real detectives don’t have breath-detecting cowls like the Dark Knight nor spirit mediums like Phoenix Wright - not usually anyway. These games use more
  <strong>
   realistic ways of solving crimes
  </strong>
  , with investigation, clues, testimony, and a lot of deduction.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated on February 7, 2025 by David Heath:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   Murder mysteries have been inspiring people for centuries, be it through classic Agatha Christie novels, or on TV through shows like Castle and Murder, She Wrote. It's even convinced some people to take up amateur sleuthing themselves, or become actual detectives, criminologists, and investigators. Even so, they tend to take some artistic licenses with crime solving.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Video games do the same thing, offering fanciful settings, powers, and other mechanics. But whether it's on Earth, in space, a fantasy world, or otherwise, there are plenty of games that have tried to be more authentic, making players search for clues, talk at length to different NPCs, and use their own logic to figure out who did what. This list has been updated with four additional games that take a realistic look at detective work: Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One; Hotel Dusk: Room 215; Song of Farca; and Judgment.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="return-of-the-obra-dinn">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Return Of The Obra Dinn
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-supernatural-game-that-requires-natural-investigative-skills-to-complete">
  A Supernatural Game That Requires Natural Investigative Skills To Complete
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1385388374" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1385388374" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1385388374" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1385388374" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1385388374-img" id="article-gallery-1-1385388374">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1385388374" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1202336846">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  By its premise alone,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Return of the Obra Dinn
   </strong>
  </em>
  doesn’t sound very realistic. The titular Obra Dinn is a ship that went missing around the Cape of Good Hope in 1803, taking all 60 souls with it. When it suddenly reappears off the coast of England 5 years later, it’s up to the player to figure out what happened to everyone aboard. The circumstances are spooky, and it’s as supernatural as the player’s ‘Memento Mortem,’ a pocket watch that lets them recreate suspected deaths.
 </p>
 <p>
  Yet getting ahead in the game involves investigating the scenes closely for all its clues, noting them down, and deducing what happened. Players must be accurate, too, as they’ve got to validate the fates in pairs or triples rather than making one educated guess. Some deaths are similar enough that players can get away with making the same conclusions, but others require more careful and exact deductions. Otherwise, the player will be left on the ship with a lot of bad memories.
 </p>
 <h2 id="paradise-killer">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Paradise Killer
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-murder-mystery-involving-aliens-sci-fi-amp-conspiracy">
  A Murder Mystery Involving Aliens, Sci-Fi, &amp; Conspiracy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-469296426" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-469296426" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-469296426" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-469296426" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-469296426-img" id="article-gallery-2-469296426">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-469296426" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-398138778">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Paradise Killer
   </em>
  </strong>
  's premise is anything but realistic, as it sees the Syndicate, an organization of immortal aliens, abduct humans from Earth in an attempt to create the perfect society on Paradise Island. When it inevitably fails, they sacrifice its citizens to create the next attempt. On the 24th incarnation of the island, the Syndicate Council are found murdered, putting its 25th recreation on hold. To solve the mystery, the Syndicate sends detective Lady Love Dies to find the true culprit, then personally execute them if they're sentenced to death.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, its gameplay is more grounded by comparison, as Lady Love Dies has to examine crime scenes, talk to witnesses and suspects, and piece the clues together to figure out the facts. It takes place in an open world, where the player can go anywhere they like and talk to whoever they want in any order and at any time. They could even solve other mysteries, and put people on trial. Though if they don't have all the evidence they need to expose the island's secrets, it's going to be a short session in court.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="disco-elysium">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Disco Elysium
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="using-dialogue-detection-and-luck-to-uncover-what-39-s-happening-in-elysium">
  Using Dialogue, Detection, And Luck To Uncover What's Happening In Elysium
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1668218779" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1668218779" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1668218779" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1668218779" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1668218779-img" id="article-gallery-3-1668218779">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1668218779" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-803779653">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Disco Elysium
   </strong>
  </em>
  takes place in a fantasy world called Elysium, where its ‘isolas’ are separated by a misty tissue called ‘The Pale’ that induces insanity and death with prolonged exposure. Beyond that, it resembles life in a Communist country and takes inspiration from grittier detective media like
  <em>
   The Wire
  </em>
  and novels by Dashiel Hammett and China Miéville. This is certainly evident in its surreal storytelling, where the player must investigate the death of a hanged man in Martinaise.
 </p>
 <p>
  The plot gradually unfolds a wider conspiracy and delves into the player’s character, Lieutenant Harry DuBois. But to get there, players must improve their detection by finding the right clues and making the right dialogue choices. Without them, they wouldn't be able to develop the right skills and thoughts needed to aid the investigation. They can also help tip things in their favor during skill checks, as players can have all they need, but they'll still need luck on their side to succeed.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-case-of-the-golden-idol">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   The Case Of The Golden Idol
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="using-logical-deduction-to-figure-out-a-family-plot">
  Using Logical Deduction To Figure Out A Family Plot
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1498432298" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1498432298" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1498432298" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1498432298" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1498432298-img" id="article-gallery-4-1498432298">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1498432298" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1949506175">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Case of the Golden Idol
   </em>
  </strong>
  uses point and click elements, as its Exploring Mode requires clicking on characters, objects, etc., to pick up keywords and phrases relevant to the story. Namely, how the titular Golden Idol is involved with the Cloudsley family and the mysterious secret society known as the Brotherhood. Things get strange quite quickly, though the way to figure out what's happening is more straightforward.
 </p>
 <p>
  When they enter Thinking Mode, players can piece the evidence together to come to different conclusions that reveal more of the plot. It can reveal the names of more Brotherhood members, the rooms they stayed in, what they had access to, etc. It's quite a merciful game, as it’ll clue players in a little by letting them know whether their segments are correctly placed or not, allowing them to rearrange things when necessary. To get all the right segments, players can't leave any stone unturned in Exploring Mode.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="judgment">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Judgment
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="help-a-lawyer-turned-detective-stop-a-conspiracy-with-sleuthing-amp-kung-fu">
  Help A Lawyer-Turned-Detective Stop A Conspiracy With Sleuthing &amp; Kung Fu
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-342476302" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-342476302" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-342476302" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-342476302" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-342476302-img" id="article-gallery-5-342476302">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-342476302" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-13494511">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Judgment
   </em>
  </strong>
  eschews supernatural fantasy elements, though it's hard to say it's fully realistic. It sees Takayuki Yagami, a former lawyer-turned-P.I., investigating a strange series of murders where the victims' eyes have been gouged out. At first, it was to get a yakuza captain off the hook, but he soon learns they're connected to a wider conspiracy involving the captain, the culprit, and an older murder case that forced him out of the courtroom.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game's a spin-off of the
  <em>
   Yakuza/Like a Dragon
  </em>
  series, so it offers more fisticuffs and colorful minigames than the average detective gets into. But, it still involves some proper legwork, like examining areas in first-person for clues, and case files for players to leaf through to come to conclusions. They can come in handy for pressing more info out of key figures during questioning sessions. He also does a lot of tailing missions where he has to follow people, which do capture the film noir detective feeling — but they also wear out their welcome after a while.
 </p>
 <h2 id="sherlock-holmes-chapter-one">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="taking-open-world-sleuthing-back-to-its-roots">
  Taking Open-World Sleuthing Back To Its Roots
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1884592464" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1884592464" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1884592464" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1884592464" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1884592464-img" id="article-gallery-6-1884592464">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1884592464" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-815072974">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Founded by French expatriates in Ukraine and Ireland, Frogwares has become the prime developer of games based on Sherlock Holmes, whether they stick to the books, tell original stories, or pit him against other Victorian foes, both fictional (
  <em>
   Sherlock Holmes Vs Arsene Lupin
  </em>
  ) and non-fictional (
  <em>
   Sherlock Holmes vs Jack The Ripper
  </em>
  ).
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One
   </em>
  </strong>
  takes things back to the start of Holmes' sleuthing career, as he and Jon Watson head back to his birthplace on the island of Cordona to uncover the mystery behind his mother's death.
 </p>
 <p>
  It builds on the open-world formula from
  <em>
   The Sinking City
  </em>
  , as Holmes &amp; Watson must tread the city streets, examine crime scenes for clues, and put them together to form a conclusion via Holmes' 'Mind Palace.' The game even gets away with replicating Batman's crime scene recreations with the Concentrate ability because it's Holmes using his imagination instead of a magic gadget. It's a stronger showcase of detecting skills than
  <em>
   Judgment
  </em>
  , though it has sloppier combat and some rough moments (e.g. Sherlock likes to imitate bad accents to go with his disguises).
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sherlock-holmes-crimes-and-punishments">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Sherlock Holmes: Crimes And Punishments
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="using-elementary-but-honed-skills-to-catch-culprits">
  Using Elementary But Honed Skills To Catch Culprits
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1911279327" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1911279327" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1911279327" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1911279327" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1911279327-img" id="article-gallery-7-1911279327">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1911279327" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1679198007">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: PS3, PS4, Xbox 360, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch, PC
  </li>
  <li>
   Released: September 30, 2014
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Frogwares
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Obra Dinn
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  have fanciful settings but use realistic detective methods, such as clue logging and pressing witnesses and suspects for information. But how about a game that has a realistic setting
  <em>
   and
  </em>
  realistic gameplay? Enter
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sherlock Holmes: Crimes and Punishments
   </em>
  </strong>
  , Frogwares' earlier, more faithful take on the world's most famous detective. This title sees Holmes and Watson go around Victorian England and solve cases based on actual
  <em>
   Holmes
  </em>
  short stories.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players search for clues, then piece them together on a ‘deduction board’ to figure out the results. Each case has multiple solutions depending on how well players figure things out, if they find the culprit, and whether they choose to absolve or condemn the criminal in question. Its fanciest detail is ‘Sherlock Vision,’ where Holmes can look more closely at items to derive new information from them, like finding hidden inscriptions or signs that something's been moved.
 </p>
 <h2 id="blade-runner-1997">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Blade Runner (1997)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-concurrent-investigation-in-the-blade-runner-world">
  A Concurrent Investigation In The Blade Runner World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-94358288" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-94358288" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-94358288" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-94358288" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-94358288-img" id="article-gallery-8-94358288">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-94358288" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1166434027">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Point &amp; Click adventure games were popular fixtures on PCs and microcomputers throughout the 1980s and early 1990s. But by the late 1990s, their gameplay and moon logic puzzles felt like old hat next to 3D platformers and first-person shooters. Still, they went out with a bang, offering some of the strongest games in the genre, with the likes of the
  <em>
   Broken Sword
  </em>
  series,
  <em>
   Grim Fandango
  </em>
  , and Westwood Studios' take on the classic movie
  <strong>
   <em>
    Blade Runner
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Well, kind of.
 </p>
 <p>
  It takes place during the flick, and features its characters, some of whom are played by their original actors. But it follows a different runner: Ray McCoy. New to the job, he's tasked with tracking down a group of replicants who killed some animals. But when he follows their trail too closely, he's framed for murder and forced to go on the run. By talking to suspects, finding clues, analyzing photos, and using the Voight-Kampf test to find replicants, he can solve the mystery, and get one of 13 endings depending on their choices in-game.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="song-of-farca">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Song Of Farca
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="where-the-truth-is-just-a-hack-away">
  Where The Truth Is Just A Hack Away
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1468840951" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1468840951" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1468840951" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1468840951" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1468840951-img" id="article-gallery-9-1468840951">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1468840951" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-2123297941">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: PC, macOS, Linux
  </li>
  <li>
   Released: July 21, 2021
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Wooden Monkeys
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Blade Runner
  </em>
  may be one of cinema's most iconic cyberpunk movies (and one of its more underrated cyberpunk games), but it's still a sci-fi story that requires some suspense of disbelief. That doesn't mean its cyborgs or techno-metropolis are bad or take away from its gameplay; it just means
  <strong>
   <em>
    Song of Farca
   </em>
  </strong>
  might feel more authentic, as its hi-tech future feels more relatable. It's a world where IT corporations practically run the planet due to society's reliance on the internet and gadgets. But, it can also work against them.
 </p>
 <p>
  Which is where the player comes in. They take on the role of Isabella 'Izy' Song, a detective with a short fuse who uses her hacking skills and gadgets to get around her house arrest. With just her computer and a fleet of drones, she can hack out information from the web and grab surveillance footage to piece together clues via a cloud screen. If they draw the right conclusions, they could nab a criminal and find out how they're connected to a wider conspiracy. Get it wrong, and Song's nearest and dearest could end up suffering the consequences.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hotel-dusk-room-215">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Hotel Dusk: Room 215
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="discover-how-much-mystery-one-room-can-contain">
  Discover How Much Mystery One Room Can Contain
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1373235341" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1373235341" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1373235341" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1373235341" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1373235341-img" id="article-gallery-10-1373235341">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1373235341" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-956669985">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It was hard to compete against the
  <em>
   Ace Attorney
  </em>
  series once its combination of detective and defense attorney work caught on. Yet, players who were turned off by its wacky anime shenanigans found themselves getting into the grittier
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hotel Dusk: Room 215
   </strong>
  </em>
  . While searching for his former partner Brian Bradley, Detective Kyle Hyde checks into the titular hotel and ends up in Room 215, a room said to grant wishes. If it can do that, it does it in a roundabout way, as Hyde discovers he has more ties to the hotel than he thought.
 </p>
 <p>
  To uncover them, players have to hold the DS like a book and move Kyle around the hotel. One screen shows a third-person view of Hyde, while the other shows his POV of his current location. Investigations take the form of finding clues, interviewing patrons and staff, and solving the odd puzzle here and there. Though they have to be careful — if they're caught in restricted areas, get caught with contraband, or mess up the end-of-chapter interrogations by asking the wrong questions and acting out of turn, they could get kicked out into a Game Over screen.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="murder-mystery-machine">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Murder Mystery Machine
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="isometric-examination">
  Isometric Examination
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-1309784897" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-1309784897" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-1309784897" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-1309784897" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-1309784897-img" id="article-gallery-11-1309784897">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-1309784897" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-106710125">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: PC, PS4, Nintendo Switch, Xbox One, Xbox Series X/S, Apple Arcade.
  </li>
  <li>
   Released: August 2021.
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Blazing Griffin.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Despite its blunt title,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Murder Mystery Machine
   </em>
  </strong>
  aims to make players really think like detectives. Players take the roles of District Crime Agency newbie Cassandra Clarke and the experienced-but-burnt-out Nathan Huston to investigate the murder of a famous politician. The evidence says he was killed in a botched robbery, but as they delve further, they touch upon a more complicated plot that could have grave consequences.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players explore settings and crime scenes as isometric dioramas, where they can move the place around to get a better look at things. Then, they can piece together their clues, witness testimony, and more on their Charlie Kelly-style mindmap. Once they link things accurately, they'll get more dialogue options to advance the case and get closer to the truth. Its controls take some getting used to, as they can be a little clunky. But its inventive approach to gameplay has kept players going back to it to solve its 8 chapters over and over.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-painscreek-killings">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   The Painscreek Killings
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="using-urban-exploration-to-figure-out-a-mystery-and-a-murder">
  Using Urban Exploration To Figure Out A Mystery And A Murder
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-2133685187" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-2133685187" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-2133685187" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-2133685187" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-2133685187-img" id="article-gallery-12-2133685187">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-2133685187" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1740301209">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platform: PC
  </li>
  <li>
   Released: September 27, 2017
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: EQ Studios
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Walking simulators are often derided for not offering much in terms of gameplay, but it can be nice to just explore a virtual world and figure out what it's like through environmental storytelling alone. Given that detective games are all about careful observation and deduction, they could fit walking simulators like a hand in a glove. At least EQ Studios must’ve thought so, as that became the basis for
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Painscreek Killings
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Players take the role of Janet, a journalist tasked with figuring out why the formerly bustling town of Painscreek was abandoned and how it connects to a series of killings in the area. They can walk all around town in search of clues and logic puzzles that involve careful observation to solve. There’s no handholding here; players must investigate the town carefully on their own to come to the right conclusions.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="contradiction-spot-the-liar">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Contradiction: Spot The Liar!
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="it-39-s-cheesy-it-39-s-campy-and-it-39-s-a-neat-display-of-detective-work">
  It's Cheesy, It's Campy, And It's A Neat Display Of Detective Work
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-844929143" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-844929143" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-844929143" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-844929143" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-844929143-img" id="article-gallery-13-844929143">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-844929143" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1218397032">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: iOS, OSX, PC
  </li>
  <li>
   Release: January 10, 2015
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Baggy Cat
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Tim Follin is better known in video games for his music, converting Capcom’s
  <em>
   Ghouls N’ Ghosts
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Bionic Commando
  </em>
  tracks for the Commodore 64. Then, in 2015, with the help of Kickstarter, he and Baggy Cat made something that hadn’t been big since the 1990s: an FMV game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Contradiction: Spot the Liar!
   </em>
  </strong>
  sees Detective Jenks explore the village of Edenton in search of clues and testimony into the apparent suicide of Kate Vine. On top of using point and click elements to open new areas, Jenks must find the contradictions in his interviewees’ statements by comparing one detail to another. The more lies and truths he exposes, the closer he gets to solving the case. While it has its flaws, it's a fun, experimental game with plenty of campy charm to go with its intriguing gameplay.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-centennial-case-a-shijima-story">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Centennial Case: A Shijima Story
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="figuring-out-what-connects-different-murders-decades-apart">
  Figuring Out What Connects Different Murders Decades Apart
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1127050974" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1127050974" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1127050974" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1127050974" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1127050974-img" id="article-gallery-14-1127050974">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1127050974" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-397152453">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  FMV games seem to be coming back in style, as there are more games experimenting with using live-action footage in their gameplay. For example,
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Centennial Case: A Shijima Story
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a mystery puzzle game that sees novelist Haruka Kagami work with Eiji Shijima, a scientist who studies aging. He thinks his family passed down a special fruit that, once eaten, could stop the aging process altogether. But when a dead body is unearthed at his ancestral home, he asks Haruka to help figure out who killed them, along with other mysteries surrounding his family.
 </p>
 <p>
  It splits its gameplay up into 3 parts. In the Incident phase, players watch the murder take place to find clues to the culprit's identity and their methods. Then they can use the collected clues to form a hypothesis in the Reasoning phase, where they can make multiple deductions and see where the mystery leads them. Then, when they're sure, they can go to the Solution phase to catch the murderer. The smarter ones will fire back with their own counter-arguments, so players have to be sure their hypothesis is airtight.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="her-story">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Her Story
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="corroborating-one-source-with-another-to-discover-the-truth">
  Corroborating One Source With Another To Discover The Truth
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-791866684" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-791866684" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-791866684" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-791866684" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-791866684-img" id="article-gallery-15-791866684">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-791866684" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-733417197">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another FMV game that plays to the strengths of the genre is
  <strong>
   <em>
    Her Story
   </em>
  </strong>
  . It takes the form of an old computer OS from 1994, as the player must watch multiple clips from an interview with Hannah Smith over the disappearance and subsequent death of her husband Simon. She’s asked off-screen questions that the player can’t hear, leaving them to deduce the context from Smith’s answers.
 </p>
 <p>
  By cross-referencing her details with information from the database, players can figure out the more complex plot surrounding the Smiths as well as how Simon met his end. The most intriguing twist involves discovering who the player’s character is. Though to learn that, players will have to try the game out for themselves.
  <em>
   Her Story
  </em>
  shows how well FMV games can work with the right minds behind them.
 </p>
 <h2 id="l-a-noire">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   L.A. Noire
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="investigating-robberies-arson-cases-and-murders-in-1940s-california">
  Investigating Robberies, Arson Cases, And Murders In 1940s California
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-49092847" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-49092847" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-49092847" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-49092847" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-49092847-img" id="article-gallery-16-49092847">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-49092847" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1850136597">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This list wouldn’t be complete without
  <strong>
   <em>
    L.A. Noire
   </em>
  </strong>
  . This game offers up multiple cases of crimes for Cole Phelps and Jack Kelso to investigate, giving players a more up-close and personal look at investigating crime scenes, gathering key information from colleagues like coroners, etc., and interrogating key people for more information. In this title, things can get quite grisly when investigating homicide cases.
 </p>
 <p>
  Its revolutionary face-scanning tech was meant to aid this, where players could look at the person’s facial expressions to figure out whether they were being economical with the truth. It worked fairly well, too, even if some of the expressions came off as funny rather than intriguing. That said, as far as detective games go, it was one of the most authentic with its setting, investigations, and the fierce pressurizing of suspects when Phelps and Kelso needed answers.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-portopia-serial-murder-case">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   The Portopia Serial Murder Case
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-most-iconic-detective-game-in-the-genre">
  The Most Iconic Detective Game In The Genre
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-426701822" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-426701822" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-426701822" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-426701822" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-426701822-img" id="article-gallery-17-426701822">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-426701822" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-133009266">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: PC-6001, PC-8801, FM-7, FM-8, MSX, Sharp X-1, Famicom (NES), PC, Java mobile phones and smartphones.
  </li>
  <li>
   Release: June 1983.
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Chunsoft.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Detective games became a craze in Japan during the mid-1980s.
  <em>
   Famicom Detective Club
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Sanma no Meitantei
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Snatcher,
  </em>
  among others, have players wander open worlds (albeit by changing screens), investigating the areas, and talking to key figures/interrogating suspects for key info. Why did it catch on so well? It’s because of Yuji Horii and
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Portopia Serial Murder Case
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  On top of revolutionizing RPGs through
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  , Horii practically invented visual novels by letting the player and their assistant Yasu figure out how bank president Kozo Yamakawa met his end in a locked room. Combining a first-person view with point and click elements, branching dialogue, and twists, it was as realistic as detective games could get in 1983, and it became the basis for many future detective games in the following decades.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best JRPGs For Kids, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-jrpgs-for-kids-children-beginners-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pass down cherished gaming memories with kid-friendly JRPGs like the Secret of Mana remaster.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ever Oasis and Yo-Kai Watch 3 offer accessible JRPG experiences for younger and older players alike.
     </li>
     <li>
      Introduce kids to classic RPGs through Final Fantasy Mystic Quest and Dragon Quest 11.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Growing up, many gamers have fond memories of playing handhelds dangerously close to their faces or sprawling out in front of home consoles. These are some of our most cherished memories — especially during rainy days or when they could convince their parents they were too sick to go to school. For many, JRPGs were the perfect escape. Bright visuals and hours of content made them the ultimate time-sink for kids without responsibilities — or back pain from sitting too long.
 </p>
 <p>
  It’s no wonder that many parents now want to pass on those cherished experiences to their own children, at least before
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  inevitably take over. Here are some of the best JRPGs for younger children — or for anyone looking for an entry-level experience to ease them into this new world.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="secret-of-mana-hd-remaster">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Secret Of Mana (HD Remaster)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="all-manner-of-fun">
  All Manner Of Fun
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-62832397" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-62832397" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-62832397" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-62832397" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-62832397-img" id="article-gallery-1-62832397">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-62832397" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-680608819">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For gamers who want to introduce their kids to one of the greatest JRPGs ever but with a more accessible lick of paint, the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Secret of Mana
   </em>
  </strong>
  remaster is the perfect answer. Originally released in 1993, the
  <em>
   Mana
  </em>
  franchise's most cherished entry gets a vibrant chibi 3D makeover.
 </p>
 <p>
  Beyond the visual refresh, the remaster includes player-friendly updates like an area map, more frequent save points, and voice acting that brings the story to life. While some nostalgic adults might not love the redesigns, newcomers won’t know any different — lucky them!
 </p>
 <h2 id="ever-oasis">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Ever Oasis
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="anyway-here-39-s-wonderwall">
  Anyway, Here's Wonderwall
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1846219585" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1846219585" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1846219585" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1846219585" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1846219585-img" id="article-gallery-2-1846219585">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1846219585" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-722790068">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hardcore JRPG fans will recognize Koichi Ishii as the mastermind behind the
  <em>
   Mana
  </em>
  series and the creator of the iconic Chocobo and Moogle from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  . Later in his career, Ishii directed another kid-friendly classic:
  <em>
   Ever Oasis
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This charming 3DS title blends JRPG elements with a sprinkle of
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  . Players control a Seedling with magical powers that lets them create an oasis on a desolate desert planet. Thanks to a helpful tutorial, simple combat mechanics, and a straightforward UI,
  <em>
   Ever Oasis
  </em>
  is an accessible adventure for young players that still offers plenty of charm for older ones.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="yo-kai-watch-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Yo-Kai Watch 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="pokeballs-for-the-wrist">
  Pokeballs For The Wrist
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-600824135" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-600824135" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-600824135" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-600824135" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-600824135-img" id="article-gallery-3-600824135">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-600824135" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1641611080">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If there's one takeaway from this list, it's that Level-5 is a go-to developer for kid-friendly JRPGs.
  <em>
   Yo-kai Watch 3
  </em>
  is one of their finest offerings. Despite the number in the title, newcomers can jump right into this standalone title without worrying about previous games — there's no complex world-building to untangle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players control dual protagonists who wield the Yo-kai Watch, granting them the ability to see, befriend, and summon
  <s>
   Pokémon
  </s>
  Yo-kai. It has everything a kid would love from a 3DS game, from exploration and simple puzzle-solving to engaging turn-based combat. Sadly, it was the last entry released internationally.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-mystic-quest">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy Mystic Quest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-most-inaccessible-accessible-game">
  The Most Inaccessible Accessible Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1995966329" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1995966329" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1995966329" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1995966329" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1995966329-img" id="article-gallery-4-1995966329">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1995966329" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1691342361">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For parents eager to transport their kids back to the early '90s,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Mystic Quest
  </em>
  serves as the perfect time machine. Widely regarded as the most accessible entry-level
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  game, it's well-suited for little gamers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Upon release, the game was criticized for being too easy and having simplistic graphics and a basic plot — exactly the right combination for kids still getting the hang of the genre! However, there’s one big kicker: nostalgic parents will need to dig out an old SNES or get creative to enjoy this charming classic.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="super-mario-rpg">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Super Mario RPG
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="iconic-turn-based-plumbing">
  Iconic Turn-Based Plumbing
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1276013871" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1276013871" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1276013871" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1276013871" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1276013871-img" id="article-gallery-5-1276013871">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1276013871" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-731716061">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Super Mario RPG
  </em>
  is a perfect fit for kids who love Mario but struggle with tougher platformers. It’s essentially a
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  game with a Mario twist, bringing the iconic plumber into the JRPG genre for the first time. And thanks to the 2023 remake, younger players now have a great way to experience it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Boasting full 3D graphics, this newer version lets players control Mario, Bowser, Princess Peach (formally known as Princess Toadstool), and newcomers Mallow and Geno. It’s a simple RPG that won’t overwhelm young minds, but it offers plenty of fun and joy along the way.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ni-no-kuni-wrath-of-the-white-witch">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Ni No Kuni: Wrath Of The White Witch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="all-kids-want-a-welsh-sidekick">
  All Kids Want A Welsh Sidekick
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1770235404" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1770235404" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1770235404" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1770235404" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1770235404-img" id="article-gallery-6-1770235404">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1770235404" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-892357416">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Every kid should experience the magic of a Studio Ghibli production. While some films may be a bit too heavy (for Totoro's sake, don’t show them
  <em>
   Grave of the Fireflies
  </em>
  ), the kid-friendly ones can be life-changing. Lucky for gamers, Level-5 partnered with the legendary studio to create
  <em>
   Ni no Kuni: Wrath of the White Witch
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This Pokémon-inspired JRPG delivers stunning hand-drawn cutscenes and one of the best stories in the medium. It’s packed with delightful gameplay, oodles of whimsy, and a lovable Welsh fairy sidekick who guides players on their journey. What more could anyone ask for?
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="paper-mario-the-thousand-year-door-remake">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door (Remake)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="perfect-for-5-year-olds-not-thousand-year-olds">
  Perfect For 5-Year-Olds, Not Thousand-Year-Olds
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-43382236" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-43382236" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-43382236" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-43382236" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-43382236-img" id="article-gallery-7-43382236">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-43382236" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-706922992">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When
  <em>
   Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door
  </em>
  originally released in 2004 for the GameCube, it was hailed as one of the best Mario games ever made and one of the greatest games of all time. What made it so special was its ability to beautifully blend whimsical storytelling and traditional JRPG mechanics, managing to captivate both younger and older fans alike.
 </p>
 <p>
  So, when Nintendo announced a remake, the world stopped, held its breath, and crossed its fingers, hoping they wouldn’t screw it up. Fortunately, it was a hit! The remake not only stayed true to the original but also made it more accessible for newcomers with improved visuals and quality-of-life enhancements.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-quest-11-echoes-of-an-elusive-age">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Quest 11: Echoes Of An Elusive Age
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="dragon-ball-lite">
  Dragon Ball Lite
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-544803891" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-544803891" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-544803891" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-544803891" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-544803891-img" id="article-gallery-8-544803891">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-544803891" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1948116424">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unfortunately for impatient parents who are fans of the franchise,
  <em>
   Dragon Ball Z
  </em>
  is geared more towards the older end of a PG audience. However, there are other methods of introducing their kids to the mesmerizing works of Akira Toriyama — and that is the vibrant world of
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  , another of Toriyama’s creations.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  is an absolute phenomenon in Japan, and for good reason. It combines the character design wizardry of the aforementioned
  <em>
   Dragon Ball
  </em>
  creator with the JRPG gameplay fans know and love. While there are plenty of entries to choose from, players can’t go wrong with the latest one:
  <em>
   Dragon Quest XI
  </em>
  . It features incredibly charming characters, an easy-to-follow plot, and one of the best localizations the series has seen.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kingdom-hearts-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Kingdom Hearts (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="young-hearts-be-free-tonight">
  Young Hearts Be Free Tonight
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-2041859856" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-2041859856" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-2041859856" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-2041859856" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-2041859856-img" id="article-gallery-9-2041859856">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-2041859856" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1540731529">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Kids love Disney, and any parent who’s heard “Let it Go” a thousand times can attest to that. So, what better way to introduce them to JRPGs than
  <em>
   Kingdom Hearts
  </em>
  ? This sprawling series brings together a ton of beloved Disney IPs — like
  <em>
   Aladdin
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   The Lion King
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Frozen —
  </em>
  and blends them up with loads of Final Fantasy goodness.
 </p>
 <p>
  The games are beautifully designed with fast-paced combat that’s easy for kids to grasp. Plus, the heartfelt story about friendship and loyalty makes it a perfect choice for young ones as they navigate the world. It’s an adventure packed with magic, wonder, and unique and surprising interactions between Disney and
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  characters.
 </p>
 <h2 id="pokemon-series">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Pokemon (Series)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="no-surprises-here">
  No Surprises Here
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1853076139" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1853076139" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1853076139" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1853076139" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1853076139-img" id="article-gallery-10-1853076139">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1853076139" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1196838336">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Who didn’t play a
  <em>
   Pokémon
  </em>
  game growing up? It’s practically a rite of passage for anyone not living under a rock. The franchise shows no signs of slowing down, and fans can pick just about any entry with their eyes closed and still have a blast.
 </p>
 <p>
  With its fantastic game loops, addictive collecting mechanics, and fun gameplay, it’s no wonder the series is considered catnip for kids. But parents, don’t be too upset when your kids can recall more Pokémon names than they can elements from the periodic table!
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best RPGs with Branching Dialogue Trees, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-rpgs-branching-dialogue-trees-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      RPGs with complex dialogue systems cater to diverse playstyles by offering branching paths.
     </li>
     <li>
      Various RPG titles like Pillars of Eternity, Tyranny, and Disco Elysium excel in deep dialogue trees.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players in games like Baldur's Gate 3 and Disco Elysium can enjoy immersive dialogue tailored to their character's attributes.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Most people love branching dialogue trees in their RPGs for obvious reasons. If players want to believe the illusion that they can play whatever role they put their minds to in these titles, then it's important to accommodate as many unique responses as possible to cater to different playstyles.
 </p>
 <p>
  This makes it important for players to check out RPGs with complex scripts that adhere to their in-game actions. The best dialogue systems take into account everything from the protagonist's background to their morality as they go through an unforgettable experience.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_4">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Games will be ranked based on the degree of complexity in the dialogue system and the extent to which responses branch out.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pillars-of-eternity">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Pillars Of Eternity
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="everything-from-the-watcher-39-s-reputation-to-their-choices-determine-dialogue-flow">
  Everything From The Watcher's Reputation To Their Choices Determine Dialogue Flow
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-424205842" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-424205842" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-424205842" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-424205842" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-424205842-img" id="article-gallery-1-424205842">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-424205842" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-382415425">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity
  </em>
  was Obsidian's attempt to bring back the glorious age of CRPGs, and they accomplished this goal to a certain extent. Players control a Watcher who takes over the fort of Caed Nua and pursues Thaos, the grandmaster of the Leaden Key, who will do everything in his power to enact the goddess Woedica's chaotic goal.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game had some missteps, but fans were pleasantly surprised by how robust the dialogue trees were. Players could channel their expertise in certain skills to give advice or fool other people. Their actions govern how people treat them after a point, as the dialogue reflects their personalities.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tyranny">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Tyranny
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="numerous-branching-paths-offer-unique-dialogue-in-every-playthrough">
  Numerous Branching Paths Offer Unique Dialogue In Every Playthrough
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-351131677" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-351131677" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-351131677" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-351131677" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-351131677-img" id="article-gallery-2-351131677">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-351131677" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1159146608">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's a shame that
  <em>
   Tyranny
  </em>
  stumbled right before the end, since fans were being treated to one of the best modern CRPGs of all time until that point. Players loved exploring what it meant to be evil in this game, using the dialogue system to decide the fate of people and cities, which ranged from somewhat good to deeply unpleasant.
 </p>
 <p>
  Based on the Loyalty and Fear of their companions, new conversation options and powers can be unlocked. This is just one of the many ways that
  <em>
   Tyranny
  </em>
  keeps players engaged with its dialogue. Players are capable of some truly heinous actions if they pursue certain paths.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dragon-age-origins">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Age: Origins
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-excellent-rpg-with-dialogue-that-covers-all-bases">
  An Excellent RPG With Dialogue That Covers All Bases
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1219827846" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1219827846" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1219827846" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1219827846" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1219827846-img" id="article-gallery-3-1219827846">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1219827846" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-87095884">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The beauty of
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Origins
  </em>
  stems from its deep role-playing gameplay, something that BioWare has struggled to live up to ever since. The Grey Warden that players control has access to numerous dialogue options in combat based on their unique origin story and the path they wish to pursue.
 </p>
 <p>
  The tactical combat and memorable characters enhance the depth of this beloved RPG. Players who want to check out a classic role-playing game with excellent branching dialogue options will love what
  <em>
   Dragon Age: Origins
  </em>
  brings to the table.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-wild-hunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="several-dialogue-options-have-major-consequences">
  Several Dialogue Options Have Major Consequences
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1232006335" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1232006335" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1232006335" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1232006335" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1232006335-img" id="article-gallery-4-1232006335">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1232006335" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-22252088">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  is one of the best open-world games ever made. Fans love experiencing Geralt's final journey as he moves heaven and earth to find Ciri, deciding the fate of everyone from simple citizens to entire kingdoms in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  The branching dialogue of
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  is deceptively complex and can lock players into certain routes based on their actions. Characters can turn on Geralt or join his cause, and the ending can be decided by some impactful dialogue choices. This makes it important to pay attention to the story and choose the most apt dialogue choices.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="mass-effect-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Mass Effect 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-tantalizing-dialogue-is-better-than-ever-before">
  The Tantalizing Dialogue Is Better Than Ever Before
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1882242050" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1882242050" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1882242050" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1882242050" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1882242050-img" id="article-gallery-5-1882242050">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1882242050" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-196491883">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The unique dialogue wheel introduced in the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  games did a great job of making simple conversation one of the best parts of the game. Nowhere is this more apparent than in
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  , a game that whisks players away on a grand adventure where Shepard makes numerous meaningful choices.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether players choose to embody the spirit of a Paragon or Renegade, there's no denying that
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  is a blast to play. The improvements made to the combat coupled with its superb script means that players will be invested in Shepard's journey, making important decisions along the way.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-new-vegas">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="incredible-role-playing-extends-to-impressive-branching-dialogue">
  Incredible Role-Playing Extends To Impressive Branching Dialogue
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-374122902" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-374122902" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-374122902" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-374122902" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-374122902-img" id="article-gallery-6-374122902">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-374122902" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1730549431">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  is one of the deepest and most engaging role-playing experiences players can enjoy. The Courier is roped into a plot against his will, and can govern the fate of New Vegas and the entire Mojave based on their actions.
 </p>
 <p>
  This makes it important to form valuable alliances, complete quests, and decide what is best for the people of this wasteland as the Courier shapes their legacy in
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  . As one would expect, the dialogue trees are massive and ensure that players will have to keep track of several storylines as they strive to make the best decisions.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="class-background-amp-skills-influence-dialogue-options">
  Class, Background, &amp; Skills Influence Dialogue Options
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-28165067" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-28165067" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-28165067" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-28165067" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-28165067-img" id="article-gallery-7-28165067">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-28165067" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1551824659">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  is one of the deepest and most intricate CRPGs players can get their hands on. The combat and story are excellent in their own right, but what makes
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  an excellent title is the numerous role-playing options it offers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Everything from the player's actions to their responses governs how they progress in this amazing game. The chosen character's background, class, and expertise are some of the many metrics that decide what they can and cannot say in every conversation, which enhances a player's immersion.
 </p>
 <h2 id="disco-elysium">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Disco Elysium
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="tantalizing-dialogue-in-a-class-of-its-own">
  Tantalizing Dialogue In A Class Of Its Own
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1935883780" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1935883780" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1935883780" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1935883780" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1935883780-img" id="article-gallery-8-1935883780">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1935883780" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-707789459">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the greatest story-driven video games of all time,
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  is perfect for players who don't want to interact with a combat loop. Rather, the crux of this plot revolves around investigations and conversations, with the latter being a story part of the experience courtesy of its impressive script.
 </p>
 <p>
  The detective players control can specialize in one of several skills, letting them empathize with characters, visualize crimes, perform athletic feats, and do anything else they set their minds to. The fact that one of the possible game-overs stems from a conversation where a powerful man dominates the player character is a testament to how magical the branching dialogue paths of
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  are.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Snap: The Best Annihilus Deck</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-snap-annihilus-deck-best-cards-strategies-counters-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       The Best Deck for Annihilus
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Play Annihilus Effectively
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How to Counter Annihilus
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Why You Should Play Annihilus in SNAP’s 2025 Metagame
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since its release in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel SNAP
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s Fly Higher, Further, Faster season in November 2023, Annihilus has become the go-to card for the junk archetype. His unique ability allows you to send your worst cards—those with negative or zero power—over to the enemy side, making him an effective disruptor. Annihilus's ability to clog lanes and create chaos has made him a formidable counter to many top-tier META decks, earning him the title of one of the most anti-META cards in
  <em>
   Marvel SNAP
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For example, when Doom 2099 rose to prominence in PvP, Annihilus was an underrated yet highly effective counter. By using him, you could clog your opponent’s lanes, preventing their DoomBots from spawning and effectively neutralizing their entire strategy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Given Annihilus’s potential to disrupt top-tier setups, we’ve crafted a solid deck that takes full advantage of his ability. For an even more dangerous lineup, you can pair him with Galactus, turning it into a risky, toxic team.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   <strong>
    Annihilus (5-6)
   </strong>
  </p>
  <p>
   <strong>
    On Reveal
   </strong>
   : Your cards with Power below 0 switch sides. Destroy those that can’t.
  </p>
  <p>
   <strong>
    Series
   </strong>
   : Five (Ultra Rare)
  </p>
  <p>
   <strong>
    Season
   </strong>
   : Higher, Further, Faster
  </p>
  <p>
   <strong>
    Release
   </strong>
   : November 21, 2023
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-best-deck-for-annihilus">
  The Best Deck for Annihilus
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="annihilus, hobgoblin, green goblin cards in marvel snap." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/annihilus-best-deck-marvel-snap.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The best deck for Annihilus is
  <strong>
   a disruption lineup with Goblins and Gorr
  </strong>
  . You can assemble this setup by teaming up Annihilus with Green Goblin, Hobgoblin, and Gorr, as well as the following On-Reveal cards: Sersi, Viper, Mysterio, Selene, Cannonball, The Hood, The Sentry, and Ravonna Renslayer.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Card
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Cost
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Power
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Annihilus
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       The Hood
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       The Sentry
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       8
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Sersi
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Green Goblin
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Hobgoblin
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -8
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Viper
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Galactus
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cannonball
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       8
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ravonna Renslayer
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Selene
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Gorr
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       -1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h3 id="synergies-of-the-annihilus-deck">
  Synergies of the Annihilus Deck
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Annihilus is your disruption provider, sending all your negative-power cards to the enemy side.
  </li>
  <li>
   The Hood, The Sentry, and the Goblins are your interrupters. You send them over to the enemy to clog their lanes and inflict negative Power. (Note that The Sentry’s Void, not The Sentry himself, is sent.)
  </li>
  <li>
   Sersi helps transform any unsuccessful shipments—negative cards that stay on your side—into more valuable cards. Viper offers a similar effect.
  </li>
  <li>
   Selene enhances your junk cards, making them even more damaging.
  </li>
  <li>
   Ravonna acts as a Cost balancer, providing a discount on your junk cards to help you play them early.
  </li>
  <li>
   Cannonball is your tech card, used to either move or destroy the enemy's big cards.
  </li>
  <li>
   Gorr is the win condition, growing into a massive drop thanks to all the On Reveal effects in the deck. He’s also buffed every time the enemy drops an On Reveal.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 id="how-to-play-annihilus-effectively">
  How to Play Annihilus Effectively
 </h2>
 <p>
  Here are some tips to help you exploit Annihilus:
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Don’t Be Too Upfront
   </strong>
   : If your opponent sees your plan early, they can counter it. One way to stay unpredictable with an Annihilus junk deck is by adding Galactus. Junks can force the enemy to abandon one lane due to clogging, creating the perfect setup for Galactus to swoop in and win the match.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Drop Your Junk Strategically
   </strong>
   : Don’t rush to play your Goblins or shoot over your Voids immediately. Wait for your opponent to reveal their strategy and expose their strongholds. Then, start disrupting their game plan with your junk.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Have a Backup Plan
   </strong>
   : Always have an alternative if Annihilus isn't drawn or can't be played. You don’t want negative-powered cards to stay on your side. Sersi and Viper are great support options for that.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-counter-annihilus">
  How to Counter Annihilus
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2016724388" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2016724388" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2016724388" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2016724388" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2016724388-img" id="article-gallery-1-2016724388">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2016724388" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-831137752">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The deadliest deck against Annihilus is a Destroy setup. With this archetype, you can turn Annihilus’ junk into treasure. For example, playing Carnage in a clogged lane lets you devour Goblins and Voids, growing your power. Other counters for Annihilus include Cosmo, Viper, and Professor X.
 </p>
 <h2 id="why-you-should-play-annihilus-in-snap-rsquo-s-2025-metagame">
  Why You Should Play Annihilus in SNAP’s 2025 Metagame
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Annihilus-Marvel" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Annihilus-Marvel.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Annihilus, and the junk archetype in general, have had a fluctuating relationship with the metagame. However, one thing that has remained consistent is that their high disruption makes them excellent anti-META setups. If you find yourself overwhelmed by an overpowered card, the solution is clear: Get yourself an Annihilus deck.
 </p>
 <p>
  Annihilus is likely to stand the test of time in 2025 because it targets a fundamental aspect of most decks—real estate. As an expert in clogging lanes, Annihilus can easily disrupt the new cards
  <em>
   SNAP
  </em>
  may release this year. The only real threat to Annihilus would be a resurgence of Destroy decks, but given the current state of the game, that seems unlikely.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Resident Evil Monsters That Look More Like Silent Hill Bosses</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/resident-evil-monsters-look-like-silent-hill-bosses/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Resident Evil and Silent Hill share unique enemy designs that could easily fit in either game's nightmarish world.
     </li>
     <li>
      Enemies like Regeneradors and Hunter Gammas exhibit qualities that evoke Silent Hill's psychological horror.
     </li>
     <li>
      It's clear that Resident Evil has more Silent Hill-style monsters than fans realize, blurring the line between the two franchises.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil
   </em>
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   <em>
    Silent Hill
   </em>
  </strong>
  are two of the biggest juggernauts in the horror game genre, constantly surpassing fan expectations. It's easy to see why; both offer nightmarish worlds, cataclysmic storylines, and enemies that continue to haunt fans of both franchises to this day. What these games share in common is their unique enemy design, which is capable of horrifying players while simultaneously hooking them with the grotesque visuals.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  is known for its gruesome monsters inspired by the trauma of its characters,
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  is known for enemies that are inspired by the storyline, whether it be parasitic or virus-induced mutations. Given the nature of both games, it's not surprising that there's some overlap - and, surprisingly,
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  has more
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  -style monsters than fans might think.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="regenerador">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Regenerador
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-humanoid-enemy-reminiscent-of-silent-hill-39-s-upright-bosses">
  A Humanoid Enemy Reminiscent Of Silent Hill's Upright Bosses
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
  </em>
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="leon kennedy and a regenerator from resident evil 4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/regenerator-resident-evil-4.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the most horrifying moments for old and new fans of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   <strong>
    4
   </strong>
  </em>
  was coming face to face with a Regenerador for the first time in the remake. These bulgy humanoids were the result of Saddler's experiments with Las Plagas on humans, resulting in this bizarre, nightmarish hybrid.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  , these would undoubtedly be inspired by the traumatic remnants of some character's tortured mind, with the result perhaps coming from their own twisted view of other humans. The Regenerador's ability to extend its arms and reel in prey only furthers the argument for its
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  -esque nature.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hunter-gamma">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Hunter Gamma
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="this-disturbing-frog-like-amphibian-exudes-silent-hill-style">
  This Disturbing Frog-Like Amphibian Exudes Silent Hill Style
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="hunter gamma and jill from resident evil 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hunter Gamma is specific to
  <em>
   <strong>
    Resident Evil 3: Nemesis
   </strong>
  </em>
  , and while this one, specifically, gives
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  vibes, that same idea could be extended to Hunter Beta and Hunter Alpha from
  <em>
   Resident Evil 3: Nemesis
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Resident Evil 0
  </em>
  , respectively. What makes the amphibious Hunter Gamma unique is its lack of eyes and teeth, which means it simply swallows its prey whole.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the world of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  , several enemies don't have typical human features like eyes or mouths, such as the Mannequins, Bubble Head Nurses, and Lying Figures from
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  . As such, it's easy to imagine a Hunter Gamma appearing somewhere in the world of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hunk">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   HUNK
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fans-of-the-silent-hill-movies-will-find-this-enemy-familiar">
  Fans Of The Silent Hill Movies Will Find This Enemy Familiar
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="HUNK from resident evil" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/hunter-gamma-resident-evil-3-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  HUNK is unique to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which is where their gas mask-covered faces were first seen in the series. While not an enemy in the sense that they've been horribly mutated, HUNK enemies are reminiscent of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  's toxic nature.
 </p>
 <p>
  For those who are fans of the movies, they're also reminiscent of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  's original inhabitants. On top of that, they are a general reminder that biohazards exist within both games, in the form of enemies or environments.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bandersnatch">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Bandersnatch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="lopsided-and-gangly-are-two-silent-hill-traits">
  Lopsided And Gangly Are Two Silent Hill Traits
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="bandersnatch from resident evil code veronica" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/bandersnatch-resident-evil.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Bandersnatch enemies are most commonly known for their appearance in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil: Code Veronica
   </em>
  </strong>
  and were bioengineered by Umbrella. These B.O.W.s (Bio-Organic Weapons) are known for bashing in the heads of their enemies thanks to their long reach, despite one side of their bodies being atrophied.
 </p>
 <p>
  This T-Virus creation is reminiscent (mostly regarding movement) of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  's often lopsided or medically limited enemies. If one were to appear in a
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  , they would likely fit in incredibly well.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="nyx">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Nyx
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="perhaps-the-most-disturbing-and-also-the-most-like-a-silent-hill-boss">
  Perhaps The Most Disturbing And Also The Most Like A Silent Hill Boss
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="nyx in resident evil" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/nyx-resident-evil.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Nyx looks like an actual nightmare straight out of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  's enemy catalog. This is perhaps the most gruesome enemy, with this particular Umbrella B.O.W. absorbing the bodies of the humans it slays. Nyx also manages to absorb Tyrant-R, ultimately creating a grotesque and formidable opponent.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Nyx first appeared in
  <em>
   Resident Evil Outbreak: File 2
  </em>
  , it easily could have been a creation from
  <em>
   Silent Hill 2
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   3
  </em>
  due to its unsettling design.
 </p>
 <h2 id="novistador">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Novistador
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="silent-hill-is-no-stranger-to-bug-like-enemies">
  Silent Hill Is No Stranger To Bug-Like Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="novistador in resident evil 4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/novistador-resident-evil.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 4
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  These oversized man-eating insects, known as Novistadors, were the result of Las Plagas in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  , but they're just one more commonality with
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  's least-loved enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whereas Novistadors won't hesitate in the slightest to attack Leon Kennedy by air,
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  chose to release their bug enemies in the form of Creepers, which take to the ground and overwhelm James Sunderland by sheer quantity.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="drain-deimos">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Drain Deimos
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-despised-resident-evil-3-nemesis-enemy-and-one-that-emulates-silent-hill-creatures">
  A Despised Resident Evil 3: Nemesis Enemy And One That Emulates Silent Hill Creatures
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="drain deimos in resident evil 3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/drain-deimos-resident-evil-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 3: Nemesis
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  As with any biohazardous problem that's left to fester, the Drain Deimos was a result of insects feeding on infected flesh in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 3: Nemesis
  </em>
  ​​​​​​. With fangs, multiple limbs, and distorted bodies thanks to the effects of the T-Virus, these are undoubtedly another enemy type that could have easily been found in
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Considering Drain Deimos thrive in dark, damp places, they'd likely inhabit every underground area in the town of Silent Hill.
 </p>
 <h2 id="licker">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Licker
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="yet-another-enemy-without-eyes-similar-to-mannequins">
  Yet Another Enemy Without Eyes, Similar To Mannequins
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="licker in resident evil 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/resident-evil-2-licker.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 2
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The tongues on these enemies alone are enough to send
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  players scrambling for flamethrowers. Lickers made their appearance in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 2
  </em>
  and stealthily crept through the halls of the Racoon City Police Department. However, they could have just as easily slunk through Brookhaven Hospital's walls in
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  , attacking players as they made their way out of the decrepit town.
 </p>
 <p>
  Lickers are disturbing enough with little need for embellishment, and Enhanced Lickers are even more of a terrifying
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  -level creation.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="iron-maiden">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Iron Maiden
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="both-silent-hill-and-resident-evil-have-these-spike-laden-enemies-in-common">
  Both Silent Hill And Resident Evil Have These Spike-Laden Enemies In Common
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="iron maiden in resident evil 4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/iron-maiden-resident-evil-4.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 4
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A Pyramid Head doesn't have spikes growing out of its body, but it won't hesitate to impale a player on its enormous Great Knife. This is reminiscent of the Iron Maiden, which did the same thing to Leon Kennedy in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  if players weren't fast enough.
 </p>
 <p>
  Iron Maidens are truly the stuff of (sharp, pointy) nightmares, and it's easy to question whether they were born of Las Plagas or of the inner workings of
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="u-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   U-3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="when-it-comes-to-ultimate-bosses-both-horror-franchises-appreciate-the-same-gruesomeness">
  When It Comes To Ultimate Bosses, Both Horror Franchises Appreciate The Same Gruesomeness
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="u-3 in resident evil 4" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/u-3-resident-evil-4.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Resident Evil 4
   </em>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  U-3 was truly a fitting final boss for
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  . This vile creature was bred from Las Plagas, boasting multiple creature parts mutating together to create an altogether disturbing enemy.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the same way that
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  enjoys combining various elements (usually humans and inanimate objects),
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  also succeeded in combining multiple parts of various enemies to create one ultimate opponent. If gamers didn't realize this boss was from
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  , it could easily be mistaken for a final boss from
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
