<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Third-Person Games With Stealth Mechanics, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-third-person-stealth-games-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Arkham Asylum's fear-based stealth sets it apart from brute force, making players feel like the hunter.
     </li>
     <li>
      Styx: Master Of Shadows offers a unique experience with deception, agility, and methodical stealth gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      A Plague Tale: Innocence emphasizes improvised stealth, with light and darkness playing a crucial role in gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Stealth games are a special breed. They demand patience, precision, and the kind of quick thinking that turns a botched attempt into a barely salvaged success. The best of them don’t just make players feel like ghosts in the shadows; they weave tension into every step, every breath, every decision to take the risk or wait for the perfect moment.
 </p>
 <p>
  These seven games are the best of the best when it comes to third-person stealth, each offering its own unique take on silent takedowns and unseen escapes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="batman-arkham-asylum">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Batman: Arkham Asylum
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-bat-is-always-watching">
  The Bat Is Always Watching
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-840335974" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-840335974" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-840335974" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-840335974" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-840335974-img" id="article-gallery-1-840335974">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-840335974" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-830569851">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gotham’s criminals are terrified of Batman, and
  <em>
   Arkham Asylum
  </em>
  makes sure players understand why. Rocksteady’s take on the Dark Knight isn’t about brute force; it’s about fear. Every encounter is a puzzle, where sneaking through vents, perching above unaware thugs, and picking them off one by one is more satisfying than any brawl. The game’s Predator sections are peak stealth design, letting players systematically dismantle rooms full of enemies until the last one is spinning in circles, panicking, and firing into the dark.
 </p>
 <p>
  But
  <em>
   Arkham Asylum
  </em>
  doesn’t just give players a random assortment of tools—it makes them feel like a hunter. The gargoyles hanging over enemy-infested rooms, the explosive gel that can be planted in advance, the silent takedowns from above or below, all reinforce the idea that Batman is the one in control. And when that fear kicks in, and armed enemies start checking their backs every second, the game’s stealth shines.
 </p>
 <h2 id="styx-master-of-shadows">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Styx: Master Of Shadows
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="short-green-and-deadly">
  Short, Green, And Deadly
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-246603509" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-246603509" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-246603509" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-246603509" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-246603509-img" id="article-gallery-2-246603509">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-246603509" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2049549971">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Stealth games often cast players as highly trained assassins, but
  <em>
   Styx: Master of Shadows
  </em>
  throws that idea out the window and replaces it with a foul-mouthed, four-foot-tall goblin. Styx isn’t built for combat—he’s weak, fragile, and goes down in a single hit. But what he lacks in durability, he more than makes up for in agility and deception.
 </p>
 <p>
  Using the environment to his advantage, Styx can climb, hide, and slip through spaces larger enemies can’t. His real ace, though, is his ability to spawn clones—perfect for distractions, baiting guards into traps, or even sneaking through areas in tandem. And unlike most stealth games that eventually let players brute-force their way through,
  <em>
   Styx
  </em>
  punishes carelessness. It’s methodical, unforgiving, and more rewarding because of it.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="a-plague-tale-innocence">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   A Plague Tale: Innocence
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-shadows-hide-more-than-secrets">
  The Shadows Hide More Than Secrets
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2087918752" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2087918752" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2087918752" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2087918752" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2087918752-img" id="article-gallery-3-2087918752">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2087918752" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1409906462">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike most stealth protagonists, Amicia de Rune isn’t a trained assassin or a hardened soldier—she’s a teenager trying to survive.
  <em>
   A Plague Tale: Innocence
  </em>
  trades high-tech gadgets and elaborate takedowns for desperate, improvised stealth. The game is built around avoidance rather than aggression, where sneaking past soldiers and Inquisition forces is more nerve-wracking than any direct confrontation.
 </p>
 <p>
  But the real wildcard is the rats. Swarms of them, flooding streets and filling rooms like a living tide. They fear light but devour anything in darkness, turning every torch and lantern into a potential lifeline or weapon. Players use this to their advantage, forcing enemies into the rat-infested dark or snuffing out their only protection. The game presents its stealth with a crude irony; where the stealth sections require Amicia and Hugo to stick to the shadows, the rat-infested levels require them to stay in the light. It’s this yin-yang duality of the game’s stealth sections that makes the game feel different from the rest.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hitman">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Hitman
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="blend-in-walk-away-no-one-saw-a-thing">
  Blend In, Walk Away, No One Saw A Thing
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1857520575" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1857520575" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1857520575" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1857520575" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1857520575-img" id="article-gallery-4-1857520575">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1857520575" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1622458137">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Stealth in
  <em>
   Hitman
  </em>
  isn’t just about staying hidden—it’s about never being suspected in the first place. While most games have players slinking through shadows, Agent 47 turns stealth into an art form, using disguises, social stealth, and the environment itself to eliminate targets without anyone realizing he was even there.
 </p>
 <p>
  What sets
  <em>
   Hitman
  </em>
  apart is its freedom. The game doesn’t just give players a mission—it gives them a playground filled with opportunities. A "silent assassin" might slip poison into a drink, rig an "accident," or snipe a target from a mile away. The best players don’t just complete objectives; they vanish, leaving behind a crime scene that looks like a bizarre string of coincidences. It’s not just about being unseen—it’s about being unnoticed.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-last-of-us">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   The Last Of Us
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-last-thing-they-hear-is-nothing-at-all">
  The Last Thing They Hear Is Nothing At All
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-73663745" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-73663745" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-73663745" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-73663745" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-73663745-img" id="article-gallery-5-73663745">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-73663745" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1918238226">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Stealth in
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  is about survival, plain and simple. Every encounter feels like it could go horribly wrong at any second, forcing players to move carefully, use resources wisely, and avoid unnecessary fights. Joel and Ellie aren’t trained operatives—they’re people trying to make it through a brutal world, and the game’s stealth reflects that.
 </p>
 <p>
  The AI is ruthless, especially in the recent remake of the game, with enemies calling out to each other, flanking, and adapting to the player’s actions. A single mistake can turn a quiet approach into a frantic scramble.
 </p>
 <p>
  And then there are the Clickers—blind, infected horrors that track movement and sound. Against them, stealth isn’t just an option; it’s a necessity. Taking one down means risking everything, so sometimes, it’s best to just stay still, breathe, and pray they pass by.
 </p>
 <h2 id="splinter-cell-chaos-theory">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="you-don-rsquo-t-see-sam-but-he-sees-you">
  You Don’t See Sam, But He Sees You
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-190698488" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-190698488" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-190698488" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-190698488" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-190698488-img" id="article-gallery-6-190698488">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-190698488" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-47054252">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Few games understand stealth as well as
  <em>
   Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory
  </em>
  . Sam Fisher isn’t just sneaking past guards—he’s controlling the space around him. Light, sound, and timing all matter, and the game makes sure players feel the weight of every move they make.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Chaos Theory
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
  </em>
  often dubbed as the best game of the franchise,
  <em>
  </em>
  introduced mechanics that would define the stealth genre, from dynamic lighting to an AI that reacts to partial detections rather than instantly going into full alert. Enemies remember disturbances, forcing players to think several steps ahead. And when everything clicks, when players use darkness, gadgets, and split-second decisions to move unseen, it’s perfection.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="metal-gear-solid-5-phantom-pain">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Metal Gear Solid 5: Phantom Pain
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-ghost-on-the-battlefield">
  A Ghost On The Battlefield
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-335774127" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-335774127" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-335774127" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-335774127" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-335774127-img" id="article-gallery-7-335774127">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-335774127" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-2003731897">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hideo Kojima’s masterpiece,
  <em>
   Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain
  </em>
  , is stealth on a grand scale. Unlike most games in the genre that focus on confined spaces and tight corridors,
  <em>
   Phantom Pain
  </em>
  throws players into massive, open-ended environments where every mission can be approached in countless ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  What makes
  <em>
   Phantom Pain
  </em>
  so special is its adaptability. Guards learn from the player’s tactics—overusing headshots means enemies start wearing helmets, and relying on night raids makes them deploy more spotlights.
 </p>
 <p>
  And then there’s the freedom. Creep through the shadows or go full "no kills, no alerts" ghost mode. Call in distractions, sabotage equipment, or turn an enemy camp into an ally base through sheer manipulation. There’s no wrong way to play, but every decision carries weight. It’s the ultimate stealth sandbox, and no other game quite does it like this.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InZOI: Karma Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/inzoi-how-manage-bad-terrible-karma-city-status/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Karma is the result and effect of every choice and action a Zoi makes throughout their life in
  <strong>
   <em>
    InZOI
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Each interaction a Zoi has during their conversation can either lead them to being blessed with the Best Karma or cursed by a Terrible Karma. Karma interactions are originally represented by a blue or red yin and yang-like symbol. The blue color represents the good type of Karma effects, and the red one represents the evil and mean interactions.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  To check a Zoi’s Karma, open the Zoi Card from the screen's lower right corner and look above the Meow Store button in
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  . Next, to check the City’s Karma Report, players must go to the map (Edit City), then select Karma Report.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-manage-karma-report-in-inzoi">
  How To Manage Karma Report In InZOI
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-827126251" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-827126251" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-827126251" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-827126251" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-827126251-img" id="article-gallery-1-827126251">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-827126251" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-479849917">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To manage Karma Report in InZOI, players must watch every move and action of their Zoi and their city's citizens. Each Zoi that lives in the city has a Karma bar that can be filled with good deeds or bad deeds, including players’ created Zois. Players are free to choose their path, but if the Karma Report leans toward the Terrible side more, then an interview with the CEO outside the
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  city is a must.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-achieve-terrible-karma">
  How To Achieve Terrible Karma
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1704474652" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1704474652" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1704474652" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1704474652" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1704474652-img" id="article-gallery-2-1704474652">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1704474652" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-182143253">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Achieving the Terrible Karma status is the easiest; players only need to be a menace to all those around them, from family, co-workers, classmates, and townies. Some of the actions players can do to achieve it are:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Choose mean interactions.
  </li>
  <li>
   Start conflicts with those around you for no reason at all.
  </li>
  <li>
   Choose the red options from the actions' category.
  </li>
  <li>
   Don’t intervene with other Zois Terrible Karma.
  </li>
  <li>
   Steal from ATMs (Terrible Karma only).
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Players going down the evil road will have a bad reputation and rumors about them will spread on Bubbly. If, by some chance, you decide to test the police limit, the Zoi will end up going to jail in
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  . However, be warned that those who die with a Terrible Karma end up as Wandering Ghosts.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-achieve-best-karma">
  How To Achieve Best Karma
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1637775655" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1637775655" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1637775655" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1637775655" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1637775655-img" id="article-gallery-3-1637775655">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1637775655" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-144930311">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To drive the Karma Report towards the good side, players must ensure their Zois are on their best behavior in private or public by:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Donating.
  </li>
  <li>
   Compensating those you’ve harmed.
  </li>
  <li>
   Acts of kindness.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_15">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Check the Karma Report regularly to intervene when needed.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  However, as mentioned before, their Zois are not the only ones contributing to it, so players need to manage their fellow citizens' Karma by scolding them when they lean toward the Terrible acts and complimenting them when they are on the good Karma side. To do so:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Open Edit City from the bottom right corner of the screen or map.
  </li>
  <li>
   Choose the Karma Report tab from the Manage Zois section.
  </li>
  <li>
   Press Karma Status.
  </li>
  <li>
   Intervene by scolding or complimenting.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Even if players put all that effort in, they will still be stubborn Zois with Terrible Karma, forcing players to take matters into their hands. A quick solution is to switch the control to the unyielding and troublesome households or Zois in town and manage their Karma personally.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Narrative Games With Stunning Visuals</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-narrative-games-with-stunning-visuals/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Baldur's Gate 3 weaves stunning visuals seamlessly into a gripping narrative, enhancing player immersion and emotional depth.
     </li>
     <li>
      Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth combines vivid visuals with dynamic battles, creating an energy that amplifies the captivating story.
     </li>
     <li>
      Life is Strange merges beautiful art with rich storytelling, deepening player connections to characters and choices for an unforgettable experience.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  In the world of gaming, narrative-driven titles often struggle to balance captivating storylines with impressive visuals. However, there are a select few that achieve this harmony, where stunning visuals are integral to the story, not just for show.
 </p>
 <p>
  These eight games stand out for their remarkable world-building and atmospheric choices, ensuring that the visuals serve a deeper narrative purpose. From vibrant landscapes to subtle environmental storytelling, each game offers a unique visual style that compliments its exploration of complex, emotionally charged stories. They prove that great graphics and powerful narratives don’t have to be mutually exclusive.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="baldur-39-s-gate-3">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-mastery-in-world-building">
  A Mastery In World Building
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1875471915" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1875471915" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1875471915" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1875471915" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1875471915-img" id="article-gallery-1-1875471915">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1875471915" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-358124212">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  , visuals do more than just impress—they elevate the story. From enchanted forests to shadowy ruins, each setting feels alive with detail, drawing players into its rich, immersive world. The stunning environments serve the narrative, enhancing the emotional weight of every decision and interaction.
 </p>
 <p>
  World-building is key here, with every location packed with lore that deepens the story.
  <em>
   Baldur’s Gate 3
  </em>
  shows that incredible graphics can be seamlessly woven into a compelling narrative, making for a truly unforgettable experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-7-rebirth">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 7: Rebirth
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="beautiful-natural-landscapes-with-vibrant-battles">
  Beautiful Natural Landscapes With Vibrant Battles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1338230490" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1338230490" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1338230490" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1338230490" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1338230490-img" id="article-gallery-2-1338230490">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1338230490" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-128530900">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  stuns with its vivid visuals, blending detailed character art with vibrant, dynamic battles. From the gritty streets of Midgar to lush, expansive landscapes, each environment is a feast for the eyes. The character designs are striking, staying true to the originals while adding depth and flair, making every character feel unique.
 </p>
 <p>
  The colorful, fast-paced battles bring even more energy to the experience, with visuals that amplify the action. It masterfully combines breathtaking visuals with a gripping story, delivering an adventure that is as visually stunning as it is emotionally engaging.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="life-is-strange-remastered">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Life Is Strange Remastered
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-emotional-story-complemented-by-stunning-visuals">
  An Emotional Story Complemented By Stunning Visuals
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-963947395" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-963947395" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-963947395" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-963947395" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-963947395-img" id="article-gallery-3-963947395">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-963947395" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2145330626">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  is a captivating narrative-driven game that stands out for its compelling story and stunning visuals. The game's hand-painted art style, combined with atmospheric lighting and detailed environments, creates a unique, immersive world. Each setting feels alive, from the tranquil landscapes of Arcadia Bay to the intense emotional moments.
 </p>
 <p>
  The striking visuals amplify the narrative, making players feel deeply connected to the characters and their choices. The game's blend of visual beauty and rich storytelling truly sets it apart as a masterpiece in interactive entertainment.
 </p>
 <h2 id="firewatch">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Firewatch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="environmental-storytelling-done-perfectly">
  Environmental Storytelling Done Perfectly
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-2113064121" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-2113064121" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-2113064121" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-2113064121" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-2113064121-img" id="article-gallery-4-2113064121">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-2113064121" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-777770292">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Firewatch
  </em>
  stands out as a narrative game with breathtaking visuals that transport players to the serene yet haunting Wyoming wilderness. The game’s unique art style features rich colors and dynamic lighting, making the environment feel both alive and expansive.
 </p>
 <p>
  As the story progresses, the stunning landscapes and meticulously crafted details deepen the emotional connection to the protagonist, Henry. The visuals not only enhance the atmosphere but also elevate the tension and mystery, making
  <em>
   Firewatch
  </em>
  a truly immersive experience.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Until Dawn
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stunning-atmospheric-horror">
  Stunning Atmospheric Horror
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-118832443" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-118832443" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-118832443" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-118832443" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-118832443-img" id="article-gallery-5-118832443">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-118832443" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-122902888">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Set primarily in a remote mountain range,
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  uses realistic graphics and cinematic lighting to create a tense, eerie environment. Each setting, from snow-covered forests to creepy interiors, enhances the psychological horror and suspense. As a mastery of environmental storytelling, the game makes no sacrifice in either visuals or story.
 </p>
 <p>
  The stunning visuals combine with the branching storyline to allow players to feel the weight of their choices as they navigate the thrilling, unpredictable narrative, making
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  a visually impressive and immersive experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-red-strings-club">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   The Red Strings Club
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="nostalgic-graphics-with-a-futuristic-storyline">
  Nostalgic Graphics With A Futuristic Storyline
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1294955188" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1294955188" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1294955188" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1294955188" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1294955188-img" id="article-gallery-6-1294955188">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1294955188" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-595416528">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Red Strings Club features a pixel art style that, while often considered less impressive, effectively blends retro nostalgia with intricate future world building. This narrative game blends striking visuals and an engaging story set in a cyberpunk-style world, taking players through an emotionally and technically complex storyline.
 </p>
 <p>
  The game’s pixel art style is rich in detail, with vibrant neon colors and atmospheric lighting that bring the futuristic city to life. Its unique visual design enhances the emotional depth of the story, where choices shape the narrative. With its sharp contrast between the game's colorful environments and darker themes,
  <em>
   The Red Strings Club
  </em>
  creates an unforgettable and immersive experience that lingers long after the game ends.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-wild-hunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="brought-to-life-from-its-literary-origins">
  Brought To Life From Its Literary Origins
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1689150583" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1689150583" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1689150583" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1689150583" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1689150583-img" id="article-gallery-7-1689150583">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1689150583" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1023381549">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </em>
  is a visually breathtaking narrative game that immerses players in a vast, detailed open world. Set in a beautifully crafted medieval fantasy universe, the game features stunning landscapes, from lush forests to war-torn villages, all brought to life with remarkable realism. The intricate environments and dynamic weather system add depth to the story, making each location feel unique and alive.
 </p>
 <p>
  The developers successfully capture the essence of the original narratives from which
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  universe originates, transforming the story into an engaging playable experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  ​​​​​​​
 </p>
 <h2 id="coffee-talk">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Coffee Talk
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="simple-yet-very-effective-visuals">
  Simple, Yet Very Effective Visuals
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-943251212" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-943251212" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-943251212" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-943251212" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-943251212-img" id="article-gallery-8-943251212">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-943251212" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1333610665">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Like
  <em>
   The Red Strings Club
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  successfully utilizes a pixel art style. In
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  , the cozy, neon-lit coffee shop created by the pixel art style provides a warm and inviting atmosphere, with each character and environment carefully designed to reflect the game's emotional depth. The soothing visuals complement the heartfelt conversations and personal stories of the diverse cast, making the world feel both intimate and relatable.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the most notable aspects of
  <em>
   Coffee Talk
  </em>
  is its minimalism, which is a trait often overlooked when discussing game visuals. It skillfully balances the realism of its Seattle setting with the fantasy characters that players meet throughout the experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  ​​​​​​​
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil: 8 Most Controversial Moments In The Series, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/resident-evil-most-controversial-moments-series-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Resident Evil games can be outlandish, with memorable moments like Salazar's statue coming to life.
     </li>
     <li>
      Piers' death in Resident Evil 6 divided fans, with some considering it a waste of a potential character.
     </li>
     <li>
      Chris punching a boulder in Resident Evil 5 was a controversial and absurd gameplay segment.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As anyone who has any experience with the series will know all too well, the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Resident Evil
   </em>
  </strong>
  games can end up getting pretty outlandish with their stories, resulting in plenty of twists and turns throughout the wider narrative to keep players guessing. This can also apply to the gameplay, where a game can suddenly introduce a new enemy or mechanic seemingly out of nowhere, making for some pretty bizarre segments. While the majority of these shocking moments are fondly remembered by fans, others, for one reason or another, ended up receiving mixed opinions, with some loving them, while others questioned if they were really necessary.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether it's a sudden character death, a strange piece of lore, or even simply a scene that goes too over the top with its action or humor, there are plenty of moments throughout this much-beloved survival horror series that have ended up becoming somewhat polarizing.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   This list contains spoilers!
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="salazar-39-s-statue-comes-to-life">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Salazar's Statue Comes To Life
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-series-arguably-reached-its-peak-of-absurdity-with-this-chase-sequence">
  The Series Arguably Reached Its Peak Of Absurdity With This Chase Sequence
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1230610888" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1230610888" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1230610888" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1230610888" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1230610888-img" id="article-gallery-1-1230610888">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1230610888" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-862905411">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  is a weird game, there's no denying that, but throughout Leon's grueling mission to save Ashley from the Los Illuminados, arguably the most outlandish thing he finds himself doing is running away from a giant statue that suddenly springs to life. This is a gameplay segment that comes not long after Leon and Ashley take refuge in Salazar's castle, with players being randomly thrown into a hectic QTE segment while a gigantic creepy depiction of Salazar stomps its way toward Leon.
 </p>
 <p>
  The fans who have embraced the more action-oriented gameplay style that
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  brought to the table love this section, considering it's just one of many QTE sections like this that go all-out with their presentation and tension. Those who were hoping for the game to be more in line with the slow and methodical survival horror roots of the series weren't as fond of this one, though, something Capcom seemingly acknowledged by keeping the statue's legs stationary in the
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4 Remake
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="piers-39-death">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Piers' Death
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-potential-new-blood-of-the-series-was-sadly-killed-in-action">
  The Potential New Blood Of The Series Was Sadly Killed In Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1308267562" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1308267562" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1308267562" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1308267562" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1308267562-img" id="article-gallery-2-1308267562">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1308267562" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-231651045">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  By the time
  <em>
   Resident Evil 6
  </em>
  had arrived, discussions were beginning to crop up concerning whether it might be time to introduce some new protagonists into the series to freshen things up. This was before Ethan made his way into the story, meaning the likes of Leon, Chris, and Claire had all been on plenty of adventures already, and while they all still deserve to play a key role in the games, it felt like
  <em>
   6
  </em>
  was the opportunity to introduce some fresh blood.
 </p>
 <p>
  Piers, a young and courageous BSAA soldier who helps to keep Chris on the straight and narrow for much of the game, was a character who could have easily assumed the role of lead protagonist in a future title, but unfortunately, he meets his untimely demise at the end of his debut game. After injecting himself to hold off the HAOS B.O.W, Piers dies in an underwater base, leading some fans to call this a waste of a character, while others praised the moment for its emotional impact on the story.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="chris-punching-the-boulder">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Chris Punching The Boulder
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-absurd-gameplay-segment-that-was-a-step-too-far-for-some-players">
  An Absurd Gameplay Segment That Was A Step Too Far For Some Players
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-482654932" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-482654932" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-482654932" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-482654932" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-482654932-img" id="article-gallery-3-482654932">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-482654932" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-358574073">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  confirmed that the series was beginning to stray into the action genre, the fifth mainline game accelerated this by implementing plenty of chaotic set pieces and tons of new melee combat abilities. However, the aesthetic and dark story still made it feel somewhat grounded in horror, so at the very end of the game, when Chis is tasked with punching a boulder triple his size to step over some lava, it was a moment that everyone would come to form their own opinion on.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nowadays, it's often embraced as little more than an absurdly funny moment that has become one of the most well-known memes from the series. At the time of the game's release, though, when fans were still cautiously wondering where the series was ahead, it felt like a step too far for some. Either way, it's a moment that has been referenced by Capcom themselves numerous times, such as with Heisenberg calling it out during his boss fight in
  <em>
   Village
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="queen-leech-reveal">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Queen Leech Reveal
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-opera-singing-madman-turned-out-to-be-a-very-smart-leech">
  The Opera Singing Madman Turned Out To Be...A Very Smart Leech?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1586383663" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1586383663" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1586383663" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1586383663" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1586383663-img" id="article-gallery-4-1586383663">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1586383663" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-2133030629">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  series is no stranger to over-the-top villains, but the Queen Leech might just take the cake for being the most outlandish of the bunch. At certain points in
  <em>
   Resident Evil 0's
  </em>
  story, Rebecca and Billy catch a glimpse of a strange man in a robe who is clearly up to no good, but it's not until the final area of the game that players learn exactly who, or what, this being actually is.
 </p>
 <p>
  It turns out this depiction of James Marcus is an evolved leech who witnessed Marcus' murder at the hands of Umbrella with its own eyes. In an attempt to get revenge, the leech assumed the form of Marcus but was eventually stopped in its tracks by Rebecca and Billy. Whether this moment was too ridiculous or simply a weird but intriguing reveal has been up for debate ever since the game was released back in 2002.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="switching-to-chris">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Switching To Chris
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="there-are-mixed-opinions-on-the-decision-to-jump-over-to-chris-in-code-veronica">
  There Are Mixed Opinions On The Decision To Jump Over To Chris In Code Veronica
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-633687180" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-633687180" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-633687180" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-633687180" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-633687180-img" id="article-gallery-5-633687180">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-633687180" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1486728468">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though Chris does appear on the box art of
  <em>
   Code Veronica
  </em>
  to let players know right from the get-go that he's part of the story, it can be easy to forget about him, considering he's absent for the first half of the game. After spending hours playing as Claire and getting engrossed in the story, the game, without any warning, will jump players over to Chris' perspective, with him becoming the new protagonist for the rest of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  This decision wasn't a problem for some people, but the reason others came to dislike it was because all the items they hadn't put in the item box as Claire wouldn't show up for Chris to use. Players who were well-prepared and organized with their box items, therefore, didn't mind this change in character, but needless to say, those who didn't would not have been all that thrilled considering how admittedly jarring of a switch it was.
 </p>
 <h2 id="chris-shooting-mia">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Chris Shooting Mia
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="chris-39-portrayal-in-the-intro-to-village-was-a-bold-move-from-capcom">
  Chris' Portrayal In The Intro To Village Was A Bold Move From Capcom
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-447970408" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-447970408" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-447970408" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-447970408" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-447970408-img" id="article-gallery-6-447970408">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-447970408" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-906532148">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To say
  <em>
   Resident Evil Village
  </em>
  starts off with a bang would be putting it mildly. After barging into Ethan's home and shooting his wife to death, Chris proceeds to steal Ethan's daughter, Rose, while keeping his true intentions a mystery. While there's no doubt this stands as one of the most memorable intros in the series, many people struggled to agree on whether it was worth it, considering it makes Chris look a little dumb in hindsight.
 </p>
 <p>
  Because Chris barely even says a word to Ethan during this whole exchange, despite admitting later in the game that he probably should have told him everything, the scene becomes a bit silly. However, that doesn't take away from how shocking and impactful it is, getting players hooked into the story right off the bat as one of the series' most iconic heroes seemingly turns into a villain.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rose-inherits-special-powers">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Rose Inherits Special Powers
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="resident-evil-hints-at-a-new-protagonist-with-supenatural-powers">
  Resident Evil Hints At A New Protagonist With Supenatural Powers
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-8545891" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-8545891" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-8545891" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-8545891" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-8545891-img" id="article-gallery-7-8545891">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-8545891" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1212814266">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Though there have been some exceptions throughout the series, the
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  games tend to remain rooted in reality, putting much of their focus on scientific experiments gone wrong as opposed to anything occult or supernatural. Whether the series should explore the concept of otherwordly enemies and superpowers in the future wasn't something that was commonly discussed - at least, it wasn't until people finally got their hands on
  <em>
   Village
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  In the post-credits scene, Rose, who is now all grown up and seemingly being watched over by a secret organization, is shown to possess unique superpowers and abilities that the normal human doesn't because of her involvement with the Mold. This would be expanded on in the Shadows of Rose DLC, where players are able to use these powers freely to defeat enemies; a breath of fresh air for some fans but a step in the wrong direction for others.
 </p>
 <h2 id="quot-umbrella-39-s-stock-crashed-quot">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   "Umbrella's Stock Crashed..."
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="was-umbrella-taken-out-of-the-story-too-early-or-was-it-the-right-time">
  Was Umbrella Taken Out Of The Story Too Early, Or Was It The Right Time?
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-128536007" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-128536007" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-128536007" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-128536007" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-128536007-img" id="article-gallery-8-128536007">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-128536007" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-275509687">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To understand why this single line in the intro of
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  has been so controversial, it's important to put into context what was built up in the games leading up to this. Almost every
  <em>
   Resident Evil
  </em>
  title, including
  <em>
   Code Veronica
  </em>
  , ended with the protagonists promising to put an end to Umbrella once and for all as a form of punishment for their crimes. Outside a single bonus story in the
  <em>
   Umbrella Chronicles
  </em>
  spin-off game, though, fans never got to see this final battle unfold.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is why, when Leon revealed the corporation had simply gone bust due to their stocks taking a hit, it was met with mixed opinions. On the one hand, throwing away this subplot so casually was a real gut punch for longtime fans who wanted to see where things were heading, but then again, it also allowed the series to leave Umbrella behind to explore new groups and factions. After all, many people love that
  <em>
   Resident Evil 4
  </em>
  feels like its own standalone story, but the decision to remove Umbrella in this way, even today, remains a hot topic of debate.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Dungeon Crawlers That Feature Companions</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-dungeon-crawlers-with-companions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Dungeon crawlers feature complex puzzles, hidden secrets, and enemies to overcome while exploring.
     </li>
     <li>
      Many games have companion systems, requiring players to consider party synergy and choices.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like The Bard's Tale 4 require strategic party management and tactical combat for success.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Dungeon crawlers are all about the player enjoying exploring subterranean structures, to find loot, treasure, and more. And of course, there are bound to be complex puzzles, hidden secrets, and a whole host of vicious enemies to overcome during the journey.
 </p>
 <p>
  Many dungeon crawlers feature a companion or party system. These companions are sometimes fully AI-controlled with the player having little impact on their actions. Other games feature a complex, interactive party management system, with each companion being fully controlled by the player. Either way, these games almost always require the player to consider how party members synergize as a combined team, and make the right choices to build a strong party.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-bard-rsquo-s-tale-4-barrows-deep">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   The Bard’s Tale 4: Barrows Deep
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="reviving-the-classic-party-base-dungeon-crawling-franchise">
  Reviving The Classic Party Base Dungeon Crawling Franchise
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-45704372" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-45704372" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-45704372" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-45704372" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-45704372-img" id="article-gallery-1-45704372">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-45704372" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-796953208">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Bard’s Tale
  </em>
  is an RPG franchise with a long history, with the original game being released way back in 1985, and being released for home computer platforms such as the Amiga and Atari ST at the time. The original game did much to set the standards for future party-based RPGs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combat in
  <em>
   The Bard’s Tale 4: Barrows Deep
  </em>
  takes place on a grid, and the player must think tactically about the actions that each companion in their party will take, and when. The game made this list because each companion has their own background quest, a full set of voice samples that are used at appropriate times, and skill sets that make them unique within the game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="legend-of-grimrock-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Legend Of Grimrock 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="classic-old-school-dungeon-crawling-requiring-synergistic-companions">
  Classic Old School Dungeon Crawling Requiring Synergistic Companions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2038342875" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2038342875" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2038342875" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2038342875" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2038342875-img" id="article-gallery-2-2038342875">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2038342875" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-16193058">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Legend of Grimrock 2
  </em>
  takes the old-school slant on dungeon crawlers, reminiscent of ancient games such as Eye of the Beholder and Bard Tale, and adds in some modern ideas, as well as much better graphics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Many of the traditional dungeon challenges must be overcome in this game, such as deadly traps, intricate mazes, and, of course, dangerous enemies. Choosing the right companions and developing them in the right way to create a synergistic team is crucial to being successful in this game. This means having damage dealers, healers, and buffers that work together to help the party survive.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="demon-gaze-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Demon Gaze 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="turn-based-dungeon-crawler-with-demon-companions">
  Turn-Based Dungeon Crawler With Demon Companions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-359988194" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-359988194" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-359988194" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-359988194" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-359988194-img" id="article-gallery-3-359988194">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-359988194" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-356371239">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Demon Gaze 2
  </em>
  has a slightly different angle on recruiting and managing a party of dungeon crawlers. In this game, players can recruit a team of powerful demons to be their allies. Each demon has a distinct personality and their own skill set.
 </p>
 <p>
  The dungeons in
  <em>
   Demon Gaze 2
  </em>
  require strategic thinking to traverse safely, which means the player needs to make tough choices about which companions to level up and upgrade. Combat is quite tactical, and takes place turn-by-turn, enabling the player to use the right companion for a role during each turn.
 </p>
 <h2 id="undernauts-labyrinth-of-yomi">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Undernauts: Labyrinth of Yomi
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="horror-game-meets-dungeon-crawler-with-customizable-companions">
  Horror Game Meets Dungeon Crawler With Customizable Companions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1449659864" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1449659864" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1449659864" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1449659864" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1449659864-img" id="article-gallery-4-1449659864">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1449659864" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-362133875">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Undernauts: Labyrinth of Yomi
  </em>
  is a dark, often grim dungeon crawler. The gameplay follows the adventures of the Undernauts, a party of subterranean workers that have been trapped in a confusing, often dangerous labyrinth.
 </p>
 <p>
  The companion system in
  <em>
   Undernauts: Labyrinth of Yomi
  </em>
  is deep, enabling the player to customize companions in many ways. Primarily, this involves making sure that companions progress in ways that make them fit well with the rest of the team, with skills and abilities that work synergistically with other team members. Indeed, combat in this game requires the entire party of companions to work as a unified whole to take down tough foes.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="wizardry-labyrinth-of-lost-souls">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Wizardry: Labyrinth of Lost Souls
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="classic-companions-classes">
  Classic Companions Classes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-974626063" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-974626063" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-974626063" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-974626063" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-974626063-img" id="article-gallery-5-974626063">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-974626063" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-921629624">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Wizardry
  </em>
  franchise is synonymous with classic RPG gameplay, replete with tough dungeons to overcome.
  <em>
   Wizardry: Labyrinth of Lost Souls
  </em>
  is considered to be one of the titles in the
  <em>
   Wizardry Renaissance
  </em>
  , following on from the original franchise where it left off in 2001, with
  <em>
   Wizardry 8
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The companion classes in this game are instantly recognizable. Mages, warriors, healers, and other well-known fantasy classes are all available. Combat is turn-based and requires tactical planning to ensure the right companion uses the right skill at the right time. Anyone who loves classic RPGs will likely enjoy
  <em>
   Wizardry: Labyrinth of Lost Souls
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="stranger-of-sword-city">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Stranger Of Sword City
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="companions-are-essential-in-this-dark-fantasy-dungeon-crawler">
  Companions Are Essential In This Dark Fantasy Dungeon Crawler
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-2041143513" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-2041143513" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-2041143513" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-2041143513" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-2041143513-img" id="article-gallery-6-2041143513">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-2041143513" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1882741855">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Platforms: Nintendo Switch, Xbox One, Microsoft Windows, PlayStation Vita, Xbox 360
  </li>
  <li>
   Released: June 5, 2014
  </li>
  <li>
   Developer: Experience Inc.
  </li>
  <li>
   Genre: Role-playing Video Game
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stranger Of Sword City
  </em>
  is a dungeon crawler with a very dark fantasy theme. In this game, companions are everything, and the wrong choice of companions or skills they offer can be disastrous. Primarily because the game’s combat can be brutal at times.
 </p>
 <p>
  To do well, players will need to consider the role of each companion in their party, evaluating their strengths and weaknesses, and how they fit into the party as a whole. Core abilities need to complement the whole team, and bring needed capabilities such as healing or buffing, alongside simple direct or ranged damage skills.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="labyrinth-of-galleria-the-moon-society">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Labyrinth Of Galleria: The Moon Society
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="deep-party-mechanics">
  Deep Party Mechanics
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1765965467" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1765965467" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1765965467" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1765965467" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1765965467-img" id="article-gallery-7-1765965467">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1765965467" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1560812422">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Labyrinth Of Galleria: The Moon Societ
  </em>
  y can be considered to be something of a spiritual successor to the classic Labyrinth of Refrain. It expands on the gameplay in relation to the companion and party mechanics.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Labyrinth Of Galleria: The Moon Societ
  </em>
  y, players have to control a veritable army of puppet-like companions. Each of them is customizable and can be tailored to fill specific roles when exploring dungeons, finding treasure, and defending enemies. The game takes a place on this list for breaking the mold and using companions in a very different way than most other dungeon crawlers.
 </p>
 <h2 id="etrian-odyssey-4-legends-of-the-titan">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Etrian Odyssey 4: Legends Of The Titan
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="cartoon-style-party-based-dungeon-crawling">
  Cartoon-Style Party-Based Dungeon Crawling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1179327917" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1179327917" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1179327917" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1179327917" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1179327917-img" id="article-gallery-8-1179327917">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1179327917" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1474744222">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Etrian Odyssey 4: Legends of the Titan
  </em>
  could be considered a definitive example of what a great dungeon crawler with comprehensive companion and party mechanics should look like. The game offers a significant challenge, even for aficionados of the genre.
 </p>
 <p>
  The reason for
  <em>
   Etrian Odyssey 4: Legends of the Titan
  </em>
  taking top place on this list, is the sheer depth of customization the player can apply to companions. When exploring the labyrinth, and dealing with dangers and enemies, the player must ensure that they have access to a team of companions that form a cohesive party. This means ensuring that party members have skills that are both needed, and complementary skills wielded by other party members.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
