<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Given Its Endless War With Call of Duty, Battlefield 6 Needs to Pick the Right Time to Strike</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/battlefield-6-call-of-duty-competition-beta-when-important/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The direct competition between the
  <em>
   <strong>
    Battlefield
   </strong>
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  franchises is one of the most storied and longstanding in the gaming industry, with both massively popular IPs catering to different sides of the first-person shooter community. While the relentless annual release schedule of
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  has made it more difficult for
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  to compete in recent years, 2025 is set to be quite unique in that it will reportedly see the launch of a
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  title, being the first time this has happened since 2021's
  <em>
   Battlefield 2042
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   CoD: Vanguard
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Some early details are already surfacing regarding this year's
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  release, including leaked gameplay footage of its thorough playtesting, with a lot of positive sentiment already surrounding the project - a clear difference from the many criticisms that
  <em>
   Battlefield 2042
  </em>
  faced throughout its life cycle. With this coming in contrast to the potentially risky route that
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  's 2025 release is reportedly taking, a huge opportunity for the
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  franchise is imminent, and the upcoming game will need to time its big reveal perfectly to maximize its chances of once again directly competing with the industry giant that is
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="a-wise-reveal-date-could-be-the-perfect-set-up-for-the-next-battlefield-game">
  A Wise Reveal Date Could Be the Perfect Set Up For the Next Battlefield Game
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1030548399" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1030548399" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1030548399" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1030548399" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1030548399-img" id="article-gallery-1-1030548399">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1030548399" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1879683951">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The playtesting for the upcoming
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  project is the most rigorous that the franchise has ever seen, with DICE launching the Battlefield Labs "community development collaboration" to put fans at the center of the title's development and creative direction. This seems to be a logical move following the lingering negative reputation that
  <em>
   Battlefield 2042
  </em>
  brought to the franchise, especially around the time of its launch, with DICE seemingly taking fan feedback to heart more than ever before with its next project.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The Battlefield Labs testing is being carried out in stages, with future playtesting expanding to more regions and eventually involving tens of thousands of early players.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  It is confirmed that the next
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  will tone things back to a modern setting, with its return to things like 64-player matches and more compact maps already drawing huge comparisons between the title and the likes of
  <em>
   Battlefield 3
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   4
  </em>
  . This has amassed a lot of early goodwill for the project, especially among long-term fans of the franchise, and the timing of the game's full announcement needs to maximize this early positive attention as much as possible.
 </p>
 <p>
  2025 is set to be a strange year for
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  , with many reports suggesting that this year's
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  release is set to be another
  <em>
   Black Ops
  </em>
  release. Rumored to be a direct sequel to 2012's
  <em>
   Black Ops 2
  </em>
  , this project would run the risk of repeating the same backlash that 2023's
  <em>
   Modern Warfare 3
  </em>
  received as the second of two back-to-back
  <em>
   Modern Warfare
  </em>
  releases, with rumors already suggesting that 2025's
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  may repeat the same remastered multiplayer map catalog that only added to
  <em>
  </em>
  the criticisms of
  <em>
   MW3
  </em>
  . - albeit with some new maps mixed in.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-well-timed-battlefield-reveal-has-a-real-chance-of-taking-steam-away-from-call-of-duty-39-s-2025-project">
  A Well-Timed Battlefield Reveal Has a Real Chance of Taking Steam Away From Call of Duty's 2025 Project
 </h3>
 <p>
  While a continuation of
  <em>
   Black Ops 2
  </em>
  's story could be a fascinating prospect, the supposedly limited amount of fresh content for the game's multiplayer could put
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  in a relative weak spot in 2025, making the excitement around the next
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  all the more valuable for the EA franchise. The
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  era of
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  recently received quite a boost with the hotly anticipated re-introduction of Verdansk to
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , and the next
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  should bide its time and wait for this hype to die down before fully introducing itself to the FPS scene.
 </p>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  reveals usually starting around April or May,
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  may be wise to wait until 2025's
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  release starts its own promotional run before revealing itself, allowing fans of the FPS genre to become fully aware of what this year's
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  offerings are and allowing for a direct comparison to be made with what
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  has in store. A well-timed reveal of the next
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  , after the initial interest in this year's
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  reveal dies down, could be invaluable for DICE, putting the ball firmly in
  <em>
   Battlefield
  </em>
  's court for what is shaping up to be one of the most intriguing showdowns that the two massive franchises have ever had.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schedule 1 Dev Teases Content Coming in Next Update</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/schedule-1-new-update-content-shops-decorations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The next Schedule 1 update will include new shops and decorations, teased by the single-person development team.
     </li>
     <li>
      Early access crime simulator Schedule 1 has peaked at over 400,000 concurrent players, surpassing expectations.
     </li>
     <li>
      The next update is tentatively scheduled for April 7.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Schedule 1
   </strong>
  </em>
  's next update is coming very soon, and its single-person development team is giving players a tease of what they can expect when it goes live. The upcoming update for
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  will give players access to a couple of new shops and cosmetic decorations, along with some other surprises that its creator, Tyler, calls "very fancy."
 </p>
 <p>
  Released in early access on March 24, the co-op crime simulator on Steam became an instant hit in its first two days, surpassing 130,000 concurrent players in that very early timeframe. It hit an even higher peak of more than 414,00 concurrent players on March 30, and its daily peaks have consistently registered well since then, never dipping below 318,000 according to SteamDB's charts.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a pair of recent posts on Twitter, Tyler has shared that the next full update will likely arrive in the early hours of April 7. Two new shops, a Boutique Store and a Pawn Shop, will be included, presumably providing players with new ways to make money in
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  . Additionally, the update will include new decorations for walls. The creator had been hoping to release an open beta version of the update one day prior to its official release, but in an effort to avoid any "glaring issue" slipping through, he ultimately decided to cancel the open beta.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="schedule-1-next-update-release-date">
  Schedule 1 Next Update Release Date
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Monday, April 7 (Tentatively)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  These new reveals are in addition to a previously announced
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  feature coming in a new update. In a prior post, Tyler had shared an image of a wall with two shelving units filled with various drugs, products, and other items, along with a caption that notes "wall-mounted stuff" will be coming in the crime simulator's next update. There hasn't been a formal explanation from the creator of just how wall-mounted features will work in
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  , but based on the comments, the prospect of having a better variety of options to store, manage, and transport items is a highly requested feature that many fans are looking forward to.
 </p>
 <p>
  The announcement of the update's impending arrival may be a relief to some fans who have been worried about the future of the game's development.
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  is under copyright infringement investigation following a claim by
  <em>
   Drug Dealer Simulator
  </em>
  series producer Movie Games S.A. regarding the similarities between
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  and its games, which were released in 2020 and 2024.
  <em>
   Schedule 1
  </em>
  's creator has not publicly responded to these claims, though the threat of legal action is causing a stir among the game's fan community.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Evolve Inkay In Pokemon GO?</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/evolve-inkay-pokemon-go/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Pokemon GO: How To Evolve Inkay
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Pokemon GO: How To Get Inkay &amp; Shiny Inkay
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Inkay has a unique evolution method in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Unlike Regular Pokemon requiring only Candies, there is an additional step in Inkay’s evolution. Only those who know the secret method can evolve their Inkay into a Malamar.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Inkay is a dual Dark and Psychic-type Pokemon with a maximum in-game Combat Power (CP) of 1048. The monster’s stat spread consists of 98 ATK, 95 DEF, and 142 HP. Evolving the monster turns it into a powerful Malamar with a maximum CP of 2667. Malamar has a balanced stat spread of 177 ATK, 165 DEF, and 200 HP. This guide details how to evolve Inkay in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  and get Malamar.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-how-to-evolve-inkay">
  Pokemon GO: How To Evolve Inkay
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="How to evolve Inkay in Pokemon GO" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-evolve-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Those with an Inkay and Shiny Inkay can evolve it into a Malamar and Shiny Malamar respectively. You must
  <strong>
   first collect 50 Inkay Candies
  </strong>
  to initiate the evolution process. Once you have the required amount of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Inkay Candies you can proceed to the next step.
 </p>
 <p>
  It is the same as the mainline Pokemon games where players must turn their consoles upside down.
  <strong>
   You must turn your Android/iOS device upside down
  </strong>
  to complete the final step of Inkay evolution in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . It is mandatory to turn your device upside down each time you evolve an Inkay into a Malamar.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     You have to catch and transfer numerous Inkay to get the Candies, doing regular tasks with Inkay as your Buddy Pokemon also rewards Inkay Candies.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-how-to-get-inkay-amp-shiny-inkay">
  Pokemon GO: How To Get Inkay &amp; Shiny Inkay
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="How to get Inkay in Pokemon GO" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/how-to-get-inkay-in-pokemon-go.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Inkay is a wild Pokemon and is often featured in events. Participants of such featured events can encounter wild Inkay at an increased rate. You can use
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  items to further boost Inkay's spawn rate during such featured events. Strategically using these in-game elements can stack their effects on top of the already boosted wild Inkay spawn rate.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Inkay spawns more in
   <strong>
    foggy and windy weather
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   You must
   <strong>
    find a PokeStop located in such weather
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   Attach a
   <strong>
    Lure Module
   </strong>
   to that specific PokeStop
  </li>
  <li>
   Activate an
   <strong>
    Incense
   </strong>
   and
   <strong>
    walk around
   </strong>
   the Lure Module’s area of effect
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     This strategy might increase the wild Inkay spawn rate around that specific PokeStop. But there are chances of other event-featured Pokemon with identical Weather Boost of foggy and windy weather spawning instead.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  You must repeat the process until you get the desired number of Inkay encounters. The more Inkay you encounter, the faster you might match its Shiny odds. Since there is no guaranteed process to get a Shiny Pokemon encounter, your best bet is to encounter numerous Inkay. Evolving Shiny Inkay in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  turns it into a Shiny Malamar.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Players Show Off Incredible Helldivers 2 Battle Recreation</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/minecraft-helldivers-2-malevelon-creek-battle-fan-creation/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Minecraft players recreated epic Malevelon Creek battle in Helldivers 2 to celebrate a fictional holiday.
     </li>
     <li>
      The group effort does a great job of capturing Helldivers 2's atmosphere in Minecraft.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A talented group of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Minecraft
   </strong>
  </em>
  players have shared their incredible recreation of the Malevelon Creek battle in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  . The epic
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  creation was brought to life to celebrate Malevelon Creek Memorial Day, a fictional holiday celebrated on April 3 within the
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  community has long been among the most creative in all of gaming. It makes sense, given how
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  's entire gameplay loop is centered on players embracing their own creativity. Over the years, players have shared plenty of their creations with others, with many using the game as an outlet to pay tribute to their other favorite franchises. For example, one
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  player recently recreated
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  's Ecruteak City in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  YouTuber Red Monster Thing shared their epic recreation of
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  's Malevelon Creek mission, featuring details from the Super Destroyer interior to the battlefield itself. They have even built Automaton dropships in the air, which look like they're ready to drop reinforcements onto the battlefield. What is most impressive about this creation is how it captures the mood of
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  , with a grungy vibe that looks like it has been pulled directly from Arrowhead Game Studios' chaotic third-person shooter.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="helldivers-2-39-s-malevelon-creek-recreated-in-minecraft">
  Helldivers 2's Malevelon Creek Recreated in Minecraft
 </h2>
 <p>
  The project was not a solo effort, with Red Monster Thing claiming to have completed it with other players. It's not clear how long the project took, only that it was made to commemorate
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  's Malevelon Creek Memorial Day. Given the scale of the impressive project, it's not unfair to speculate that this was quite the undertaking. According to the YouTuber, the world download will be released for free when they hit the 1,000 subscriber milestone.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1353358920" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1353358920" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1353358920" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1353358920" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1353358920-img" id="article-gallery-1-1353358920">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1353358920" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-456107798">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  's ongoing popularity among gamers, the title continues to receive frequent content updates from developer Mojang. The most recent release was
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  's Spring to Life update, with even more experimental features coming in the future. No matter how long
  <em>
   Minecraft
  </em>
  has been around, it remains as enormous as ever, with no sign of a decline.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Stranding 2 May Be Hiding a Fun Surprise in Plain Sight</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/death-stranding-2-hiding-plain-sight-cameo-charlie-explained-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
   </em>
  </strong>
  has greatly expanded its cast of characters since the first chapter. The cast for the first
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  was already stacked with some of the film and television industry's biggest stars, but
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  kicks the roster up a notch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Now that protagonist Sam has begun to connect with the world around him,
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  brings plenty of new characters into the fold to help push the franchise's themes of connection. As a huge lover of film and TV, Hideo Kojima has made serious efforts to put some of his favorite actors into his projects. From Mads Mikkelsen to Conan O'Brien,
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  was marked by a series of compelling performances. The latest trailer for
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  offered a brief glimpse at the new cast, and one character in particular seems to possibly be teasing a potential cameo: Charlie.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="charlie-is-one-of-death-stranding-2-39-s-most-mysterious-characters">
  Charlie is One of Death Stranding 2's Most Mysterious Characters
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1692388919" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1692388919" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1692388919" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1692388919" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1692388919-img" id="article-gallery-1-1692388919">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1692388919" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1950018290">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="everything-known-about-charlie-so-far">
  Everything Known About Charlie, So Far
 </h3>
 <p>
  Right now, all that is known about Charlie is that he's a bodyless and limbless mannequin head that has a similar appearance to a crash test dummy. He's proven to be one of the most intriguing characters introduced in the latest
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  trailer, as many fans have been theorizing what his role could be within the game.
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  has teased plenty of characters who look important to the game's overall plot, but it's been hard to pin down exactly how Charlie could prove pivotal.
 </p>
 <p>
  While Charlie may be mysterious at the moment, Hideo Kojima's extensive social media footprint could hold clues as to who is behind the character. Many different actors have visited Kojima Productions since its founding, but two of the most notable have been Keanu Reeves and Timothee Chalamet.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Another character who has yet to have an actor connected to them is Red Samurai. Although this is purely speculation, both Charlie and Red Samurai could be ready to deliver exciting cameos.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="a-kojima-and-reeves-team-up-has-been-expected-for-a-while-now">
  A Kojima and Reeves Team-Up Has Been Expected For a While Now
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   The role of Cliff Unger in
   <em>
    Death Stranding
   </em>
   was almost given to Keanu Reeves instead of Mads Mikkelsen.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Kojima Productions has yet to confirm any kind of collaboration with Keanu Reeves, but his presence within Kojima's orbit has sparked hope in a lot of fans. Keanu Reeves appeared on Norman Reedus' biker-focused travel show
  <em>
   Ride With Norman Reedus
  </em>
  , and Kojima shared screenshots from the episode. Since Reedus plays protagonist Sam and Reeves has been photographed at Kojima Productions, it has made many wonder if the latter is destined for a spot in a future game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     <em>
      Death Stranding 2
     </em>
     brings plenty of new characters into the fold to help push the franchise's themes of connection.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="timothee-chalamet-has-been-on-an-impressive-acting-run">
  Timothee Chalamet Has Been On an Impressive Acting Run
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dune
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Call Me by Your Name
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   A Complete Unknown
  </em>
  are just a small portion of the major film projects Chalamet has been part of. Not only that, but he's a noted gamer as well. Before breaking big in Hollywood, Chalamet ran his own YouTube channel called ModdedController360, where he showed off his customized Xbox 360 controllers. If there's any famous actor who understands Kojima's impact on gaming, it's likely Chalamet.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_15">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Other new characters include Tomorrow, Rainy, Tarman, Dollman, The President, Neil, and Doctor.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="the-wait-to-find-out-charlie-39-s-purpose-in-death-stranding-2-won-39-t-be-much-longer">
  The Wait to Find Out Charlie's Purpose in Death Stranding 2 Won't Be Much Longer
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <em>
    Death Stranding 2
   </em>
   is scheduled to launch on June 26, 2025, for the PS5.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  It's possible that Charlie's place in the story doesn't hold a secret cameo, but Kojima is known for surprising players and keeping them on their toes. As the release of
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  draws closer, it will be interesting to see how Charlie affects the greater narrative.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
