<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Red Dead Redemption 2: 8 Things That Prove Arthur Morgan is a Good Man</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/red-dead-redemption-2-arthur-morgan-good-man-proof/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Arthur Morgan is described as someone with a good man inside them, but one that is wrestling with a giant. This makes the protagonist of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Red Dead Redemption 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  one of the most complex characters in recent memory and one who will be immortalized as an incredible character with such a rich story. Yet, despite the bad that Arthur Morgan might have done, there’s plenty to counter it on his road to redemption.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  presents Arthur Morgan as a good man underneath his burliness and self-loathing, and those who commit to high honor playthroughs will get to experience this for themselves as they battle Arthur’s demons and attempt to leave the world with some semblance of good.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   Spoilers ahead for Red Dead Redemption 2!
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="helping-strangers-for-no-real-reason">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Helping Strangers for No Real Reason
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-can-involve-himself-with-some-strangers-for-no-reason-other-than-fun">
  Arthur Can Involve Himself With Some Strangers For No Reason Other Than Fun
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-615286445" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-615286445" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-615286445" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-615286445" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-615286445-img" id="article-gallery-1-615286445">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-615286445" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-167381250">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Throughout the many states that Arthur can explore, he can often encounter some weird strangers who require his help, and Arthur is more often than not, happy to oblige, even if they do not immediately tell him of all the riches that he will get for doing so. Whether it’s helping Hamish Sinclair, the veteran, with his horse, or teaching Charlotte Balfour to hunt, Arthur helps them out of the kindness of his heart.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are even other instances of strangers that Arthur helps just because he can, like the photographer, Albert Mason, whom Arthur saves from grizzly wildlife death over and over. Arthur’s active involvement in the lives of so many strangers has made him a memorable figure, even if their encounters were brief.
 </p>
 <h2 id="assisting-mary-despite-their-love-having-passed">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Assisting Mary, Despite Their Love Having Passed
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="helping-mary-linton-proves-arthur-morgan-has-a-heart">
  Helping Mary Linton Proves Arthur Morgan Has a Heart
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1065653732" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1065653732" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1065653732" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1065653732" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1065653732-img" id="article-gallery-2-1065653732">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1065653732" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1121862281">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The love story of Arthur Morgan and Mary Linton is one of tragedy. Such a young love, squandered by the parallel lives that they lead. While Arthur’s loyalty remained with Dutch and the life of an outlaw, his heart will always be held by that of Mary Linton, the sweet woman who just wants to seek a better life with her man by her side.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite the fact that Mary broke Arthur’s heart, and in turn, he broke hers, the two can often involve themselves with each other outside of romance with Arthur electing to help her brother and later her father. Despite gaining nothing from this, Arthur helping Mary proves his deep-rooted care for those in his life, even if he sees himself as a fool for doing so.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="fighting-against-racism">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Fighting Against Racism
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-won-rsquo-t-stand-for-prejudice-against-people-of-color">
  Arthur Won’t Stand for Prejudice Against People of Color
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1071204353" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1071204353" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1071204353" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1071204353" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1071204353-img" id="article-gallery-3-1071204353">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1071204353" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1904254551">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Arthur Morgan doesn’t seem to care about all that much other than the gang, but within that gang is some damn fine people that he considers family, and those family members happen to be of a different ethnicity. Characters like Charles, Javier, Lenny, and Tilly are all persecuted because of the color of their skin, especially in the deep south state of Lemoyne.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur can come across a few racists in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  that he can antagonize and even attack with no detriment to his honor level. Whether it’s a former slave catcher, a KKK meeting, or other moronic racists spouting nonsense, Arthur Morgan just won’t stand for it.
 </p>
 <h2 id="giving-to-the-poor">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Giving to the Poor
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-morgan-can-help-the-homeless-and-other-poor-souls">
  Arthur Morgan Can Help the Homeless and Other Poor Souls
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-949434331" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-949434331" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-949434331" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-949434331" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-949434331-img" id="article-gallery-4-949434331">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-949434331" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-356224573">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While Herr Strauss is more focused on taking from the poor and forcing them into loans that they cannot repay, Arthur Morgan seems less interested in this business, and will instead prefer to give to the poor. Characters like the false veteran, Mickey, in Valentine are prime examples of Arthur’s generosity.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur also talks about the Van der Linde gang’s old days in which they would steal from the rich and often give money to those less fortunate than themselves, but those days have long since passed. There are a few homeless characters and those who request just a dollar or two, and Arthur providing them with cash shows how he’s not as selfish and rough as he seems.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="standing-for-women-rsquo-s-rights">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Standing for Women’s Rights
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-defends-women-even-if-he-doesn-rsquo-t-care-so-much-about-the-politics">
  Arthur Defends Women, Even if He Doesn’t Care So Much About the Politics
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-315561899" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-315561899" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-315561899" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-315561899" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-315561899-img" id="article-gallery-5-315561899">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-315561899" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-310063854">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In 1899, women still did not have the right to vote in America, and the suffragette movement would fight for women’s rights. As a result of this, a few women in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  campaigned for women’s rights, including the suffragette in Saint Denis, Dorothea Wicklow. While most men insult Dorothea or even attempt to attack her, Arthur will antagonize those against her, but claim he doesn’t really care about women’s suffrage.
 </p>
 <p>
  Outside of Ms. Wicklow, Arthur can rescue quite a few women in the states, abused and kidnapped by men. Arthur is always ready to defend the honor of women, and that’s not because they are weak, but because the men in 1899 can be rather cruel.
 </p>
 <h2 id="absolving-the-debts-of-strauss-rsquo-s-victims">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Absolving the Debts of Strauss’s Victims
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="loan-shark-victims-are-freed-of-debt-from-a-dying-arthur-morgan">
  Loan Shark Victims Are Freed of Debt From a Dying Arthur Morgan
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1682043293" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1682043293" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1682043293" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1682043293" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1682043293-img" id="article-gallery-6-1682043293">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1682043293" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-147092235">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Arthur has a lot of reflecting to do after he is diagnosed with tuberculosis, and a lot of resentment towards Strauss, who Arthur finally realizes is a blood-sucking culprit who preys on weak and vulnerable citizens to put them in irreparable debt that will see everything they owned taken by Arthur Morgan.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Arthur sick and the Van der Linde gang falling apart, Arthur takes responsibility for the debts for himself and absolves them, allowing those who were in Strauss’ seedy debt to go free. Arthur’s heart shows in those who could lose their lives to the practice of debt, and so he gets rid of it at the source by kicking Strauss out of the camp.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="aiding-the-native-american-people">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Aiding the Native American People
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="helping-rains-fall-and-the-wapiti-indian-reservation-makes-arthur-a-hero">
  Helping Rains Fall and the Wapiti Indian Reservation Makes Arthur a Hero
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-481763071" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-481763071" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-481763071" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-481763071" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-481763071-img" id="article-gallery-7-481763071">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-481763071" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1297305176">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Arthur Morgan has no real reason to help Rains Fall, as it doesn’t benefit him or the Van der Linde gang in any way. Even Dutch understands this and instead seeks to manipulate the youthful men into angry soldiers for his own crusade. Meanwhile, Arthur takes it upon himself to help Rains Fall and bring peace to the reservation against the U.S. Army.
 </p>
 <p>
  Arthur’s respect for Native American culture, and his relationship with the wise Rains Fall, show that he’s on the right path of bravery and gentleness, and how he might find peace in his redemption as he helps those who are being abused by greater powers.
 </p>
 <h2 id="helping-john-marston-escape">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Helping John Marston Escape
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arthur-prioritises-john-getting-back-to-his-family-over-his-own-safety-or-greed">
  Arthur Prioritises John Getting Back to His Family Over His Own Safety or Greed
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1437601294" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1437601294" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1437601294" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1437601294" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1437601294-img" id="article-gallery-8-1437601294">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1437601294" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-391862816">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With the fall of the Van der Linde gang and the final assault from the Pinkertons at Beaver Hollow, Arthur Morgan is left with two choices: Help an injured John Marston escape so that he can reunite with his wife and son and start a new life, or fight through Pinkertons and his old gang in order to try and greedily grab the money that Dutch has stashed away.
 </p>
 <p>
  Should Arthur choose to make his final stand as a hero, he will ride with John Marston and save him, proving how much John means to him as a little brother. While Arthur’s fate remains the same, it shows how high his honor is that he would make his last moments one of heroism to save the life of a man who still has a chance to turn his life around.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Update Breaks Season 2 Battle Pass</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/call-of-duty-black-ops-6-season-2-battle-pass-not-working/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Call of Duty: Black Ops 6's Season 2 Battle Pass appears to be broken for many users.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players take to Reddit to show how the game is preventing them from accessing the Battle Pass after the most recent update.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some players claim restarting the game fixes the issue, while others state that it is only a temporary fix.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  players are reporting a serious issue with the Season 2 Battle Pass, as many users appear to have been completely locked out of the feature following the release of a recent game update. While
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  continues to receive a steady stream of new updates, fans of the shooter are becoming increasingly frustrated with the many bugs, glitches, and general issues that seem to arise after every patch.
 </p>
 <p>
  After one of
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  's longest seasons to date, developer Treyarch Studios finally released the highly anticipated Season 2 update for
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  on January 28. The patch brought a plethora of new content to the hit shooter, including new multiplayer maps, weapons, events, and much more. But before the launch of the new season, publisher Activision responded to complaints from fans with a lengthy community update. In the blog post, the studio said it would have "notable bug fixes" for Season 2 based on player feedback. While the patch did include plenty of improvements, fans are still unhappy with the sheer number of issues plaguing the game's multiplayer.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="black-ops-6-players-report-broken-battle-pass-following-latest-update">
  Black Ops 6 Players Report Broken Battle Pass Following Latest Update
 </h2>
 <p>
  On February 11, Treyarch Studios deployed a small update for
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  . The patch included a handful of bug fixes and brought about some new restrictions for the game's Ranked Play mode, but fans have been left angered after it seemingly introduced a new bug that has broken the game's Battle Pass. Over on Reddit, various posts have begun appearing as fans report issues accessing the in-game Battle Pass tab. As seen in the post below, which comes from Reddit user Internal_Page_486, some users are being kicked straight back to the lobby when they try and access the Battle Pass. Dozens of other users responded to the post and said they were experiencing a similar problem.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the time of writing, Treyarch Studios has yet to address the issue with
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  's Season 2 Battle Pass, but some players have revealed that restarting the game does temporarily fix the issue. Reddit user FlapjackUK said they had to "reload the game from scratch" on Xbox Series X to access the Battle Pass, but another user says that they did the same thing, only for the issue to occur again 15 minutes later. Some users are even reporting a similar issue outside of the Battle Pass, as Ino4x4 and Dethlord_youtube both claim that they are being sent back to the lobby when trying to access their loadouts or edit certain weapons within the gunsmith.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-54527518" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-54527518" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-54527518" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-54527518" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-54527518-img" id="article-gallery-1-54527518">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-54527518" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-5275679">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  This isn't the first time a serious issue has occurred after the release of a new update. Earlier this month, Treyarch released an emergency update for
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  on PC after a previous patch practically made the game unplayable for many users. Shortly after a new update went live, players began reporting an increase in blue screen errors, with PC players around the world being forced to restart their games when the error occurred. Treyarch was quick to fix the issue, but the studio has remained silent on the latest Battle Pass glitch.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Gaiden 2 Black Gets a Major Update</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ninja-gaiden-2-black-major-update-new-game-plus-patch-notes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A new update for Ninja Gaiden 2 Black adds New Game Plus and photo mode.
     </li>
     <li>
      The patch balances difficulty in some levels by adjusting enemy HP and increasing enemy numbers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
   </em>
  </strong>
  has introduced a bunch of new changes, ranging from a New Game Plus mode to some gameplay fixes, in its new update. The latest patch for
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  is the first major one since the game's release on January 23, 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the Xbox Developer Direct 2025,
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  kickstarted the franchise's revival with the announcement of a forthcoming mainline game and the shadow-dropping of a remastered classic. While
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 4
  </em>
  is set to be the first major entry in the series since 2012,
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  has given the 2008 original a new layer of sheen on current-gen platforms. In the little time that has passed since its release, the remaster has attracted positive reviews from critics and fans alike, with an OpenCritic score of 81. Adding to this momentum, Team Ninja recently announced some major additions coming to the hack-and-slash game.
 </p>
 <p>
  With patch version 1.003.000 on PlayStation and patch version 1.0.7.0 on PC and Xbox,
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  has received a New Game Plus mode that enables players to start a new save without losing the unlocked weapons and Ninpo from their original playthrough. The update also adds a photo mode, accessible from the in-game options, allowing fans to capture
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  's Ryu Hayabusa in the thick of action. Moreover, the player now also has the option to toggle the visibility of the projectile weapon carried on the back, by going into "Settings" from the options screen.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition to these new features, there are several bug fixes and balancing changes bundled in the February patch as well. On one hand, the enemy HP in Chapter 8 and Chapter 11 has been lowered, toning down the difficulty of those levels. On the other hand, the number of enemies in Chapter 13 and 14 has been increased, making these levels more of a challenge than before. The damage inflicted by Ayane, one of
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  's playable characters, has also been dialed up. Further, certain bugs that caused crashes, stopped players from progressing, and interfered with the controls have been resolved by the devs.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-245807471" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-245807471" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-245807471" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-245807471" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-245807471-img" id="article-gallery-1-245807471">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-245807471" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2086722461">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  already out and
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 4
  </em>
  scheduled to arrive later in 2025, it is turning out to be an eventful year for fans of the action-adventure series. Not to forget, there's another spin-off,
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden: Ragebound
  </em>
  , set to roll out in 2025 as well. However, this side-scrolling title is in development at The Game Kitchen, a new developer for the franchise.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="">
 </h2>
 <h2 id="ninja-gaiden-2-black-version-1-003-000-version-1-0-7-0-patch-notes">
  Ninja Gaiden 2 Black Version 1.003.000/Version 1.0.7.0 Patch Notes
 </h2>
 <h3 id="additional-content">
  Additional Content:
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   New Game+ Added the ability to begin a new game on a difficulty level you have previously cleared with the weapons and Ninpo you obtained in your previous playthrough already unlocked. When starting a new game this way, your weapons and Ninpo will be reverted to level 1.
  </li>
  <li>
   Photo Mode Added Photo Mode to the in-game Options Menu. You can move the camera around within a set limit to take screenshots.
  </li>
  <li>
   Ability to Hide Projectile Weapon Added a "Show Projectile Weapon" option under "Game Settings" in the Options Menu, which allows you to hide your projectile weapon while it is carried on your back.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="adjustments">
  Adjustments:
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Lowered the HP of enemies in Ch. 8, "City of the Fallen Goddess"
  </li>
  <li>
   Lowered the HP of enemies in Ch. 11, "Night in the City of Water"
  </li>
  <li>
   Raised the number of enemies in Ch. 13, "The Temple of Sacrifice"
  </li>
  <li>
   Raised the number of enemies in Ch. 14, "A Tempered Gravestone"
  </li>
  <li>
   Raised the damage dealt by some of Ayane's attacks.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="bug-fixes">
  Bug Fixes:
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Fixed control issues that occurred when playing at over 120 FPS or while under high computing load.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed an issue where controllers would not vibrate based on computing load or FPS settings.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed bugs that caused the player to go out of bounds during certain chapters.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed bugs that made it impossible to progress during certain chapters.
  </li>
  <li>
   Fixed a bug which caused the game to crash during long play sessions.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Other minor bug fixes
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Obsidian Entertainment Games With The Best Real-Time Combat, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/obsidian-entertainment-games-with-best-real-time-combat-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Obsidian excels in creating quality RPGs, with engaging real-time combat and deep storytelling.
     </li>
     <li>
      Classic Obsidian games like Alpha Protocol and KotOR 2 offer enjoyable gameplay despite initial issues.
     </li>
     <li>
      Grounded's combat relies on perfect blocks and reliable weapons for survival against giant pests.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Obsidian Entertainment is one of the most beloved RPG developers around. Despite the roadblocks they've endured, the studio continues to make quality role-playing games that fans can't get enough of.
 </p>
 <p>
  From CRPG throwbacks to modern action RPGs, Obsidian are kings of this genre and know how to make their role-playing experiences as riveting as possible. Their takes on real-time combat have been amazing more often than not, letting players micromanage their parties in combat or control a single character as they lay waste to the many threats standing in their way.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="neverwinter-nights-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Neverwinter Nights 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-combat-can-be-clumsy-at-time-but-the-real-time-tactics-are-fun-to-mess-around-with-nevertheless">
  The Combat Can Be Clumsy At Time, But The Real-Time Tactics Are Fun To Mess Around With Nevertheless
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-239965637" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-239965637" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-239965637" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-239965637" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-239965637-img" id="article-gallery-1-239965637">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-239965637" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-99374458">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Neverwinter Nights 2
  </em>
  is a sequel to a beloved BioWare game that more fans need to check out. It's a classic CRPG that boasts impressive depth and an easy-to-digest story that doesn't complicate things too much.
 </p>
 <p>
  The combat occurs in real-time, but players can pause the action to give individual instructions or prioritize healing. This hybrid combat system makes the best of both worlds and ensures that players can make the most of fast real-time combat without being overwhelmed if they have to manage multiple party members at once.
 </p>
 <h2 id="alpha-protocol">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Alpha Protocol
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-game-can-still-be-janky-at-times-but-it-never-gets-in-the-way-of-a-player-39-s-fun">
  The Game Can Still Be Janky At Times, But It Never Gets In The Way Of A Player's Fun
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1416805102" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1416805102" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1416805102" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1416805102" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1416805102-img" id="article-gallery-2-1416805102">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1416805102" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1393877029">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Alpha Protocol
  </em>
  is an espionage RPG that could've been great had bugs not dampened the impressions this title made at launch. After most of the glitches were ironed out, fans were treated to an excellent role-playing game that combined modern stealth and action gameplay for a tantalizing combination.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players could embody one of the three JBs of spy media (James Bond, Jason Bourne, or Jack Bauer) as they made their way through numerous missions and completed objectives however they saw fit. Players can use both ranged and melee combat to take out their foes or go down the silent and charming route, depending on what suits their fancy.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="star-wars-knights-of-the-old-republic-2-the-sith-lords">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Star Wars Knights Of The Old Republic 2: The Sith Lords
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-game-39-s-auto-combat-can-be-managed-with-great-care-to-unleash-abilities-at-the-right-time">
  The Game's Auto-Combat Can Be Managed With Great Care To Unleash Abilities At The Right Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2047302727" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2047302727" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2047302727" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2047302727" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2047302727-img" id="article-gallery-3-2047302727">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2047302727" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-214039693">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Knights of the Old Republic 2
  </em>
  is another Obsidian game that came out buggy and unfinished, tarnishing its reputation in the eyes of many. It's a shame since most people who gave this title a fair shot were impressed by how riveting the story was.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kreia has established herself as the greatest
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  villain in the eyes of many. Before fighting their mentor, the protagonists must go through their fair share of trials and tribulations as they become masters in combat and use a wealth of Jedi techniques to take out anyone and anything standing in their way.
 </p>
 <h2 id="pillars-of-eternity-2-deadfire">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Pillars Of Eternity 2: Deadfire
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-great-improvement-over-the-first-game-with-multi-classing-being-one-of-the-best-additions">
  A Great Improvement Over The First Game, With Multi-classing Being One Of The Best Additions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1009520715" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1009520715" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1009520715" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1009520715" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1009520715-img" id="article-gallery-4-1009520715">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1009520715" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1284090960">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity 2: Deadfire
  </em>
  is a refinement of the first game that features robust combat, multiclassing, and a whole lot of options to choose from when heading into combat. Players can use stealth to position themselves before ambushing enemies and taking them out in no time.
 </p>
 <p>
  A highlight of
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity 2
  </em>
  is the ship traversal, with players loving the act of hunting down bounties and boarding their ships. The music and combat are top-notch during these segments and ensure that players will never think about engaging in complex ship combat when the real-time alternative is so much better.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tyranny">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Tyranny
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-inclusion-of-team-attacks-coupled-with-a-robust-magical-system-helps-tyranny-stand-out">
  The Inclusion Of Team Attacks Coupled With A Robust Magical System Helps Tyranny Stand Out
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-765089531" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-765089531" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-765089531" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-765089531" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-765089531-img" id="article-gallery-5-765089531">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-765089531" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-499312345">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Tyranny
  </em>
  is a CRPG that could've been generational had it achieved its full vision. As things stand, fans will still love the journey this game takes them on, even if the ending can be a bit too sudden for most people's liking.
 </p>
 <p>
  The combat rewards players for building up Loyalty and Fear with their companions, letting them use various tag-team techniques in the heat of battle. It's a great way to enhance the splendor of
  <em>
   Tyranny
  </em>
  's combat, with fans always having the option of pausing the game if they want to micromanage certain things in battle.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-new-vegas">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="simple-yet-engaging-combat-that-can-be-played-in-either-first-or-third-person">
  Simple Yet Engaging Combat That Can Be Played In Either First Or Third-Person
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-22577369" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-22577369" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-22577369" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-22577369" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-22577369-img" id="article-gallery-6-22577369">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-22577369" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-200578504">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There's a reason why many people see
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  as the best Obsidian game ever made. The role-playing in this title is off the charts as players take their Courier on an adventure for the ages, with the hunt for Lenny spiraling into a plot to take over control of New Vegas.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combat is great in
  <em>
   New Vegas
  </em>
  , with players enjoying a palpable sense of growth as their fragile Courier transforms into a legend of the Mojave. The satisfaction players enjoy from taking out a horde of cazadors after being decimated by them early on is a thrill fans can't get enough of.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-outer-worlds">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   The Outer Worlds
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="first-person-combat-where-players-can-use-guns-or-melee-weapons-to-beat-down-their-foes">
  First-Person Combat Where Players Can Use Guns Or Melee Weapons To Beat Down Their Foes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-627725169" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-627725169" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-627725169" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-627725169" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-627725169-img" id="article-gallery-7-627725169">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-627725169" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-2092747051">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the short length and lack of interesting world-building may take away from
  <em>
   The Outer Words
  </em>
  to an extent, the title more than makes up for it with its stellar visuals and fun combat. Players can use both ranged and melee weaponry to beat down their foes to a pulp.
 </p>
 <p>
  Getting up close and personal with enemies is a viable strategy, but players who want to prioritize self-preservation would prefer to use the many sci-fi guns in the game instead. Shocking and melting foes is a thrill that fans can't get enough of and ensures that players will love switching out and modding their weapons till the very end of
  <em>
   The Outer Worlds
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="grounded">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Grounded
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="nailing-perfect-blocks-and-finding-reliable-weapons-makes-combat-more-manageable">
  Nailing Perfect Blocks And Finding Reliable Weapons Makes Combat More Manageable
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-898632234" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-898632234" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-898632234" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-898632234" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-898632234-img" id="article-gallery-8-898632234">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-898632234" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-985760647">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike most of Obsidian's games,
  <em>
   Grounded
  </em>
  is a co-op survival title that is more competent than players would assume. It's a video game version of
  <em>
   Honey, I Shrunk the Kids
  </em>
  where players control one of four miniaturized characters who must survive against regular pests that have become gigantic.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combat in
  <em>
   Grounded
  </em>
  is heavily reliant on perfect blocks, and this is something the game hammers in early on. Players who eventually master defense can use their attack windows to punish foes, acquiring more powerful weaponry in the process to deal with tougher foes.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helldivers 2: Best Armor Perks, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/helldivers-2-best-armor-perks-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Surviving the tyrannical enemies of democracy in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Helldivers 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  involves more than smart positioning. When push comes to shove, the armor a Helldiver is wearing will often determine if they survive or not.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Armor perks are usually the deciding factor when it comes to choosing what suit to wear before diving. While the Armor Rating system in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  is the one that
  <em>
  </em>
  dictates a suit's general defensive effectiveness, perks grant additional benefits that augment certain playstyles. The following list includes all the armor perks in the game, ranked according to their versatility. All perks have their uses — the ones at the bottom are niche picks with very novel or specific goals, while the ones at the top are general-use perks that are effective regardless of what mission they're brought to.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated February 12, 2025 by Marc Santos:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   Helldivers 2 has received plenty of updates during its first year, and it has since received a number of new armor perks for players to try out. We've updated this list to include a few of these armor perks, and we've ranked them accordingly. Perks that we've deemed to be too niche, too weak, or too redundant are not included on this list.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="electrical-conduit">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Electrical Conduit
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="electrician-in-the-field">
  Electrician In The Field
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Electrical Conduit perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405132101_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Reduces incoming arc damage by 95%
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Electrical Conduit perk came as part of the Cutting Edge Premium Warbond in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  , and it offers a very specific bonus: it makes players almost immune to damage from lightning-based weapons. Arc Throwers, which are notorious for vaporizing teammates in friendly fire incidents, will deal very little damage to anyone wearing armor that has this perk.
 </p>
 <p>
  While 95% arc damage resistance is great, admittedly, it's not that useful unless players are using arc weapons or tesla towers. Electrical Conduit isn't useless by any means, but since its use case is so specific, it deserves a spot here at the bottom of this list, where all niche armor perks will reside.
 </p>
 <h2 id="inflammable">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Inflammable
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="freedom-is-somewhat-fireproof">
  Freedom is (Somewhat) Fireproof
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Inflammable armor perk description in HD2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155519617.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Reduces all incoming Fire damage by 75%.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Much like Electrical Conduit, Inflammable is a highly situational armor perk. It's great for planets with Fire Tornado, and it's not bad in the Automaton front either, since melee Hulks use flamethrowers. The perk also protects players from Fire damage coming from teammates or their own weapons, allowing for a greater deal of flexibility with flame-based loadouts.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Inflammable perk is best used together with the Double Edged Sickle, one of the weapons in the Servants of Freedom Warbond. It deals Fire damage to the wearer as it builds heat, and if used with Vitality Booster and an armor set with the Inflammable perk, the DE Sickle's damage becomes negligible (until the user combusts, that is).
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="democracy-protects">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Democracy Protects
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="no-health-no-limbs-no-problem">
  No Health, No Limbs, No Problem
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Democracy Protects perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194815_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Gain a 50% chance to survive lethal damage. Prevents all bleeding damage if the chest is injured.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This armor perk is a literal lifesaver. It protects players from any form of lethal damage, whether it's a 500KG Bomb, a direct hit from an Automaton Cannon, or a random meteor strike from the heavens above. When Democracy Protects will leave its wearer with a sliver of health — assuming that it actually triggers. The bleed damage immunity is nice to have, but considering how rare chest injuries are incurred and how easily they can be fixed with Stims, this part of the perk isn't that valuable in practice.
 </p>
 <p>
  Surviving a massive explosion that leaves players with 1 HP and no functioning limbs is cathartic, but since Democracy Protects only has a 50% chance of triggering, it's hard to recommend it over all the others. It's great and often hilarious when it works, especially if it procs consecutively, but for anyone who wants a more consistent experience, then literally everything else is better.
 </p>
 <h2 id="scout">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Scout
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="extra-sneakiness-for-intrepid-hellcrawlers">
  Extra Sneakiness For Intrepid Hellcrawlers
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Scout armor perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194840_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Markers placed on the map will detect nearby enemies every two seconds. Reduce the range at which enemies spot the user by 30%.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Scout is an excellent perk for stealthy divers who would rather sneak past patrols than go in guns blazing. It makes the wearer harder to detect, giving players ample time to move away from any enemy's line of sight without triggering alarms. The radar ping functionality also makes planning routes and engagements much easier.
 </p>
 <p>
  This perk offers very little for when bugs and bullets start flying. It's great for premade groups or players attempting solo missions in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  , but it's not as useful in public games with random people.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="extra-padding">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Extra Padding
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="extra-armor-extra-survivability">
  Extra Armor, Extra Survivability
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Extra Padding armor perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131426_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Gain +50 Armor Rating.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Extra Padding is a sweet and simple perk that gives bonus armor. While it sounds uninteresting, what it essentially does is it boosts the Armor Rating tier of an armor piece by one. This means Medium Armor with Extra Padding will have the same effectiveness as Heavy Armor but without the speed and stamina penalties. This is what makes the B-08 Light Gunner one of the best light armor sets in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  <em>
   .
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  Overall, this is an excellent perk for when players simply want to take extra hits before dying. However, keep in mind that hits to the head will still instantly kill a Helldiver regardless of their Armor Rating.
 </p>
 <h2 id="acclimated">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Acclimated
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="all-around-elemental-resistance">
  All-Around Elemental Resistance
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Acclimated armor perk description in HD2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155428060.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Reduces incoming Fire, Gas, Acid, and Arc damage by 50%.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This is another universal armor set like Extra Padding, except it focuses on reducing elemental damage (Fire, Gas, Acid, and Arc). It's a great pick for the Illuminate front, as it can protect against electric attacks from Harvesters, Tesla Towers, and Observers, while giving wearers some insurance against friendly Gas and Fire weapons, which are frequently used against the squids.
 </p>
 <p>
  Acclimated is a decent perk overall, but it's only ever recommended for players who are having trouble avoiding damage in the first place. Overall, this perk is more valuable than Electric Conduit, Inflammable, and Advanced Filtration simply because of how good it is in all fronts and against all elements, instead of just one.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="med-kit">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Med Kit
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="for-combat-medics-and-stim-junkies-alike">
  For Combat Medics and Stim Junkies Alike
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Med Kit perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240405131523_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increases initial Stim count and max Stim capacity by 2. Stim effect duration is increased by 2 seconds.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Armor with the Med Kit perk is perfect for players who want to get more out of their Stim injectors. Not only does it bump the max Stim count from four to six, but it also makes each injector last longer. For those who don't know, Stims give players infinite stamina and make them virtually indestructible. Having two extra seconds of Stim duration can spell the difference between life and death.
 </p>
 <p>
  Taking this perk (as well as any of the next options) all boils down to personal preference. Players who are having trouble surviving high-difficulty missions may want to use Med Kit on a heavy armor piece until they develop a better game sense.
 </p>
 <h2 id="servo-assisted">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Servo-Assisted
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="perfect-for-slinging-stratagems">
  Perfect for Slinging Stratagems
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Servo-Assisted perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194808_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increase throwing range by 30% and all limbs gain 50% extra health.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Servo-Assisted is an excellent choice for Helldivers who rely on Stratagems to destroy buildings and bug holes. It increases the wearer's throwing range, and this affects both grenades and Stratagem balls. It's especially useful when doing Automaton side-objectives in
  <em>
   Helldivers 2
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  as bot outposts tend to have machine guns and cannons guarding their perimeters.
 </p>
 <p>
  The second half of this perk is nice to have, though it's most noticeable when paired with heavy armor. However, as mentioned earlier, injuries are very easy to fix, and unless players have no Stims left, the extra limb health will usually go unnoticed by the majority of players.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="engineering-kit">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Engineering Kit
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="when-four-grenades-just-aren-39-t-enough">
  When Four Grenades Just Aren't Enough
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Engineering Kit perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194813_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increase initial grenade inventory and maximum capacity by 2. Reduce recoil by an additional 30% when shooting while crouching or prone.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This perk is essentially an offensive variant of Med Kit. Instead of Stims, players get more grenades, and instead of more Stim duration, wearers get better recoil reduction. Having more throwable explosives is always useful, especially when players need to deal with Automaton Scout Striders and Terminid Bile/Nursing Spewers. Recoil reduction is also universally welcome — it works extremely well with weapons like the Autocannon, allowing it to fire more quickly without losing accuracy.
 </p>
 <p>
  Engineering Kit is only going to become more valuable once more specialized grenade types are introduced. Having a few extra Stun Grenades, for example, can make dealing with heavy units like Chargers and Hulks much easier, effectively increasing the variety of Stratagems and weapons that a player can bring to a mission.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fortified">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Fortified
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="say-goodbye-to-blast-damage">
  ​​Say Goodbye To Blast Damage
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Fortified perk in Helldivers 2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240404194830_1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Decrease incoming explosive damage by 50%. Reduce recoil by an additional 30% when shooting while crouching or prone.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Fortified is arguably the best armor perk in the game simply because it negates one of the deadliest threats on the battlefield: explosives. It will keep players from dying to rockets, mines, exploding railguns, splash damage from plasma weapons, and more, assuming that the damage itself does not exceed the wearer's maximum health. Fortified will greatly increase the wearer's survivability against Automatons, and it's not bad against Terminids either if players are using the PLAS-1 Scorcher or similar weapons with the potential for self-damage.
 </p>
 <p>
  Wearing heavy armor with the Fortified perk makes players extremely hard to kill in Automaton missions, especially if someone in the squad is using the Vitality Enhancement Booster to negate injuries. Luckily, this perk is present in all armor categories, so players can enjoy its benefits if they want to use Light or Medium armor instead.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="siege-ready">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Siege-Ready
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="more-bullets-more-freedom">
  More Bullets, More Freedom
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Street Scout armor set in HD2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png" decoding="async" height="1080" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/image_2025-02-12_155323468.png" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1920"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Increase primary weapon reload speed by 30%. Increase ammo reserves of all weapons by 20%.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Siege-Ready perk was added to the game in the Omens of Tyranny update, which also saw the introduction of the Illuminate faction. This is one of the best armor perks for aggressive players as it gives them more ammo and a faster reload speed for primary weapons. Siege-Ready is great for all mission types, but it is especially useful in Blitz: Search and Destroy missions.
 </p>
 <p>
  This perk initially increased the ammo reserves of Support and Secondary Weapons due to a bug, but Arrowhead accepted it officially as a feature. Still, the reload speed bonus is strictly for primary weapons only.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
