<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Who Could Be The Other 'Horror Avengers' Working on Hideo Kojima’s OD?</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kojima-productions-od-horror-game-actors-jordan-peele-del-toro/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Kojima Productions currently has three projects in the pipeline, and
  <strong>
   <em>
    OD
   </em>
  </strong>
  is one of the most mysterious of these.
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Physint
  </em>
  promise an intriguing follow-up and an espionage thriller, but
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  stands as a secretive and compelling horror title. Hideo Kojima made waves with the horror teaser
  <em>
   PT
  </em>
  back in 2014, but the endgame of that vision unfortunately never came to fruition. Even though
  <em>
   PT
  </em>
  was a small teaser of a now-canceled game, it inspired many indie games and is still discussed within the genre, and that's what makes Kojima's return to horror so exciting.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  So far, there isn't much known about
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  's story. Announced at the 2023 Game Awards with a strange and unsettling teaser trailer, Kojima revealed that horror film heavyweight Jordan Peele would be assisting with writing. Kojima is a well-known lover of pop culture, so it's not surprising that he's a fan of Peele. However, what's even more exciting is that Kojima has confirmed that Peele isn't the only big name helping with
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  . On his official YouTube channel, he has stated, "We're actually calling them 'The Avengers' but we have other members like him. If I announced the names, you'd be surprised."
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="theories-about-who-hideo-kojima-39-s-quot-avengers-quot-could-be">
  Theories About Who Hideo Kojima's "Avengers" Could Be
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1135782559" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1135782559" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1135782559" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1135782559" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1135782559-img" id="article-gallery-1-1135782559">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1135782559" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-308654613">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="guillermo-del-toro-and-nicolas-winding-refn">
  Guillermo Del Toro and Nicolas Winding Refn
 </h3>
 <p>
  Del Toro is a safe bet for another team-up. The horror legend has helped Kojima in the past, as the two were set to co-direct the ill-fated
  <em>
   Silent Hills
  </em>
  starring Norman Reedus. Once Kojima Productions was formed, Del Toro and Reedus joined Kojima for
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  's teaser trailer promised a strong cast of actors, but Del Toro's expertise as a writer and director could be just as helpful for the project. Nicolas Winding Refn also offered his likeness to
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , and while it's highly possible that he and Del Toro could be assisting with
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  , Kojima's hush, hush discussion of these "Avengers" suggests other names.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The likenesses of Del Toro and Winding Refn were used for
     <em>
      Death Stranding
     </em>
     's Deadman and Heartman.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="mike-flanagan">
  Mike Flanagan
 </h3>
 <p>
  Flanagan has made his mark in the horror genre with series like
  <em>
   Haunting of Hill House
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Midnight Mass
  </em>
  . Also, it's worth noting that Flanagan has had a persistent presence on Kojima's Instagram. Kojima's Instagram is a useful tool in trying to theorize who he could be working with next, as it's often updated with pictures of the various filmmakers and artists he has met. Of course, the two could merely be admirers of one another, but Kojima has a habit of including his favorite creators in his work.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     We're actually calling them 'The Avengers' but we have other members like him. If I announced the names, you'd be surprised.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="ari-aster">
  Ari Aster
 </h3>
 <p>
  This horror filmmaker has also been featured on Kojima's Instagram. Responsible for chilling works like
  <em>
   Midsommar
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Hereditary
  </em>
  , Aster boasts the mind-bending qualities that Kojima also brings to his projects. Ari Aster's balance of surrealism and terror is right up Kojima's alley, so it wouldn't be shocking for the two to collaborate in the future, even if it's not on
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="lars-von-trier">
  Lars von Trier
 </h3>
 <p>
  Another experimental legend, Lars von Trier's portfolio isn't fully horror. However, with films like
  <em>
   Antichrist
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The House That Jack Built
  </em>
  , he's clearly skilled in the genre. He already has a connection to
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  , though not directly.
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  cast member Udo Kier is a longtime collaborator of von Trier, making the possible inclusion of the veteran director much more possible.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_15">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Other confirmed actors for
     <em>
      OD
     </em>
     include Sophia Lillis and Hunter Schafer.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="more-od-news-is-hopefully-imminent">
  More OD News is Hopefully Imminent
 </h3>
 <p>
  It's unclear when Kojima Productions will offer more updates on
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  , but that day is hopefully coming soon. Kojima seemingly has his hands full with three projects in the works. After
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  releases this year, more insight into
  <em>
   OD
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Physint
  </em>
  is bound to follow.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Blade Zero Could Be 2026’s Black Myth: Wukong</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/phantom-blade-zero-2026-next-black-myth-wukong-soulslike/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  On January 21, 2025, developer S-GAME released
  <strong>
   <em>
    Phantom Blade Zero
   </em>
  </strong>
  ’s Year of the Snake gameplay trailer to celebrate the start of the Chinese zodiac calendar year. The unedited boss fight was as creative as it was fluid, and it immediately drove two points home: dark, grisly combat is here to stay, and
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  was just the tip of the iceberg in Chinese tradition and culture. That’s saying something since there’s a lot of content that
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s developer is still holding close to its chest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The title was first revealed during the Sony PlayStation Showcase in 2023, and it has steadily built anticipation among fans. The top reasons include its fluid combat, dark lore and world, and fusion of Chinese folklore and cyberpunk influences. Further, it’s being made in Unreal Engine 5, just like the ode to the Monkey King last year. While
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  ’s record-breaking run in 2024 may seem undefeatable,
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s open world and combat system may just take the throne upon launch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="phantom-blade-zero-digs-deep-into-chinese-culture-and-cyberpunk">
  Phantom Blade Zero Digs Deep Into Chinese Culture and Cyberpunk
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-46461780" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-46461780" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-46461780" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-46461780" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-46461780-img" id="article-gallery-1-46461780">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-46461780" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-497476412">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Summer Game Fest 2024 gave fans another look at
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s cinematic and gameplay prowess, shining a light on the design concept that S-GAME Founder and CEO Soulframe Liang termed Kung Fu Punk. This, as may seem clear right away, is a fusion of martial arts with cyberpunk and steampunk genres.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s world, combat, and traversal mechanics are based not only on this amalgamation of Kung Fu, cyberpunk, steampunk, and the occult, but also on Chinese Wuxia - a fantasy world that one can enter, but leave only upon death. The blend of traditional temples, traditionalistic architecture, colors, and environmental scenery with features like robotic limbs and machinery makes the experience singular. Soulframe has even talked about how the game’s specific approach makes it more accessible to everyone. Whether it’s a fan who frequently plays foreign games or someone who’s diving into unchartered waters for the first time, the design will remain appealing regardless.
 </p>
 <p>
  It should be mentioned that while it draws from Chinese traditions, heavy mythological influences aren’t present—at least, from what’s known so far. While both
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  are based on the culture, stark differences are present.
 </p>
 <h2 id="phantom-blade-zero-rsquo-s-combat-is-as-gory-as-it-is-flashy">
  Phantom Blade Zero’s Combat Is As Gory As It Is Flashy
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="phantom blade zero summer game fest hands-on" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-phantom-edge.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Due to
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s combat and world system, it has frequently been called a soulslike. Surprisingly, the similarities to the genre end at level design and select elements. The fighting mechanics, as violent as they may be, fall under a different category: they have martial arts and fancy footwork at the core. Thus, they are more in line with games like
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Devil May Cry
  </em>
  than proper soulslikes such as
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Dark Souls 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  The game has 30 weapons, and Soul can switch between two at any time in combat. He also gets about 20 Phantom Edges, which are essentially ranged gear like bows and arrows and hand cannons. Fans have already seen a few of these across the various trailers, such as a single red sword, two short and straight blades, a soft and flexible blade, and two serpent-like swords.
 </p>
 <p>
  Aside from these, the game strongly emphasizes dodging and parrying, with getting the timing down being an incredibly important skill. Getting in the flow means opening up various counterattack opportunities and dealing extra damage, or even bypassing the enemy’s blocks. As such, learning weapons and an enemy’s moveset and building up combos is what the system is focused on.
 </p>
 <p>
  Soulframe’s dedicated PlayStation blog published in May 2023 shed more light on how
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  's combat works when it's this stylish and fantastical. He explained that Mr. Kenji Tanigaki, a renowned action and film director from classic Chinese Kung Fu movies, is the game’s action director. Soulframe also explained that each of the game’s fights is handcrafted animation, as “motion capturing can’t do it justice.” This not only allows the developers to make the combat more realistic and gory but also allows them to weave in fancy footwork and movement mechanics that are usually limited by motion-capture technology. The result is an exemplary showcase of flashy but gruesome martial arts and swordplay.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="phantom-blade-zero-shows-black-myth-wukong-was-just-the-tip-of-the-iceberg">
  Phantom Blade Zero Shows Black Myth: Wukong Was Just The Tip Of The Iceberg
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape mobile-optimized">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="phantom blade zero summer game fest hands-on" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/phantom-blade-zero-screenshot-chracter-running.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It was expected that
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  would fly high, but not just how high. Its visual fidelity and Chinese lore-woven story were spectacular, but it was the combat system and the enemy variety and mechanics, not to mention the sheer design creativity, that hit it out of the ballpark. As a result, many fans felt it was snubbed at The Game Awards 2024 when
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  won Game of the Year.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  came from a relatively unknown developer at the time, Game Science, and was an ambitious project. A game diving heavily into Chinese culture may have been seen as risky by many, but its success was unprecedented. Now,
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  has shown fans there’s more where that came from.
 </p>
 <p>
  Developer S-GAME’s title isn’t a true-blue experience as it blends in cyberpunk and other influences. However, the fact that it draws heavily from Chinese culture for world and character design, lore, and fighting and traversal mechanics, lends the belief that there’s a long time before the well runs dry. The combat is also rich, even more feature- and rhythm-heavy. Given the game design and story elements at play, it may not be a far cry to say that
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  may be the next
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  ’s tentative release date is sometime in Fall 2026, although this may change. Fortunately, the Year of the Snake gameplay trailer stated that the release date will be announced in 2025. Between that and more potential content reveals, fans may have more news coming their way in due time.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fisch: How To Get &amp; Use Fish Radar</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fisch-how-get-use-fish-radar/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Get Fish Radar In Fisch
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Use Fish Radar In Fisch
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Roblox's
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fisch
   </em>
  </strong>
  is a popular fishing game where you catch fish of different rarities, like Common, Uncommon, Unusual, Rare, Legendary, Mythical, and more. While catching common fish is easy, getting higher-rarity ones can be a real challenge, especially with the vast ocean and so many islands to explore.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Thankfully, there’s a tool called the Fish Radar that helps you pinpoint fish locations. It’s perfect for completing limited-time events and bestiaries, making it a must-have for any player. This guide will show you how to get and use the Fish Radar in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-fish-radar-in-fisch">
  How To Get Fish Radar In Fisch
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-abb92be81a9f2890" id="emaki-video-player-abb92be81a9f2890">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Fish Radar can be found in Moosewood, Roslit Bay, or Terrapin Island in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  . These are the three locations where you can grab one with in-game money. Since
  <strong>
   Moosewood
  </strong>
  is your starting area, it’s the easiest place to get it. Look for a rock near the Shipwright, where you’ll spot the Fish Radar. It's a small device with a black body and a green screen, so it'll be quick to spot.
 </p>
 <p>
  When you find it, interact with it by pressing the E key or clicking the icon, then confirm your purchase by hitting Yes. The Fish Radar costs 8,000 in-game cash, so make sure you’ve saved up enough. If you’re short on cash, sell some random fish to the Merchant to farm them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Roslit Bay
  </strong>
  is west of Moosewood. Use the compass above to stay on course. Dock at the southwest side near the Shipwright, and you’ll find the Fish Radar sitting on a wooden block. For
  <strong>
   Terrapin Island
  </strong>
  , head south from Moosewood. When you arrive, stop at the island’s entrance, where you’ll see the Shipwright and the Angler Quest NPC. Just climb the wooden stairs, and you’ll see the Fish Radar on the left side. Moreover, players can also get this tool through the starter pack by spending real money (or Robux).
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-use-fish-radar-in-fisch">
  How To Use Fish Radar In Fisch
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1078475011" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1078475011" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1078475011" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1078475011" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1078475011-img" id="article-gallery-1-1078475011">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1078475011" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1799356584">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you get the Fish Radar, it becomes a permanent part of your gear in the game. To use Fish Radar in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  , open your inventory (press the Tilde key on PC or tap the 'Open to Interact' button in the bottom navigation bar on mobile), select the Fish Radar, and click anywhere on the screen to
  <strong>
   enable it
  </strong>
  . After that, just hop into your boat and head out to the ocean or any island. You’ll spot
  <strong>
   big patches on the water
  </strong>
  with the names of specific fish displayed above them. Cast your rod in those spots to start fishing. Keep in mind that you won’t always catch the fish you’re after on the first try—it might take a few attempts.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki: Furious Ribbon Locations</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-in-how-get-furious-ribbon-find-raging-sack-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Furious Ribbon Locations In Infinity Nikki
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       How To Get Furious Ribbon In Infinity Nikki
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Esselings in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Infinity Nikki
   </strong>
  </em>
  are hostile creatures that must be purified so they can be in peace. They can be found all around Miraland, and for most people, they can be quite dangerous, as not everyone has the ability to purify Esselings. The protagonist, Nikki, learns to do this a while after falling into Miraland, although later she and Momo must craft it themselves as the ability outfit was taken away.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Esselings aren't only a danger to the common folks, but they can also be purified to grant some useful materials. The drops are commonly used to craft Fragrances in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  . One example of this is how players need to
  <strong>
   get Furious Ribbon by finding Raging Sack locations in
   <em>
    Infinity Nikki
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="furious-ribbon-locations-in-infinity-nikki">
  Furious Ribbon Locations In Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1200161230" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1200161230" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1200161230" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1200161230" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1200161230-img" id="article-gallery-1-1200161230">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1200161230" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1372664177">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Furious Ribbon in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  can be found by exploring the northern area of the Firework Isles. There are around 9 spots players can visit in the open-world. After hunting the nine, Stylists can also visit two caves to find four more Raging Sacks. One is available inside Songbreeze Cavern, while three reside in Waterfall Cavern.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   It's not necessary to find firework locations to access the caves
  </strong>
  as the fireworks are only for the treasure chamber, like the Gloomy Cavern in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-furious-ribbon-in-infinity-nikki">
  How To Get Furious Ribbon In Infinity Nikki
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-379993219" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-379993219" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-379993219" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-379993219" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-379993219-img" id="article-gallery-2-379993219">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-379993219" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1593968254">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Name
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Furious Ribbon (from Raging Sack)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       A scrap of fabric obtained from purifying a Raging Sack. With nowhere to let out its fury, the pursuit of a broken dream eventually left it covered in scars.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Location
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Firework Isles
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <th scope="row">
      <p>
       Rarity
      </p>
     </th>
     <td>
      <p>
       Brown (enemy drop)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  After obtaining at least one Furious Ribbon, players can also use the
  <strong>
   Dig, Pear-Pal
  </strong>
  feature to get more of this
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  material. By doing the digging process for 20 hours, players can earn five Furious Ribbons at the cost of a mere 1000 Bling.
 </p>
 <p>
  Raging Sacks always have a Hard Sack on top of it, and just like the Hard Sack, it also has three HP instead of one. Therefore, when hunting Furious Ribbon, players will also earn Hard Scrap in the process, as long as the Hard Sack is also being defeated.
 </p>
 <p>
  Furious Ribbons are required to craft the Fragrance of Firework Isles, such as Light of Dawn hair oil and Breath of Wilderness hand powder. Both fragrances call for 10 Furious Ribbons, which means hunting the enemies throughout the map is required if Stylists don't wish to wait four days for the Pear-Pal digging.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation Now Has the Perfect One-Two Punch for Classic and Modern Mascot Platformers</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/playstation-astro-bot-ratchet-clank-classic-modern-mascot-platformers/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   PlayStation
  </strong>
  has brought gamers 30 years worth of stories and memories all around the world. Sony's beloved console has continued its impressive run with help from both its devoted fan base and extensive roster of exclusive first-party titles. Through the years, the PlayStation has evolved with the ever-changing landscape of the industry, but one thing it has consistently done well is bring strong single-player stories to life.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Within the single-player landscape, the platformer genre quickly found a home on the PlayStation, and it greatly defined the early life of the console. As time passed, mascot platformers became less prevalent across all consoles, not just PlayStation. The more modern era of Sony's consoles have focused more on strong character-driven narratives, like
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  . This trend still continues, but the arrival of
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  in 2024 marked an important milestone for Sony. Now, between
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  , PlayStation has two mascots that perfectly define these separate eras.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="ratchet-amp-clank-and-astro-bot-show-two-sides-of-playstation-39-s-history">
  Ratchet &amp; Clank and Astro Bot Show Two Sides of PlayStation's History
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1793226796" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1793226796" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1793226796" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1793226796" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1793226796-img" id="article-gallery-1-1793226796">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1793226796" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1253022190">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="ratchet-amp-clank-helped-kickstart-playstation-39-s-legacy-of-mascot-platformers">
  Ratchet &amp; Clank Helped Kickstart PlayStation's Legacy of Mascot Platformers
 </h3>
 <p>
  Of course, it's important to note that
  <em>
   Crash Bandicoot
  </em>
  came before
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  made it onto the scene, but the former hasn't been a Sony exclusive since the 90s. However, once the PS2 dropped in 2000, it signaled a new era for Sony, paving the way for
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  to become a huge marketing pull for the console. The first
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  wouldn't arrive until two years later in 2002, but its impact on the console is unmistakable. The lovable Lombax and his robot companion quickly became an iconic duo, spawning years of sequels and spin-offs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even today,
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  has still played a part in Sony's plans.
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  , launched for the PS5 in 2021, and there is still the possibility of more entries in the future. However, there is also the chance that the
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  franchise may be coming to a close. Developer Insomniac hasn't confirmed such a decision, but as time passes,
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  's importance to Sony doesn't feel as prevalent as it once did. Only time will tell, but if the series eventually meets an end,
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  is already carrying the torch into the future.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     According to the notorious 2023 Insomniac leaks, the next
     <em>
      Ratchet &amp; Clank
     </em>
     game may not arrive until 2029.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="astro-bot-is-now-the-modern-face-of-sony">
  Astro Bot is Now the Modern Face of Sony
 </h3>
 <p>
  For a free game that originally served as a tech demo for the PS5's DualSense controller,
  <em>
   Astro's Playroom
  </em>
  kickstarted excitement for the genre again. Thanks to the success of this incredibly fun demo, developer Team Asobi got the opportunity to create a full-blown
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  game. Since its launch in 2024,
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  has been praised for its blend of nostalgia and innovation that balances something fresh with the classic PlayStation platformer feel.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Astro Bot
     </em>
     sold 1.5 million copies in its first 2 months.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  The game took 2024's gaming awards season by storm, racking up an impressive number of Game of the Year titles.
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  is a celebration of the PlayStation itself, but also marks the return of something the PS5 and Sony's modern era have been sorely missing; a mascot that appeals to a wide demographic. Characters like Ellie from
  <em>
   TLOU
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  's Aloy are great in their own right, but Astro has the benefit of being both family-friendly and a joy for adult gamers.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Now, between
     <em>
      Ratchet &amp; Clank
     </em>
     and
     <em>
      Astro Bot
     </em>
     , PlayStation has two mascots that perfectly define these separate eras.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="the-playstation-39-s-future-will-likely-continue-to-put-astro-bot-in-the-spotlight">
  The PlayStation's Future Will Likely Continue to Put Astro Bot in the Spotlight
 </h3>
 <p>
  While it's unfortunate that
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  may take a backseat moving forward,
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  being the newfound face of the PlayStation brand at least puts the console's legacy in great hands. As the years continue, it will be fascinating to see how much more prevalent
  <em>
   Astro Bot
  </em>
  continues to become in Sony's marketing.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
