<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>One Pokemon TCG Pocket Type Needs a Major Improvement</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-pocket-dragon-type-cards-energy-rng-good-bad-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon TCG Pocket differs from the physical game with distinct deckbuilding rules limited to 20 cards.
     </li>
     <li>
      Dragon-type Pokemon in Pocket struggle due to Energy requirements and random Energy generation.
     </li>
     <li>
      To improve gameplay, Pocket could implement Energy manipulation to support Dragon decks and enhance diversity.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are many ways in which
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket
   </em>
  </strong>
  resembles and follows in the footsteps of the physical version of
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  , starting with the way card conventions are established and the types of critters available in the game. Although Fairy Pokemon cards were added to the physical game in the past,
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  removed Fairy as a type with the launch of the Gen 8 series, but Dragon remained despite its similar status. In
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  , the gameplay loop is quite different from the physical version of the game, and that is because deckbuilding rules differ as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, decks are limited to 20 cards, and the number of cards can neither exceed nor be inferior to that. There is a major difference in the fact that Energy cards don't exist in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  , but rather, the game generates Energy randomly based on the Energy types used by the deck or those selected by players when creating it. This is no problem for decks that use just one type of Energy, but it can be for those that don't. The result is that the mobile game does feature Dragon Pokemon, but they need one big addition for their Energy requirements.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-tcg-pocket-39-s-energy-zone-makes-dragon-types-nearly-unplayable">
  Pokemon TCG Pocket's Energy Zone Makes Dragon Types Nearly Unplayable
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-289013766" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-289013766" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-289013766" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-289013766" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-289013766-img" id="article-gallery-1-289013766">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-289013766" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-312004013">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Currently, there are seven different Dragon-type Pokemon cards in the game, though that is one is not counting the two illustration rare versions of both Dragonite and Garchomp. They all have one thing in common, with the exception of Gible, and that is that their attacks require at least two different types of Energy. In the case of
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  's Dragonite line, they all need at least one Water and one Electric Energy to attack, whereas Druddigon requires Water and Fire, and both Gabite and Garchomp require Water and Fighting.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Gible can attack with any Energy type for 20 damage with Gnaw.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  The main problem with this approach, given that Energy cards are not in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  at all, is that one can potentially never get enough Energy of a given type because each one is generated randomly between the possible types in the deck. For example, a Garchomp deck that uses other critters, like the Greninja line, may be forever stuck on all Water Energy and never get the one Fighting Energy needed for the Dragon Pokemon to attack. Since Energy generation is random, there are a few ways for the game to be improved for multi-type and Dragon decks:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Rather than generating Energy randomly, the game could have a system where the Energy Zone generates Energy types based on the number of Pokemon of each type present in the deck. For example, three Water Pokemon and one Dragon Pokemon with Water and Fighting requirements could result in one guaranteed Fighting Energy for every three Water Energy
  </li>
  <li>
   Another option could be adding a Trainer card to
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket
   </em>
   , possibly one based on the legendary Dragon Pokemon trainer Lance, that allows Dragon-type critters to attack regardless of the Energy types attached to them (provided they have enough Energy to attack). An alternative could be a similar card that instead changes the Energy type available in the Energy Zone to one chosen by the player
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="why-pokemon-tcg-pocket-needs-energy-manipulation">
  Why Pokemon TCG Pocket Needs Energy Manipulation
 </h3>
 <p>
  With some kind of Energy type manipulation or control, Dragon-type decks could finally enjoy some time in the limelight, as the current meta decks in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  only use one Energy type in the Energy Zone. Decks like Darkrai Ex and Magnezone use multiple types of Energy in the actual gameplay, but the unstable nature of RNG privileges decks that only use one Energy type in the Energy Zone. It remains to be seen if any changes will be made, but these would be great to support Dragon-type decks as well as more deckbuilding diversity for those players who would like to use two or more Pokemon types in a given deck.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open World RPG Where Winds Meet is Already a Big Hit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/where-winds-meet-player-count-february-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Where Winds Meet, an open-world action RPG, has amassed over 15 million players since its December 2024 release in China.
     </li>
     <li>
      The title is scheduled to be released globally in 2025, but only the iOS version.
     </li>
     <li>
      Other platforms will follow, though it's unclear when.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Where Winds Meet
   </strong>
  </em>
  , a historical game from
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  publisher NetEase, has amassed over 15 million players since its China-exclusive launch on PC and mobile in December 2024. Similar to
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  , another AAA game to come from China,
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  also takes place in an open world and features action-RPG elements.
 </p>
 <p>
  After establishing itself in the mobile gaming landscape over the past decade or so, the Chinese game industry seems to have set its sights on repeating the same success with PC and console titles in the future. In 2024, the first international AAA release developed by a China-based studio,
  <em>
   Black Myth: Wukong
  </em>
  , rolled out and immediately experienced overwhelming player engagement as well as incredible sales performance. Selling over 25 million copies in less than six months, Game Science's
  <em>
   Journey to the West
  </em>
  -inspired title set a major benchmark for future Chinese-made releases targeting the PC and consoles. It now appears that
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  by Everstone Studios may very well be equipped to follow in those footsteps, having produced some remarkable numbers after its China-exclusive arrival.
 </p>
 <p>
  In its earnings report for Q4 2024 and early 2025, NetEase Games announced that the player base of
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  exceeded 15 million players in China across PC and mobile after only two weeks of its January 9 launch on the latter platform. During those couple of weeks "approximately," the martial arts-themed game also sat at the top of the iOS downloads leaderboard. This success on mobile came after
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  's strong PC launch on December 27, 2024, in which it raced past three million downloads within four days. In the same report, NetEase also gave an exciting update about its highly popular hero shooter game,
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , sharing that the
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  competitor had attracted more than 45 million players so far.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-winds-meet-is-set-to-launch-worldwide-in-2025-but-there-39-s-a-catch">
  Where Winds Meet is Set to Launch Worldwide in 2025, But There's a Catch
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-622272031" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-622272031" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-622272031" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-622272031" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-622272031-img" id="article-gallery-1-622272031">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-622272031" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1319340126">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  has previously been announced for a global release at some point in the future, but so far not all platforms have been confirmed to arrive worldwide in 2025. The last official update from the studio on Twitter, shared in October 2024, specifically talked about the iOS version being rolled out overseas in 2025, with no explicit release information about its PC and console ports. While this may be slightly worrisome to exciting fans, the eventual arrival of the mobile version could make room for a follow-up announcement about the progress of
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  on other platforms.
 </p>
 <p>
  Interestingly, there's another major console release from China coming soon which also has the theme of martial arts in common with
  <em>
   Where Winds Meet
  </em>
  . Initially announced in May 2023,
  <em>
   Phantom Blade Zero
  </em>
  is an RPG for the PC and the PS5, which is slated for a Fall 2026 launch.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive Passes Incredible Sales Milestone</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pacific-drive-sales/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pacific Drive hit one million copies sold in its first year.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game earned a Game Awards nomination in 2024.
     </li>
     <li>
      A TV adaptation of the game is in the works.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pacific Drive
   </strong>
  </em>
  has passed a major sales milestone in the first year of its release. The eerie survival game quickly gained notoriety for its unique take on the genre, engaging story, and challenging gameplay, and it seems those qualities have helped its small studio's finances in a big way. Despite being Ironwood Studios' first game,
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  has sold an impressive amount for a first-year indie title.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's been a landmark year for Ironwood Studios.
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  was nominated at the 2024 Game Awards, and while it ended up losing the title of Best Debut Indie Game to
  <em>
   Balatro
  </em>
  , the nomination alone is a respectable achievement. Fans have latched onto the game, too, as seen by its latest sales figures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Total sales of
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  across both PC and PlayStation have passed the one million mark days before the game hit its one-year anniversary. During its development, Ironwood had to delay
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  from 2023 to 2024. That time gave the small team the space it needed to get the title to where it hoped to be, and fans apparently did not take the delay poorly, considering many still bought the game after release.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pacific-drive-passes-one-million-copies-sold-in-its-first-year">
  Pacific Drive Passes One Million Copies Sold in its First Year
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-688129813" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-688129813" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-688129813" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-688129813" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-688129813-img" id="article-gallery-1-688129813">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-688129813" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1335960225">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hitting the one million mark was not the only good news for Ironwood Studios in recent months. In December 2024, it revealed that
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  will be getting a TV adaptation from the same production company that made horror films
  <em>
   M3GAN
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Malignant
  </em>
  . Details around the project remain scarce, as it's still in its earliest stages, but getting such notoriety so soon is a rare achievement for a studio of Ironwoods' size. As for the game itself, Ironwood has said that it's not done with it yet, so future updates may be in the works for players to look forward to, but fans will need to wait for more official news to learn more.
 </p>
 <p>
  This recent string of achievements may not surprise gamers who've spent much time in the title. According to some,
  <em>
   Pacific Drive
  </em>
  is one of the best driving-centric indie games available today. Its unique spin on the roguelike genre also makes it stand out in an increasingly crowded market. What's next for the game remains unclear at this point, but things are looking good for Ironwood Studios.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Us 3D Launching For PC, Bringing PC And VR Players Together</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/among-us-3d-vr-pc-steam-launch/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In 2022, popular social deduction game
  <em>
   <strong>
    Among Us
   </strong>
  </em>
  came to multiple VR platforms as
  <em>
   <strong>
   </strong>
   Among Us VR,
  </em>
  a three-dimensional first-person re-imagining of the space-set game where innocent crewmates seek to identify and eject dangerous impostors. Now,
  <em>
   Among Us VR
  </em>
  is re-branding as
  <em>
   Among Us 3D,
  </em>
  bringing the first-person version of the game to Steam and allowing PC and VR players to experience
  <em>
   Among Us
  </em>
  together.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="among-us-3d-is-coming-to-pc-while-vr-rebrands">
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  Is Coming To PC While VR Rebrands
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1260989846" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1260989846" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1260989846" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1260989846" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1260989846-img" id="article-gallery-1-1260989846">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1260989846" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-6619789">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  will launch for PC at some point in the near future. Its release date is currently unconfirmed. However, players interested in experiencing
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  as soon as possible can do so via a demo that will be available during Steam Next Fest beginning on Monday, February 24. Players can also currently wishlist the game on Steam.
 </p>
 <p>
  Cross-play will be available between the PC version of
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  and all current
  <em>
   Among Us VR
  </em>
  platforms including Steam VR, the Meta Quest and Meta Quest 2, and the PICO 4.
  <em>
   Among Us VR
  </em>
  will be rebranding to
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  to reflect the new non-VR availability of the 3D version.
 </p>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-9adce7b5d503547b" id="emaki-video-player-9adce7b5d503547b">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  All new content currently available for
  <em>
   Among Us VR
  </em>
  will be brought to
  <em>
   Among Us 3D.
  </em>
  This includes voice chat, the Engineer role, and all currently released VR cosmetics such as hats, gloves, and skins. The PC version of
  <em>
   Among Us 3D
  </em>
  will have a HUD that displays players' task lists, name, crewmate or imposter status, and other key information.
 </p>
 <p>
  The team at Innersloth and Schell Games confirmed that they plan to release new cosmetics, roles, game modes, and collaborations in the future for
  <em>
   Among Us 3D.
  </em>
  Cosmetics will be implemented in the form of a new currency called Stardust, which players will be able to collect exclusively in
  <em>
   Among Us 3D,
  </em>
  and will include a mix of brand-new items and returning fan favorites from the 2D version of the game. The 2D version of
  <em>
   Among Us
  </em>
  will remain available, but cross-play will not be supported between the 2D and 3D versions of the game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Rocksteady Could Be Working on a Batman Beyond Game</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/batman-beyond-games-rumors-rocksteady/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Rocksteady is rumored to be working on a new Batman Beyond game.
     </li>
     <li>
      The rumored Batman Beyond game may be a PlayStation exclusive and possibly funded by Sony.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Rocksteady, the studio known for its incredibly successful catalog of single-player
  <em>
   Batman
  </em>
  games, is working on its next project, which is rumored to be a new take on
  <strong>
   <em>
    Batman Beyond
   </em>
  </strong>
  . According to a leaker, Rocksteady is looking toward the classic animated show
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  as the foundation for its next game, a series that, despite only running for a few short years, has since developed a cult fan base.
 </p>
 <p>
  While many studios have tried to capture the magic of comic books in video game form, few have succeeded quite like Rocksteady, which put itself on the map with its richly detailed and immersive releases like
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Asylum
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Arkham City
  </em>
  . Pitting the player against some of Batman's greatest foes, Rocksteady's
  <em>
   Arkham
  </em>
  series stands tall among its comic book counterparts and is plainly considered one of the best games series ever. Rocksteady certainly faced a few struggles over the years, namely with the company's detour into the world of
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  . However, rumors suggest the studio is returning to its
  <em>
   Batman
  </em>
  roots for its next project.
 </p>
 <p>
  According to leaker Lunatic Ignus, Rocksteady is looking at
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  for its next take on the Caped Crusader for its next game. The new rumor follows other reports that Rocksteady is gearing up to return to the realm of single-player
  <em>
   Batman
  </em>
  games. However, this rumor claims the proposed
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  game may be a PlayStation exclusive, something that goes against the grain when looking at the studio's past releases. This rumored exclusivity is likely a result of unverified reports about Sony funding the upcoming game. This would certainly be a perplexing decision as one would think Warner Bros. would want the most players possible on this new
  <em>
   Batman
  </em>
  game, especially considering the large amounts of money it reportedly lost on Rocksteady's
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="rocksteady-rumored-to-be-creating-new-batman-beyond-game">
  Rocksteady Rumored to Be Creating New Batman Beyond Game
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1559439417" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1559439417" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1559439417" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1559439417" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1559439417-img" id="article-gallery-1-1559439417">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1559439417" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-256138408">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Taking place in the future,
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  sees Bruce Wayne hang up his cape, handing off the mantle to Terry McGinnis. Under Wayne's guidance, McGinnis faces off against iconic foes like Mr. Freeze as well as a wide range of other bad guys like Shriek, Spellbinder, Inque, and Blight, who could all serve as interesting combatants for Rocksteady's rumored new
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  game. The new rumor also claims that Rocksteady's supposed
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  project will serve as the first piece of a new trilogy of Batman games.
 </p>
 <p>
  As stated earlier, Rocksteady's most recent outing left both it and the game's publisher hurting. It was clear from the start that
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  would struggle amid its controversial live-service features and somewhat lackluster main campaign.
  <em>
   Suicide Squad
  </em>
  's sales came in way under expectations, resulting in layoffs at Rocksteady. The game has since ended, with
  <em>
   Suicide Squad
  </em>
  wrapping up its final season in early 2025, paving a clear path for a new
  <strong>
   <em>
    Batman
   </em>
   <em>
    Beyond
   </em>
  </strong>
  project if this is actually what Rocksteady intends to do.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
