<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Leaker Makes First Cryptic Post of the New Year</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-leaker-cryptic-post-twitter-legends-z-a/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A Pokemon leaker has shared a cryptic post to start off 2025, potentially hinting at several inclusions in the roster of Pokemon for Pokemon Legends: Z-A.
     </li>
     <li>
      The list includes multiple Starter Evolutions like Scorbunny and Meowscarada, alongside Legendary and Mythical Pokemon like Meloetta and Reshiram.
     </li>
     <li>
      Recent rumors have suggested that Pokemon may also be planning another major release this year alongside Pokemon Legends: Z-A.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A prominent
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon
   </em>
  </strong>
  leaker has kicked off the new year with a cryptic post potentially hinting at future content, asking players to choose from several Pokemon. The massively popular monster-catching franchise is set to have a major year in 2025, with a main title already confirmed to be on the way. The Pokemon Company officially revealed
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  early last year as a follow-up to 2022's
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Arceus
  </em>
  , set in the Kalos region specifically centered in Lumiose City. Now, a well-known leaker may be dropping a hint at some of the game's content.
 </p>
 <p>
  While The Pokemon Company has revealed relatively little about its next main-series game, leaks and rumors have already begun to tease early details of
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . The game is expected to welcome the return of Mega Evolutions to the franchise, which haven't appeared in a main-series game since
  <em>
   Pokemon Let's Go Pikachu
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Let's Go Eevee
  </em>
  . Leaks have also debated the potential selection of Starter Pokemon within
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  , with both mixed selections and the Gen 6 trio rumored to appear. A new leak may now hint at even more Pokemon set to appear in
  <em>
   Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-leaker-drops-cryptic-post-teasing-new-pokemon">
  Pokemon Leaker Drops Cryptic Post Teasing New Pokemon
 </h2>
 <p>
  A post shared by prominent
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  leaker Riddler Khu is potentially hinting at some inclusions in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends; Z-A
  </em>
  's Pokedex. The tweet features images of 30 different Pokemon, with Khu asking fans and followers to choose from among the included sets of creatures. The lineup of Pokemon includes several Starter Pokemon evolutions, with Meowscarada, Cinderace, Braixen, and Primarina all featured. The list also shows some Legendary and Mythical Pokemon, showing Reshiram, Meloetta, and even Pheromosa in the selection.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Mega Gardevoir
  </li>
  <li>
   Pheromosa
  </li>
  <li>
   Mega Lopunny
  </li>
  <li>
   Tsareena
  </li>
  <li>
   Florges
  </li>
  <li>
   Tinkaton
  </li>
  <li>
   Alcremie
  </li>
  <li>
   Lilligant
  </li>
  <li>
   Meowscarada
  </li>
  <li>
   Primarina
  </li>
  <li>
   Indeedee
  </li>
  <li>
   Salazzle
  </li>
  <li>
   Scorbunny
  </li>
  <li>
   Milotic
  </li>
  <li>
   Hatterene
  </li>
  <li>
   Gothorita
  </li>
  <li>
   Braixen
  </li>
  <li>
   Sylveon
  </li>
  <li>
   Jynx
  </li>
  <li>
   Purugly
  </li>
  <li>
   Shiny Machamp
  </li>
  <li>
   Reshiram
  </li>
  <li>
   Mawile
  </li>
  <li>
   Sneasler
  </li>
  <li>
   Goodra
  </li>
  <li>
   Ditto
  </li>
  <li>
   Froslass
  </li>
  <li>
   Audino
  </li>
  <li>
   Diancie
  </li>
  <li>
   Meloetta
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While the intent of the leaker's post is unclear, the leak may include some hints about the lineup of creatures set to appear in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . Scorbunny had previously been leaked as one of the possible Starter Pokemon for
  <em>
   Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  , while multiple included Pokemon like Florges and Diancie first debuted in the sixth-generation games. The post also includes two different Mega Evolutions within its selection, suggesting that Mega Gardevoir and Mega Lopunny may be returning in
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  . The Pokemon Company has not yet confirmed an official release date for
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-821654852" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-821654852" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-821654852" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-821654852" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-821654852-img" id="article-gallery-1-821654852">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-821654852" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1573065078">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  's launch on the horizon, rumors have swirled about another
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  game potentially coming this year. Previous leaks from Riddler Khu have suggested that
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  is planning to debut another game during 2025 for the Switch 2, though it reportedly will not be
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  's tenth generation. Fans have already begun to speculate about numerous previously-rumored games, ranging from
  <em>
   Pokemon Black and White
  </em>
  remakes to
  <em>
   Pokemon Let's Go
  </em>
  games set in the Johto region. With potentially two major releases on the way, 2025 could prove to be a big year for
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pikmin Bloom Reveals January 2025 Community Day Plans</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pikmin-bloom-community-day-january-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pikmin Bloom's Community Day on January 11-12 requires players to walk 10,000 steps for a badge.
     </li>
     <li>
      Big Flowers in-game grow into Camellias, and bonuses help with planting and growth speed.
     </li>
     <li>
      A code offers free items until March 1, 2025, rewarding players with colored petals and an accelerator.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Nintendo and Niantic have announced their plans for
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pikmin Bloom
   </strong>
  </em>
  's Community Day, which will be taking place on January 11, 2025.
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  is a free-to-play AR spin-off in the
  <em>
   Pikmin
  </em>
  series that takes after Niantic's
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . Much like
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  , players spend time outside and their real-world movements are tracked by the game, rewarding them with items that can grow or feed Pikmin. Some of these big rewards can be earned by going to various real-world landmarks, which are represented by large flowers in-game. Players can also take pictures of their Pikmin against a real-world backdrop.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  hosts Community Day events, which take place one weekend of every month. Each one requires players to walk 10,000 steps in order to get a special badge that is themed around the Flower of the Month. 2024's last Community Day was hosted from December 14-15, themed after poinsettas.
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  's first Community Day of 2025 will take place later this month, giving players a whole weekend to get some rewards around Camellias.
 </p>
 <p>
  As detailed by a post made by the official
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  account, Camellias are January 2025's Flower of the Month. It is a repeat theme of
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  's January 2022 Community Day, running from January 11-12, 2025. The in-game shop will also be offering a limited-time Community Day bundle pack and a special mission ticket to tie into this event as well. The special Community Day mission ticket will be available to purchase during this period, and players must complete it before January 13, 2025, at 23:59 local time. Completing the 10,000-step goal in
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  will reward them with a Blue Camellia Flower Badge.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="when-is-pikmin-bloom-39-s-january-2025-community-day">
  When is Pikmin Bloom's January 2025 Community Day?
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   January 11 - January 12
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  's in-app bonuses during Community Day were also detailed, re-iterating that Big Flowers will bloom into Camellias when the player plants a regular blue, red, yellow, or white petal. Seedlings in the planter pack will also grow at 1.5x the usual speed. The post notes that players who don't achieve the 10K step goal by the end of January 11 will have their progress reset on January 12, which will not result in them receiving the badge if it goes over the required amount. The best way to ensure the player gets the badge is to launch the app on the day when the player wants to achieve the 10,000-step task.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1290423967" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1290423967" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1290423967" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1290423967" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1290423967-img" id="article-gallery-1-1290423967">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1290423967" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-470649744">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Niantic has also given players a code for
  <em>
   Pikmin Bloom
  </em>
  that gives out free items, which will be valid until March 1, 2025, at 0:00 UTC. Redeeming this code on
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pikmin Bloom
   </strong>
  </em>
  's official website gives players three different colored petals and one Flower Planting Accelerator item.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3's Airship Needs to Be More than Just Transportation</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-7-remake-part-3-airship-highwind-gameplay/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The airship has long been a hallmark of the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  franchise, serving as a gateway to exploration, freedom, and progression. With
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 7
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   Remake Part 3
  </em>
  on the horizon, the reimagined Highwind offers Square Enix an opportunity to modernize airship mechanics while paying homage to its roots.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  As
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  has already redefined exploration with its "wide linear" approach, the airship in the trilogy’s conclusion must rise beyond mere transportation to solidify its place in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  history.
 </p>
 <h3 id="">
 </h3>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-legacy-of-airships-in-final-fantasy">
  The Legacy of Airships in Final Fantasy
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-202427909" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-202427909" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-202427909" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-202427909" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-202427909-img" id="article-gallery-1-202427909">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-202427909" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-747863477">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Airships have always been more than just vehicles in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  games. In
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 4
  </em>
  , the Enterprise introduced the thrill of exploring uncharted skies, while
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 9
  </em>
  ’s Invincible became a plot device intertwined with the game’s climax. Encountering the Highwind in the original
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  was a pivotal moment, allowing players to fully explore the map and confront the looming threat of Sephiroth.
 </p>
 <p>
  Modernizing airship gameplay in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  could draw from these examples, blending narrative significance with interactive mechanics. This wouldn’t just honor the series' history but also enrich the player experience in meaningful ways.
 </p>
 <h3 id="expanding-airship-features-in-final-fantasy-7">
  Expanding Airship Features in Final Fantasy 7
 </h3>
 <p>
  Square Enix has hinted that airship gameplay will play a key role in the final installment of the trilogy. While past
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  airships largely served as a mode of travel, the Highwind in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  could offer something much more dynamic.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combat integration could be one revolutionary step. Players could find themselves using the Highwind to engage in battles against massive Weapons, such as Ruby or Emerald, in high-stakes aerial combat. This would align with the series’ history of epic encounters while introducing a fresh gameplay mechanic. The Highwind could also become a mobile base, allowing players to customize party builds, upgrade equipment, or interact with NPCs onboard between missions.
 </p>
 <p>
  Additionally, environmental storytelling tied to the Highwind could make the world feel more alive. For instance, the crew could react to story developments, and players might unlock new dialogue or missions by interacting with them during flights.
 </p>
 <h3 id="sticking-the-landing-with-a-lofty-story">
  Sticking the Landing with a Lofty Story
 </h3>
 <p>
  The challenge for
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  goes beyond airship mechanics. Square Enix must conclude its ambitious trilogy while delivering a satisfying and coherent ending to the multiverse-spanning story introduced in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake
  </em>
  and expanded in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Sephiroth’s multiversal plans and the divergence of timelines have raised the stakes to unprecedented levels. The airship could be pivotal in this narrative, perhaps acting as a bridge between realities or a tool for combating Sephiroth’s ambitions. A climactic sequence involving the Highwind—whether through a daring escape, an aerial showdown, or a journey into the Lifestream—could cement its place as a central piece of the story. This approach would mirror the original
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7’s
  </em>
  blending of gameplay and storytelling, elevating the Highwind from a functional asset to a narrative symbol.
 </p>
 <h3 id="honoring-final-fantasy-7-nostalgia-while-embracing-innovation">
  Honoring Final Fantasy 7 Nostalgia While Embracing Innovation
 </h3>
 <p>
  Balancing nostalgia with innovation is a tightrope that Square Enix has walked successfully in the
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake
  </em>
  series. The final game must ensure the Highwind respects the charm of its 1997 counterpart while embracing the potential of modern technology and gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  For example, while maintaining its design, the Highwind could feature advanced customization options, allowing players to tweak its appearance, speed, and capabilities. A return to the thrilling freedom of exploration seen in older
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  titles could also be appropriate, but this should be paired with meaningful content, such as hidden areas, secret bosses, and lore-rich locations that can only be accessed via the airship.
 </p>
 <p>
  This combination of old and new would make the Highwind not just a tribute to the past but also a testament to the evolution of the franchise. As
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  has already expanded the scope of the world,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  has the chance to make airship travel a defining feature of the trilogy’s legacy.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liar's Bar is Getting a New Game Mode</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/liars-bar-poker-game-mode-coming-soon/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Liar's Bar will introduce a new Poker game mode soon, adding more excitement to the popular multiplayer title.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game blends Liar's Dice, Liar's Deck, and Russian Roulette, gaining huge Twitch popularity in 2024.
     </li>
     <li>
      Although Poker was always planned, it's arriving early in the Early Access phase, allowing time to address bugs before the full release.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Curve Animation has announced that its popular multiplayer title
  <em>
   <strong>
    Liar's Bar
   </strong>
  </em>
  is set to receive a brand-new game mode in the form of Poker.
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  's version of Poker should bring more heart-racing moments to the $6.99 party game.
 </p>
 <p>
  <span style="box-sizing:border-box; margin:0px; padding:0px">
   <em>
    Liar's Bar
   </em>
   was released into Early Access in late 2024 and became an instant success.
  </span>
  It was arguably one of the games that surpassed expectations the most in 2024, especially considering how few gamers had ever heard of it prior to launch.
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  is a strange hybrid of the Liar's Dice and Liar's Deck games alongside Russian Roulette. It's made a little wacky by the humanoid animal characters and cartoon art style, and is a perfect party game to play with friends. The game saw major popularity on Twitch at the time of its release, catapulting it to an all-time peak player count of 113,798 on Steam.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a very cryptic post on Steam, Curve Animation confirmed that Poker is coming to
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  , claiming, "The highly anticipated Liar's Poker is coming soon to your table." The post was void of any details about what the mode is going to entail, but the fact that Poker typically involves even more bluffing than the game modes already in
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  should indicate it's going to be a blast. It certainly cements
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  as one of the top Early Access games to keep an eye on this year.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="poker-is-coming-to-liar-39-s-bar-soon">
  Poker is Coming to Liar's Bar Soon
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1424846790" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1424846790" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1424846790" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1424846790" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1424846790-img" id="article-gallery-1-1424846790">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1424846790" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1251583040">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It has never been a secret that Poker would come to
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  at some point. Although
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  launched with Liar's Dice and Liar's Deck, the roadmap for the game has always had Liar's Poker down as coming with the full release. However, Curve Animation has already confirmed that
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  will be in Early Access for at least six months, so if Liar's Poker is in fact just around the corner, it's likely a case of the new game mode arriving ahead of schedule. This is good, as it allows the developer to squash any bugs found by players before the full release.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hopefully, the addition of Liar's Poker will help
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  climb the Steam charts once again. The game's current player count on Steam sits at a 24-hour peak of 6,298. While it's a far cry from the heights of its launch, a fall-off was always expected, and it's impressive that a game of this stature has managed to retain as many players as it has. With more updates like Poker and the recent
  <em>
   Liar's Bar
  </em>
  Chaos Mode update, the game is set to be in a good state for its eventual full release, boding well for player numbers in the future.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Long Wait For Fallout 5 Would Have One Obvious Benefit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-5-long-wait-good-why-graphics/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise is in a bit of a weird place right now. On the one hand, the recent
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  TV show was a massive success for both Bethesda Game Studios and Amazon, and
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  is still popular to this day, despite its infamously bad launch. On the other hand, though, no new
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  game has been released in more than half a decade, and there is almost nothing on the horizon for fans to look forward to. There is a second season of the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  show in the works, yes, but when it comes to games, the future of the franchise for the next few years is a complete mystery.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  With how popular the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  IP is these days, it seems strange that Bethesda's parent company, Microsoft, has done little to capitalize on it. For years, fans have asked for remasters or remakes of classic entries in the franchise, like
  <em>
   Fallout 3
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Fallout: 2
  </em>
  , but outside of some leaked (and potentially outdated) documents, there has been nothing formally announced on this front. The same can be said for the long-awaited
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas 2
  </em>
  , which has been in the rumor mill for quite some time, but hasn't come to fruition just yet. The only game that has been officially announced by Bethesda so far is
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , the next mainline installment in the series. This particular game is still ages away from being released, but at the very least, it may be a graphical powerhouse when it eventually comes out.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fallout-5-could-have-far-better-graphics-than-previous-bethesda-games">
  Fallout 5 Could Have Far Better Graphics than Previous Bethesda Games
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1437385048" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1437385048" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1437385048" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1437385048" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1437385048-img" id="article-gallery-1-1437385048">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1437385048" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-428508765">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="bethesda-games-aren-39-t-known-for-having-great-graphics-but-that-wasn-39-t-always-the-case">
  Bethesda Games Aren't Known for Having Great Graphics, But That Wasn't Always the Case
 </h3>
 <p>
  In recent times, Bethesda games haven't exactly been known for having outstanding graphics. While its titles have often had impressive art design and distinct visuals, they haven't been industry leaders from a technical point of view. The Maryland-based studio's most recent game,
  <em>
   Starfield
  </em>
  , was widely criticized for its graphics and facial animations, in particular. The space-faring RPG certainly looked a lot more realistic than most of Bethesda's previous works, such as
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim
  </em>
  , but it paled in comparison to other contemporary games in the same genre, including
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Some of Bethesda's early titles, however, were considered visually impressive for their time.
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion
  </em>
  became the benchmark for open world graphics when it was released on Xbox 360 and PC in 2006. Likewise,
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 3: Morrowind
  </em>
  's visuals were considered advanced by some back in the early 2000s. In the present era,
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Morrowind
  </em>
  look really outdated by modern standards, even compared to
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Fallout 4
  </em>
  , and the like. Nonetheless, since the graphics of Bethesda games were once considered cutting-edge, it’s clear that the company does have the capability to push technical boundaries. Hopefully, it can embrace this approach again with
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  .
  <strong>
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h3 id="fallout-5-39-s-distant-launch-could-allow-it-to-take-advantage-of-future-graphical-advancements">
  Fallout 5's Distant Launch Could Allow It to Take Advantage of Future Graphical Advancements
 </h3>
 <p>
  The existence of
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  was first acknowledged by Bethesda Game Studios head Todd Howard during an interview with IGN in June 2022. At the time, he stated that the team at BGS would get to work on
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  after finishing development of
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  . There was one big problem with the roadmap that Howard outlined, however:
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  was still years away from being released. The next numbered entry in the
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  franchise has only recently entered production, and likely won't come out until the late 2020s or early 2030s. Because of this,
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  will probably not launch until the mid-2030s at the earliest.
 </p>
 <p>
  By the time the 2030s roll around, Bethesda games may have far more realistic graphics than they currently do.
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  , for example, could end up having more detailed facial animations, environments, and NPCs thanks to the advent of new graphics technologies. It may even include immersive new features, like visible weapon degradation, improved water physics, injuries reflecting on player characters, real-time weather systems, and much more. Ultimately, a major increase in graphical fidelity could make the 10-year wait for
  <em>
   Fallout 5
  </em>
  a little more understandable, at least for fans that want a hyper-realistic
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout
   </em>
  </strong>
  game.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
