<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>15 Years Ago, Mass Effect 2 Changed the Conversation Around Player Choice in Video Games</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/mass-effect-2-15th-anniversary-player-choice-influence/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mass Effect 2 redefined player choice by making every decision impactful, not just for the story but also in tangible outcomes.
     </li>
     <li>
      Loyalty missions in Mass Effect 2 played a crucial role in determining the survival of crew members during the "Suicide Mission."
     </li>
     <li>
      Choices made in Mass Effect 2 not only affected immediate outcomes but carried over to the next game in the series, creating lasting consequences.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When
  <strong>
   <em>
    Mass Effect 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  launched in 2010, it's likely no one really knew what they were in for with it. The first
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  game launched in 2007 to favorable reviews, so, of course, its fans were looking forward to spending more time on the Normandy with Commander Shepard and their crew. However,
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  would go on to become the new entry point to the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  series, with its refined combat and exploration, fulfilling relationship-building mechanics, and an increased emphasis on player agency. From then on, the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  series became an RPG phenomenon, with a significant portion of its reputation owing to its unprecedented value for player choice.
 </p>
 <p>
  Prior to the launch of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  , player choice had already been introduced as a value in gaming, with series like
  <em>
   Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic
  </em>
  relying heavily on the concept. However,
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  took the idea and raised the stakes in such a way that the players themselves would feel the impact of their choices, instead of merely witnessing the impact they have on the protagonist and those around them.
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  ultimately accomplished this by presenting players with opportunities to invest a part of themselves into every relationship they build with the game's companions, none of whom are guaranteed to make it through the story alive.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-mass-effect-2-changed-player-choice-forever">
  How Mass Effect 2 Changed Player Choice Forever
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-288077185" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-288077185" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-288077185" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-288077185" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-288077185-img" id="article-gallery-1-288077185">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-288077185" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-765679126">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="mass-effect-2-made-player-choice-more-than-a-gimmick">
  Mass Effect 2 Made Player Choice More Than a Gimmick
 </h3>
 <p>
  Before the release of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  , player choice was more of a gimmick than anything else. Sure, players could make important decisions in the stories they played, but these choices often boiled down to binary outcomes, with obvious "good" and "evil" paths to take. The first
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  began introducing the idea of moral complexity, but
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  ultimately took the concept further by ensuring that every choice players made during the narrative would go on to haunt them once the credits rolled at its end.
 </p>
 <p>
  At the heart of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's story is Commander Shepard and the ragtag team of crew members they have assembled to take on what very well could be considered a near-suicidal mission. As players progress through this story, they are often presented with opportunities to increase the loyalty of each crew member by regularly engaging with them and completing missions for them, all to ensure they would do anything for Commander Shepard by the time the proverbial suicide mission takes place. Many of these missions revolved around moral dilemmas where players would almost help shape their companions by helping them make choices.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     For example, when Garrus comes to a crossroads of either exacting revenge on his former comrade or letting go of the vendetta altogether, players are given a chance to be directly involved in the character's narrative by helping him make the choice.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  This loyalty would go on to impact more than the player's, and Commander Shepard's, relationship with their companions, as it would play a part in the outcome of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's "Suicide Mission." The more loyal a crew member was, the more likely they were to survive the mission, so players were encouraged to consider their time with each companion valuable, and to not simply go their own way in the game without considering what was best for their crew. In the end, this all made every choice feel meaningful, not just from a story standpoint, but also in terms of tangible outcomes.
 </p>
 <h3 id="mass-effect-2-gave-players-choices-with-lasting-consequences">
  Mass Effect 2 Gave Players Choices With Lasting Consequences
 </h3>
 <p>
  While it was certainly devastating for players to reach the "Suicide Mission" only to witness the death of companions they failed to build a relationship with over the course of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's story, these immediate emotional consequences weren't the only thing players needed to consider, as their choices would then carry on to the next game in the
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  series,
  <em>
   Mass Effect 3
  </em>
  . This meant that, if any of the player's companions didn't survive
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's "Suicide Mission," they would be excluded from the next game's roster.
 </p>
 <p>
  This didn't just include the game's companions either, as even specific choices regarding the Normandy in
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  could cause certain crew members to be lost during the final moments of the game's story. It was this, the incredibly high stakes of
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's choices, that would evoke something in the gaming industry, leaving many future developers even wondering how they could replicate the system without looking like copycats. To this day, 15 years later, very few developers have been able to create a choice system that carries as much weight as
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  's.
 </p>
 <p>
  In other words,
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  didn't just tell an original story; it, more or less, invited players to co-author its story by giving every decision a personal edge and encouraging them to consider every path carefully before taking it. By utilizing the concept of player choice that had been introduced before it, and then expanding on the idea with a blend of branching narratives, moral ambiguity, and lasting, permanent consequences,
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  effectively redefined what it meant for players to have agency in video games. Today, these design choices continue to influence the way developers approach storytelling, and it's likely that
  <em>
   Mass Effect 2
  </em>
  will persist as the gold standard for many years to come.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best JRPGs With Anti-Heroes As Protagonists, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-jrpgs-with-anti-heroes-protagonists-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Anti-heroes don't need to be dark and broody, just lack typical heroic qualities.
     </li>
     <li>
      Anti-heroes like Caim, Ace, and Velvet have depth and moral ambiguity.
     </li>
     <li>
      Characters like Laharl, Ichiban, and Cloud exhibit selfishness and lack of typical hero morals.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are many well-written anti-heroes in gaming, with a handful representing the JRPG genre. However, an anti-hero doesn’t need to be dark and broody. In fact, the only requirement they need to be considered an anti-hero is that they do not possess typical heroic qualities. Heroes are usually portrayed as selfless and morally true, while anti-heroes can be flawed, morally ambiguous, or even doing the right thing for the wrong reasons.
 </p>
 <p>
  This makes being an anti-hero a very gray area with a lot of potential candidates — more than one might imagine. Anti-heroes are compelling choices for protagonists because they have depth, and can cause a strong emotional connection with the players because of their internal struggles — which can have players feel sympathy for them. This relatability is one of the reasons they can be so likable.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="caim-drakengard">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Caim (Drakengard)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-hero-before-becoming-the-villain">
  The Hero Before Becoming The Villain
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1757898195" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1757898195" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1757898195" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1757898195" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1757898195-img" id="article-gallery-1-1757898195">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1757898195" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1658711597">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Ruthless
  </li>
  <li>
   Selfish
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Violence, selfishness, and moral ambiguity — all classic traits of the anti-hero archetype. Caim has these traits in spades, driven by vengeance and bloodlust. While heroes do what they need to do to bring about peace and enact justice, Caim has little to no hesitation turning to bloodshed. He seeks to slay all those responsible for the destruction of his home.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, Caim doesn’t just see violence as a means to an end, he revels in butchering his foes. This complete lack of compassion puts him closer to a villain than many of the other entries on this list. Caim later serves as the villain of the game’s sequel. There are several entries in the Drakengard and Nier franchise, with this being one of the earliest.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ace-final-fantasy-type-0">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Ace (Final Fantasy Type-0)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="face-of-a-group-of-misled-child-soldiers">
  Face of a Group of Misled Child Soldiers
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1028066059" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1028066059" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1028066059" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1028066059" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1028066059-img" id="article-gallery-2-1028066059">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1028066059" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-50282822">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Warped Emotions
  </li>
  <li>
   Blindly Loyal
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Sometimes a hero is misled or deceived into doing bad things. This still makes them a hero, just one that is suffering and in need of getting back on the right path. However, Class Zero are a group of child soldiers that have been raised with twisted idealism instilled in their very being.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are several playable characters in the game, with Ace serving as the face of the group. While not entirely heartless, he shows a lot of moral ambiguity throughout the story. He has a constant sense of doubt about his actions, and if they are the right ones, but will blindly complete the mission regardless of what needs to be done.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="laharl-disgaea-hour-of-darkness">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Laharl (Disgaea: Hour of Darkness)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="selfish-prince-of-the-nether-realm">
  Selfish Prince of the Nether Realm
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1970550146" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1970550146" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1970550146" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1970550146" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1970550146-img" id="article-gallery-3-1970550146">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1970550146" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2138925205">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Thirst for Conquest
  </li>
  <li>
   Egotistical
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Laharl is a demon and the son of the late Overlord of the Nether Realm. Upon awakening, he decides to reclaim his birthright as the new overlord. This sets him on a journey against other demons, angels, and technologically superior humans. He has also appeared in numerous games where other characters take center stage.
 </p>
 <p>
  While he may be borderline villainous at times, he has shown to also possess good in his heart and even do the right thing. This moral ambiguity is what brings him closer to an anti-hero than an outright villain. His egotistical nature is due to a lack of emotional growth, but he slowly develops over the course of the game.
  <em>
   Disgaea: Hour of Darkness
  </em>
  is one of many PS2 games that still hold up to this very day.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ichiban-kasuga-yakuza-like-a-dragon">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Ichiban Kasuga (Yakuza: Like A Dragon)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-criminal-with-a-heart-of-gold">
  A Criminal with a Heart of Gold
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1501429290" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1501429290" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1501429290" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1501429290" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1501429290-img" id="article-gallery-4-1501429290">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1501429290" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-725607747">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Former member of the Yakuza
  </li>
  <li>
   Not bound by typical heroic morals
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  has one of the best stories in the franchise. While Ichiban’s story involves him turning over a new leaf and not killing anyone, he still has many traits that push him away from being a traditional hero. He is a member of the Japanese crime syndicate, the Yakuza. An organization that holds very strong ideals in terms of loyalty and honor but is still on the opposite side of the law.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ichiban has been able to deal out Batman levels of hurt on his enemies during street brawls. He also does not have a morally sound sense of justice, as he has no problem breaking and entering to accomplish his goals. He once again takes the protagonist role for the game's follow-up,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="velvet-crowe-tales-of-berseria">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Velvet Crowe (Tales of Berseria)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-heroic-heart-that-is-out-for-blood">
  A Heroic Heart That is Out for Blood
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-309692436" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-309692436" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-309692436" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-309692436" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-309692436-img" id="article-gallery-5-309692436">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-309692436" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1168866292">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Driven by revenge
  </li>
  <li>
   Doesn’t care about innocent lives
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Just like
  <em>
   Marvel’s
  </em>
  own Punisher, Velvet is driven by her need for revenge. She is on a journey to kill the man known as Artorius, whom she holds responsible for the death of her brother, Laphicet.
 </p>
 <p>
  She easily lets this cloud her judgement, throwing caution and the safety of those around her aside to pursue this ambition. While the usual hero will defend the innocent, Velvet cares little about the collateral damage caused by her actions and the destruction left in her wake.
 </p>
 <h2 id="therion-octopath-traveler">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Therion (Octopath Traveler)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-street-smart-thief-of-the-group">
  The Street Smart Thief of the Group
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1240671938" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1240671938" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1240671938" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1240671938" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1240671938-img" id="article-gallery-6-1240671938">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1240671938" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2076489288">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Thievius background
  </li>
  <li>
   Darkened world view
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Octopath Traveler has 8 central protagonists, with the player able to choose any of them at the start of the game. One of which is Therion, the thief. While some of the protagonist choices are heroic, some neutral, Therion is one of the darker options.
 </p>
 <p>
  He is a thief whose first mission in the game is committing burglary. He has lived a life of crime and has known many hardships. He is untrusting and verbally expresses reluctance to help someone in need.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cloud-strife-final-fantasy-7">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Cloud Strife (Final Fantasy 7)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ex-soldier-of-shinra-turned-mercenary">
  Ex-Soldier of Shinra Turned Mercenary
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-512090492" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-512090492" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-512090492" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-512090492" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-512090492-img" id="article-gallery-7-512090492">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-512090492" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1974750644">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Driven by selfish desires
  </li>
  <li>
   Lack of altruism
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Many would argue that Cloud has no place on this list. However, there are many aspects of his personality that cannot be overlooked. When the character is introduced, he has no emotional ties to the party. He is a mercenary doing a job for the money and because of his friendship with Tifa.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_54">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     I’m just here for the money.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Cloud doesn’t show compassion or sympathy to his opponents, taking to violence as if it were second nature to him. Cloud does not strive to save and protect because it is the right thing to do, but because it benefits him and those he cares about. His drive to defeat Sephiorth is due to personal matters and not because Sephiroth is a villain.
 </p>
 <h2 id="joker-persona-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Joker (Persona 5)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="imposes-justice-from-his-perspective">
  Imposes Justice from His Perspective
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-925556724" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-925556724" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-925556724" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-925556724" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-925556724-img" id="article-gallery-8-925556724">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-925556724" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1441280705">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Rebels against authority
  </li>
  <li>
   Dashing rogue persona
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Dashing Rogue archetype makes for a great anti-hero. Some good examples are someone who fights against the law because they believe it is morally just or a vigilante who works outside the law on their own terms.
 </p>
 <p>
  True to the Dashing Rogue archetype, Joker uses an abundance of charisma and useful skills throughout the game. Joker and his band of Phantom Thieves actions break numerous laws in the pursuit of accomplishing their view of justice.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Game Pass New Games for February 2025 Wish List</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-game-pass-new-games-february-2025-wish-list-civilization-elden-ring/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  After a slower start to the year,
  <strong>
   Xbox Game Pass
  </strong>
  is really starting to regain its momentum. The last week of January is set to be a pretty big one for Xbox Game Pass, with
  <em>
   Ninja Gaiden 2 Black
  </em>
  having just been shadow-dropped, and
  <em>
   Eternal Strands
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Sniper Elite: Resistance
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper 2: Starward Vector
  </em>
  all set to hit the service day-one.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  But while Xbox Game Pass is closing out January with a bang, its February line-up is still looking a little bare, with just two games currently confirmed at the time of writing.
  <em>
   Far Cry New Dawn
  </em>
  should begin the month nicely, and hopefully Obsidian's
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  will knock it out of the park on February 18, but the subscription service could use another handful of games to ensure February keeps up the pace.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="xbox-game-pass-wish-list-for-february-2025-thank-goodness-you-39-re-here">
  Xbox Game Pass Wish List for February 2025: Thank Goodness You're Here!
 </h2>
 <h3 id="release-date-available-now-on-playstation-switch-and-pc">
  Release Date: Available Now on PlayStation, Switch, and PC
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2087857359" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2087857359" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2087857359" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2087857359" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2087857359-img" id="article-gallery-1-2087857359">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2087857359" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1381671322">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite not receiving any flowers during The Game Awards,
  <em>
   Thank Goodness You're Here!
  </em>
  earned universal acclaim last year for its irreverent humor, witty writing, and good integration of gameplay mechanics and comedy. Developed by Yorkshire-based indie studio Coal Supper,
  <em>
   Thank Goodness You're Here!
  </em>
  sees players take control of a tiny traveling salesman as he platforms and slaps his way through a small Northern English town filled with absurd, colorful figures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Currently,
  <em>
   Thank Goodness You're Here!
  </em>
  isn't available on Xbox and there's no word on when/if it'll make it to the platform. But it'd be the perfect Xbox Game Pass experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="xbox-game-pass-wish-list-for-february-2025-civilization-6">
  Xbox Game Pass Wish List for February 2025: Civilization 6
 </h2>
 <h3 id="release-date-available-now">
  Release Date: Available Now
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1246342618" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1246342618" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1246342618" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1246342618" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1246342618-img" id="article-gallery-2-1246342618">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1246342618" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1182810167">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After almost nine years of waiting, the next mainline
  <em>
   Civilization
  </em>
  game is finally set to hit consoles and PC on February 11. While it's fairly unlikely
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  will come to Xbox Game Pass anytime soon, it might be an idea for Firaxis to release
  <em>
   Civilization 6
  </em>
  on Game Pass at the start of the month in an attempt to get newcomers on board just before
  <em>
   Civ 7
  </em>
  's release. Though
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  is making some big changes to the series formula,
  <em>
   Civ 6
  </em>
  would still do a good job of teaching players the general mechanics they can expect to see in the upcoming sequel.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xbox-game-pass-wish-list-for-february-2025-kingdom-come-deliverance">
  Xbox Game Pass Wish List for February 2025: Kingdom Come: Deliverance
 </h2>
 <h3 id="release-date-available-now">
  Release Date: Available Now
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-32995823" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-32995823" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-32995823" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-32995823" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-32995823-img" id="article-gallery-3-32995823">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-32995823" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1227853373">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On a similar note,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  is set to launch on February 4. While the historically accurate action-RPG series has grown quite a strong following since the first game's release in 2018,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  is still a fairly niche series in the grand scheme of the gaming world. It might be a good idea for Warhorse Studios and Deep Silver to bring the first
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  to Xbox Game Pass this month, as it could introduce the series to a wider audience, which could eventually lead to more sales of the sequel.
 </p>
 <h2 id="xbox-game-pass-wish-list-for-february-2025-elden-ring">
  Xbox Game Pass Wish List for February 2025: Elden Ring
 </h2>
 <h3 id="release-date-available-now">
  Release Date: Available Now
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1111297333" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1111297333" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1111297333" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1111297333" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1111297333-img" id="article-gallery-4-1111297333">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1111297333" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1763498787">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Probably one of the most requested Xbox Game Pass additions of the last few years, it'd be great to see
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  finally come to the subscription service three years after its initial release. While
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  has already amassed a huge following, a release on Xbox Game Pass would still open the game up to an even wider audience, which could be worthwhile in the lead-up to
  <em>
   Elden Ring Nightreign
  </em>
  's launch later this year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best PlayStation Plus Games (January 2025)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/playstation-ps-plus-premium-best-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  On June 13, 2022, Sony launched its new
  <strong>
   PlayStation Plus
  </strong>
  in North America. Split into three tiers, this model combines the previous version of PS Plus with PS Now; depending on which level someone subscribes to, they will gain access to certain services and games.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Essential ($9.99/month):
   </strong>
   This tier is the equivalent of the old PS Plus. A subscription includes online access, monthly free games, and discounts.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Extra ($14.99/month):
   </strong>
   Along with the Essential tier benefits, Extra provides access to hundreds of PS4 and PS5 games.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation Plus Premium ($17.99/month):
   </strong>
   Along with the Essential and Extra tier benefits, Premium includes a library of classic games (PS3, PS2, PSP, and PS1), trials, and cloud streaming in certain regions.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  <strong>
   PS Plus Premium
  </strong>
  has over 700 games covering more than two decades of PlayStation history. Such a huge collection can be overwhelming, and the PS Plus app does not make it very easy to browse through the library; as such, it can be useful to know this tier's highlights before investing in a subscription. Each month, Sony adds a handful of new games. While most of these are PS5 and PS4 releases, they are occasionally accompanied by a few classic titles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Let's take a look at some of the
  <strong>
   best PlayStation Plus games
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated on January 26, 2025, by Mark Sammut
   </strong>
  </em>
  :
  <em>
   PlayStation Plus Extra and Premium's January games are available now, and the lineup has quite a few good titles that can keep somebody busy for a long time. One particularly unique RPG has been added to this discussion, and its PS Plus debut came at the perfect time as the sequel, Citizen Sleeper 2, is about to launch.
  </em>
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The rankings are not based solely on a game's quality but also take into account things like their PS Plus addition date. For instance, new
     <strong>
      PS Plus games
     </strong>
     will be temporarily placed in the top spots for visibility, and PS Plus Essential games will also be highlighted first if they are mentioned.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-stanley-parable-ultra-deluxe-january-2025-ps-plus-essential">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   God Of War Ragnarok
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="kratos-39-norse-mythology-saga-comes-to-an-epic-end">
  Kratos' Norse Mythology Saga Comes To An Epic End
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-677191564" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-677191564" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-677191564" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-677191564" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-677191564-img" id="article-gallery-1-677191564">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-677191564" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-629777030">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Now, this is how to get a year started on the right note. Sure, PS Plus Essential's January 2025 selection was nothing to write home about, but Sony made up for it with a fairly stacked Extra and Premium lineup.
  <em>
   Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Atlas Fallen
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   MediEvil 2
  </em>
  are all big deals in their own right, but they exist entirely in the shadow of one game:
  <em>
   God of War Ragnarok
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  A direct sequel to 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  brings the franchise's Norse saga to an end, or at least that seems to be the case. As suggested by the title, the story revolves around the pending onset of Ragnarok, an end-of-the-world event said to coincide with the destruction of the realms and the gods. Kratos wants to stop that, but he is also on the cusp of war with Odin; in the meantime, the All-Father is trying to bring Atreus to his side.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gameplay-wise,
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  plays similar to 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  , albeit with a few tweaks and the introduction of a new weapon. The combat is still crunchy, satisfying, and intense; that said, if someone hated the system in the previous game, they likely will not get too much out of the sequel. While Atreus is still the main companion, Kratos is also aided by a few other characters, all of whom have unique abilities that are fun to use in battles. The campaign is fairly long and generally ambitious, blending character-driven moments with an epic sense of scale.
  <em>
   Ragnarok
  </em>
  also comes with Valhalla, an epilogue mode that is just all-around brilliant.
 </p>
 <h2 id="citizen-sleeper">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-gripping-sci-fi-rpg-inspired-by-tabletop-gaming">
  A Gripping Sci-Fi RPG Inspired By Tabletop Gaming
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1247639344" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1247639344" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1247639344" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1247639344" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1247639344-img" id="article-gallery-2-1247639344">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1247639344" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1791338919">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  is somewhat difficult to describe in a way that fully reflects its magic. Jump Over the Age's sci-fi RPG is undeniably inspired by tabletop gaming, to the point that dice rolls play a significant part in determining the outcome of events. Also, similar to tabletop RPGs,
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  is very much driven by player choice, and that goes beyond just big fork-in-the-road decisions found in many other narratives.
 </p>
 <p>
  A Sleeper on the run from the corporation that owns them, players must try to settle down on the Eye, a space station that houses many folks who are just trying to survive. Once there, players enter the daily grind, which means working to earn some cash, interacting with NPCs, buying resources, and trying to stay ahead of bounty hunters who are trying to collect.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  's brilliance lies in its immersion, dropping players into a fully-formed ecosystem filled with characters who have rich histories and engaging stories to tell. In a single playthrough, decisions will need to be made that promote specific relationships and hinder others, and players are mostly free to go down whichever direction they want. While not part of the survival genre, the game incorporates some aspects from that blueprint, mainly in the form of a few meters that determine the player's health.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="return-to-los-santos">
  Return To Los Santos
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-190749832" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-190749832" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-190749832" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-190749832" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-190749832-img" id="article-gallery-3-190749832">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-190749832" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-599808869">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Removed from PS Plus Extra in June 2024,
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  only stayed away for a couple of months, returning as part of the November 2024 lineup. Obviously, Rockstar's game is among the most popular projects of all time, so it is a big deal in a vacuum. That said, some of that excitement is hurt by its "leave and bring back" cycle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Still,
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  is great, and there is nothing really that can change that. The story campaign has likely been experienced by most people at this point, but the PS4 and PS5 versions available on PS Plus could be worth trying if somebody only played the original PS3 release.
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  is the ultimate time sink too.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-witcher-3-wild-hunt">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-top-contender-for-the-best-rpg-of-all-time">
  A Top-Contender For The Best RPG Of All Time
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-490601834" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-490601834" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-490601834" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-490601834" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-490601834-img" id="article-gallery-4-490601834">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-490601834" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1795805848">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For most months, picking the biggest new PS Plus Extra game is just a matter of personal taste; however, August 2024 was not one of those months. That's not meant as a criticism of games like
  <em>
   Wild Hearts
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Watch Dogs 2
  </em>
  , but rather a celebration of CD Projekt Red's RPG masterpiece.
  <em>
   The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt
  </em>
  was a landmark release for the genre, establishing a new era that emphasized storytelling, secondary content, and world-building more than ever before. While not flawless, the 2015 game is arguably timeless, at least up to this point. Hard as it is to believe,
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  has been out for nearly a decade, and its shadow continues to loom large over RPGs and even CD Projekt Red specifically.
 </p>
 <p>
  Due to its popularity and relative accessibility,
  <em>
   Wild Hunt
  </em>
  is probably not a new game for most PS Plus subscribers. Certain projects are so big that they stop being exciting additions to subscription services, simply since most people would already own them. Still, there must be a few exceptions who have never loaded up Geralt's final (full) chapter, and they can now experience the best console iteration since PS Plus Extra has both the PS5 and PS4 versions. They will find an ambitious and (at times) overwhelming open-world RPG with fully realized characters, immersive exploration, rich side quests, and a unique combat system.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="cult-of-the-lamb">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Cult Of The Lamb
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="make-friends-defeat-non-believers-and-resurrect-a-god">
  Make Friends, Defeat Non-Believers, And Resurrect A God
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1728863471" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1728863471" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1728863471" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1728863471" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1728863471-img" id="article-gallery-5-1728863471">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1728863471" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1182929155">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Is this the cutest cult simulator of all time?
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  is an unapologetically dark roguelite that follows a Lamb as they diligently work to set the stage for their god's return, a process that involves defeating four bishops, recruiting plenty of followers, and the occasional sacrifice. Roguelikes are a dime-a-dozen nowadays, and the genre can be automatically written off if someone does not see the appeal of endlessly replaying the same loop.
 </p>
 <p>
  In cases like this, roguelites can act as a fun middle-ground between the replayable nature of roguelikes and more story-driven adventures, and
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  walks this line expertly. While, for the most part, players will revisit the same four (randomly generated) dungeons to try and clear them out and take out their bosses, they will constantly be recruiting new characters for their town/cult, which will further unlock new mechanics and upgrades.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most importantly,
  <em>
   Cult of the Lamb
  </em>
  is just an absolute sinister delight that revels in macabre imagery and ideas. Along with just being very dark, the humor frequently hits the mark as it constantly pushes the envelope. Furthermore, the gameplay is rock-solid as well, be it the dungeon runs or the town-management aspect. The latter is arguably the best part of the game, as the followers have a ton of personality and evolve alongside the Lamb and cult.
 </p>
 <h2 id="timesplitters-2-and-future-perfect">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   TimeSplitters 2 And Future Perfect
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="two-all-time-classic-fps-games-that-are-great-solo-or-with-a-friend">
  Two All-Time Classic FPS Games That Are Great Solo Or With A Friend
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-96417576" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-96417576" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-96417576" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-96417576" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-96417576-img" id="article-gallery-6-96417576">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-96417576" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-117611553">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list specs">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  was the biggest PS Plus game of August 2024, an argument could be made that it was not the most exciting. In a move that was a long time coming, Free Radical Design's
  <em>
   TimeSplitters
  </em>
  trilogy finally made its way to modern systems, with all three PS2 games landing on the PS4 and PS5. These are mostly straight ports of the original versions, and they do show their age in a few ways. However, they are still fantastic console shooters that represent the genre at its early best, especially
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Both entries are great, and they also shine in somewhat different areas. In terms of pure gunplay,
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  is arguably the superior of the two games, and it still sits among the best shooters of all time. Although containing something resembling a plot, the story mode is mostly just a series of extraction-style maps, all of which are well-designed and a blast to master. As the franchise's title suggests, players travel through time, ensuring the stages have quite a bit of variety to them. Co-op is supported as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  has a far more robust and prominent story that creates a cohesive adventure rather than a loosely connected jumble of maps. While not high art, the campaign is fun in the way that a blockbuster can be. The gameplay is quite good, although it is notably less intense and frantic than
  <em>
   TimeSplitters 2
  </em>
  . Nothing wrong with that, but
  <em>
   Future Perfect
  </em>
  feels a touch less special in this area.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_47">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The first
     <em>
      TimeSplitters
     </em>
     has charm as well, but it is rightfully overshadowed by both of its sequels. To be clear, the 2000 release is worth a playthrough, as long as newcomers prepare themselves for a somewhat rough experience. Also, its gameplay is not that similar to
     <em>
      TimeSplitters 2
     </em>
     or
     <em>
      Future Perfect
     </em>
     , so do not ignore the latter if the former fails to strike a chord.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-last-of-us-remastered">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   The Last Of Us: Remastered
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="naughty-dog-39-s-definitive-masterpiece">
  Naughty Dog's Definitive Masterpiece
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1794960269" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1794960269" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1794960269" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1794960269" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1794960269-img" id="article-gallery-7-1794960269">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1794960269" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1479920065">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the PlayStation 3 had a somewhat slow start to life, the console bowed out in style. Naughty Dog's
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  is a haunting action-adventure game set in a post-apocalyptic world overrun with infected creatures. The narrative follows the grizzled Joel and the immune Ellie as they travel across the United States in search of a group rumored to be able to craft a cure.
 </p>
 <p>
  The journey is tough, brutal, and unforgettable. Both of the main characters undergo a great deal of development, particularly Joel, while
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  raises questions of morality through its ambiguous narrative. Even though PS Plus does not have the PS5 remake, the PS4 remaster of
  <em>
   The Last of Us
  </em>
  holds up well and offers a fantastic means to experience an industry-defining gaming story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="bloodborne">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Bloodborne
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fromsoftware-39-s-lovecraftian-ps4-soulslike">
  FromSoftware's Lovecraftian PS4 Soulslike
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-971402374" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-971402374" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-971402374" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-971402374" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-971402374-img" id="article-gallery-8-971402374">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-971402374" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-763346590">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  FromSoftware has cornered the hard-hitting action RPG genre through its immaculate
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  trilogy, and that looks set to continue with
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  . Out of all the studio's many great games,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  might just be FromSoftware's magnum opus.
 </p>
 <p>
  Boasting a Gothic aesthetic and reflex-based combat that demands aggression from players,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  delivers a kinetic experience that delights on a visual, auditory, and gameplay level. Naturally,
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  is not an easy game, but it is one of the most rewarding PS4 exclusives. Consequently, it is easily among the best games on PS Plus.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_60">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Both versions of
     <em>
      Demon's Souls
     </em>
     are also on PS Plus.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="celeste">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Celeste
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="story-driven-2d-platformer-with-high-skill-ceiling">
  Story-Driven 2D Platformer With High Skill Ceiling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-808061091" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-808061091" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-808061091" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-808061091" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-808061091-img" id="article-gallery-9-808061091">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-808061091" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-62630027">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Celeste
  </em>
  is a highly regarded side-scrolling indie game with a steep learning curve and an absorbing narrative. As Madeline, players climb the Celeste mountain, taking on seemingly impossible challenges and dangerous foes in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Celeste
  </em>
  's campaign guides the character and players on an emotional journey of self-discovery. This voyage is not meant to be easy, and the game makes sure that it is not. The unforgettable story is accompanied by precise gameplay and a soundtrack that ranks among the most memorable of the late 2010s.
 </p>
 <h2 id="god-of-war">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   God Of War
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-great-evolution-of-a-great-playstation-franchise">
  A Great Evolution Of A Great PlayStation Franchise
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1489916454" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1489916454" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1489916454" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1489916454" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1489916454-img" id="article-gallery-10-1489916454">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1489916454" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1489275751">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are a handful of
  <strong>
   PS Plus games
  </strong>
  that everyone with an account should play, and 2018's
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  should be at the top of that list. This "reboot" of the series sees Kratos living in a different part of the world, far from the Greecian roots players are used to seeing him in.
 </p>
 <p>
  Kratos' move to Midgard gave developers a chance to shine a spotlight on some different gods, tapping into the deep Scandinavian folklore surrounding the Norse Gods and their mythology. With RPG elements, an incredible story, breathtaking visuals, and some awesome combat mechanics,
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  is a
  <strong>
   must-play PS Plus game
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dave-the-diver">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Dave The Diver
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="genre-blend-done-really-well">
  Genre Blend Done Really Well
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-906086138" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-906086138" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-906086138" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-906086138" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-906086138-img" id="article-gallery-11-906086138">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-906086138" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-436873023">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not unheard of, Day 1 PS Plus arrivals are rare, with most months not featuring this type of release. Consequently, whenever an exception materializes, it is always a cause for celebration; more importantly,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  is an exceptional exception. Technically, Mintrocket's indie darling has been around since 2023, but it had to wait until April 16, 2024, to make its PlayStation debut, so it still counts as a Day 1 addition. When this year comes to an end,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  will almost certainly be remembered as one of the best PS Plus newcomers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Combining restaurant management with fishing, Mintrocket created a package that feels oddly unique, despite sharing similarities with many other projects. As Dave, players have two general responsibilities: catch and serve fish. The former takes up the protagonist's days, forcing him to constantly make trips into an evolving ocean in search of materials that can be used to create sushi at his restaurant. Naturally, the nights are spent running the establishment, making sure that customers are satisfied. While the management aspect is not as deep as some other titles on the market,
  <em>
   Dave the Diver
  </em>
  gives players more than enough control to make these segments engaging. However, the fishing element is the game's highlight and adds the most replay value.
 </p>
 <h2 id="animal-well">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Animal Well
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="atmospheric-metroidvania-with-great-puzzles">
  Atmospheric Metroidvania With Great Puzzles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-1772142407" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-1772142407" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-1772142407" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-1772142407" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-1772142407-img" id="article-gallery-12-1772142407">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-1772142407" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1292457647">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the
  <strong>
   best PlayStation Plus games
  </strong>
  to launch on Day 1,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  is an inspired Metroidvania with simple but effective controls. For the most part, the game sticks very close to the genre's standard formula of unbound exploration, puzzles, platforming, and the gradual reveal of new items that provide access to different areas; however, Shared Memory succeeded in stitching these well-worn pieces together to create something that feels at least somewhat fresh. A big part of this comes down to
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  's haunting aesthetic and ambient music, which combine to create a campaign oozing in atmosphere and style, making up for a lack of a conventional story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although fun, the platforming sections are quite easy, with most of the jumps providing players with plenty of room for error. However,
  <em>
   Animal Well
  </em>
  is still pretty darn difficult due to its puzzles, very open nature, and clever boss fights. The game's brainteasers often require lateral thinking (and clever use of a slink), while the latter could cause players to feel lost on occasion. That said, the in-game map is detailed and useful.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ratchet-amp-clank-rift-apart">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dependable-playstation-ip-39-s-ps5-debut">
  A Dependable PlayStation IP's PS5 Debut
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-1795177434" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-1795177434" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-1795177434" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-1795177434" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-1795177434-img" id="article-gallery-13-1795177434">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-1795177434" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-2126059012">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank: Rift Apart
  </em>
  is among the most high-profile PS5 games available on PS Plus Extra. As a console exclusive, this reveal seemed destined to transpire sooner or later, although almost two years from the game's debut had to pass for this moment to arrive.
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  might very well still be the most beautiful PS5 title on the market, a testament to Insomniac's mastery of technology and talent for creating vibrant and stunning worlds that would not look out of place in a Pixar movie.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  backs up its good looks with fantastic gameplay and an enjoyable story that allows its lovable characters to shine. Although Ratchet and his robotic companion take center stage, they are accompanied by a new playable Lombax in the form of Rivet, who also comes with her own partner. In combat, the characters largely control the same; however, the game does a great job of establishing Rivet's own identity through her personality.
 </p>
 <p>
  Ultimately,
  <em>
   Ratchet &amp; Clank
  </em>
  lives and dies on the strength of its gameplay, and
  <em>
   Rift Apart
  </em>
  is right up there with the franchise's best efforts. Ratchet and Rivet have access to a wide assortment of fun weapons, all of which serve a purpose within the campaign.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-quest-11-s-echoes-of-an-elusive-age">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Dragon Quest 11 S: Echoes Of An Elusive Age
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-classic-turn-based-jrpg-formula-that-never-goes-out-of-fashion">
  The Classic Turn-Based JRPG Formula That Never Goes Out Of Fashion
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1440592600" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1440592600" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1440592600" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1440592600" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1440592600-img" id="article-gallery-14-1440592600">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1440592600" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-777795825">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While the
  <em>
   Heroes
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Builders
  </em>
  spin-offs that are on PS Plus Extra are enjoyable,
  <em>
   Dragon Quest 11 S
  </em>
  is on a whole other level as it is one of the best JRPGs on the PS4. Set in a vibrant world brimming with style and personality,
  <em>
   DQ11
  </em>
  delivers familiar but addictive turn-based combat, lovable characters, and a simple but effective storyline.
 </p>
 <p>
  Rather than reinventing a wheel that has never been broken,
  <em>
   DQ11
  </em>
  opts to modernize mechanics and concepts that have been successful for decades. Ultimately, this game just proves that
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  is timeless. The version on PS Plus Extra expands on the vanilla release in a few neat ways too, including a 16-bit mode.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="ghost-of-tsushima-director-39-s-cut">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost Of Tsushima: Director's Cut
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="gorgeous-open-world-with-unique-historical-japanese-setting">
  Gorgeous Open-World With Unique Historical Japanese Setting
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-1239383704" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-1239383704" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-1239383704" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-1239383704" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-1239383704-img" id="article-gallery-15-1239383704">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-1239383704" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-833490852">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Insomniac's
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  ended the PS4's life as Sony's main console on a high, and the
  <em>
   Director's Cut
  </em>
  is just a better version of that already great game. Taking place during the Mongolian invasion of Japan, This samurai epic tells a tale of revenge as Jin Sakai seeks to protect Tsushima Island.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Ghost of Tsushima
  </em>
  might be the most beautiful game on PS Plus Premium, and it is not just a looker. The hack and slash combat is a great deal of fun, managing to be deep and also cinematic. Narratively, the title does not do anything too out of the ordinary, but the unique setting helps set
  <em>
   GOT
  </em>
  apart from the many other open-world games on the market.
 </p>
 <h2 id="returnal">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Returnal
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="challenging-roguelike-with-incredible-action">
  Challenging Roguelike With Incredible Action
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-539282220" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-539282220" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-539282220" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-539282220" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-539282220-img" id="article-gallery-16-539282220">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-539282220" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-2058263764">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not quite as recognizable as Naughty Dog or Insomniac, Housemarque has been producing PlayStation gold for more than a decade, and the studio was even picked up by Sony in 2021.
  <em>
   Resogun
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Alienation
  </em>
  are fantastic and easy recommendations for anyone who enjoys shoot 'em ups or top-down shooters, respectively; however, Housemarque's portfolio seemed to be all leading to one particular project:
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  . Among the first titles to truly showcase the next-generation hardware, the 2021 release is still comfortably among the best PS5 games, even if it comes with a fairly steep learning curve.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  is a roguelike third-person shooter set on a strange alien planet. As Selene, players will have to make their way through six biomes, all of which are reasonably large, filled with secrets, feature unique enemies, and culminate in spectacular boss fights. Death means returning to the start or the mid-point, depending on how far someone managed to get. As with most roguelikes, players need to find and upgrade their weapons and stats during each run, and things like parasites and artifacts add extra nuance.
 </p>
 <p>
  While overwhelming at first,
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  's gameplay will eventually feel second nature, transforming players into powerful entities capable of destroying most enemies without breaking a sweat. When this moment strikes, the game becomes even more special.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="undertale">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Undertale
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-definitive-indie-rpg">
  The Definitive Indie RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-742308610" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-742308610" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-742308610" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-742308610" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-742308610-img" id="article-gallery-17-742308610">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-742308610" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-709139427">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The 2010s was the decade of indie games, so much so that it is near impossible to select the independent scene's crowning achievement for that period. That said,
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  is undoubtedly one of the top contenders. Inspired by the
  <em>
   Mother
  </em>
  series, Toby Fox's RPG follows a child as they explore the Underground, a seemingly typical monster-filled setting for the genre. Obviously, players can decide to adhere to RPG tradition and massacre everything that moves, but they do not have to do that.
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  does not force anyone to play a certain way, and players can follow a few different routes.
 </p>
 <p>
  Blending meta-commentary with nuanced world-building and a strong narrative,
  <em>
   Undertale
  </em>
  is the full package. Anyone remotely interested in RPGs or just gaming in general should give this seminal project a try, and the game's player-driven structure means multiple playthroughs are encouraged.
 </p>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-rise">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="capcom-39-s-most-accessible-monster-hunter-that-is-still-great-for-veterans">
  Capcom's Most Accessible Monster Hunter (That Is Still Great For Veterans)
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1074302863" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1074302863" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1074302863" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1074302863" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1074302863-img" id="article-gallery-18-1074302863">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1074302863" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-1718763150">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While no longer exclusive to PlayStation consoles,
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  will always be associated with Sony's brand to an extent. In recent years, Capcom has tried to lower the barrier of entry for the franchise, crafting projects that are more accessible in their opening hours, all the while retaining most of the earlier entries' depth.
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  is the most beginner-friendly project in the series, and it comes with a short "campaign" that should teach the basics in roughly 10 hours. Just to be clear to people not familiar with
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  , finishing
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  's village quests and rolling the credits only means they have completed the tutorial. Now, they can focus on working through the Gathering Hub missions as they collect resources to craft better equipment, allowing them to take on harder quests that will reward higher-tier resources. Repeat the cycle until the end of time (or until it becomes dull).
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Rise
  </em>
  has a fairly simple formula, but it is expected to perfection. Lasting less than an hour at most (and usually considerably shorter), quests drop players in open but not massive maps which will have a few major monsters, including that mission's specific target. Players will then have to track down the enemy and slowly whack away at their health, all the while utilizing the tools at their disposal. Eventually, the fun comes in the preparation for each hunt, crafting a loadout designed to fully target a monster's weaknesses while elevating the hunter's strengths.
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  has a robust selection of weapon types as well, and they all control differently.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="remnant-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   19
  </span>
  <span>
   Remnant 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="co-op-soulslike-shooter-with-high-replay-value">
  Co-Op Soulslike Shooter With High Replay Value
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-19-49992713" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-19-49992713" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-19-49992713" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-19-49992713" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-19-49992713-img" id="article-gallery-19-49992713">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-19-49992713" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-19">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-19-slides-container-1274755703">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  PS Plus has more than a few Soulslike games, reflecting the genre's explosion in popularity over the last couple of years. In most cases, people's first exposure will be a FromSoftware project, be it
  <em>
   Dark Souls
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Elden Ring
  </em>
  , or
  <em>
   Bloodborne
  </em>
  . These are all great places to start, but if the introductory game fails to hit the mark with a new player, they might conclude that Soulslikes are just not for them and ignore any releases by other developers. While most titles take heavy inspiration from the
  <em>
   Souls
  </em>
  games, the genre has enough variety to offer genuine alternatives that do their own thing. Gunfire's
  <em>
   Remnant
  </em>
  games serve as prime examples of Soulslikes with unique identities that set them apart from their contemporaries. The first game is not available on PS Plus, but Sony's subscription service has the (arguably) superior sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  Starting with the most "obvious" distinction,
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  is predominantly a third-person shooter, although melee weapons are available as secondary options. Players steadily gain access to a respectable selection of hand and long guns, with the latter generally acting as a loadout's main option. While most guns are purchased rather than looted, enemies regularly drop mods and mutators that can be used to modify builds on the fly, providing customization without flooding the inventory.
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  's class system is also fantastic.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Remnant 2
  </em>
  is at its best when played in 3-player co-op, to the point that many of the archetypes (classes) and bosses feel tailor-made for parties rather than solo runners. The latter can pick a class that includes a dog companion, so they have an option; however, they might find the campaign to be quite difficult, even on the lowest challenge level. Still, the gameplay is fun, the build variety is solid, and the world-hopping structure is pretty awesome. The bosses are also awesome, including a few that have an impressive sense of scale.
 </p>
 <h2 id="pistol-whip">
  <span class="item-num">
   20
  </span>
  <span>
   Pistol Whip
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-virtual-reality-showcase-that-is-also-among-the-best-games-on-ps-plus-in-general">
  A Virtual Reality Showcase That Is Also Among The Best Games On PS Plus In General
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-20-411281190" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-20-411281190" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-20-411281190" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-20-411281190" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-20-411281190-img" id="article-gallery-20-411281190">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-20-411281190" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-20">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-20-slides-container-816658007">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  80% of PS Plus Premium subscribers will ignore
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  , and they might have no choice since it requires a PS VR2 headset. Consequently, one of the
  <strong>
   best PS Plus games
  </strong>
  will only be experienced by a very small group of players; however, anyone who has the required hardware should download Cloudhead's project ASAP. Sony has been steadily adding virtual reality games to the service since June 2024, and
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  is currently the top pick in this niche bracket.
 </p>
 <p>
  So, what is
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  ? Well, it is basically a modern take on the traditional on-rails shooter format, albeit with a beat thrown in for good measure. Across a series of stages, players will work their way through creative and fairly abstract levels filled with enemies that need to be shot down, all while a song plays in the background. While they don't have to shoot with the rhythm, players earn more points for doing so, and it is just satisfying to pull off.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although not necessarily the deepest game ever,
  <em>
   Pistol Whip
  </em>
  is simply fun and a great showcase of virtual reality's appeal and capabilities.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO: Best Moveset For Deoxys Attack Forme &amp; Deoxys Defense Forme</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-best-deoxys-attack-defense-forme-moveset/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Best Moveset For Deoxys Attack Forme in Pokemon GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Best Moveset For Deoxys Defense Forme in Pokemon GO
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  follows a live-service format, frequently introducing new Seasons of the game with each one following a different theme. With each new season that arrives, a variety of one-off and recurring events takes place within. These events can range from the more frequent Spotlight Hours, Community Days, and Max Mondays, to more specialized one-off events that follow certain themes or celebrations. Throughout these events, many different Pokemon are generally able to be encountered as Raid bosses, and captured by Trainers.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  During the Dual Destiny Season, both Deoxys Attack Forme and Deoxys Defense Forme have made a return to
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Raids - meaning plenty of Trainers have since obtained them and added them to their collections. Following this, many players will be looking to further utilize Deoxys Attack &amp; Deoxys Defense Forme in further battling opportunities, such as future Raids, Team GO Rocket battles, or PvP Cups and Leagues. To help trainers get their Deoxys ready for battle, a breakdown of the best moveset combinations for both the Attack Forme and Defense Forme have been outlined in the guide below.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="best-moveset-for-deoxys-attack-forme-in-pokemon-go">
  Best Moveset For Deoxys Attack Forme in Pokemon GO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="deoxys attack" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-attack.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Deoxys' Attack Forme has a maximum
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  <strong>
   CP of 2916
  </strong>
  , with a stat spread of
  <strong>
   414 ATK, 46 DEF, and 137 STA
  </strong>
  . With stats like these, Deoxys Attack Forme's strongest asset is the ability to deliver significant blows, but it also has the vulnerability of low defenses which can be exploited by the enemy.
 </p>
 <p>
  The best moveset for Deoxys Attack Forme incorporates
  <strong>
   Zen Headbutt as the Fast Move
  </strong>
  and
  <strong>
   Psycho Boost as the Charged Move
  </strong>
  . When equipped with this combination, players can expect Deoxys Attack Forme to deal
  <strong>
   8.87 damage per second
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   a total damage output of around 33.80
  </strong>
  before it faints in combat.
 </p>
 <h3 id="best-deoxys-attack-forme-moveset">
  Best Deoxys Attack Forme Moveset
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Fast Move:
   </strong>
   Zen Headbutt
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Charged Move:
   </strong>
   Psycho Boost
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="secondary-deoxys-attack-forme-moveset-options">
  Secondary Deoxys Attack Forme Moveset Options
 </h3>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Fast Move
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Charged Move
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       DPS
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       TDO
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Posion Jab
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Psycho Boost
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        8,87
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        32.4
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Zen Headbutt
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Dark Pulse
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        6.26
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        23.9
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Poison Jab
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Dark Pulse
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        5.93
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        22.6
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="best-moveset-for-deoxys-defense-forme-in-pokemon-go">
  Best Moveset For Deoxys Defense Forme in Pokemon GO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="deoxys defense" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/deoxys-defense.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In contrast to Deoxys' Attack Forme, Deoxys Defense Forme has
  <strong>
   a maximum CP of 2570
  </strong>
  , and a stat spread of
  <strong>
   144 ATK, 330 DEF, and 137 STA
  </strong>
  . This means that in comparison to its offensive formation, Deoxys Defense Forme has a more spread out balance. However, ensuring that the best possible moveset is equipped is still highly important, to ensure you reach the full potential of this monster.
 </p>
 <p>
  Deoxys Defense Forme's best moveset combination consists of Zen Headbutt for the Fast Move, and Thunderbolt for the Charged Move. With this combination, players can expect their Deoxys Defense Forme to dish out approximately
  <strong>
   7.89 damage per second
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   a total damage output of near 170.0
  </strong>
  before it is defeated in battle.
 </p>
 <h3 id="best-deoxys-defense-forme-moveset">
  Best Deoxys Defense Forme Moveset
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Fast Move:
   </strong>
   Zen Headbutt
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Charged Move:
   </strong>
   Thunderbolt
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="secondary-deoxys-defense-forme-moveset-options">
  Secondary Deoxys Defense Forme Moveset Options
 </h3>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Fast Move
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Charged Move
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       DPS
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       TDO
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Counter
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Thunderbolt
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        7.84
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        168.9
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Zen Headbutt
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Rock Slide
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        7.64
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        164.6
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Counter
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       <strong>
        Rock Slide
       </strong>
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        7.58
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
     <td>
      <ul>
       <li>
        163.4
       </li>
       <p>
       </p>
      </ul>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
