<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii’s Emotional Core Sets It Apart From Other Entries</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii-emotional-majima-noah-substories/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Majima's amnesia brings emotional depth in Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii.
     </li>
     <li>
      Majima's bond with Noah adds paternal complexity to the story.
     </li>
     <li>
      Substories like "The Symbol of the City, the Street Surfer" evoke emotional connections.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  /
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  series is known for a lot of things — like its over-the-top action, quirky humor, and bizarre side stories — but its emotional storytelling might be closer to the top of that list than anything else. Almost every entry in the series features some incredibly strong character-driven narratives, especially with protagonists like Kazuma Kiryu and Ichiban Kasuga, who undergo intense personal struggles. As such, it's no surprise that the latest entry,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
   </em>
  </strong>
  , does the same. However, this particular installment might hit a much deeper emotional level than most of the entries that came before it.
 </p>
 <p>
  Much of this emotion surrounds the character of Goro Majima, who has been portrayed in one rather consistent way throughout the entire series but is now forcing players to look at him in a completely different light. This is largely realized in his amnesia, which allows his new companion Noah to have an impact on him as well. Even
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  's substories play a major part in making the latest entry be more emotional than most that came before it. Overall, this one just hits on a different level.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii-is-the-series-39-most-emotional-entry-yet">
  Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii Is the Series' Most Emotional Entry Yet
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-362164776" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-362164776" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-362164776" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-362164776" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-362164776-img" id="article-gallery-1-362164776">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-362164776" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-381835167">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="majima-39-s-amnesia-leads-him-to-intense-introspection-in-like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii">
  Majima's Amnesia Leads Him to Intense Introspection in Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
 </h3>
 <p>
  At the heart of
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  's story is Goro Majima's amnesia, and while that trope has been known to be used in a capacity that is both predictable and cliche, it ultimately serves as a pivotal narrative device in the latest
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  game. Since Majima has lost his memory in
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  , his quest to regain that memory eventually results in profound introspection as he grapples with who he once was and who he desires to be now. Naturally, this leads to a much more emotional story than
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  might have been without the amnesia trope, as it allows both the character and players to explore Majima's true self beyond his established "Mad Dog" image.
 </p>
 <h3 id="majima-39-s-relationship-with-noah-in-like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii-is-an-emotional-highlight">
  Majima's Relationship With Noah in Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii Is an Emotional Highlight
 </h3>
 <p>
  Majima's amnesia in
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  is introduced alongside his newfound relationship with a young individual by the name of Noah Rich, who initially fills the role of guide to Majima. However, while Majima initially follows Noah as a guide on Rich Island, his relationship with the ten-year-old child eventually evolves into something more paternal in nature, which produces deeper character development in each of them as individuals and in Majima, especially, as Noah's innocence encourages Majima towards an innocence he has long been lacking. The bond the two of them share thereby heightens
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  's emotional impact, particularly when Noah's life is in danger, or he expresses his affection for Majima.
 </p>
 <h3 id="like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii-39-s-substories-can-be-quite-emotional">
  Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii's Substories Can Be Quite Emotional
 </h3>
 <p>
  It's not just
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  's main story that carries emotional weight either, as even its substories can be quite emotional. The substory called "The Symbol of the City, the Street Surfer," for example, portrays Majima's relationship with Noah in a way that not many other stories in the game do. This specific substory shows Majima and Noah role-playing as father and son in what begins as a bit of a joke but ends up actually being a heartfelt connection between the two characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  retains the series' signature blend of action and humor, its emotional depth sets it apart. Goro Majima's amnesia isn’t just a common trope but a way to reframe his character, stripping away his established persona and allowing for a more introspective exploration of his identity. His relationship with Noah enhances this shift in his character, showing Majima's capacity for genuine connection beyond his usual chaotic nature. Even the game's substories contribute to this deeper characterization, making Majima's journey feel more personal and emotional than ever before.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Theft Auto 5 Players Are Planning 'One Last Drive' Before the Release of GTA 6</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/grand-theft-auto-5-players-plan-one-last-drive-before-gta-6-release-day/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Grand Theft Auto 5 players are planning "one last drive" through San Andreas on the night before the release of Grand Theft Auto 6.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players in the community are divided about the plans, with some fans believing that Grand Theft Auto 5 is worth revisiting at any time.
     </li>
     <li>
      Many fans are frustrated about the lack of updates for Grand Theft Auto 6 and are ready to move on from GTA 5.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Grand Theft Auto 5
   </em>
  </strong>
  community has laid out plans for "one last drive" through San Andreas before the release of the long-awaited sequel,
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  players have been exploring the region in the single-player campaign and
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto Online
  </em>
  for nearly 12 years, and some fans are eager to move on to the sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  takes players back to Vice City in the state of Leonida, which is Rockstar Games' fictional version of Florida. The expectations from fans are certainly high after the critical acclaim and long-term success of
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  , and the community appears to already be preparing for their departure from San Andreas months before the launch of
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user Accomplished-Hat5373 and other players in the community are planning "one last drive" in
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  on the night before the release day of
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  . The drive follows a main highway that runs through Los Santos and Blaine County, allowing players to take in the sights and scenery of San Andreas for what could be the final time for some
  <em>
   GTA
  </em>
  fans. Although the drive commemorates
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  , many players weren't happy about Accomplished-Hat5373's Reddit post. Some players believe the drive shouldn't happen since
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  is worth revisiting after
  <em>
   GTA 6's
  </em>
  launch, and it sparked a massive debate in the community.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-5-players-are-planning-quot-one-last-drive-quot-in-los-santos-and-blaine-county-before-moving-on-to-gta-6">
  Grand Theft Auto 5 Players Are Planning "One Last Drive" in Los Santos and Blaine County Before Moving On To GTA 6
 </h2>
 <p>
  The community's last drive in
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  has some fans divided about the game's longevity, with a notable portion of the community wanting to move on from the game completely to experience what's new in
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  . The lack of news and updates regarding gameplay and other notable features of
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  has also contributed to frustrations in the community. On the other hand, other players want to revisit
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  to compare it to its successor and reminisce about the game's over-decade run of post-launch support.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1509815049" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1509815049" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1509815049" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1509815049" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1509815049-img" id="article-gallery-1-1509815049">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1509815049" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1216457935">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Before
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  releases in fall 2025,
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  will receive a major upgrade on PC to bring features and enhancements that were previously locked to the game's PS5 and Xbox Series X|S editions. There will also be added support for upscaling features like AMD's FSR 3 and Nvidia's DLSS 3, and the implementation of ray tracing and other features means that the PC version's hardware requirements will be bumped up. The new PC update will release on March 4, so
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  players on PC won't have to wait long to see what has changed.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch 2 Player Suggests Fun Way to Improve Mei's Perks</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/overwatch-2-mei-perks-speed-boost-player-idea/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mei players in Overwatch 2 want a new perk allowing her to skate on her ice for increased movement speed.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Permafrost perk increases the Ice Wall duration but also its cooldown, making it widely disliked by Mei players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Time will tell if Blizzard adjusts Mei's perks in the future.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Some Mei players in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Overwatch 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  have suggested overhauling one of her perks by allowing her to skate on the ice she creates and increase her movement speed. This discussion quickly gained popularity largely thanks to Mei players in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  feeling like the hero's minor perks are extremely one-sided, with one perk affecting her Ice Wall being widely viewed as a downgrade for the ability.
 </p>
 <p>
  The hero perk system in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  is a significant addition to the hero shooter, recently introduced in Season 15. Most perks offer relatively simple boosts to heroes' existing abilities, but even these seemingly small changes allow for completely new ways to play the game. With each hero featuring a total of four perks unique to them, players can choose one minor perk and one major perk each game to further customize their play style and dig deeper into their advantages against certain enemies. All players start with an equal advantage each game and can unlock perks during the match by performing well, with players able to choose different combinations of perks each time they jump into a game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Though some characters' perks in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  can offer bigger advantages than others, one Mei perk has enthusiasts of the character particularly unhappy. The perk is called Permafrost, and increases the duration of Ice Wall by two seconds, but also its cooldown. This essentially makes the perk detrimental both to the ability and Mei's play style in most cases, but this has opened an opportunity for some fans to discuss an interesting alternative. The idea was first put forward by the fan known as Limedoe-, and involves a replacement perk that would allow Mei to create ice on the floor with her primary fire that can then be skated on for a speed boost.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="mei-39-s-perks-in-overwatch-2-explained">
  Mei's Perks in Overwatch 2 Explained
 </h2>
 <p>
  Many other fans have gone on to discuss and expand upon the idea, with some debating the possibility of the perk also allowing teammates to speed up. Aside from the previously mentioned Permafrost perk, Mei's other minor perk in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  allows for a 30% increased primary fire range, giving her a big advantage in securing territory and keeping enemies away. When it comes to her major perks, one option allows her Cryo-Freeze ability to damage nearby enemies, with the other allowing her secondary fire to decrease enemy movement upon hits.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-592914107" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-592914107" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-592914107" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-592914107" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-592914107-img" id="article-gallery-1-592914107">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-592914107" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-130529886">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Considering how unpopular the Permafrost perk is among the Mei community, it may be a good idea for Blizzard to take a look at the climate scientist first if they ever decide to switch up certain hero perks in
  <em>
   Overwatch 2
  </em>
  . Fans of the game are still just getting accustomed to these new perks, and as ideal perk combinations and potential exploits are discovered in the future, it's very likely that the team behind the game will have to make some revisions.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Did I Drop On You!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-did-i-drop-on-you/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player lands their car on an enemy in PUBG and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3's Weapon Bosses Could Take a Page Out of FF16's Book</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-7-remake-pt-3-weapon-bosses-ff-16-eikons-good-why-how/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3 will feature the famously tough Weapon bosses.
     </li>
     <li>
      FF16's Eikons can inspire the design of the Weapons to create challenging and cinematic battles in Remake Part 3.
     </li>
     <li>
      Square Enix could potentially rework and iterate on the Weapon encounters by letting fans control Summons similar to Eikons in the final chapter.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Last year Square Enix delivered
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
   </em>
  </strong>
  , the second installment of the modern reworking of its landmark 1997 seventh numbered entry in the series. Continuing Cloud Strife and his close-knit circle of friends' tale as they reckon with Sephiroth's machinations as well as their own demons,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  was much larger in scope than 2020's
  <em>
   FF7 Remake
  </em>
  , which focused mainly on the party's journey through the city of Midgar and its surrounding area. Both titles, though, had numerous twists and turns, upending and subverting expectations regarding the original story and characters.
 </p>
 <p>
  The final entry in the updated trilogy will contain well-known later game content, like The Highwind airship. In addition, players can expect to see the Weapons, some of the famously toughest boss encounters in
  <em>
   FF7
  </em>
  and throughout the entire series. These were briefly glimpsed in
  <em>
   Rebirth
  </em>
  , and given how Square Enix so far has reimagined various aspects, it can look to combine recognizable elements of the original Weapons' designs with
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 16
  </em>
  's Eikons to make the former all the more memorable in
  <em>
   FF7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Development on
     <em>
      Final Fantasy Remake Part 3
     </em>
     is progressing smoothly according to studio officials, with a potential release in 2027.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-7-remake-part-3-39-s-weapon-boss-encounters-could-be-redesigned-to-resemble-ff16-39-s-eikons">
  Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3's Weapon Boss Encounters Could Be Redesigned to Resemble FF16's Eikons
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-879653310" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-879653310" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-879653310" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-879653310" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-879653310-img" id="article-gallery-1-879653310">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-879653310" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1079677080">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="final-fantasy-7-39-s-iconically-challenging-weapon-bosses">
  Final Fantasy 7's Iconically Challenging Weapon Bosses
 </h3>
 <p>
  Formed as Gaia's natural defenses against the threat of Jenova when it first fell onto the planet,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  's collection of Weapons consists of:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Sapphire
  </li>
  <li>
   Diamond
  </li>
  <li>
   Emerald
  </li>
  <li>
   Ruby
  </li>
  <li>
   Ultimate
  </li>
 </ul>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Emerald and Ruby Weapon were not in the original Japanese version of
     <em>
      FF7
     </em>
     , but were added to the North American and other versions.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Although all are optional fights not required to complete the story, many fans sought them out to test their mettle against these imposing foes and reap the rewards for overcoming them. It's a safe bet that
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  's Weapon bosses will present just as much of a daunting endeavor again in
  <em>
   FF7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  . And the most recent mainline entry in the franchise provides a great template for how they might be incorporated.
 </p>
 <h3 id="final-fantasy-16-39-s-epic-eikon-encounters">
  Final Fantasy 16's Epic Eikon Encounters
 </h3>
 <p>
  With a grittier medieval setting and narrative, one of the other standouts of
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 16
  </em>
  was the battles between its Eikons. Resembling kaiju-like clashes, these saw protagonist Clive Rosfield take the form of the fiery demon Ifrit and square off against other behemoths like the dragon Bahamut and the dark horseman Odin. The fights were stunning and cinematic, letting players control an extremely powerful monstrous entity while still sometimes being dwarfed by foes.
  <em>
   FF7
  </em>
  's Weapons are much like kaiju themselves, and the Eikons' presentation and design could translate well into something similar for the former in the next installment.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-final-fantasy-7-remake-part-3-could-make-its-weapon-bosses-more-like-ff16-39-s-eikons">
  How Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3 Could Make its Weapon Bosses More Like FF16's Eikons
 </h3>
 <p>
  As the culmination,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  will likely be pulling out all the stops, and this presumably will extend to the Weapons. Taking a cue from
  <em>
   FF16
  </em>
  for the grueling battles against them would be a potential direction to bring them in line with the vision the studio has displayed thus far. Of course, since none of
  <em>
   FF7
  </em>
  's party can turn into an Eikon like Clive, they couldn't be exactly the same. However, one possibility would be to design them more like the showdown with
  <em>
   FF16
  </em>
  's Titan, which mirrors
  <em>
   Shadow of the Colossus
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  's classic fights by having fans climbing up a massive enemy as they slowly whittle it down while weathering its onslaughts.
 </p>
 <p>
  Another idea would be to expand on
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7
  </em>
  's summons, perhaps by temporarily letting players directly control them to put them on a more even field, but limiting this mechanic to the Weapon encounters. This would feel more in line with
  <em>
   FF16
  </em>
  's Eikons without disrupting existing gameplay too much, but still offering a cool new twist. Whatever other surprises or major alternations
  <em>
   FF7 Remake Part 3
  </em>
  might have in store, looking to
  <em>
   FF16
  </em>
  's Eikons for the Weapons bosses would be a good way to provide fans with the best of both worlds in the third and final chapter.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
