<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy 14 Mobile's Leaked UI Can't Be Restricted to One Platform</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/final-fantasy-14-mobile-leaked-ui-ability-wheels-console-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
   </em>
  </strong>
  is, as its name suggests, a mobile game adaptation of the hit MMO
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </em>
  <em>
   Online
  </em>
  . It's a bit of an anomaly in Square Enix's portfolio, considering the publisher generally doesn't release iOS/Android versions of its modern AAA console games. There have been mainline
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  games on mobile phones before, of course, but the majority of them are ports of older entries, like the
  <em>
   FF Pixel Remasters
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
  </em>
  , on the other hand, is less like the
  <em>
   Pixel Remasters
  </em>
  and more like
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 15: Pocket Edition
  </em>
  . In other words, it's more of a new, standalone game inspired by the console title of the same name, rather than a one-to-one port.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  When
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
  </em>
  was officially announced by Square Enix and developer LightSpeed Studios in November 2024, no gameplay footage was released. The only thing that was shared was a four-minute teaser trailer that mostly showed in-game cinematics and developer commentaries. However, earlier this month, some screenshots from
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
  </em>
  's closed beta tests were leaked online, giving players their first, unofficial look at the game in action. Unsurprisingly,
  <em>
   FF14 Mobile
  </em>
  's gameplay looks very similar to that of
  <em>
   FF14
  </em>
  <em>
   Online
  </em>
  , but it seems to feature some new UI elements that make it stand out.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_2">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Square Enix dropped an official gameplay reveal trailer for
     <em>
      Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
     </em>
     on December 9, thus confirming the legitimacy of the leaks.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-14-online-should-take-a-ui-element-from-final-fantasy-14-mobile">
  Final Fantasy 14 Online Should Take a UI Element from Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-317170233" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-317170233" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-317170233" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-317170233" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-317170233-img" id="article-gallery-1-317170233">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-317170233" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1981751176">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="final-fantasy-14-mobile-uses-ability-wheels-instead-of-cross-hotbars">
  Final Fantasy 14 Mobile Uses Ability Wheels Instead of Cross Hotbars
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
  </em>
  's leaked screenshots don't really show off any combat or NPC interactions, but they do provide an in-depth look at the game's menus. The UI clearly takes a lot of inspiration from the original
  <em>
   FF14
  </em>
  ; not only does it have a minimap in the upper right corner of the screen, it also has HP and MP bars right at the very bottom. The one aspect of
  <em>
   FF14 Mobile
  </em>
  's UI that differs, however, is its hotbar layout. In the bottom right corner of the screen, there appears to be an ability wheel that players can use to access skills and perform attacks. This UI element seems to be a replacement for the cross hotbars in
  <em>
   FF14 Online
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Cross hotbars, for those who are unaware, are UI elements unique to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Online
  </em>
  that are meant to make playing with a controller easier, especially on consoles. Players can utilize the cross hotbars to access the skills they want to use during combat (and other situations), without having to sift through tons of menus. To put it bluntly, they're basically just advanced versions of shortcut keys, much like the ability wheels from
  <em>
   FF14 Mobile
  </em>
  . Each cross hotbar has 16 individual skill slots, and there are a total of 8 cross hotbars in
  <em>
   FF14 Online
  </em>
  . As such, players can technically use up to 128 slots at any given time.
 </p>
 <h3 id="ability-wheels-would-be-easier-to-use-on-a-controller-compared-to-cross-hotbars">
  Ability Wheels Would Be Easier to Use on a Controller Compared to Cross Hotbars
 </h3>
 <p>
  Although cross hotbars do convert the MMO keyboard-and-mouse experience to controllers quite well, they're still a bit finicky to use. In order to select one of the skills in these hotbars, players need to hold one of the LT or RT buttons (L1 or R1 on PlayStation) on their controllers and press either a face or D-pad button. The use of button combinations does allow for more intricate control schemes, but it makes the
  <em>
   FF14 Online
  </em>
  gameplay experience less user-friendly on consoles.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
  </em>
  's ability wheels seem like they would work far better on consoles than the cross hotbars. If players could select a skill by holding down a button and moving a thumbstick around in a certain direction, playing
  <em>
   FF14 Online
  </em>
  on a controller would probably become a lot easier.
  <strong>
  </strong>
  Therefore, Square Enix should consider adding
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 14 Mobile
   </em>
  </strong>
  's new control layout to the original
  <em>
   FF14
  </em>
  sometime in the near future, at least on current-gen consoles.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking Every Batman Arkham Game From Worst To Best</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/best-batman-arkham-games-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Today, we'll be discussing every game in the Batman Arkham Universe and seeing how they stack up against each other from worst to best.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon TCG Pocket Launches New Mass Outbreak Event</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-tcg-pocket-electric-type-mass-outbreak-event/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon TCG Pocket launched an Electric-Type mass outbreak, offering increased chances to collect specific cards.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can obtain Electric-Type Pokemon cards, like Zapdos and Pikachu, through Bonus Picks and Rare Picks.
     </li>
     <li>
      The event runs from December 26, 2024, to January 1, 2025, with missions for Wonder Hourglasses and Shop Tickets.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon TCG Pocket
   </em>
  </strong>
  has just launched its latest mass outbreak event, offering players new opportunities to collect Electric-type Pokemon cards. This time-limited event gives
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  players increased chances to get specific Pokemon cards they may be needing for their collections.
 </p>
 <p>
  For those unfamiliar,
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  is a mobile adaptation of the
  <em>
   Pokemon Trading Card Game
  </em>
  . Players can collect and battle with their favorite Pokemon cards, taking on both AI challengers and real opponents worldwide. While
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  is free to play, players can purchase various items in-game, from cosmetic elements to extra boosters to open in hopes of collecting a rare card. Less than a month after its initial release in October 30, Pokemon TCG Pocket made over $120 million, and its popularity shows no sign of slowing down.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  launched a Electric-Type mass outbreak, focusing on adding electrifying new cards to players’ decks. During the event, players will have an increased chance of encountering and obtaining Electric-type Pokemon cards, like Zapdos, Magnemite, Helioptile, or the most famous Electric-type Pokemon of them all, Pikachu. Players can get these cards through Bonus Picks and Rare Picks in the Wonder Pick pool. On top of these cards, this Electric-type Pokemon mass outbreak event comes with six missions to complete, granting Wonder Hourglasses and Shop Tickets upon completion. This mass outbreak in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  will run from December 26, 2024 to January 1, 2025.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-tcg-pocket-lighting-mass-outbreak-new-cards-and-missions">
  Pokemon TCG Pocket Lighting Mass Outbreak New Cards And Missions
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1595084670" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1595084670" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1595084670" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1595084670" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1595084670-img" id="article-gallery-1-1595084670">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1595084670" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1343852570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Here are all the missions coming with the new
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  Lighting mass outbreak and their rewards:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Wonder Pick 3 times: Wonder Hourglass x1, Shop Ticket x1
  </li>
  <li>
   Wonder Pick 5 times: Wonder Hourglass x3, Shop Ticket x3
  </li>
  <li>
   Collect 5 Electric-type cards: Wonder Hourglass x2, Shop Ticket x3
  </li>
  <li>
   Collect 10 Electric-type cards: Wonder Hourglass x3, Shop Ticket x5
  </li>
  <li>
   Collect 15 Electric-type cards: Wonder Hourglass x4, Shop Ticket x7
  </li>
  <li>
   Collect 1 Zapdos ex card: Wonder Hourglass x1, Shop Ticket x1
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Cards that can appear in the Bonus Picks:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Magnemite
  </li>
  <li>
   Helioptile
  </li>
  <li>
   Heliolisk
  </li>
  <li>
   Pincurchin
  </li>
  <li>
   Pikachu (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Electabuzz (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Joltik (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Galvantula (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Dedenne (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Lt. Surge
  </li>
  <li>
   Pack Hourglass
  </li>
  <li>
   Wonder Hourglass
  </li>
  <li>
   Shop Ticket
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Cards that can appear in the Rare Picks:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Zapdos ex
  </li>
  <li>
   Magneton
  </li>
  <li>
   Pincurchin
  </li>
  <li>
   Raichu (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Electabuzz (Mythical Island)
  </li>
  <li>
   Galvantula (Mythical Island)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This isn’t the first time
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  has held a mass outbreak event. Earlier this year,
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  introduced a Fire Pokemon-themed mass outbreak, starring the cards of pocket monsters like Moltres, Charizard, and Arcanine ex. Similar to the Electric-Type mass outbreak, the Fire event featured unique rewards, collectible cards, and a series of in-game tasks to complete.
 </p>
 <p>
  Looking ahead, fans of
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  can hope for more events and extra cards to add to their collection. A recent
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  leak revealed plans for late 2024 and early 2025, accurately teasing the Mythical Island-themed PvP event and this mass outbreak of Electric-type Pokemon. According to the leak, the next major event in
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  will take place from January 1 to 15, with a new Solo Battle event and a Blastoise promotional card. The next mass outbreak event is reportedly set for January 23, starring Psychic-type Pokemon and an exclusive Mex ex card.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon GO Players Are Sick of 'Rediscover Kanto'</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-spawn-pools-gen-1-rediscover-kanto/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players are disappointed with the ongoing dominance of Kanto Pokemon in Pokemon GO's spawn pool.
     </li>
     <li>
      The continuous presence of Gen 1 creatures hinders players from finding newer Pokemon.
     </li>
     <li>
      Complaints highlight issues with event duration, task difficulty, and lack of variety.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Several
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  players have expressed their disappointment with the Rediscover Kanto spawn pool changes, which has been around since April 2024. Some
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  fans feel like the game’s spawn system could use a serious update.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Rediscover Kanto event was introduced as part of a larger
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  update that brought various quality-of-life improvements. This update refreshed biomes, making specific Pokemon appear in settings similar to their natural habitats. Rediscover Kanto makes Generation 1 Pokemon appear more often, giving players more opportunities to catch creatures like Mankey, Machop, Rattata, or Koffing. It changed the spawn pool of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  accordingly, featuring more of these Pokemon compared to other creatures.
 </p>
 <p>
  Eight months after its debut, the Rediscover Kanto is starting to wear on
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players. While it was made as a way for players to relive nostalgic memories, it appears that the same Kanto Pokemon keep appearing, preventing players from capturing other creatures. Players on Reddit have been voicing their frustration, pointing out how the overwhelming presence of Kanto Pokemon in the wild is making it tough to find newer or more diverse Pokemon. For some, this has made gameplay feel stale, particularly for veteran players who have long completed their Pokedex for the Kanto region.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-go-players-disappointed-with-39-rediscover-kanto-39">
  Pokemon GO Players Disappointed With 'Rediscover Kanto'
 </h2>
 <p>
  This isn’t the first time Niantic has faced criticism over the spawn pool changes brought by Rediscover Kanto. Players already expressed disappointment over the heavy Gen 1 focus, with many feeling it alienated those interested in catching Pokemon from later generations. While some appreciated the accessible tasks and rewards, others argued that the event’s extended duration took away opportunities for more balanced spawn rotations. Some
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players also expressed concerns about the Rediscover Kanto Special Research tasks, finding them daunting or outright boring.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-963751482" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-963751482" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-963751482" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-963751482" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-963751482-img" id="article-gallery-1-963751482">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-963751482" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-881783028">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players have also raised concerns about other spawn-related issues, such as the lack of variety in Pokemon spawns during the holiday season. Many expected Ice-type Pokemon to dominate the event, but instead found themselves swarmed with less festive creatures, as Dark and Poison-type Pokemon dominated spawn points.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  players expressed their concerns to Niantic, as they hoped for more holiday-themed creatures and more variety in the Pokemon they can capture throughout the year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Fallout 76 Would Be Wise to Keep Visiting American East Coast Cities</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallout-76-american-east-coast-cities-focus-good-why-tv/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The success of the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  series debut on Prime Video earlier this year has managed to not only elevate the IP, but the popularity of the universe's distinct post-apocalyptic locations. Through featuring a focus on the West Coast of the United States largely unseen since Bethesda obtained the rights to the games, the well-received
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  TV show has more in common with the early days of isometric RPGs than newer titles in several ways. As
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout 76
   </em>
  </strong>
  continues its live service run, however, leaning even further into these core geographic distances might be the best way forward for building out the world for years to come.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It has primarily been set in a more natural region of West Virginia, but
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  has increasingly featured more urban locations in the vein of its predecessors as updates have expanded its scope. Given its starting point, there are several clear opportunities for treading new ground in the ruined America that has lent major cities iconic identities in previous games.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-popularity-of-the-fallout-tv-series-has-represented-a-return-to-fallout-39-s-west-coast-cities">
  The Popularity of the Fallout TV Series Has Represented a Return to Fallout's West Coast Cities
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-960920718" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-960920718" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-960920718" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-960920718" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-960920718-img" id="article-gallery-1-960920718">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-960920718" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1396534180">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="a-new-look-into-post-apocalyptic-los-angeles">
  A New Look into Post-Apocalyptic Los Angeles
 </h3>
 <p>
  Although it follows familiar concepts through having a Vault Dweller and Brotherhood of Steel member in its cast, Amazon's
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  show is set in Los Angeles, bringing a new spin to the series' Californian origins. After several games set in the East Coast changed the perception of the series, a return to a sunnier, arid environment juxtaposed with corruptions of recognizable urban landscapes has yielded a measurable spike in popularity for the Fallout franchise as a whole.
 </p>
 <h3 id="new-vegas-is-hinted-to-be-the-focus-of-the-upcoming-season-2">
  New Vegas is Hinted to Be the Focus of the Upcoming Season 2
 </h3>
 <p>
  Despite its relatively disconnected premise, the ending of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  's first season prominently showcases New Vegas as the destination of Lucy MacLean's now-estranged father. It now appears that a game location will become vital to the show's plot in the future, but the distance between this city and the current entry's surrounding area makes the development of two separate
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  pillars easily possible through one concession.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fallout-76-can-complement-the-tv-series-39-worldbuilding-with-its-own-new-cities">
  Fallout 76 Can Complement the TV Series' Worldbuilding with Its Own New Cities
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-58490351" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-58490351" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-58490351" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-58490351" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-58490351-img" id="article-gallery-2-58490351">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-58490351" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1802516983">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-opportunity-to-explore-more-of-fallout-39-s-east-coast-than-ever">
  The Opportunity to Explore More of Fallout's East Coast Than Ever
 </h3>
 <p>
  While the TV series is enriching the West Coast worldbuilding by interacting with New Vegas references,
  <em>
   76
  </em>
  has already laid a foundation for delving deeper into prominent places in the East Coast. Beyond the base game's Appalachian wilderness theming, Charleston, Pittsburgh, and even Atlantic City in
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  have all been novel outings into destroyed civilization. Between these cities and the likes of Boston and D.C. before them, this side of the country has ended up more well-documented than where
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  itself began. With pre-war lore indicating that Canada was seemingly annexed by the United States in this world, it could be argued that even places in the far north are equally fair game.
 </p>
 <p>
  By being capable of expansions that bridge the gap between the resource intensiveness of full mainline entries,
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  's ongoing content updates are theoretically able to cover more ground than any prior game in the series. It would be risky to go in a direction as ambitious as translating New York City into its framework, but there are several smaller options which could still match the precedent of American locations with name recognition. Depending on whether this direction remains closer to West Virginia or veers towards the fringes, there's a high degree of freedom. Cities of the eastern US that could fit into future
  <em>
   Fallout 76
  </em>
  updates include:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Richmond, VA
  </li>
  <li>
   Philadelphia, PA
  </li>
  <li>
   Baltimore, MA
  </li>
  <li>
   Providence, RI
  </li>
  <li>
   Savannah, GA
  </li>
  <li>
   Newark, NJ
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
