<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki Leak Reveals Upcoming Eurekas</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-eurekas-version-1-4-leak/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      According to a leak, the next set of Eurekas in Infinity Nikki will include purple, green, yellow, blue, and pink versions with a hearts and roses theme.
     </li>
     <li>
      Eurekas can enhance outfit scores and are found in dungeons.
     </li>
     <li>
      Version 1.4 of Infinity Nikki may introduce a dye system along with other features.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A recent
  <em>
   <strong>
    Infinity Nikki
   </strong>
  </em>
  leak has revealed the next set of Eurekas, likely scheduled to make their debut in the upcoming update. While clothes and accessories make up the majority of an outfit score in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  , Eurekas help give players that extra push in Styling Challenges. Each Eureka has a tag and a main attribute, and from a visual standpoint, sometimes even corresponds to an existing outfit. For example, the Dream Waltz set fits Fairytale Swan, while Afterglow was clearly made with Wishful Aurosa in mind.
 </p>
 <p>
  Eurekas in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  can be gathered from dungeons, which come in three difficulties, and are initiated by interacting with a waypoint in the game. 5-Star Eurekas come in a set of five colors when fully upgraded, with Iridescent being significantly harder to obtain. While dungeons are unlocked by progressing through the main story in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  , not every dungeon has been featured in the Realm of Eureka just yet.
 </p>
 <p>
  As discovered by pantipera, the new 5-Star Eureka will have a purple baseline version, with recolors of green, yellow, and blue. The Iridescent version is pink, while the design and theme of the set are hearts and roses. Given that the dungeons were added in chronological order, and that each new Eureka set introduced a dungeon to Realm Challenges, the next dungeon in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  will likely be Timis' Beauty Lab.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="infinity-nikki-list-of-eureka-dungeons">
  Infinity Nikki: List of Eureka Dungeons
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-45672599" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-45672599" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-45672599" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-45672599" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-45672599-img" id="article-gallery-1-45672599">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-45672599" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-294049038">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="released-dungeons">
  Released Dungeons
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Well of Fortune
  </li>
  <li>
   Dream Warehouse
  </li>
  <li>
   Ripple Wine Cellar
  </li>
  <li>
   Ghost Train
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="unreleased-dungeons">
  Unreleased Dungeons
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Timis' Beauty Lab
  </li>
  <li>
   Swordsmith Ruins
  </li>
  <li>
   Queen's Palace Ruins: Inner Court
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  As a concept, Eurekas in
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  tend to play second fiddle to the outfits, and it remains to be seen how Infold will expand on the system in the future. In theory, Eurekas can always represent some new and unique combination of attributes, tags, and colors, but there is a high likelihood that players will find them stale after the first few regions of Miraland.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the next dungeon hasn't been officially confirmed by the developers, the most likely patch to debut the new Eurekas is Version 1.4 – which will presumably introduce a dye system to
  <em>
   Infinity Nikki
  </em>
  as well. In terms of upcoming content, datamined data implies that players can expect housing, a new Ability Outfit, and even a new Wishfield zone before the end of Spring 2025. However, the exact release order for these features remains unknown. The next set of banners for Version 1.3 is slated to arrive in the second half of the month, while Version 1.4 eyes its launch on March 25, 2025.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds: How To Get Nerscylla Claws</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monster-hunter-mh-wilds-how-get-nerscylla-claws/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Defeating a monster in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </strong>
  </em>
  will allow you to carve it up and get a few materials from that monster. During a fight, you can also open wounds and target them to break them, dealing additional damage and knocking additional materials off the monster.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Each monster's body part can drop specific materials, so hunters can target specific body parts in order to get a specific material in a fight instead of relying on chance after the fight is over. Nerscylla Claws are one of the harder materials to knock off these giant spiders; here's how to do it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="where-to-find-nerscyllas-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  Where To Find Nerscyllas In Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-993439400" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-993439400" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-993439400" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-993439400" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-993439400-img" id="article-gallery-1-993439400">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-993439400" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-437159924">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Nerscyllas spawn in three different regions:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Basin
  </li>
  <li>
   Cliffs
  </li>
  <li>
   Wyveria
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While you can go to each of these regions and look for the purple spider icon on the map to try and track one down, a much easier option is optional quests.
  <strong>
   Talk to Alma and scroll down to the Optional Quests menu
  </strong>
  to find a quest that involves hunting or slaying a Nerscylla. Accepting this quest will take you to a region where a Nerscylla is and will already have your scout flies tracking it as the quest begins.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-nerscylla-claws-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  How To Get Nerscylla Claws In Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-160194867" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-160194867" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-160194867" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-160194867" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-160194867-img" id="article-gallery-2-160194867">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-160194867" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-305174306">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Nerscylla's are weak to fire and thunder attacks.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Nerscylla Claws are obtained by
  <strong>
   breaking off the large claws held to the left side of the spider's face
  </strong>
  , not to be confused with the large pincers that occasionally come out of its mouth. These claws are rock-solid and will block attacks from the front, leading to very little damage and the claw not getting knocked off.
 </p>
 <p>
  The main trick to getting Nerscylla Claws is to fight standing beneath the creature facing the left. Both claws can be attacked, but
  <strong>
   only the left claw can be broken off to get a
  </strong>
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3431889" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/03/nerscylla_claw_item_equipment_material_mhwilds_wiki_guide_85px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Nerscylla Claw
  </span>
  . Only the front of the claws reflect attacks, and if you're standing under the creature you can attack the soft limbs behind the hard section of the claws, which can also get wounded and broken. You also don't have to wound and break the claw to get a claw, as enough attacks to the softer stem of the claw will eventually break it off.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_14">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Fighting it in Area 4 of the cliffs can have it get stuck in the webbing and flail it's claw in the air unprotected.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Standing beneath the creature is also a fairly safe place to fight from, since a lot of its attacks will have it lunge forward, meaning you only have to dodge in the opposite direction it attacks to stay well outside of the danger zone. Even if you break off one claw and get a
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3431889" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/03/nerscylla_claw_item_equipment_material_mhwilds_wiki_guide_85px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Nerscylla Claw
  </span>
  , there's
  <strong>
   still a chance you can get another one by carving up the corpse after killing it
  </strong>
  , which can at least be turned into Armor Spheres if you don't need any more claws.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst Comments on GTA 6’s Potential Launch Price</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/grand-theft-auto-6-launch-price-expensive-analyst/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Grand Theft Auto 6 may have a higher price point of $100, signaling a shift in industry pricing norms.
     </li>
     <li>
      Take-Two Interactive could tie GTA 6 to GTA Online to justify the higher cost for players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite potential resistance, GTA 6 could lead to more games having higher price points if successful.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new report from the managing director of an equity research group indicates that
  <em>
   <strong>
    Grand Theft Auto 6
   </strong>
  </em>
  could potentially hit the market with a much higher price point than some might expect. With
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  expected to follow in the footsteps of its predecessors in terms of popularity and sales, Rockstar Games and parent company Take-Two Interactive may be pushing the envelope in terms of price.
 </p>
 <p>
  Certain game and console launches have been so anticipated that they've had a tangible effect on real life, with gamers going so far as to call in sick when major titles like
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  , or systems like the Nintendo Switch came out. With
  <em>
   GTA 5
  </em>
  still showing up on best seller lists all these years after its initial launch, Take-Two Interactive may be able to price
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  higher than most games and still see extreme demand.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, Michael Pachter, the managing director of Wedbush Securities' equity research (via VideoGamesChronicle), has stated that
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  could sell for $100 or even more. Pachter notes that the path for Take-Two Interactive to sell the game at this price point would be to tie it into
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto Online
  </em>
  , giving players a "large amount" of the online component's currency. Pachter points to
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  's success with
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Call of Duty Mobile
  </em>
  , stating that the integration of the online game experience with a "premium game" led to a 40% increase in sales. Take-Two Interactive, on the other hand, has notably been pushing the envelope on game prices since 2020's
  <em>
   NBA 2K21
  </em>
  release.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-706222373" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-706222373" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-706222373" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-706222373" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-706222373-img" id="article-gallery-1-706222373">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-706222373" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1735417561">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-6-could-signal-a-change-in-the-industry">
  Grand Theft Auto 6 Could Signal a Change in the Industry
 </h2>
 <p>
  Much about
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  is still being kept under wraps, so the actual price the game will go for is still up in the air. However, it seems that the game industry as a whole may be watching with bated breath to see what happens with the next
  <em>
   GTA
  </em>
  . It's been suggested that if
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto 6
  </em>
  launches for a higher price, other games may follow suit. Gamers have been resistant to price increases on video games despite inflation and the overall cost of development going up. In essence,
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  has the potential to break the glass ceiling and normalize higher prices for video games.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, there are still some caveats to this. While
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  has been very popular, not every player who enjoys the single-player story experience of
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto
  </em>
  games will want to play online with others. Additionally, it's not clear if Pacther is referring to the current
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  experience, or a new version based upon
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  . While
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  still maintains a strong playerbase and just released an improved version for PC, gamers may not be enthused about spending up to $100 to get currency in an old online game. Thus far, Rockstar Games hasn't indicated whether a new version of
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  will launch alongside
  <em>
   GTA 6
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTs Strands Hints, Tips, and Answers for Today, March 6, 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/nyt-strands-hints-tips-answers-march-6-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Strands
   </em>
  </strong>
  is here again with another grid of letters, filled to the brim with challenging hidden themed words. In order to win, you need to figure out all the themed words from one little clue and find them hidden inside the letter grid.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It's pretty easy to get stuck on this puzzle, even if you know the rules of
  <em>
   Strands
  </em>
  well. If you are looking for a hand, you can find everything from general hints to the full answer in the article below.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-nyt-games-strands-love-is-in-the-apps-368-march-6-2025">
  The NYT Games Strands Love is in the Apps #368 March 6, 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="NYT-New-York-Times-Games-Strands-March-06-2025" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nyt-new-york-times-games-strands-march-06-2025.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Strands
  </em>
  puzzle for today has the clue
  <strong>
   Love is in the Apps
  </strong>
  . It has eight things to find: the Spangram and seven themed words.
 </p>
 <h2 id="nyt-strands-hints">
  NYT Strands Hints
 </h2>
 <p>
  Searching for some spoiler-free help? If you don't like the in-game hints in this challenging puzzle game because they give too much away, you can find theme hints in the sections below that don't give away any of the answers.
 </p>
 <h3 id="general-spangram-hint-1">
  General Spangram Hint 1
 </h3>
 <h3 id="general-spangram-hint-2">
  General Spangram Hint 2
 </h3>
 <h3 id="general-spangram-hint-3">
  General Spangram Hint 3
 </h3>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="spoilers-for-today-39-s-new-york-times-strands">
  Spoilers for Today's New York Times Strands
 </h2>
 <p>
  The two sections below have a single spoiled word in each one. If you want to see a spoiler but don't feel like looking for non-themed words for an in-game hint, you should check out these two below.
 </p>
 <h3 id="spoiler-1">
  Spoiler 1
 </h3>
 <h3 id="spoiler-2">
  Spoiler 2
 </h3>
 <h2 id="the-answer-to-the-nyt-love-is-in-the-apps-strands">
  The Answer to the NYT Love is in the Apps Strands
 </h2>
 <p>
  The complete answer to this mobile puzzle game can be found in the expandable section below. Open it up to see all the themed words and their locations in the letter grid as well.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="today-39-s-strands-explained">
  Today's Strands Explained
 </h2>
 <p>
  Don't get today's puzzle? In the section below is a breakdown of how the theme, the clue, and the words all fit together and make sense in this puzzle game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Want to play? Check out the New York Times Games Strands website available on almost any device with a browser.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPO: How To Play Online With Friends</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/repo-how-play-online-friends/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Like most other co-op horror games, teamwork is the key to survival in
  <strong>
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
  </strong>
  . Plus, the more people there are, the more fun the experience is. So, this guide will tell you how to play
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  online with friends.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Since the game is in early access, many features are missing. For example, at the time of writing, players can only play with friends through invitations. As for joining strangers, you'll have to contact them through third-party resources and then add them as friends on Steam.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-play-repo-online-with-friends">
  How To Play REPO Online With Friends
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO lobby" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To start playing with friends in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  , you just need to make a few clicks in the main menu. However, first of all, you must fulfill two key conditions, namely, have the best Internet connection and also have the people you are going to play with in your
  <strong>
   Steam friends list
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  It is important to note that having the best Internet connection on your team is only a condition for the player who will host. This is because
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  does not have dedicated servers. So, if the host has network problems, other players may also encounter repeated bugs and errors. In the worst case, all players could be kicked out of the server, and you will lose your progress.
 </p>
 <p>
  As for the second condition, everything is obvious here since
  <strong>
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   uses an invite system through the Steam overlay
  </strong>
  . So, to invite other players, you need to have them on your friends list.
 </p>
 <p>
  When all the conditions are met, follow these steps to start playing
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  online with friends:
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Launch
   <em>
    REPO
   </em>
   and select the
   <strong>
    Host Game
   </strong>
   option.
  </li>
  <li>
   Next, click Yes on the notification about the need for a good internet connection.
  </li>
  <li>
   Then, create a game to join the lobby.
  </li>
  <li>
   Finally, click the Invite button to invite your friends.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <p>
  While in the lobby, players can chat with each other, as well as customize their characters. However, at the moment,
  <strong>
   customization consists only of changing the color
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="is-game-progress-saved-between-sessions-in-repo">
  Is Game Progress Saved Between Sessions In REPO?
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="REPO lobby" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/repo-friends-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As you complete your quota level by level, you will probably want to take a break. And fortunately, your progress is saved, provided that the same player is hosting. Therefore, when creating a lobby in
  <em>
   REPO
  </em>
  , instead of creating a new game, you need to
  <strong>
   join an existing one to start from the same point where you stopped
  </strong>
  in the last game session.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
