<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout's Game Awards 2024 Win Makes a New Case for an Elder Scrolls Show</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fallouts-game-awards-2024-win-elder-scrolls-show-good-proof/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Bethesda had a huge year in 2024 and it's shockingly not because of anything coming out of its gaming division. Instead, the slam dunk mainstream success of the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fallout
   </em>
  </strong>
  television show on Prime has taken the series and its studio to new heights in the public consciousness. The series was recognized at The Game Awards, and is a likely contender for a few Emmys. And though a second season is already in the works, it’s still a ways off, which leaves Bethesda and Amazon with a lot of time to plan their next follow-up moves.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A second season of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  was always going to be a no-brainer. Longtime fans and newcomers to the wasteland alike both found a lot to love in characters like Lucy, the Ghoul, and Maximus. But
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  is far from the only major franchise Bethesda has under its belt, nor is it the only of the studio's IPs begging for a television series. And despite Todd Howard’s previous reluctance to pursue it, now might be the perfect time to explore the studio’s other beloved RPG in the form of a small screen adventure.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fallout-39-s-success-on-prime-is-proof-an-elder-scrolls-show-could-work-despite-the-studio-39-s-hesitations">
  Fallout's Success on Prime is Proof an Elder Scrolls Show Could Work, Despite The Studio's Hesitations
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-203860883" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-203860883" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-203860883" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-203860883" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-203860883-img" id="article-gallery-1-203860883">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-203860883" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-734796941">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  ’s meteoric success on streaming is the perfect sign for Bethesda to finally pull the trigger on a live action
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  project. Studio head Todd Howard has said multiple times over the years that there were no plans to adopt
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  into a movie or show, but it’ll be hard to keep that stance after all the accolades for the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  show continue rolling in over the next few weeks and months.
 </p>
 <p>
  Time and again, audiences have shown that there’s a high demand for shows set in high fantasy settings. The cultural ubiquity of
  <em>
   Game of Thrones
  </em>
  , its prequel series
  <em>
   House of the Dragon
  </em>
  , and even Prime's
  <em>
   Rings of Power
  </em>
  shows that there is a clear demand for high-budget fantasy stories on television. And few fantasy settings have more potential for a long-running television show than
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  . Bethesda can strike while the iron is hot, capitalize on the success of
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  and that market desire for fantasy television, and make something truly special that will do right by existing diehards while introducing a whole new generation of fans to Tamriel.
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-can-an-elder-scrolls-show-even-be-about">
  What Can an Elder Scrolls Show Even Be About?
 </h3>
 <p>
  The best thing for an
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  show would be to take a note from
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  and create a new, smaller scale narrative within the setting using new characters. The key would be finding this show’s own Lucy MacLean: a fish out of water character who is experiencing the world alongside the viewers. From there, giving the audience a band of quirky, yet relatable party members like the Ghoul or Maximus would be ideal, and then having them set out on an adventure like any classic fantasy story.
 </p>
 <p>
  The great thing about a potential
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  show is that the sky really is the limit to what it could actually be about. The series timeline spans hundreds of years and is spread across Tamriel’s nine provinces. The hardest part would be picking a time period and running from there. The obvious first picks would be setting the show in the same general era as either
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  or
  <em>
   Oblivion
  </em>
  , the two most recent and popular titles in the series.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-would-bethesda-approach-the-elder-scrolls-as-a-tv-show">
  How Would Bethesda Approach The Elder Scrolls as a TV Show?
 </h3>
 <p>
  The fantasy world of Tamriel is massive and expansive, even more so than the wastelands formerly known as America in
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  . It would be a challenge to show so much of that world within the confines of just one story, though maybe that doesn't have to be the case. Following in the direction of shows like
  <em>
   American Horror Story
  </em>
  , each season of an
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  show could revolve around a different set of characters. This would allow the show to explore different provinces, time periods, and cultures across Tamriel’s expansive and storied history.
 </p>
 <p>
  An anthology approach might be the best way for an
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  show to proceed. Bethesda wouldn’t have to focus on expansive, multi-season narratives and could instead focus on tight, impactful stories that are woven together by the sheer fact that they all take place inside the same universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is an obvious contrast to the
  <em>
   Fallout
  </em>
  show, which will continue Lucy’s story in Season 2, but it might be just what an
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  project needs to maintain that sense of continuously finding a new adventure. Everyone who’s ever played an
  <em>
   Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  title can easily recall the sense of wonder and scale they felt when they first booted up their first game in the series; a whole wide open world full of adventure waiting at their fingertips, ready to be explored. A television or streaming show has the potential to recreate that feeling for both series veterans and folks who’ve never experienced waking up in a wagon bound for Helgen.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Best Third-Party Games On The Nintendo Switch</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/best-third-party-games-nintendo-switch/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Players looking for the best games on the Switch not made by Nintendo will find these titles hit the ball out of the park.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuthering Waves Reveals What's Coming in Version 2.0</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/wuthering-waves-version-2-update-gameplay-features-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Version 2.0 of Wuthering Waves introduces Rinascita, new gameplay features, and characters like Carlotta and Roccia.
     </li>
     <li>
      Rinascita is a festive nation with unique Echoes like Gondola and Wingray for exploration and new game modes.
     </li>
     <li>
      High expectations for the 2.0 update include new elements for the MC and leaks hinting at more features like gender switch and battle damage effects.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Wuthering Waves
   </em>
  </strong>
  has shared an official trailer and new information about the features, Echoes, and lore that are coming in Version 2.0. The update will introduce the nation of Rinascita and a plethora of new characters.
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  Version 2.0 is set for release in early 2025 and there are high expectations about the next main explorable region in Solaris-3.
 </p>
 <p>
  Known as the Land of Echoes, Rinascita is a nation marked by festivities. As previously revealed by
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  , players will experience the Carnevale, a celebration in the city of Ragunna that will set in motion the Rinascita storyline. While
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  shared a first look at Rinascita earlier in November, developer Kuro Games has recently unveiled more information about the upcoming novelties of Version 2.0.
 </p>
 <p>
  Through an official trailer,
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  has showcased different landscapes of Rinascita, as well as some interesting new gameplay features. Some new Echoes can be seen that provide new exploration abilities. The official
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  website detailed how the Gondola Echo allows players to sail Rinascita's waterways, while the Wingray Echo lets them fly at high speed rather than the usual gliding. Kuro Games also shared several new game modes coming in the 2.0 update, including Flight Challenges and Dream Patrols, special challenges with juicy rewards. The Version 2.0 trailer also revealed the in-game appearances of characters like Carlotta, Roccia, Zani, Brant, and Phoebe. Moreover, Phrolova is seen playing an important role, which may confirm her as the main antagonist for the 2.0 cycle.
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  Version 2.0 will go live on January 2, 2025, which will also mark the game's debut on PlayStation 5.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wuthering-waves-reveals-version-2-0-features">
  Wuthering Waves Reveals Version 2.0 Features
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-f39bda4926cb25f6" id="emaki-video-player-f39bda4926cb25f6">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="new-echoes">
  New Echoes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Gondola
  </li>
  <li>
   Wingray
  </li>
  <li>
   Lottie Lost
  </li>
  <li>
   Cuddle Wuddle
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="new-features-and-game-modes">
  New Features and Game Modes
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Archive of Melodies
  </li>
  <li>
   Rinascita Sonance Casket Collector
  </li>
  <li>
   Monnaie (commemorative coin)
  </li>
  <li>
   Flight Challenge
  </li>
  <li>
   Overflowing Palette
  </li>
  <li>
   Dream Patrol
  </li>
  <li>
   Tactical Hologram: Vitreum Dancer
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Kuro Games revealed that the nation of Rinascita is actually an archipelago of various independent city-states. Rinascita used to be isolated from the rest of Solaris-3 after the Lament, but the nation has recently reconnected with other regions through maritime routes. The trailer teases that the Rover arrives at Ragunna by boat. On the other hand, while developers have shared several additions in Version 2.0, earlier leaks reported that even more features are on their way. It was rumored that players would be able to switch the gender of
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ' main character in the next update. Other leaks revealed new battle damage special effects for playable characters.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1786415582" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1786415582" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1786415582" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1786415582" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1786415582-img" id="article-gallery-1-1786415582">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1786415582" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2109124123">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are high expectations for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Wuthering Waves
   </em>
  </strong>
  Version 2.0. Two new 5-star playable units, Carlotta and Roccia, have been confirmed to join the roster, and it is expected that the MC will finally obtain their third element, too. To have a headstart for Version 2.0,
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  players can get a free 5-star Echo through an official limited web event.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Like a Dragon Series Could Be Sega’s Ideal Solution for Game Preservation</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/like-a-dragon-series-sega-game-preservation-how-arcade-machines/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The Japanese publisher
  <strong>
   Sega
  </strong>
  has been around in the gaming industry longer than most of its competitors. The company was established in the 1960s and got its start making electro-mechanical arcade games for the American and Japanese markets. Since then, Sega has developed hundreds upon hundreds of video games throughout the ages, both for its consoles (during the 80s-90s) and other platforms. Taking that into consideration, it should come as no surprise that there are many Sega games that aren't exactly easily accessible on modern platforms. Some of the titles that have been published by the company have been stuck on aging hardware, while others have been outright delisted from online storefronts.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Just a few weeks ago, Sega announced that it was removing several of its retro titles from modern platforms, such as Steam and the Microsoft Store. These games, which included iconic classics like
  <em>
   Jet Set Radio
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   NiGHTS into Dreams
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Virtua Fighter 2
  </em>
  , were swiftly delisted from all platforms on December 6. Even though the majority of these games can be accessed through other means like emulation, the fact that they were removed from sale is nonetheless a major blow to game preservation efforts. If Sega isn't interested in keeping its older games available on digital storefronts, then it could at least try putting some of them in the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  games.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="sega-should-preserve-its-retro-titles-by-putting-them-into-the-like-a-dragon-games">
  Sega Should Preserve Its Retro Titles By Putting Them Into the Like a Dragon Games
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-776431478" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-776431478" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-776431478" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-776431478" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-776431478-img" id="article-gallery-1-776431478">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-776431478" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-353644900">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To the uninitiated, the concept of preserving classic Sega titles by placing them inside
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  games may sound absurd. However, for fans of the hit beat-em-up franchise, this probably won't sound that strange. After all, if there's one thing the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  series is known for having besides crazy side quests and gritty crime stories, it's arcade minigames. Ever since
  <em>
   Yakuza 2
  </em>
  , the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  games have almost always had explorable Club SEGA arcades that players can visit in-game. These virtual arcades, which are based off of their real-life counterparts in Japan, typically include emulated versions of classic Sega titles, most of which are playable inside the game.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The
     <em>
      Like a Dragon
     </em>
     franchise was known as
     <em>
      Yakuza
     </em>
     in the West, prior to 2022.
     <em>
      Like a Dragon
     </em>
     is the original Japanese name of the series.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  The early
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  titles only featured a few arcade minigames, but recent entries in the series have had many more of them. 2020's
  <em>
   Yakuza: Like a Dragon
  </em>
  , for instance, includes six retro Sega games, such as
  <em>
   Super Hang-On
  </em>
  from 1987 and
  <em>
   Space Harrier
  </em>
  from 1986. Even the 2023 spin-off entry,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name
  </em>
  , contains a few classic gems, like 1996's
  <em>
   Sonic the Fighters
  </em>
  and 1998's
  <em>
   Fighting Vipers 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-ocean-hunter-is-being-preserved-on-modern-platforms-thanks-to-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii">
  The Ocean Hunter is Being Preserved on Modern Platforms Thanks to Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
 </h3>
 <p>
  The next installment in the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  series,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  , is going to continue the franchise's tradition of featuring Club SEGA arcades. Interestingly, though, one of the retro titles that's going to be included in this upcoming hack-and-slash game is 1998's
  <em>
   The Ocean Hunter
  </em>
  . This Sega-developed rail shooter was released exclusively in arcades across the world, but it was never ported to any other platform. Therefore,
  <em>
   The Ocean Hunter
  </em>
  's appearance in
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  will be the first time the game will become playable on something other than a 30-year-old arcade cabinet.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sega should repeat what it did with
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  by bringing other retro games to modern platforms in future
  <em>
   Like A Dragon
  </em>
  installments. While most classic titles from the publisher are better off being sold individually on digital storefronts, there are some niche games that are probably best suited as minigames in the
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  franchise. A 90s rail shooter like
  <em>
   The Ocean Hunter
  </em>
  , for example, is probably not something that most people would be interested in buying. However, by adding it to a
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  title, the game not only gets preserved on current-gen platforms, it also becomes a selling point for a new entry in the hit
  <strong>
   Sega
  </strong>
  series.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenless Zone Zero - TGA 2024 Special Video</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/zenless-zone-zero-tga-2024-special-video/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  During The Game Awards 2024, HoYoverse reveals the next two characters coming to Zenless Zone Zero: Astra Yao and Evelyn Chevalier.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
