<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: How To Open The Secret Room at Outlaw Oasis</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-outlaw-oasis-secret-room-location-how-to-open/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  Lawless ramps up the action for Chapter 6, launching players onto a revamped island filled with unique locations where they can pull off their own heists. Breaking into Armored Transports, stealing from vaults, and acquiring unique Medallions are just a few of the activities players can engage in this season, each increasing their chances of securing a Victory Royale.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The most contested areas of the map right now seem to be vault locations, as each offers the potential to obtain Legendary and Mythic weapons through specific strategies. However, there are also hidden rooms scattered across the island in less congested areas, each offering exclusive rewards. One such hidden location is
  <strong>
   the secret room in Outlaw Oasis
  </strong>
  , which requires players to solve a puzzle to gain entry.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-open-the-outlaw-oasis-secret-room-in-fortnite">
  How To Open The Outlaw Oasis Secret Room in Fortnite
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-141db4d7abca9999" id="emaki-video-player-141db4d7abca9999">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There is a hidden secret room within Outlaw Oasis, one that allows players to
  <strong>
   get their hands on high-tier loot
  </strong>
  right from the get-go without much effort at all. This secret room can be accessed in all playlists, both Zero Build and Battle Royale, and can be opened both solo or as part of a squad.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-703508793" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-703508793" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-703508793" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-703508793" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-703508793-img" id="article-gallery-1-703508793">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-703508793" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1228300048">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To find the Outlaw Oasis secret room, players must
  <strong>
   head down to the building on the far south side
  </strong>
  of the POI. Here, they will find three golden wolf statues, each of which can be interacted with to turn them. The key here is to
  <strong>
   turn all the statues
  </strong>
  so that they are all
  <strong>
   facing toward the north side of Outlaw Oasis.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-72723017" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-72723017" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-72723017" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-72723017" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-72723017-img" id="article-gallery-2-72723017">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-72723017" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-896020802">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If done successfully, all the gold statues will begin to glow. A
  <strong>
   trapdoor hidden underneath the carpet
  </strong>
  just in front of the statues will also open up, taking players down to a hidden room underneath the building.
 </p>
 <p>
  Within this hidden room, players can
  <strong>
   find several Chests, a Rare Chest, and even Gold Bars
  </strong>
  to stock up on. Once the room has been looted, players can either exit the room through the same trap door or take a port-a-potty out of the secret room.
 </p>
 <p>
  While players will have a good chance of acquiring high-tier loot within this secret room, this will not always be the case, as
  <strong>
   occasionally the room will be empty.
  </strong>
  Regardless, it serves as an excellent place to get stocked up on some of the best weapons in the game—along with offering the potential to grab one of the season's roster of unique Boons—without requiring all too much effort.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk 2077's Sequel Can Make Good on One Chekhov's Gun Hidden in a Data Shard</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cyberpunk-2077-sequel-data-shard-netwatch-faction-project-orion/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Cyberpunk 2077
   </em>
  </strong>
  is filled to the brim with fascinating lore that makes Night City feel even more alive. One of the best ways to learn more about the history of Night City and the outside world is through Data Shards. These collectible digital items contain everything, from images and texts to audio and maps. In
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  , these Data Shards are hidden all throughout the game, and one in particular deserves to be revisited in its sequel,
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players can stumble upon a Data Shard that reads, "Looking for a career change? Join NetWatch!" The rest of the Data Shard reads like a run-of-the-mill job recruit ad that explains what is to be expected of a NetWatch agent.
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  is bound to improve upon its predecessor, and one fascinating route would be to allow players to actually answer the call of this Data Shard.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077-39-s-netwatch-data-shard-could-open-the-door-to-a-fascinating-life-path">
  Cyberpunk 2077's NetWatch Data Shard Could Open the Door to a Fascinating Life Path
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2074742853" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2074742853" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2074742853" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2074742853" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2074742853-img" id="article-gallery-1-2074742853">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2074742853" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-212616761">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="netwatch-data-shard-locations-in-cyberpunk-2077">
  NetWatch Data Shard Locations in Cyberpunk 2077
 </h3>
 <ul>
  <li>
   V's desk, located on floor 33 inside Arasaka Tower. This is specifically during the Corpo-Rat prologue.
  </li>
  <li>
   The upstairs of El Coyote Cojo
  </li>
  <li>
   On the bar counter inside The Afterlife
  </li>
  <li>
   In Yuca during the game's Nomad prologue
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  It's an intriguing piece of lore to come across in the game, but it would be even more exciting if V was able to follow up on the Data Shard's offer. Whether
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  revisits V as a protagonist or features a brand-new lead, being given the opportunity to become a NetWatch agent could be a compelling route for a life path.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     NetWatch's main goal is to keep others from entering the Blackwall, which keeps AIs from breaking out.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  One of the biggest criticisms of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  at launch is that the game's teased life paths were lackluster. The RPG has come a long way since its notorious launch, but the life path concept is still merely scratching the surface. No matter which of the three options a player chooses for V, the only real difference it makes is with the story's prologue. If CD Projekt Red wants to right the wrongs of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's launch, giving
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  more dynamic life paths would be a great start.
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's three options, Nomad, Street Kid, and Corpo could make a return, but adding more options into the mix is a strong way to elevate the game's role-playing.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_10">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Other life paths that would be fascinating for
     <em>
      Project Orion
     </em>
     to explore would be Ripperdocs, NCPD, and Rockers.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="becoming-a-netwatch-agent-could-offer-a-deep-dive-into-the-organization">
  Becoming a NetWatch Agent Could Offer a Deep Dive Into the Organization
 </h3>
 <p>
  Each faction and organization featured throughout Night City helps breathe life into the setting, and NetWatch is one of the franchise's more compelling groups. The role of NetWatch is fascinating, and showcasing more of the cyber policing team sets the stage for
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  to explore compelling moral dilemmas regarding internet safety and censorship. Depending on one's views, NetWatch is either doing a service or keeping the public from valuable information, and getting to actively take part in that role would be a fun role-playing route.
 </p>
 <h3 id="project-orion-can-take-night-city-to-greater-heights">
  Project Orion Can Take Night City to Greater Heights
 </h3>
 <p>
  Nearly five years later,
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  has redeemed itself, especially after the release of the
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  DLC. Now that CD Projekt Red has the experience of a rocky launch to learn from, it will be interesting to see how the developer makes improvements with
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_15">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Looking for a career change? Join NetWatch!
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  is likely several years away at this point, but expanding the franchise's world through more dynamic life paths and factions is probably one of the best ways for the sequel to kick things up a notch. The NetWatch Data Shard could simply be a fun way to expand the game's lore, but it's also a thread worth following further.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket League Season 17 Gets Extension</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/rocket-league-season-17-extension-s18-teaser-crossbar-ping/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Rocket League Season 17 has been extended to March 14.
     </li>
     <li>
      The season was initially planned to conclude nine days earlier.
     </li>
     <li>
      Rocket League Season 18 will start with a "crossbar ping," Psyonix said, without elaborating on what this means.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Rocket League
   </em>
  </strong>
  Season 17 has been extended and will now end on March 14, Psyonix has revealed. The company's extension announcement was accompanied by a brief teaser hinting at what's coming as part of
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  's next seasonal content drop.
 </p>
 <p>
  Season 17 officially kicked off on December 4, 2024. It introduced a new Rocket Pass vehicle, Shokunin, as well as the Neo Tokyo (Arcade) Arena Variant, among other novelties. A few limited-time
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  events were also offered during the ongoing season, including the Free Play Party and Frosty Fest 2024. As per usual, Season 17 was planned to run for three months, ending on March 5.
 </p>
 <p>
  Psyonix has now revised this schedule, announcing that the ongoing
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  season has been extended by nine days, until March 14. Season 18 has hence also been delayed until that date. Since March 14 happens to fall on a Friday, this postponement will result in a rare instance of a new season not starting on a Wednesday.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="psyonix-teases-39-crossbar-ping-39-for-rocket-league-season-18">
  Psyonix Teases 'Crossbar Ping' for Rocket League Season 18
 </h2>
 <p>
  Psyonix did not offer an official reason for the delay, but it did announce the extension alongside a brief teaser stating that Season 18 will begin with a "crossbar ping." Whether this statement is meant to be taken literally—implying the next batch of
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  seasonal content will include a new audio effect—is unclear. Based on the social media reactions to this announcement, some fans think there's more to the teaser than that, speculating that the developer could be hinting at addressing some of the buggy physics that occasionally come into play when the ball hits a crossbar.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1392813902" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1392813902" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1392813902" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1392813902" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1392813902-img" id="article-gallery-1-1392813902">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1392813902" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-228885016">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="what-39-s-coming-in-rocket-league-season-18">
  What's Coming in Rocket League Season 18?
 </h3>
 <p>
  Psyonix hasn't yet officially detailed Season 18, so the "crossbar ping" teaser is the only clue about the upcoming content drop as of this writing. The developer typically announces new seasons around 10 days before they start, so it was expected to do so in the final week of February before Season 18 was pushed back to mid-March 2025. Following the postponement, the new update is expected to be detailed on or around March 4.
 </p>
 <p>
  Based on Psyonix's long-established track record, Season 18 is all but certain to debut a new
  <em>
   Rocket League
  </em>
  Rocket Pass with a unique theme, new car body, and multiple other cosmetics. An additional Arena variant and limited-time modes and events should also be part of the package, together with another competitive playlist rotation, community spotlight, and possibly some new collaborations.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elder Scrolls 6 Taking Place in Hammerfell Could Be a Boon for One Unique TES Race</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/elder-scrolls-6-hammerfell-sloads-eso-necromancy-lore/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  includes many different races beyond the playable ones, and
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Elder Scrolls 6
   </strong>
  </em>
  has the chance to showcase more of them in the mainline series. One such example are the Sloads, one of the oldest races who haven't yet featured in any of the main
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  games yet, but could have a part to play if
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  takes part in Hammerfell.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the most famous Sloads, N'Gasta, who was an ally of Mannimarco, lived on an island close to Stros M'kai, placing the Sloads in proximity to Hammerfell. The Sloads appeared in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls Online
  </em>
  as antagonists, and in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  lore, they once wiped out half of Tamriel's population. With
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  possibly being the first game set in proximity to the Sloads in such a long time, it may be time for them to appear in a mainline game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="justifying-the-appearance-of-sloads-in-the-elder-scrolls-6">
  Justifying the Appearance of Sloads in The Elder Scrolls 6
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1020012765" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1020012765" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1020012765" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1020012765" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1020012765-img" id="article-gallery-1-1020012765">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1020012765" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-481298232">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Sloads are an odd-looking, grotesque race that are fiercely intelligent. So far, they've been mentioned in most of
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  games, but have only actually appeared in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls: Redguard
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls Online
  </em>
  . Despite the fact that they appear to be a "joke" race, with the appearance of giant slugs crossed with toads, Sloads in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  lore are deep thinkers and are experts in necromancy. This is an area of magic that is severely limited in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  and could use the development that Sloads could potentially bring.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the reasons Sloads haven't appeared in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  mainline games yet is because their homeland is not on Tamriel's mainland. Instead, Sloads come from an island located in the Abecean Sea, which is located on the western side of Tamriel, alongside the provinces of the Summerset Isles, Cyrodiil, and Hammerfell. This proximity to Hammerfell, including Stros M'Kai, is one of the reasons why the Sloads may make an appearance in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  if it's set in Hammerfell, particularly if Stros M'Kai is included.
 </p>
 <h2 id="implementing-sloads-in-the-elder-scrolls-6">
  Implementing Sloads In The Elder Scrolls 6
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1975981255" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1975981255" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1975981255" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1975981255" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1975981255-img" id="article-gallery-2-1975981255">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1975981255" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1184076245">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Culturally, Sloads focus heavily on both seafaring and magic, particularly necromancy. Sloads are also proficient in teleportation spells due to their limited mobility on land. Both teleportation and necromancy magic were underdeveloped in
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  , and including Sloads would be a chance to develop them under the school of conjuration. As masters of necromancy, it's unsurprising that, despite their relative isolation, they're also associated with one of the most famous necromancers in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls
  </em>
  , Mannimarco.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Sloads' isolation may be partially due to their troubled history with the rest of Tamriel. Aside from the general distaste most of Tamriel has towards necromancy, the Sloads were responsible for engineering and unleashing a plague on Tamriel in the First Era. Known as the Thrassian Plague, it resulted in the deaths of half of Tamriel's population.
 </p>
 <p>
  In response, Tamriel's forces sunk Thras, the Sload homeland, into the ocean using magic. Thras and the Sloads eventually recovered in time, but the two groups haven't been friendly since. This animosity could be a source of tension in
  <em>
   The Elder Scrolls 6
  </em>
  , particularly along the eastern coastline of Hammerfell. Despite this, player characters could also perhaps learn necromancy and teleportation from a couple of friendly or neutral Sloads, which would add variety while still being true to the lore.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Warcraft: The War Within Was Built for Undermine</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/world-warcraft-wow-war-within-update-undermine-good-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  After players have spent months exploring the brand-new zones of Khaz Algar, all eyes are on what the next chapter of
  <strong>
   <em>
    World of Warcraft: The War Within
   </em>
  </strong>
  will entail. Dubbed Undermine(d), this first major patch is set to bring players to the capital of the Goblin Trade Empire for the very first time. Alongside that will also come a plethora of new stories, mechanics, dungeons, and an exciting new raid for players to enjoy. While
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  players are excited to finally explore Undermine, some may be wondering why it took so long to be introduced.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Goblins have been playable in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  ever since 2010's Cataclysm expansion and have been a part of the lore for even longer. However, players have never really gotten to explore their capital city until now. Game Rant recently had the chance to talk to associate game directors Morgan Day and Katrina Yepiz about just why that is. They not only shared what made The War Within the perfect expansion to finally delve into Undermine, but also all the other goblin-focused content that players can expect when they go exploring.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-war-within-was-the-perfect-time-to-explore-goblin-culture">
  The War WIthin Was the Perfect Time to Explore Goblin Culture
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-641821107" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-641821107" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-641821107" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-641821107" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-641821107-img" id="article-gallery-1-641821107">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-641821107" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-454688719">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="undermine-plays-right-into-the-theme-of-the-war-within">
  Undermine Plays Right Into the Theme of The War Within
 </h3>
 <p>
  The capital city of Undermine has been talked about in
  <em>
   World of Warcraft
  </em>
  for what feels like forever. So many goblins have mentioned where they hailed from, players have met various characters that have called it home, and it has been a very important part of the lore. Because of that, it seemed strange that players had not really gotten to explore it. Luckily, Yepiz said Blizzard felt like now was the best time to finally deliver that.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "I think the reason mainly now is that we have a whole storyline that's featured within the crust of our planet. It's been a zone that's been talked about in the game for a very long time, and it just kind of felt like the perfect time to introduce another underground zone in the underground expansion."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  The entire theme of The War Within is around letting players delve deep into Azeroth. This has introduced them to brand-new entirely underground zones, the likes of which
  <em>
   WoW
  </em>
  has not really dealt with before. So, it only seemed natural for the underground capital of Undermine to finally enter the spotlight. And because it is finally being shown off, players can also expect a whole host of goblin-filled adventures throughout Undermine(d).
 </p>
 <h3 id="undermine-d-also-puts-a-goblin-spin-on-the-entire-expansion">
  Undermine(d) Also Puts a Goblin Spin on the Entire Expansion
 </h3>
 <p>
  Not only will Undermine(d) give players access to the capital of the Goblin Trade Empire, but the goblins are also going to affect the zones that have already been introduced. Right now, players can find various goblin areas and NPC quest givers throughout the Ringing Deeps. If they listen closely, they may also be able to hear goblin jackhammers or mining within the very walls themselves. According to Day, this is because things are about to get a lot bigger down there.
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "We knew we wanted to have a goblin drill kind of ram through a wall and see a new space open up behind the Ringing Deeps. Because not only is there the Undermine city space that we are adding with this update, there's an expansion of the Ringing Deeps as well. There is a whole area down there where there's tons of black blood being harvested by the goblins, which we've seen Alleria making use of that stuff. So she's up to no good again here."
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  While the primary focus of the expansion is on the city of Undermine, players can expect even more goblin adventures across The War Within's zones. Because the expansion is focused on that subterranean world, Blizzard knew that the goblins would need to be at the forefront at some point, and now it seems like they will be. Plus, there may even be more secrets in store for goblin fans as the content continues to roll out.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
