<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Path of Exile 2 Shouldn't Sleep on One Clear Endgame Addition</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/path-of-exile-2-poe2-trials-sekhemas-chaos-atlas-passive-skill-tree-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Path of Exile 2 has various endgame farming methods like mapping for Divine Orbs.
     </li>
     <li>
      Adding Atlas Passive Trees for Trials of Sekhemas and Chaos could improve farming.
     </li>
     <li>
      Trials of Chaos could benefit from Atlas Passive Skills to control boss fights and timers.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are various ways for players to enjoy the endgame section of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Path of Exile 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , as the game includes multiple returning mechanics from its predecessor as well as some notable differences in how its Atlas system works. Mapping is still one of the best methods to get Divine Orbs in
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  , as juiced maps with many affixes can yield great rewards, especially if players also use Tablets on Towers to further make some map nodes as affix-rich as possible. Still, there are other interesting ways to farm currency in the game, and two of them should get a much-needed addition further down the line.
 </p>
 <p>
  A great way to optimize farming Waystones in
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  is not only to clear "unwanted" map nodes on the Atlas and then use Tablets on nearby Towers, but to make sure one has as many Atlas Passive Skills allocated as possible. These can provide major boons, like increased Item Rarity and Quantity or increased modifiers on Rare monsters, which all make farming more worthwhile. Considering that Trials of the Sekhemas and Trials of Chaos both can yield some valuable loot when farmed consistently, it would only make sense to add Atlas Passive Trees for them too.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="path-of-exile-2-should-add-atlas-trees-for-trials-of-the-sekhemas-and-trials-of-chaos">
  Path of Exile 2 Should Add Atlas Trees For Trials of the Sekhemas and Trials of Chaos
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1846430244" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1846430244" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1846430244" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1846430244" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1846430244-img" id="article-gallery-1-1846430244">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1846430244" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1357806646">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are multiple Atlas Passive Trees in
  <em>
   Path of Exile
  </em>
  2 so far. These include:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Atlas Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
  <li>
   Breach Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
  <li>
   Expedition Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
  <li>
   Map Boss Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
  <li>
   Delirium Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
  <li>
   Ritual Passive Skill Tree
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Each of these trees includes multiple ways to customize the farming experience for players, which adds another layer to the overall customization-focused approach of
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  as well as makes the process more interesting. These Skill Trees are not present for Trials of Chaos or Trials of the Sekhemas in
  <em>
   PoE 2
  </em>
  , but there are multiple ways to add them.
 </p>
 <h3 id="trials-of-the-sekhemas-could-be-greater-with-atlas-passive-skills">
  Trials of the Sekhemas Could Be Greater With Atlas Passive Skills
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Path of Exile 2 Trial of the Sekhemas" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-the-sekhemas.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For example, a dedicated Atlas Passive Tree for Trials of the Sekhemas could have nodes that increase the amount of Sacred Water found when killing monsters or nodes that increase the effects of both Unique and non-Unique Relics, maybe even in separated branches. Another option could be to add a node that allows players to choose between two Boons or Afflictions when a random one is gained, slightly reducing the randomness of it. There could also be nodes focused on giving players a higher chance to get Bronze, Silver, or Gold Keys when killing enemies or a higher chance for Relics of all rarities to drop. However, a great way to improve rewards could be to make chests in Trials of the Sekhemas roll two different sets of loot and choose the better one.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-path-of-exile-2-passive-skills-for-trials-of-chaos-would-improve-farming">
  How Path of Exile 2 Passive Skills For Trials of Chaos Would Improve Farming
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="path of exile 2 trial of chaos gameplay" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/path-of-exile-2-trial-of-chaos-gameplay.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Likewise,
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  's Trials of Chaos could use some Atlas Passive Skills to make farming this activity more worthwhile. An example could be to allow players to choose which boss they should fight among two or three options, thus also giving them some kind of agency regarding which Soul Cores they obtain at the end.
 </p>
 <p>
  Much like in Trials of the Sekhemas, there could be nodes that allow players to make the overall experience either easier in order to complete it more reliably and quickly or ways to make it more challenging but with better loot. Something that can be rather frustrating in the endgame when tackling Trials of Chaos is that the timed rooms take much longer than intended to complete because players may defeat hordes of monsters easily, but still have to wait for the timer. As such, nodes to make the timer tick faster or have the next wave of enemies spawn as soon as the previous is wiped would be extremely helpful.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are many ways for
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  to improve its endgame, and adding more Passive Skill Trees for all its activities would be a welcome addition. For example, Trials of Chaos can easily allow players to farm a lot of currency and useful items, but in their current state, it may still be better to run Waystones.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diablo 4 Trick Makes One Witchcraft Power Even More Powerful</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/diablo-4-witchcraft-power-souls-harvest-damage-buff-trick/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Souls Harvest in Diablo 4 can be made 20% more powerful by strategically using it on larger groups of mobs.
     </li>
     <li>
      Diablo 4's seventh season offers players 25 witchcraft powers to choose from, enhancing gameplay.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can activate Souls Harvest's powerful effect by attacking multiple targets, boosting main stats by up to 20%.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <strong>
   <em>
    Diablo 4
   </em>
  </strong>
  player has discovered a way to make the witchcraft power Souls Harvest even more powerful. Blizzard introduces a new mechanic to
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  players every season. Similar to what happened in the game's second season, players can now explore the powers of witchcraft.
 </p>
 <p>
  The seventh
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  season introduced four schools of witchcraft powers - Eldritch, Psyche, Growth &amp; Decay, and Lost Powers. Each of these schools has seven abilities, except for the Lost Powers, of which there are four, totaling 25 powers from which players can choose six - five normal and one Unique. These abilities give the player various attributes, including the power to summon explosive frogs in
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  . To learn a witchcraft power, players must look for the altar of the respective school in the Tree of Whispers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Streamer Rob2628 has shared another
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  trick, and this time, he makes the witchcraft power Souls Harvest even more powerful. In the video, he explains that the Souls Harvest effect can be manipulated, increasing the damage buff provided by the ability by 20% when attacking groups of larger mobs. Then he demonstrates the trick, and at one point the marker shows impressive numbers, some reaching 259 million and 34.8 billion damage. Souls Harvest is considered one of
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  's most powerful witchcraft powers, improving the character's main stat by 1% for 15 seconds. To trigger the effect, the player needs to use a skill with a cooldown.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-diablo-4-players-can-make-souls-harvest-even-more-powerful">
  How Diablo 4 Players Can Make Souls Harvest Even More Powerful
 </h2>
 <p>
  The catch is that Souls Harvest's effect can be activated using single-target skills, skills that deal damage in an area or to multiple targets. Therefore, by attacking numerous targets with Souls Harvest equipped, players can activate its effect multiple times, improving the main stat by up to 20%. In the video, Rob2628 says that he believes that this
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  witchcraft power is intended to provide a 5% or 6% buff when using most abilities. However, if the gamer plays strategically, this buff can go to 15%, even 20%.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1301516416" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1301516416" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1301516416" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1301516416" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1301516416-img" id="article-gallery-1-1301516416">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1301516416" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-737603516">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The seventh
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  season began on January 21, and in just a few days other unusual discoveries were made by players. In another video, the streamer shared a broken
  <em>
   Diablo 4
  </em>
  Druid build that quickly went viral. As for the Souls Harvest trick, some players believe that it will be patched, and others that it won't because it's not an exploit. Blizzard has yet to address the issue and reveal whether it will maintain this interaction or not.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Players Are Frustrated by One Feature</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-frustrated-feature-spa/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players in Stardew Valley are frustrated by slow walking speed in the spa, leading many to avoid it.
     </li>
     <li>
      The slow walking speed in the spa takes up valuable in-game time, making it inconvenient.
     </li>
     <li>
      Despite the convenience of the spa, many players ignore it past early gameplay due to time constraints.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  players are frustrated by the walking speed in the game's spa. The frustration seems to be a widespread one among
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  players, with many noting that the issue is annoying enough that they avoid the area outright.
 </p>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , players can recover the energy they expend in a variety of ways. Most players rely upon food, which can restore energy and health, while others prefer to tuck into bed early and simply go to the next day. The
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  spa is also an option for restoring energy, but it would seem that few use it due to this frustration.
 </p>
 <p>
  Reddit user Prim_rose1999 pointed out how incredibly annoyed they are by the slow walking speed in the spa. When a player enters the spa, they can no longer run around like they do in town, and are instead forced to slowly walk through the game's dressing area leading to the pool, and then in the pool itself. Thankfully, the spa is only rarely used in the plot of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , so players can avoid it for the most part. However, that also means depriving one's self of a potential resource.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-players-share-spa-disappointment">
  Stardew Valley Players Share Spa Disappointment
 </h2>
 <p>
  A few players have pointed out that in real life, it's common practice to disallow running so that nobody slips on the wet ground and hurts themselves. However, others have pointed out that there are plenty of ways that
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  doesn't emulate real life, beginning with how easy it is to raise crops. As such, the realism here isn't really necessary.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-145103621" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-145103621" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-145103621" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-145103621" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-145103621-img" id="article-gallery-1-145103621">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-145103621" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-252754083">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the biggest issues the walking speed in the spa presents is that it takes up time, which is limited. While players can continue their
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  playthroughs for as long as they like, each day has a set amount of time in it, and the player must be tucked back in bed in time or risk energy and inventory penalties. One player noted that in order to get fully restored via the spa, it takes about an hour and a half of in-game time. That's a considerable chunk of the 20 hours per
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  day a player is given, especially since it doesn't take into account how long it would take to get back to the farm, since the spa is a considerable distance away.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the spa in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  seems like a good opportunity initially, problems like these are holding it back. It would seem that past the first couple of seasons in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , many players ignore the spa completely unless the story requires them to go there. Unless one finds themselves in the area, it's likely a better option to simply eat or lie in one's bed for a while to restore energy. As the game progresses, most players will likely find that running out of energy is a thing of the past.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Win - Hitching A Ride!</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/accidental-win-hitching-a-ride/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A player lands a truck atop another truck in GTA and more accidental wins.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Dead Redemption 2: Best Repeaters &amp; How to Get Them, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/red-dead-redemption-2-best-repeaters-locations/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There are 4 repeaters in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Red Dead Redemption 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  , and each of them provides different functions within a gunfight, so it’s fairly important that players know what each of them does before they commit to one or the other. The best repeaters in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  are going to carry Arthur Morgan through the early game, especially with their high ammo capacity, accuracy, and moderate damage.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  However, understanding all repeaters in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  means understanding their stats, what makes them work, and what makes them not work. With only 4 repeaters to choose from, players are going to need to be aware of the repeaters that are worth their time, and the others that aren’t.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="carbine-repeater">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Carbine Repeater
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-starting-repeater-that-rsquo-s-reliable-but-not-overly-powerful">
  A Starting Repeater That’s Reliable, But Not Overly Powerful
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-225109493" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-225109493" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-225109493" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-225109493" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-225109493-img" id="article-gallery-1-225109493">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-225109493" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1981375282">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Damage
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       60
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fire Rate
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       53
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Accuracy
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       73
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Range
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reload
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       73
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ammo Capacity
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    How to Get the Carbine Repeater:
   </strong>
   Purchased from a Gunsmith for $90 after Old Friends (Chapter 1)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Carbine Repeater is one of the first repeaters players will have access to, and despite its popularity and ease of access, it’s not the best. The Carbine Repeater has an average amount of damage, and its range and fire rate don’t really compliment it as decent competition against other repeaters, especially when there is an army to push through.
 </p>
 <p>
  The lack of bullets with a total of 7 in a magazine makes the Carbine Repeater a tad annoying to reload, even if the reload speed is fairly fast. What players have with the Carbine Repeater is a decent enough starting gun that won’t let them down, but can definitely be left behind for superior guns.
 </p>
 <h2 id="litchfield-repeater">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Litchfield Repeater
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="great-damage-but-lacks-in-fire-rate-and-accuracy">
  Great Damage, But Lacks in Fire Rate and Accuracy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-110175024" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-110175024" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-110175024" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-110175024" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-110175024-img" id="article-gallery-2-110175024">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-110175024" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-269445346">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Damage
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fire Rate
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Accuracy
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       68
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Range
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reload
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ammo Capacity
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       16
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    How to Get the Litchfield Repeater:
   </strong>
   Purchased from a Gunsmith for $145 after Goodbye, Dear Friend (Chapter 6)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Litchfield Repeater shouldn’t be underestimated, as its 16-bullet capacity makes it an easily wielded weapon for putting bullets in gang members. However, the Litchfield Repeater may boast of its highest damage stat across the repeaters, but it also suffers from a slow reload speed and an even slower fire rate.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Litchfield Repeater might be more accurate due to the slow fire rate, but in that case, maybe try out a rifle instead. It’s a decent and pretty enough repeater that is definitely worth trying out due to its ammo capacity and damage, perfect for hunts and shootouts, but there are better options.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="evans-repeater">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Evans Repeater
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="moderate-damage-with-an-extremely-high-ammo-capacity">
  Moderate Damage with an Extremely High Ammo Capacity
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-425343695" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-425343695" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-425343695" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-425343695" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-425343695-img" id="article-gallery-3-425343695">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-425343695" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-595543711">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Damage
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fire Rate
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       62
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Accuracy
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       74
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Range
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reload
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       62
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ammo Capacity
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       26
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    How to Get the Evans Repeater:
   </strong>
   Purchased from a Gunsmith for $140 after American Distillation (Chapter 3)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Evans Repeater isn’t exactly the most deadly, especially since it’s a weird gun that might have players miss a few shots here and there, but that really doesn’t matter. In the end, the Evans Repeater is going to hit the target, since this repeater has an ammo capacity of 26, which is truly diabolical when compared to other repeaters.
 </p>
 <p>
  With ammo for every combat encounter, players are going to have a modern repeater with a sleek design that can shoot through an army of gang members or law enforcement, and its fairly decent range and accuracy will be a mighty aid in Arthur’s fight.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lancaster-repeater">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Lancaster Repeater
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fast-aiming-great-accuracy-and-exceptional-handling">
  Fast Aiming, Great Accuracy, and Exceptional Handling
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1621004413" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1621004413" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1621004413" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1621004413" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1621004413-img" id="article-gallery-4-1621004413">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1621004413" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1474080598">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Damage
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       55
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Fire Rate
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       59
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Accuracy
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       76
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Range
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reload
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       70
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Ammo Capacity
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       14
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    How to Get the Lancaster Repeater:
   </strong>
   Purchased from a Gunsmith for $135 after An American Pastoral Scene (Chapter 2)
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The Lancaster Repeater is the best repeater in
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  for a few reasons. Not only does it have a fair ammo capacity of 14 bullets, or a balanced damage output, but it boasts of a high accuracy and an easy amount of handling for each shot to make for a weapon that will truly kill everyone that is facing the barrel.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Lancaster Repeater is easily the greatest, and with its accuracy and fast reticle, aiming at anyone in the vicinity will turn Arthur Morgan into death incarnate as he unleashes a deadly fury without the need for Dead Eye to lay waste to his foes.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
