<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Disco Elysium is Coming to Another Platform</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/disco-elysium-mobile-release-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      A mobile version of Disco Elysium will be released exclusively for Android devices in Summer 2025.
     </li>
     <li>
      Pre-registration is now available on Google Play.
     </li>
     <li>
      Designed for short play sessions, the mobile version promises to provide a 'fun, on-the-go alternative' to the popular RPG.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  An official mobile version of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Disco Elysium
   </em>
  </strong>
  will be released exclusively on Android devices in Summer 2025. Those wanting to pick up the non-traditional RPG can pre-register now on Google Play, and those who have played
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  before shouldn't expect the same experience in this reimagined version of the 2019 ZA/UM title.
 </p>
 <p>
  Featuring one of the most eccentric and immersive stories in gaming,
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  has cultivated a dedicated fanbase, with players quickly drawn in by its fleshed-out world, unique NPCs, and largely luck-based gameplay. The title follows a detective suffering from alcohol and drug-induced amnesia who is tasked with solving a murder case alongside his more stable partner, Kim Kitsuragi. Taking place in the world of Elysium, the game is known for being dialogue-heavy, including a script of over one million words and full voice acting in
  <em>
   Disco Elysium: The Final Cut
  </em>
  . An entirely new audience is about to gain access to this beloved title, and the wait is almost over.
 </p>
 <p>
  As reported by IGN, ZA/UM has announced that an official mobile version of
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  will be coming to Android devices in Summer 2025, with a concrete release date to be announced. Pre-registration is now open on Google Play, and fans were treated to their first look at gameplay in the title's announcement trailer, highlighting how different this version of
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  is when compared to its initial release. According to a studio spokesperson, this mobile edition of the RPG is meant to pull in new players, particularly the TikTok audience, by providing a "fun, on-the-go alternative." The Android release of
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  promises to reimagine the title, and will be "optimized for short play sessions, allowing players to dive in anytime." The first two chapters of the game will be available for free, after which the full game can be purchased for a single fee.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="disco-elysium-coming-to-android-devices-in-summer-2025">
  Disco Elysium Coming to Android Devices in Summer 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-d4f8cc0f13d31e65" id="emaki-video-player-d4f8cc0f13d31e65">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  First released for PC,
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  was brought to PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 with the release of
  <em>
   The Final Cut
  </em>
  in March 2021, with versions for Nintendo Switch, Xbox One, and Xbox Series X/S following later that year.
  <em>
   Disco Elysium: The Final Cut
  </em>
  introduced full voice acting for the game's nearly 100 characters and its narration, with the recording process taking nearly 14 months. It also included additional musical tracks and artwork.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-697896367" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-697896367" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-697896367" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-697896367" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-697896367-img" id="article-gallery-1-697896367">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-697896367" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1328766896">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  On March 11, ZA/UM revealed its new game project
  <em>
   ,
  </em>
  <em>
   C4
  </em>
  . While little is known about the upcoming title, it is said to be a spy espionage game that will be set in an entirely different universe than
  <em>
   Disco Elysium
  </em>
  . No platforms have been announced, nor has a release window.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Wuthering Waves Fans Should Try Zenless Zone Zero</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/games-like-wuthering-waves-what-to-play-after-zenless-zone-zero-zzz/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Since launching almost a year ago,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Wuthering Waves
   </em>
  </strong>
  has captured the hearts of millions of players worldwide, most especially gacha fans. Set in the post-apocalyptic world of Solaris-3,
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  follows the amnesiac protagonist, Rover, as they explore the new world and meet other characters, known as Resonators, along the way. Players also have to form strong teams and master the combat system to fight against different monsters.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ' open-world setting, and some of its gameplay mechanics, have been compared to HoYoverse's
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . However, both games also have clear distinctions when it comes to combat and exploration, giving players very different experiences when they play through their stories. One title that
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  fans should definitely try, though, is HoYoverse's
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wuthering-waves-and-zenless-zone-zero-have-similar-post-apocalyptic-story-beats">
  Wuthering Waves and Zenless Zone Zero Have Similar Post-Apocalyptic Story Beats
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1481372618" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1481372618" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1481372618" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1481372618" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1481372618-img" id="article-gallery-1-1481372618">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1481372618" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2096246163">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Just like
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  is set in a futuristic and post-apocalyptic world, primarily focused on the city of New Eridu. Its protagonists, the Proxy siblings Belle and Wise (aka Phaethon), help Agents, and other people, navigate the Hollows and defeat powerful enemies. Hollows are essentially supernatural disasters, with dimensions that swallow up large parts of the city and contain monsters called Ethereals. They are also similar to
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ' Laments, which are connected to disaster trends and the Waveworn Phenomena happening in the game's world.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  allow players to explore disaster-ridden worlds, to discover the truth behind the worlds' anomalies, and, ultimately, to find ways to eradicate the anomalies and save humanity. In terms of gameplay, both games are action-adventure gacha titles, where players have to farm upgrade materials and optimal items to build powerful units. The exploration also provides opportunities to find treasures, to engage in side quests, and to interact with interesting NPCs who expand the games' respective worlds.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-role-of-zenless-zone-zero-39-s-proxy-compared-to-wuthering-waves-39-rover">
  The Role of Zenless Zone Zero's Proxy Compared to Wuthering Waves' Rover
 </h3>
 <p>
  The first clear difference between
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  is that the former's protagonist, Proxy (Belle or Wise), doesn't go into combat.
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  has playable Agents with different elements and fighting styles, and they are the ones who enter Hollows and fight Ethereals. The Proxy also "enters" Hollows in the form of Eous, a Bangboo they control remotely to accompany Agents and provide support in battle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Meanwhile,
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ' Rover is a playable multi-attribute Resonator, with alternate forms being unlocked as players progress through the story. They're more similar to
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's Traveler and
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's Trailblazer in this respect.
 </p>
 <h3 id="the-similarities-and-differences-between-zenless-zone-zero-and-wuthering-waves-39-combat">
  The Similarities and Differences Between Zenless Zone Zero and Wuthering Waves' Combat
 </h3>
 <p>
  As mentioned,
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  has drawn comparisons to
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  because of its fantasy approach to combat. However, certain elements of
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  ' combat mechanics clearly stand apart from the HoYoverse title, such as Concerto Effects applying buffs to the next character that is swapped in.
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's approach is different, with Elemental Resonances that apply buffs to the entire party. Evasion and stunning are also important in
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves,
  </em>
  as they allow players to trigger additional powerful attacks against enemies.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  is often likened to a fighting game because of its beat-em-up mechanics and team-up features. Just like
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  , dodging attacks at the right time allows Agents to immediately deal Dodge Counters to enemies. What makes
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  stand out is that Agents can get stat buffs when their allies have the same elements, fighting style, and come from the same faction.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  doesn't have the same fantasy approach as
  <em>
   Wuthering Waves
  </em>
  , the post-apocalyptic atmosphere brings a sense of familiarity. Plus, the more modern take on
  <em>
   Zenless Zone Zero
  </em>
  's characters and environment also make it relatable to the real world in a way.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monopoly GO: Shamrock Shenanigans Rewards And Milestones</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monopoly-go-shamrock-shenanigans-rewards-and-milestones/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Monopoly GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  has finally dropped its much-awaited Partners Event for March, called St. Paddy’s Partners, to celebrate St. Patrick’s Day in style. This event is packed with awesome rewards, but like always, you'll need tokens to take part. That’s where the Shamrock Shenanigans banner event comes in.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The Shamrock Shenanigans banner event started on March 13 and will run for
  <strong>
   two days, ending on March 15
  </strong>
  . It’s loaded with many awesome rewards. Along with St. Paddy's Partner tokens, you can grab tons of other useful rewards like sticker packs, cash, and dice to keep you rolling on the board. If you want to find out all the milestones and rewards for the Shamrock Shenanigans
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  event, you’re in the right place. Read on to learn more.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="shamrock-shenanigans-monopoly-go-rewards-and-milestones">
  Shamrock Shenanigans Monopoly GO Rewards And Milestones
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Monopoly Go mascot with a dog" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The table below highlights all the rewards available in the Shamrock Shenanigans
  <em>
   Monopoly GO
  </em>
  solo event:
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Shamrock Shenanigans Milestones
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Points Required
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Shamrock Shenanigans Rewards
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Five
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       70 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       10
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       25 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       15
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       4
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       25
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       One-Star Sticker Pack
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       6
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       30
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       80 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       7
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       35
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       One-Star Sticker Pack
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       8
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       40
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       40 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       9
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       120 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       10
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       160
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       150 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       11
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       12
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       55
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       50 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       13
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       65
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       160 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       14
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       80
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Two-Star Sticker Pack
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       15
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       425
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       375 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       16
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       70
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       180 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       17
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       80
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       70 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       18
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       85
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Builder's Bash For 15 Minutes
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       19
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       95
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       20
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       685
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       575 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       21
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       100
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       200 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       22
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       115
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       95 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       23
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       110
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       24
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       130
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       220 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       25
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,150
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       925 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       26
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       140
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Three-Star Sticker Pack
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       27
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       150
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       28
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       160
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       29
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       750
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       575 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       30
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       180
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       270 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       31
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       190
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       32
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       210
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       150 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       33
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       160
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Boost For 10 Minutes
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       34
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       230
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       35
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,500
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,100 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       36
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       300 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       37
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       300
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       200 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       38
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       450
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       39
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,350
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       925 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       40
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       325
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       41
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       350
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       350 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       42
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       375
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       43
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2,250
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,400 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       44
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       350
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Color Wheel Boost For 15 Minutes
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       45
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       450
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       380 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       46
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       575
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       350 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       47
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       500
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       48
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3,000
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,650 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       49
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       550
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       400 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       50
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       450
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Mega Heist For 40 Minutes
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       51
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       650
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       52
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,800
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       800 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       53
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       700
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       450 Leaf Tokens
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       54
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       825
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       500 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       55
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       950
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       56
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4,500
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2,200 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       57
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       500
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Boost For 15 Minutes
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       58
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       800
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       375 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       59
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       950
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       60
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,400
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       625 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       61
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1,500
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Cash Reward
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       62
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       10,000
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5,000 Free Dice Rolls
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="shamrock-shenanigans-monopoly-go-rewards-summary">
  Shamrock Shenanigans Monopoly GO Rewards Summary
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Monopoly mascot and dog in Monopoly Go" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1099" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/monopoly-go-cover-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Shamrock Shenanigans banner event is spread over
  <strong>
   62 milestones
  </strong>
  . Expectedly then, beating it is going to take a lot of time. However, if you manage to do so, you will walk away with many awesome rewards. Surprisingly, there's no five-star sticker pack this time around, even at the final milestone. Here is a quick look at the most useful rewards tycoons can earn:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   18,205 Dice Rolls
  </li>
  <li>
   3,430 Leaf Tokens for St. Paddy's Partners
  </li>
  <li>
   Top Reward of 5,000 Dice Rolls
  </li>
  <li>
   A 15-Minute Color Wheel Boost at the 44th Milestone
  </li>
  <li>
   A 40-Minute Mega Heist at the 50th Milestone
  </li>
  <li>
   A 15-Minute Builder's Bash at the 18th Milestone
  </li>
  <li>
   A 15-Minute Cash Grab Boost at the 57th Milestone.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  With the St. Paddy's Partners minigame active, players can win thousands of Leaf Tokens needed to participate. The minigame features many amazing rewards like the Shamrock Scottie board token and the Swap Pack. In addition to tokens, you can win thousands of dice rolls and a variety of other rewards for players like dice and cash to help you upgrade your buildings. There are also many different flash events scattered across 62 milestones.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The Shamrock Shenanigans
     <em>
      Monopoly GO
     </em>
     event will only last for two days, so join in now to win all the fabulous rewards.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-get-points-in-shamrock-shenanigans-monopoly-go">
  How To Get Points In Shamrock Shenanigans Monopoly GO
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="monopoly go cover " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/monopoly-go-cover-1-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players who want to earn points and advance in the Shamrock Shenanigans solo event should focus on hitting the four
  <strong>
   corner tiles
  </strong>
  of their boards. Every time you hit one of them, you will earn
  <strong>
   four points
  </strong>
  toward your next milestone. The tiles to target are:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Go
  </li>
  <li>
   Free Parking
  </li>
  <li>
   In Jail
  </li>
  <li>
   Go to Jail.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  All the corner tiles give you the same number of points, so it’s easy to keep track of your progress. Like always, if you want to complete milestones faster, the best way is to boost your roll multiplier.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Characters Are Most Likely to Return in Horizon 3?</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/horizon-3-returning-characters-likely-erend-sylens-avad/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The post-apocalyptic, animalist machine-filled world of the
  <strong>
   <em>
    Horizon
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise is filled with a wide variety of human tribes and several intriguing characters beyond the protagonist, Aloy. Aside from Aloy’s isolationist Nora home tribe, six other tribes can be encountered throughout the post-apocalyptic western United States in the
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  franchise. From the shamanistic Banuk to the seafaring Quen, each tribe has their own unique customs, beliefs, and members whom Aloy confronts or allies with in her quest to save the world from rogue artificial intelligences, warmongers, and genocidal aliens. While
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  may be months or years away, players can still predict which characters will appear alongside Aloy during the climactic battle against the alien AI Nemesis.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="characters-who-appear-in-horizon-zero-dawn-forbidden-west-and-call-of-the-mountain">
  Characters Who Appear in Horizon Zero Dawn, Forbidden West, and Call of the Mountain
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1820386267" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1820386267" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1820386267" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1820386267" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1820386267-img" id="article-gallery-1-1820386267">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1820386267" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1982894837">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Aside from
  <em>
   LEGO Horizon Adventures
  </em>
  , each
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  game has both introduced new characters and included old favorites from previous titles in a range of roles. In
  <em>
   Horizon Zero Dawn
  </em>
  , Aloy encountered several allies who helped her defeat the Eclipse cultists and stop the rogue AI HADES from destroying all life. Some served minor roles, such as the Nora stitcher Teb, while others were the centerpoints of vital quests and directly helped Aloy in combat scenarios. Some of Aloys most notable allies in
  <em>
   Zero Dawn
  </em>
  include the Oseram Erend and Petra, the Banuk Sylens and Aluki, and the Nora Varl, Sona, and Nakoa. Many members of the Carja tribe also aided Aloy, including:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Sun-King Avad
  </li>
  <li>
   Prince Itamen
  </li>
  <li>
   Dowager Queen Nasadi
  </li>
  <li>
   Spymaster Blameless Marad
  </li>
  <li>
   Spy Vanasha
  </li>
  <li>
   Senior Military Advisor Uthid
  </li>
  <li>
   Elida
  </li>
  <li>
   Warden Janeva
  </li>
  <li>
   Nil
  </li>
  <li>
   Sunhawk Talanah
  </li>
  <li>
   Sun-Priest Namman.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Only a handful of characters from
  <em>
   Zero Dawn
  </em>
  play major roles in
  <em>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </em>
  , including Erend, Varl, and Sylens. However, a few
  <em>
   Zero Dawn
  </em>
  characters do briefly appear in
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  ’s prologue and select side quests, such as Avad, Itamen, Marad, Nil, Talanah, Vanasha, and Uthid, but they don’t play major roles in the sequel. Elisabet Sobeck and Aloy’s fatherly guardian Rost also appear a couple of times in
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  , but only in ancient holograms, audio logs, and dreams. One character who appears in both game’s DLCs, the Frozen Wilds and Burning Shores, is the enthusiastic Oseram delver Gildun, who seeks to discover old world treasures in the Greycatch and Hoover dams as well as the Murmuring Hollow in post-apocalyptic Los Angeles.
 </p>
 <h3 id="returning-zero-dawn-and-forbidden-west-characters-in-horizon-call-of-the-mountain">
  Returning Zero Dawn and Forbidden West Characters in Horizon Call of the Mountain
 </h3>
 <p>
  In the virtual reality spin-off
  <em>
   Horizon Call of the Mountain
  </em>
  , several characters from both
  <em>
   Horizon Zero Dawn
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Horizon Forbidden West
  </em>
  appear. Blameless Marad returns as a sort of guide, while
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  ’s minor antagonist and leader of the Oseram Sons of Prometheus, Asera, returns to threaten the Carja and the fragile peace between the tribes. Asera’s appearance in
  <em>
   Call of the Mountain
  </em>
  is actually a prequel to her appearance in
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  as the VR game takes place during the events of
  <em>
   Zero Dawn
  </em>
  . Aloy additionally returns in
  <em>
   Call of the Mountain
  </em>
  , but as an NPC for the first time, offering guidance to the redeemed Shadow Carja and Itamen’s Shadow, Ryas,
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  ’s first new leading protagonist besides the Sobeck clone.
 </p>
 <h2 id="characters-most-likely-to-appear-in-horizon-3">
  Characters Most Likely to Appear in Horizon 3
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1807783309" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1807783309" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1807783309" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1807783309" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1807783309-img" id="article-gallery-2-1807783309">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1807783309" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1701276449">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Little is currently known about the plot or setting of
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  aside from the fact that it will follow Aloy in stopping the Far Zenith-created alien AI Nemesis from destroying all life on Earth. Guerrilla Games is currently working on a story-focused multiplayer
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  spin-off and NCSoft is rumored to be developing a
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  MMO with both expected to release before the mainline
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  . While some characters from
  <em>
   Zero Dawn
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Call of the Mountain
  </em>
  may appear in these spin-offs, they can still pop up in and play pivotal roles in
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  . The most likely characters to return in
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  are those who appeared in most games so far, such as
  <strong>
   Avad
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Erend
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Marad
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Nil
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Sylens
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Talanah
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Vanasha
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Uthid
  </strong>
  , with the Carja expected to help fight Nemesis.
 </p>
 <p>
  Significant allies made in
  <em>
   Forbidden West
  </em>
  will also have a high probability of appearing in the next mainline
  <em>
   Horizon
  </em>
  game in some capacity, ranging from brief appearances like the Carja leadership or major companions such as Erend and Varl. Those close to Aloy who were given Focus devices have a high probability of helping combat Nemesis in
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  , including Alva, Beta, Erend, Gildun, Kotallo, and Zo. Erend and Zo will probably have significant plotlines in
  <em>
   Horizon 3
  </em>
  since Erend is now Aloy’s closest living friend and Zo will likely give birth to Varl’s child at some point in the game. If Aloy does travel to the faraway Quen Empire for aid, Alva and Seyka should play important roles in negotiations between the east and west. The latter seems especially likely to appear given her potential romance with Aloy.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Game Releasing May 22</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tactical-takedown-release-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown is coming to PC on May 22, offering a new turn-based TMNT experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      The game features a unique storyline with the Turtles facing adulthood after the deaths of Splinter and Shredder.
     </li>
     <li>
      Players can enjoy action-packed campaigns, strategic gameplay, and a bold, comic-style art direction in the game.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A new, turn-based
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  game, titled
  <strong>
   <em>
    Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown
   </em>
  </strong>
  , is coming to PC on May 22. The past few years have been an exciting time for fans of the pizza-munching, crime-fighting Heroes in a Half-Shell, who have kicked off a brand-new era thanks to 2023’s
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem
  </em>
  and its connected
  <em>
   Tales of the TMNT
  </em>
  animated series. There have also been some exciting
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
  </em>
  games announced and released recently, with former Apple Arcade exclusive
  <em>
   TMNT: Splintered Fate
  </em>
  making the jump to Switch and PC last year and a game based on
  <em>
   The Last Ronin
  </em>
  on the way.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Turtles have also continued guest starring in other properties thanks to their
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  crossovers and more recent appearance as Operator skins in
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Warzone
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , and more nostalgic gamers can now enjoy the
  <em>
   TMNT: Cowabunga Collection
  </em>
  for free on PlayStation Plus Essential. Meanwhile, a demo for a turn-based
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  game titled
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  was made available on Steam in late February as part of Steam’s Next Fest event.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now fans who have tried the game out know when
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  will launch in full, as confirmed by developer Strange Scaffold.
  <em>
   TMNT: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  will be released on PC through Steam on May 22. The news came with a new trailer for the game, featuring the Turtles battling the forces of the evil Foot Clan on the rooftops of New York City using turn-based grid movement and special attacks. A playable demo of
  <em>
   TMNT: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  will also be available at the Game Developers Conference on May 16.
  <em>
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tactical-takedown-release-date">
  Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown Release Date
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-a5719bf4bdfbfcf2" id="emaki-video-player-a5719bf4bdfbfcf2">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   May 22, 2025
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The story of
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  sees the Turtles faced with impending adulthood following the deaths of their beloved Master Splinter and most hated enemy the Shredder, as well as another evil plot by the Foot and other foes. This emotional tale spans 20 levels filled with iconic villains to fight, a bold, comic-inspired art style, and a multi-genre soundtrack by
  <em>
   I Am Your Beast
  </em>
  composer RJ Lake. Players can unlock special abilities for all four Turtles, modify load-outs, and coordinate attacks across a diorama-inspired game world.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1279063484" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1279063484" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1279063484" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1279063484" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1279063484-img" id="article-gallery-1-1279063484">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1279063484" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-375227829">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
   </em>
  </strong>
  franchise already has a rich history with gaming, and
  <em>
   Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  ’s mix of turn-based strategy and fast-paced beat-em-up combat looks to be a fresh direction for the Turtles. Gamers will finally get to experience this direction in full when
  <em>
   TMNT: Tactical Takedown
  </em>
  launches on Steam on May 22.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
