<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>7 Unique Death Mechanics in Roguelike Games, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/roguelike-games-with-unique-death-mechanics-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Death in roguelikes can be more than just a setback - unique mechanics like in Sifu and Bad North offer new opportunities rather than frustrations.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like Tales of Maj'Eyal and Rogue Legacy 2 implement innovative death mechanics to keep players returning after each demise.
     </li>
     <li>
      Titles like Shiren the Wanderer and Hades soften the blow of death by allowing players to retain certain progress or resources upon restarting.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players haven't truly played a roguelike if they haven't died. This is a genre that thrives on difficulty, where the punishment for underestimating an enemy or simple bad luck is often severe. The most severe, arguably, as punishments don't really get much worse than death, and video-game punishments don't get much worse than losing progress. Whether players are gluttons for punishment, or the tight, cohesive game design that goes into roguelikes just appeals to them, this genre of games is constantly booming, especially among indie developers.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even if it's an inherent draw to the genre, however, dying can become tedious after a while. Games often get around this with engaging combat to keep people coming back for more, or a story where death is woven into it, so there's an 'in-universe' explanation for a character dying and coming back. There are some games, however, that create unique mechanics that help give death some more identity. These games in particular have interesting death mechanics that in some way push the player ahead or work in some way besides simply starting from scratch at the beginning.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="tales-of-maj-rsquo-eyal">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Tales of Maj’Eyal
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="adventurer-mode-makes-death-a-warning">
  Adventurer Mode Makes Death A Warning
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1849562136" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1849562136" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1849562136" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1849562136" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1849562136-img" id="article-gallery-1-1849562136">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1849562136" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1787579054">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Among some of the best open-world roguelikes available to date,
  <em>
   Tales of Maj'Eyal
  </em>
  is an indie passion project that's bloomed into one of the most expansive and content-filled roguelikes on the shelves. The most basic sword-and-board style warrior in
  <em>
   Tales of Maj'Eyal
  </em>
  has more depth and customization than the average mage in many other RPGs, and it keeps this level of depth without sacrificing its approachability.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is best seen with its most popular difficulty mode, Adventurer Mode. When a player dies in Adventure Mode, they lose one of their lives, but are able to continue playing. These lives are limited, and players only gain one at set level intervals that grow more distant as the character's level grows higher, meaning that the spirit of a roguelike is remarkably well-intact despite the slightly more accessible gameplay.
 </p>
 <h2 id="shiren-the-wanderer-the-tower-of-fortune-and-the-dice-of-fate">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Shiren The Wanderer: The Tower Of Fortune And The Dice Of Fate
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="classic-mystery-dungeon-mechanics-with-a-twist">
  Classic Mystery Dungeon Mechanics With A Twist
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-927347417" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-927347417" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-927347417" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-927347417" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-927347417-img" id="article-gallery-2-927347417">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-927347417" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1030972246">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  What makes
  <em>
   Shiren the Wanderer: The Tower of Fortune and the Dice of Fate
  </em>
  so interesting among mystery dungeon titles is the difference between the things that remain and the things that reset upon death. This game series is nothing short of a staple within the mystery dungeon genre, though most mystery dungeon games outside of
  <em>
   Pokémon
  </em>
  tend to be rather obscure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Unlike most instances of death in mystery dungeon games, which result in the player losing all their items, money, and in Shiren's case, levels, there are a few mechanics that work in this title to soften death's blow. Companions, who have many unique perks that aid Shiren, don't lose their levels if players die and they're still alive. Weapons can also be marked so they can be found again in subsequent runs with their upgrades intact.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bad-north">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Bad North
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="death-might-just-make-the-next-run-easier">
  Death Might Just Make The Next Run Easier
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2145810322" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2145810322" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2145810322" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2145810322" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2145810322-img" id="article-gallery-3-2145810322">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2145810322" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1293907978">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Squad leaders in
  <em>
   Bad North
  </em>
  are the lifeblood of the game; they are who the players directly command to get into positions, with their soldiers trailing behind them. The initial squad leaders that players will unlock, while quirky little randomized dudes with plenty of personality, don't actually do much in terms of bringing anything else to the table.
 </p>
 <p>
  When players unlock new personality traits in a run, however, it gives them incentive to return after dying, as they can start a new run with a leader that has a special effect, such as a high move speed or a larger squad.
 </p>
 <h2 id="blazblue-entropy-effect">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   BlazBlue: Entropy Effect
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="death-provides-a-unique-opportunity-to-enhance-further-runs">
  Death Provides A Unique Opportunity To Enhance Further Runs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1780661326" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1780661326" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1780661326" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1780661326" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1780661326-img" id="article-gallery-4-1780661326">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1780661326" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-69612373">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Few games hold the same kind of atmosphere and tone as
  <em>
   Blazblue: Entropy Effect
  </em>
  . Players who love JRPGs and cyberpunk-styled titles will be right at home with this roguelike, but what really makes this game pop is the modular nature of death.
 </p>
 <p>
  When players die, they're able to take back with them two of their acquired mode buffs to be implemented at the beginning of the next run, allowing for freedom of customization to characters and runs that makes death feel more like an opportunity than anything else.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sifu">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Sifu
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="failure-is-just-another-part-of-the-story">
  Failure Is Just Another Part Of The Story
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1811023611" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1811023611" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1811023611" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1811023611" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1811023611-img" id="article-gallery-5-1811023611">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1811023611" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-343592938">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As far as roguelikes go,
  <em>
   Sifu
  </em>
  is incredibly unique and well worth giving a shot, even if fighting games are not usually your cup of tea. The punchy, incredibly tacticle combat style that lets players really feel every punch delivered and received makes the game incredibly satisfying.
 </p>
 <p>
  Beyond this, being defeated in
  <em>
   Sifu
  </em>
  , 'dying' in a mechanical sense, is by no means the end of the story. 'Death' in this sense lets players start again, this time as an older, wiser martial artist. They will have less overall HP, but compensating for this, they are able to dish out more damage with their attacks.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hades">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Hades
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-addictive-and-inspiring-roguelike">
  An Addictive And Inspiring Roguelike
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-874418846" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-874418846" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-874418846" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-874418846" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-874418846-img" id="article-gallery-6-874418846">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-874418846" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-70759430">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Moreso than perhaps any other game on this list,
  <em>
   Hades
  </em>
  is a game where players can actually look forward to death. Death means returning to home in order to spend used up resources on new gear and perks.
 </p>
 <p>
  Returning home also means progressing relationships, furthering the story, and overall rerolling certain features of the subsequent dungeons, which could provide players with even more things to do on their next return home.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="rogue-legacy-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Rogue Legacy 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="death-builds-up-a-legacy">
  Death Builds Up A Legacy
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-801850315" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-801850315" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-801850315" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-801850315" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-801850315-img" id="article-gallery-7-801850315">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-801850315" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-855179760">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rounding out this list is an incredibly popular title that brings all the charm and procedural narratives of
  <em>
   Crusader Kings 3
  </em>
  to the world of roguelike, dungeon-delving platformers. This is an unabashedly delightful game that has an incredibly compelling death mechanic.
 </p>
 <p>
  When players die, they continue on in the next generation as the previous hero's child, increasing the prestige of their bloodline, inheriting certain treasures and traits, and overall continuing on the legacy of a bloodline that grows with each death.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genshin Impact Reveals Ifa's Design and Element</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/genshin-impact-ifa-design-element-stars-reveal/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      New Natlan character Ifa is confirmed for Genshin Impact and is the first Anemo with a unique design.
     </li>
     <li>
      Varesa and Iansan from Pyro nation to join in update 5.5 and Varesa is a five-star.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ifa's expected release in version 5.6 on May 7, separate from confirmed 5.5 characters.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Genshin Impact
   </em>
  </strong>
  has officially revealed the appearance and element of a new Natlan character named Ifa, who is expected to join the roster in the coming months. Since the Natlan region arrived, every new
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  update has introduced at least one five-star character, with Mizuki being the most recent addition.
 </p>
 <p>
  HoYoverse's recent livestream event also confirmed the arrival of two new characters, Varesa and Iansan, in the upcoming
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  update 5.5. Both characters belong to the Collective of Plenty, one of the six tribes in the Pyro nation, and are known for their incredible strength.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  's most recent Special Program event has finally revealed the design of the long-awaited Natlan character Ifa, who has been mentioned a few times in the main storyline. The livestream confirmed that Ifa will have a tall male model, silver-blue hair, and a tech-inspired outfit with a cowboy-style hat. One in-game scene also confirmed that Ifa will be a new Anemo character, making him the first playable unit in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  to have this element and model type combination. The official storyline previously revealed that Ifa is a renowned Saurian veterinarian from the Flower-Feather Clan. The grumpy, bird-like creature floating next to Ifa is likely Cacucu, a Qucusaurus who works as his assistant.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="genshin-impact-ifa-39-s-element-confirmed">
  Genshin Impact: Ifa's Element Confirmed
 </h2>
 <p>
  Another interesting fact about Ifa is that he is very close friends with Ororon, another Natlan character in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . Regarding Ifa's rarity, there is still no official information or credible leaks, but fans hope he will be a five-star character. Players also speculate that due to his affiliation with Saurians, Ifa may have special interactions with these creatures, which are exclusive to the Pyro nation. To get more credible information about Ifa, players will likely have to wait for his beta phase to begin.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-179703190" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-179703190" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-179703190" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-179703190" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-179703190-img" id="article-gallery-1-179703190">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-179703190" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-43656480">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As for his release date, Ifa is expected to arrive in version 5.6. Based on HoYoverse's usual update schedule, players can anticipate 5.6 dropping around May 7. The only confirmed detail about his release is that he will not be joining the roster in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  update 5.5, as HoYoverse has confirmed that two other characters, Varesa and Iansan, will appear on the Limited Character Banner in the next update.
 </p>
 <p>
  Both Varesa and Iansan will be featured in the first banner cycle, expected to launch on March 26. Despite being Varesa's teacher, Iansan will have a lower four-star rarity compared to her student, who has been confirmed as a five-star character in
  <em>
   Genshin Impact
  </em>
  . Fortunately for players who want to add both of them to their roster, Varesa and Iansan being on the same banner means it will be easier to acquire both, as players won’t need to pull on separate banners.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Fan Finds Perfect Use for Work Plaque</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-fan-rare-charizard-display-image-card-tcg/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Pokemon TCG fan repurposes work plaque to display prized Charizard holo card.
     </li>
     <li>
      New Pokemon TCG Journey Together expansion set to be released in English on March 28.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Pokemon community showcases creativity in displaying rare cards, including a custom Eevee evolution unit.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon TCG
   </strong>
  </em>
  fan has used a commemorative plaque from their place of work to display one of their treasured cards. The
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  Trading Card Game has been in existence almost as long as the franchise itself, with the first cards rolled out in October 1996 and going strong ever since. In fact, the latest set will be released in a matter of weeks.
 </p>
 <p>
  Meanwhile, the new
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Journey Together
  </em>
  expansion
  <em>
   will be released on March 28
  </em>
  for the first time in English. The new set is based on
  <em>
   Pokemon Scarlet and Violet
  </em>
  and features over 180 new cards. The announced cards include N’s Zoroark ex, Iono’s Bellibolt ex, Lillie’s Clefairy ex, and Hop’s Zacian ex, with The Pokemon Company teasing many more surprises. As the excitement for the next batch of trading cards continues to build, one collector has revealed a unique way of displaying their most precious Pokemon.
 </p>
 <p>
  A user on Reddit named mikeygribbin has found a novel way of displaying their most prized
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  card. The
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  collector was given a celebratory plaque for completing a decade in their job. Instead of displaying the commemorative work achievement, the fan decided to repurpose the plaque to display an original Charizard holo. Fans were quick to praise mikeygribbin’s crafty recycling, with the post amassing over 57,000 upvotes at the time of writing.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="a-pokemon-tcg-fan-showcases-their-new-display">
  A Pokemon TCG Fan Showcases Their New Display
 </h2>
 <p>
  The comments praised the creativity of the original poster, with some arguing it was better than its original contents. Others shared similar photos of their rare
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  trading cards, including one who posted their rare Ancient Mew card. Other users warned about keeping the card sandwiched for long periods as the type of plastic could eventually cause damage to the precious card if not carefully looked after.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1928085569" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1928085569" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1928085569" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1928085569" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1928085569-img" id="article-gallery-1-1928085569">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1928085569" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1372339373">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  fans have always found creative ways to display their cards. A dedicated Eevee fan built a custom display unit that proudly showed off every evolution. The impressive unit showcased every one of Eevee’s evolutions with a unique border surrounding the Kanto original. On completing the task, the poster joked that Game Freak had best not introduce any more evolutions to Eevee’s line, something which the company hasn't done since
  <em>
   Pokemon X and Y
  </em>
  in 2013.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  community will find unique ways of displaying their cards, attention turns to the future of the trading card game. Several
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  cards have leaked ahead of an official reveal by The Pokemon Company. The Heat Wave Arena will be the next set to be released in Japan and will feature full art cards that include Rotom, Shaymin, and Cynthia's Roserade.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2 Villain Deserves to Be as Reviled as RDR2's Micah Bell</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/kingdom-come-deliverance-2-brabant-red-dead-redemption-micah-similar/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_0">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     This article contains major spoilers for
     <em>
      Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
     </em>
     and
     <em>
      Red Dead Redemption 2
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There is no shortage of compelling villains in gaming, but some of the best are often considered so because they are sympathetic or tragic. However, games with villains that really make players hate them can be just as effective as those that earn players' sympathy, and
  <strong>
   <em>
    Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  features both sides of this spectrum. One character is particularly despicable and conjures comparisons to the infamously hated Micah Bell from
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  constantly asks players to grapple with moral choices, often around whether to kill a foe in the name of revenge or spare them and embrace forgiveness. For as awful as characters like Istvan Toth and Markvart von Aulitz are, their villainy is much more palatable since they make their intentions clear from the start. However, the betrayal of Vauquelin Brabant makes him so much more loathsome since his two-faced nature seems to stem from a selfish place, rather than one of ideals, showing a clear parallel to
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  's Micah.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="vauquelin-brabant-is-as-despicable-as-red-dead-redemption-39-s-micah-bell">
  Vauquelin Brabant is as Despicable as Red Dead Redemption's Micah Bell
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1865328975" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1865328975" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1865328975" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1865328975" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1865328975-img" id="article-gallery-1-1865328975">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1865328975" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-945656635">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="micah-bell-is-one-of-gaming-39-s-most-hated-characters">
  Micah Bell is One of Gaming's Most Hated Characters
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  players are likely well acquainted with the villain of Micah Bell, whose misdeeds throughout the course of the game paint him as one of the most treacherous characters in gaming. While Micah is an ally of the Van Der Linde Gang for most of the game, red flags start appearing before he takes a hard left turn toward betrayal. With a suspicious background and questionable behavior shown in the Strawberry Massacre, it's not surprising that Micah ended up as an informant for the Pinkertons, selling out the gang's whereabouts for personal fortune.
 </p>
 <p>
  Traitors are already some of the easiest characters to hate in any narrative, especially those who sell out their comrades for personal gain. What makes Micah an even more despicable traitor is the fact that he manipulated Dutch's paranoia to drive a wedge between him and Arthur so he could secure the money from the Blackwater job for himself. The finale of
  <em>
   RDR2
  </em>
  's epilogue can be one of the most cathartic experiences in the game, where players finally get to kill Micah as John Marston and put an end to his villainy.
 </p>
 <h3 id="brabant-39-s-betrayal-solidifies-him-as-another-micah-bell">
  Brabant's Betrayal Solidifies Him as Another Micah Bell
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's Vauquelin Brabant follows a similar character arc to Micah, and plays a nearly identical role in the game's narrative. Players will first encounter him as a prisoner of Otto von Bergow alongside Hans Capon when Henry sneaks into Maleshov fortress to rescue his liege. Despite having reservations about taking Brabant along in their flight from the fortress, Capon assures Henry that Brabant is an ally, having led the defense of Kuttenberg against Sigismund's army before being captured.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, it's clear that Brabant is only an opportunist after he attempts to run off with the silver Zizka, Henry, and the gang stole from the Italian Court, killing Adder in the process. Although Brabant claims to be a French Baron, a quick look at his history reveals he is a charlatan who stumbled his way into nobility and jumps at the chance to manipulate whoever he can for personal gain. The final twist of the knife comes when it is revealed that Brabant is commanding the Prague troops laying siege to Suchdol castle, and after he captures and tortures Samuel during the Reckoning main quest mission, players can make the easy choice to kill him in the Praguer camp.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     If players choose to spare Brabant here, he will immediately call for guards and blow the player's cover, further demonstrating that he will go to whatever lengths necessary to save his own skin.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  It's not often that players are confronted by truly evil villains in games, and Micah Bell and Vauquelin Brabant are the poster children for these types of traitorous scoundrels. Neither is driven by anything other than their own self-interest, going so far as to sacrifice the lives of the ones they call allies if it helps them achieve their goals. With how detested Micah Bell has become in the gaming community since the release of
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  , it's only fair that Brabant is elevated to the same notoriety in the wake of
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  's release.
 </p>
 <ul class="w-display-card-list even-cards tag-group-video">
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
  <li class="display-card-element">
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jujutsu Infinite: How To Get &amp; Use Fuga Flame Chant</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/roblox-jujutsu-infinite-how-get-use-fuga-flame-chant/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   Roblox
  </em>
  ’s
  <strong>
   <em>
    Jujutsu Infinite
   </em>
  </strong>
  is packed with a variety of innate techniques and skills that help players remove curses. Among these is the Fuga Chant, a move unlike anything else you’ve learned so far. This chant uses the power of fire, triggering a massive blast that burns everything around you to ashes.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While the Fuga Chant is an exceptional move, unlocking it is quite a challenge. Players must not only reach at least level 240, but they must also complete a series of tasks and gather specific materials to get it. For those curious, here's
  <strong>
   how to get the Fuga Chant in
   <em>
    Jujutsu Infinite
   </em>
  </strong>
  and how to use it as well.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-fuga-flame-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Get Fuga Flame Chant In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1257905469" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1257905469" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1257905469" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1257905469" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1257905469-img" id="article-gallery-1-1257905469">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1257905469" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-447698993">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To get the Fuga Chant in
  <em>
   Jujutsu Infinite
  </em>
  , you need to complete the
  <strong>
   Frost Sorcerer
  </strong>
  quest in
  <strong>
   Yuki Fortress
  </strong>
  . This NPC can be found standing outside the last region near the frozen ice fortress. He’ll give you five different quests, each time asking for one of the following materials in exchange for teaching you this special chant:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    1 Cursed Spine
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    1 Cursed Eyes
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    1 Cursed Skull
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    1 Cursed Legs
   </strong>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    1 Cursed Heart
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h3 id="how-to-find-cursed-spine-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Find Cursed Spine In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get fuga chant in jujutsu infinite " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-7.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The first thing Frost Sorcerer asks for is the Cursed Spine. To obtain it, you must
  <strong>
   activate six hidden buttons
  </strong>
  throughout Yuki Fortress, enter the giant temple door near Fortress Commander, and
  <strong>
   light up four torches
  </strong>
  inside. Each torch requires you to stop the mini-game on the blue line and defeat Flame Sorcerers. Failing to do so will reduce your health, but your progress will be saved even if you die.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once all torches are lit and 20 Flame Sorcerers are killed, you'll receive the Cursed Spine—return it to Frost Sorcerer to proceed.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-find-cursed-eyes-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Find Cursed Eyes In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get fuga chant in jujutsu infinite " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-5.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Next, Frost Sorcerer will ask for the Cursed Eyes, which you can snag by
  <strong>
   taking down another player
  </strong>
  at an ancient ritual site. To complete this task, you'll need a teammate who has already got the Cursed Spine. Take them to the site (near the Investigate Quest Level 30), stand on the podiums, and battle each other in the teleported arena.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once your opponent is defeated, you'll receive the Cursed Eyes—give it to Frost Sorcerer to continue.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-find-cursed-skull-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Find Cursed Skull In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get demon blob in jujutsu infinite " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/how-to-get-demon-blob-in-jujutsu-infinite-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The third item needed to unlock the Fuga Chant is the Cursed Skull, which you can get from the Blob Collector. You’ll find her somewhere to the left of Frost Sorcerer.
 </p>
 <p>
  She’ll ask for
  <strong>
   200 Demon Blobs
  </strong>
  in exchange for the Cursed Skull, so you'll need to grind by defeating the
  <strong>
   Heian Imaginary Demon
  </strong>
  (Level 420) multiple times. If you're looking for ways to farm Demon Blobs quickly, this guide might help you.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-find-cursed-legs-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Find Cursed Legs In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get fuga chant in jujutsu infinite " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-fuga-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite-4.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Cursed Legs is the fourth item Frost Sorcerer needs. They are hidden in one of three temples and can be obtained by defeating dangerous curses inside. To unlock the temple gates, you'll need to use specific Demon Vessel techniques, so make sure you have them ready.
 </p>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       <strong>
        Temples
       </strong>
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       <strong>
        Locations
       </strong>
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       <strong>
        Demon Vessel Techniques
       </strong>
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       1
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shijo Town
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Flame Arrow and Switch.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       2
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Shijo Town (Shijo Town Near Level 1 Mission Area)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Dismantle, Cleave, and Flame Arrow.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       3
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Umi Village
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Switch, Dismantle, and Cleave.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once you take down all three Flame Arrow Curses inside, you'll get the Cursed Legs.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-to-find-cursed-heart-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Find Cursed Heart In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Jujutsu Infinite Curse Market" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/demon-fingers-in-jujutsu-infinite-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Cursed Heart is the final item needed for the Fuga Flame Arrow Chant. You can get it from the
  <strong>
   Finger Collector
  </strong>
  , who is the twin brother of the Blob Collector. He’s located behind a rock near Frost Temple in Yuki Fortress and will trade the Cursed Heart for
  <strong>
   20 Demon Fingers
  </strong>
  . You can gather these by opening chests or buying them from the Cursed Market.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once you have the Cursed Heart, hand it over to Frost Sorcerer, and he’ll teach you the Fuga Flame Arrow Chant.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-use-fuga-flame-chant-in-jujutsu-infinite">
  How To Use Fuga Flame Chant In Jujutsu Infinite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1445290352" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1445290352" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1445290352" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1445290352" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1445290352-img" id="article-gallery-2-1445290352">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1445290352" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1519187561">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To use Fuga Chant in
  <em>
   Jujutsu Infinite
  </em>
  , you first need to
  <strong>
   unlock Chanting
  </strong>
  from the technique tab in the stat tree. After that, activate Heian Awakening or get Domain Expansion. Once activated, an orange fuel bar will appear on the left side of the screen—let it fill by dealing damage. When it's full, simply press right-click and Flame Arrow to trigger the chant.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
