<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>New Call of Duty Mobile Games Could Be in Development</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/new-call-of-duty-mobile-games-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Activision is gauging player interest in two new Call of Duty mobile games: Call of Duty: Zombie Defender and Call of Duty: Sniper.
     </li>
     <li>
      Both games are set to be designed specifically for mobile users, with one focusing solely on sniping and the other centered around the fan-favorite Call of Duty Zombies experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      Those wanting to see these games released are invited to provide feedback.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Activision may be exploring the development of multiple
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty
   </em>
  </strong>
  games for mobile devices, further expanding the franchise’s reach. This move would align with the company’s ongoing strategy of bringing one of gaming’s most iconic series to a broader audience by delivering a
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  experience specifically tailored for mobile platforms.
 </p>
 <p>
  Throughout its history,
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  has released numerous titles across different gaming platforms, with consoles remaining the most popular among many players. However, the launch of
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Mobile
  </em>
  in 2019 significantly boosted the franchise’s reach, also impacting Activision’s earnings and helping make mobile gaming one of the largest revenue sources for
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  . This growth expanded further with the release of
  <em>
   Warzone Mobile
  </em>
  in March 2024. While it didn’t achieve the same level of popularity as
  <em>
   CoD Mobile
  </em>
  , it still generated significant revenue for Activision.
 </p>
 <p>
  Recently, Activision has been posting ads on its official social media channels for two new
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  titles:
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Sniper
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Zombie Defender
  </em>
  . Both games are set to be designed specifically for mobile users, with one focusing solely on sniping and the other centered around the fan-favorite
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  Zombies experience. The ads shared by the company feature various AI-generated images showcasing the concept of each game, along with a button linking to a fake mobile store landing page. When players click on the Download button, they are redirected to a survey where they can provide feedback.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="activision-is-reportedly-considering-the-development-of-casual-call-of-duty-mobile-games">
  Activision Is Reportedly Considering the Development of Casual Call of Duty Mobile Games
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Call of Duty: Zombie Defender
  </li>
  <li>
   Call of Duty: Sniper
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  While both
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  mobile games featured in Activision’s social media ads are currently unavailable, they could be developed based on feedback from players through survey responses. If the company sees enough interest, these games could potentially be brought to life. Based on the concept images, it seems that the potential mobile games of
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  could be designed to offer a more casual experience, and one that probably doesn’t require a significant entry investment like the PC and console versions. Instead, much like other popular mobile games, it could allow players to kill time while enjoying a title based on the iconic shooter.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-100746106" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-100746106" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-100746106" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-100746106" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-100746106-img" id="article-gallery-1-100746106">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-100746106" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-295133299">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since this isn’t the premium
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  experience that many players are accustomed to, in which development is kept under wraps and the release is supported by a massive marketing campaign, using targeted ads to directly engage fans is an effective way to test whether the game can generate enough interest. Although it’s unclear whether these experiences will be linked to other
  <em>
   CoD
  </em>
  titles on different platforms if they are ever developed and released, they could still help attract more players to
  <em>
   Call of Duty
  </em>
  , ultimately expanding its player base across all platforms.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Unleashed Gets Unofficial PC Port</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/sonic-unleashed-pc-port/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Fans create an unofficial port of Sonic Unleashed for PC with higher resolution and mod support.
     </li>
     <li>
      The port requires the Xbox 360 version to run.
     </li>
     <li>
      It is uncertain how Sega will react to the project.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  A talented group of fans has created an updated PC port of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic Unleashed
   </em>
  </strong>
  , potentially paving the way for more upscaled versions of old Xbox 360 titles.
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  was released on Xbox 360, PlayStation 2, and Nintendo Wii in late 2008, with a PS3 version launching shortly afterward. It famously saw Sonic transform into a werewolf-like “Werehog” as he raced to gather the Chaos Emeralds and restore the shattered world after another one of Dr. Eggman’s schemes goes awry. As a result,
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  split its gameplay into day and night sections, with the regular Sonic speeding through the former and the Werehog smashing his way across the latter.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  received a mixed reception at launch, with some players praising the game’s impressive graphics and fast-paced daytime platforming sections while others decried the more sluggish,
  <em>
   God of War
  </em>
  -like Werehog segments. Later titles like
  <em>
   Sonic Colors
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Sonic Forces
  </em>
  would reuse the boost gauge mechanic introduced in
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  , and the latter was also represented in
  <em>
   Sonic Generations
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  through the Rooftop Run stage and Egg Dragoon boss battle. However, there was never a PC version of
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  nor any rerelease on modern systems.
 </p>
 <p>
  17 years after
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  was released, a group of fans have taken it upon themselves to develop an unofficial PC port, as reported by IGN. This port, dubbed
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed Recompiled
  </em>
  is no simple PC emulation of the Xbox 360 original. Instead, it is a complete recompiling of the game from the group up, complete with new features like high-resolution support, high framerate support, support for ultra-wide displays, and mod support. It can also run on the Steam Deck, but there is a major catch for curious gamers who wish to try it out.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="unofficial-sonic-unleashed-pc-port-enhances-xbox-360-original">
  Unofficial Sonic Unleashed PC Port Enhances Xbox 360 Original
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-c30e751b49c180af" id="emaki-video-player-c30e751b49c180af">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed Recompiled
  </em>
  requires a copy of the Xbox 360 version of the game to run, as it recompiles the original game files into a playable PC format through a technique called static recompilation. Despite this potential roadblock, Xbox 360 fans are excited about what this unofficial
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  port could mean for other titles of the seventh console generation getting similar PC versions down the line.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-930295586" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-930295586" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-930295586" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-930295586" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-930295586-img" id="article-gallery-1-930295586">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-930295586" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1660595275">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Others are simply thrilled at the chance to play
  <em>
   Sonic Unleashed
  </em>
  , already an impressive visual showcase on its native consoles, with modern hardware and updated graphics. It remains uncertain how Sega will react to this unauthorized
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sonic Unleashed
   </em>
  </strong>
  PC port, as companies like Nintendo have historically taken legal action against similar projects in the past.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Epic Games Store Free Game For March 6 Throws Some Unique Punches</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/epic-games-store-free-game-march-2025-thems-fighting-herds-good/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Epic Games Store
  </strong>
  is still offering free games every week in its seventh year running, remaining to be one of the best ways to expand players' libraries to this day. If gamers check back to the store regularly every Thursday, they can snag a new freebie and see what they can expect next week in advance. As long as players have an account on the Epic Games Store, they can pick from the one or two offerings on the free games page, purchase it at no cost at all, and keep it among the other titles they have or haven't played just yet. The promotion does a great job at helping users return to the store frequently, while also offering players the chance to fill their collections with a wide variety of experiences.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Of course, with how long Epic has been giving players this opportunity, there's bound to be a few repeat offerings down the line. The title being given away on March 6 is an example, offered for the first time as a December mystery game back in 2022. While this may make those who have already snagged the fighting game being offered feel like they're missing out on a new game they were looking forward to this week, it's ultimately a good thing that the former mystery game is being offered once again. Whether players either missed the one-day window for its mystery game debut, or simply weren't around to grab it the first time,
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  will be free once again for an entire week.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="epic-games-store-free-game-them-39-s-fightin-39-herds-explained">
  Epic Games Store Free Game Them's Fightin' Herds Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-393721927" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-393721927" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-393721927" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-393721927" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-393721927-img" id="article-gallery-1-393721927">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-393721927" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-621326235">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  originally began as a fan game for a popular TV show that began back in 2010, but was given a cease and desist order by the intellectual property owner during development. Instead of scrapping the entire project, however, the development team known as Mane6 decided to keep the core gameplay mechanics they created and create a game that was wholly original.
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  was then released, featuring critters made by the character designer of the very show that was the game's original inspiration,
  <em>
   My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  carries the passion it began with into the final product, impressing as a beautifully hand-drawn classic fighting game.
 </p>
 <p>
  Mane6's four-legged brawler holds a "great for beginners" designation on its Epic Games Store page, serving as a statement about how accessible
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  is while also staying true to the genre's expectations. Rollback netcode, juggle decay, and personalized adaptive music for each fighter are only just the beginning of the many features that elevate
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  ' refreshing yet familiar experience that makes itself fun to learn yet challenging to master. Unfortunately, while the core gameplay and matchmaking features are well-crafted and full of depth, other parts of
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  were cut short, like the game's Story Mode.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even still,
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  has been praised as a worthwhile fighting game by fans, while also holding a "strong" rating on OpenCritic through its reviews. If players try out the title through Epic and like what it offers, there are plenty of DLC characters to buy and try out afterward for more action. On top of that, through
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  being available for seven days rather than one, there's time for players to try the game out and spread the word among friends to enjoy it together online or locally.
 </p>
 <p>
  Fighting games aren't for everyone, and
  <em>
   Them's Fightin' Herds
  </em>
  is already an underdog through its
  <em>
   My Little Pony
  </em>
  inspiration, leading potential players to judge it at first glance. While the chance to try
  <em>
   Them's Fighting Herds
  </em>
  for free opens up an avenue for many players to find something to enjoy with what it offers, some gamers might want a different game over
  <em>
   Them's Fighting Herds
  </em>
  for their own reasons. Luckily for the uninterested players, there is always another Epic Games Store freebie around the corner with the next game set to be announced on March 6 at 10 AM CT.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds' Wound Mechanic is a Double-Edged Sword</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monster-hunter-wilds-wound-mechanic-damage-stagger-easy-hunts-strategy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </strong>
  </em>
  ' wound mechanic is a powerful new feature, but it might not be the best idea that the game introduced. Players will undoubtedly see the wound mechanic in action a lot during
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , and in that time, they will undoubtedly benefit from it time and time again. However, while wounds are definitely useful, it may be worth questioning how well the mechanic fits into
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  . The game just came out, so there's plenty of time to see how it works. However, it remains to be seen if
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  will be its sole appearance.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Taking on hunts in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  requires a solid strategy, just like in past games. Every monster has their own threats that players have to look out for, and every weapon gives players a different set of skills to deal with them. These are in addition to general skills such as dodging and knowing when to back away to heal or sharpen the hunter's weapon.
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  has a lot of intricacies, and players will only find more the longer they play the game. With
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , players will have even more elements to experiment with against the game's roster of monsters.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="wounds-are-powerful-but-easy-to-exploit-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  Wounds Are Powerful, but Easy to Exploit in Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-755906380" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-755906380" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-755906380" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-755906380" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-755906380-img" id="article-gallery-1-755906380">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-755906380" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1436956708">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="wounds-are-a-reliable-damage-source-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  Wounds Are a Reliable Damage Source in Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h3>
 <p>
  With the new wound mechanic in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  , monsters will receive visible injuries as they take damage. By hitting a wound, players will be able to deal bonus damage with each hit. Hitting a wound enough will cause it to explode, dealing heavy damage and momentarily stunning the monster. Using Focus Mode will make wounds more visible while also enabling the player to use powerful Focus Strikes, which hit incredibly hard, but will instantly remove the wound after completion. Wounds introduce a new element to
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  that players can easily use to their advantage in almost any hunt.
 </p>
 <h3 id="exploiting-wounds-makes-monster-hunter-wilds-39-hunts-easier">
  Exploiting Wounds Makes Monster Hunter Wilds' Hunts Easier
 </h3>
 <p>
  The usefulness of wounds is evident even in the earliest stage of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  . Since wounds occur naturally during a hunt as long as the player is dealing damage, they present a clear target for the player to focus on. With the bonus damage and eventual staggering from the wound explosion, it offers a significant reward for simply attacking the same area repeatedly. The mechanic makes sense, and the player has to keep up their attacks lest the opportunity pass them by. However, utilizing wounds is much easier than most methods of inflicting stuns or heavy damage that they arguably make the hunts less challenging.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Wounds introduce a new element to
     <em>
      Monster Hunter Wilds
     </em>
     that players can easily use to their advantage in almost any hunt.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="monster-hunter-wilds-has-other-tricks-more-intricate-than-wounds">
  Monster Hunter Wilds Has Other Tricks More Intricate Than Wounds
 </h3>
 <p>
  Historically, the main ways to stun monsters have involved using
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  's crafted traps, or using environmental hazards to ensnare them. For instance, Paratoads can temporarily paralyze both monsters and hunters, and certain net-like grounds can entrap a monster. These options leave the monster open for whatever combos the player has in store. These methods require planning and positioning, but it's incredibly rewarding to pull it off. In comparison, attacking wounds is easy, although the stun from wound explosions is much shorter. Simply put, attacking wounds doesn't teach players to be resourceful, while
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  's other tricks teach that in spades.
 </p>
 <p>
  Wounds are undoubtedly a major aspect of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  ' strategy. However, while players just starting in
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  will benefit greatly from them, they do admittedly make plenty of hunts easier than anticipated. Of course, there's nothing wrong with the game being welcoming to new players. At the same time, a lot of
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  's appeal comes from the long, challenging hunts that players can throw themselves into. With wounds being an easily-available source of damage andd stuns,
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds
  </em>
  ' monsters seem a little less intimidating.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Blue Prince Devs Added Exploration and Strategy into the Puzzle Mix</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/blue-prince-genre-features-puzzles-exploration-strategy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Publisher Raw Fury has teamed up with independent studio Dogubomb to release the new puzzle game,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Blue Prince,
   </em>
  </strong>
  on April 10. This is Dogubomb's debut title, as the studio has worked on
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  for over eight years. At first glance, players might think the game is another linear puzzle adventure, but there is more than meets the eye when it comes to
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The game adds exploration to its formula by asking players to discover the room route of the Mt. Holly estate. At the same time, the house is filled with different puzzles and riddles that will help the player progress through the story and find Room 46. The house resets itself each dawn, however, prompting players to draw up a new blueprint every day. This progression reset system makes every day in
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  unpredictable. In an interview with Game Rant ahead of
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  's release, Dogumbomb director and game creator Tonda Ros explained how the game challenges players with these elements.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="blue-prince-progression-reset-system-explained">
  Blue Prince Progression Reset System Explained
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1879983186" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1879983186" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1879983186" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1879983186" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1879983186-img" id="article-gallery-1-1879983186">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1879983186" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1458446289">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  According to Ros, one of the biggest flaws of the puzzle genre is how more traditional puzzle games can cause a player to get stuck in the same challenge. As a result, players will be forced to either look up the solution to a puzzle or give up on progressing entirely. "It's a binary check," as Ros puts it, adding,
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "In Blue Prince, however, you will always have the option to move on and keep exploring. If you run out of options, you can always just begin a new day with all new rooms. Nothing will be stopping or blocking you from progressing".
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  , players are transported to the Mt. Holly house and are tasked to find Room 46. Every time they encounter a closed door, players can choose which kind of room they wish to explore from a random set of three. Some rooms include puzzles or bonuses, while others can involve setbacks. For example, a pantry grants players coins, while a closet gives them two items. As they explore the mansion, players draft a blueprint of 45 slots, presented in a 5x9 table format, to avoid dead ends and see how far they are from Room 46.
 </p>
 <p>
  In addition, every time players enter a room, a step is taken. Once they run out of steps, they are forced to "call it a day" and the house resets itself the next dawn. Players will then start a new blueprint with new choices and rooms. Comparable to a roguelike game, this progression reset element in
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  dares players to really analyze their next step. As Ros describes, players can also use the reset to their advantage so that no puzzle can stop their playthrough. Moreover, some upgrades to the blueprint are permanent, though these bonuses are harder to find.
 </p>
 <p>
  To Ros, coming up with strategies is one of the most fun aspects of the game, and one of his goals was to craft a game that "both strategic players and puzzle enthusiasts could enjoy." Ros adds that another key aspect of the game is exploration because the many puzzles in
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  have multiple solutions instead of a single one. The multiple items and clues that are found while exploring can provide alternate routes to the puzzles' originally intended solutions. Ros comments that this encourages players' creativity when bypassing obstacles while also balancing out puzzle difficulty:
 </p>
 <blockquote>
  <p>
   "To that end, puzzle difficulty is largely determined by the player themselves by allowing them to solve things at their own pace whenever they feel they have enough information".
  </p>
 </blockquote>
 <p>
  Ros remarks that Dogubomb has been playtesting
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  since 2020, and the team spent the past four years watching "hundreds of hours of playthroughs" to polish
  <strong>
   <em>
    Blue Prince
   </em>
  </strong>
  . He believes that the largely positive response to
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  's demo has made the effort spent feel worth it. Considering that the demo only gave players a four-day playthrough, Ros says it will be interesting to see which puzzles and challenges will be players' favorites once the full game is released.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
