<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals: 6 Heroes Who Need Nerfs (Season 1)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-heroes-who-need-nerfs/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Season 1 of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has brought about a few nerfs and buffs to some famed heroes, but perhaps some buffs might have been too much, some nerfs not enough, and some heroes have gone completely untouched. There are some truly overpowered heroes in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , and a few balances never hurt anyone to keep the competition fair and the meta evolving.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While sometimes an overpowered character can be fun, for others, it can be pretty infuriating. As
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  heads through Season 1, it’s a good time to look at some heroes that could do with a few balancing tweaks and nerfs.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="iron-fist">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Iron Fist
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-highly-mobile-aggressive-easy-to-use-duelist">
  A Highly Mobile, Aggressive, Easy-to-Use Duelist
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-563954163" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-563954163" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-563954163" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-563954163" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-563954163-img" id="article-gallery-1-563954163">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-563954163" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-359327380">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Duelist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       4/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Despite Iron Fist’s low attack range as a melee Duelist, he more than makes up for it with his abilities and mobility. Iron Fist is extremely fast, and within seconds he can be in his enemy’s backlines, punching the life out of Strategists and beating up flying characters until they drop dead. There’s hardly anything that can stop it, and it’s pretty annoying when one considers Iron Fist’s attack is basically just holding down one button.
 </p>
 <p>
  Iron Fist can recover health with his Harmony Recovery ability, which means he doesn’t even need a Strategist to pocket-heal him in case of emergencies. His kicks and punches mean he is always attacking and always on the move, and his move set just seems so unfairly in his favor to keep his health and damage top-notch.
 </p>
 <h2 id="scarlet-witch">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Scarlet Witch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="chaos-magic-has-too-much-range-accuracy-and-infinite-ammo">
  Chaos Magic Has Too Much Range, Accuracy, and Infinite Ammo
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1782476927" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1782476927" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1782476927" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1782476927" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1782476927-img" id="article-gallery-2-1782476927">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1782476927" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1502243792">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Duelist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Scarlet Witch might only be able to focus on one enemy at a time, but thanks to her abilities of attack, that enemy isn’t exactly going to last long. Scarlet Witch doesn’t require skill to use as her main method of attack is her drain the life of her enemies by holding her attack button. The range is too generous, and the fact that it’s an infinite stream with no punishment, paired with an auto-aim feature, makes Scarlet Witch a bit too strong.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sure, Scarlet Witch’s Ultimate is pretty hard to get right considering she is so easy to delete in this vulnerable state, but her primary attack definitely needs some work, as the Chthonian Burst attack requires no time to use during her Chaos Control, leading to fast and punishing kills all around.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="hela">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Hela
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-goddess-of-death-negates-previous-nerfs">
  The Goddess of Death Negates Previous Nerfs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1760774794" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1760774794" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1760774794" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1760774794" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1760774794-img" id="article-gallery-3-1760774794">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1760774794" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-466920029">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Duelist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  A brutal Duelist whose main attack methods of Nightsword Thorns provide easy and deadly headshots, while still being hitscan instead of projectiles, proves that despite recent nerfs, Hela is unstoppable. Hela is extremely deadly, and her single-cast direct-hit weapons can almost two-shot most heroes, and the easy fix to that is to make it so that she cannot do extra damage with headshots.
 </p>
 <p>
  Hela’s other abilities make it so that she can easily escape the fight and get to high ground, and her explosive stuns and Astral Flock transformations mean she’s always around to cause further death. Her invulnerable and unkillable Goddess of Death Ultimate is also a cause for concern, and the fact that her team-up with Thor and Loki means she can resurrect them both is disastrous for opposing teams.
 </p>
 <h2 id="luna-snow">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Luna Snow
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-dazzling-pop-star-hero-with-too-much-healing">
  A Dazzling Pop Star Hero With Too Much Healing
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-634276555" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-634276555" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-634276555" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-634276555" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-634276555-img" id="article-gallery-4-634276555">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-634276555" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1197815382">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Strategist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       275
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Luna Snow benefits greatly from her high healing output, which can both save allies’ lives in the middle of a fight by restoring their HP and granting them ability bonuses to further infuriate their enemies. Luna also has great mobility thanks to her skating, so she’s never too far away from her allies. If an enemy gets too close? She can just freeze them. Her kit is great, but it might be a bit too much for a Strategist.
 </p>
 <p>
  Where Luna Snow really needs a nerf is in her Ultimate, as it provides the entire team who are within her vicinity with invincibility for 12 seconds. 12 entire seconds in a Hero Shooter where players cannot be damaged? That might be a little bit too much.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="iron-man">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Iron Man
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-genius-who-fights-from-the-sky-with-overpowered-attacks">
  A Genius Who Fights From the Sky With Overpowered Attacks
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-207718260" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-207718260" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-207718260" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-207718260" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-207718260-img" id="article-gallery-5-207718260">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-207718260" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-296669894">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Duelist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       2/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Iron Man always stays in the air, making him the perfect counter to enemies that are using melee-focused Duelists like Magik and Wolverine. With Iron Man’s air abilities, he’s going to constantly cause trouble for the backlines as he shoots out deadly Repulsor Blasts, Unibeams, and Micro-Missle Barrages, while staying mobile and in the air to make him a hard target to reach as the enemy team advances on the ground.
 </p>
 <p>
  Iron Man is a true nuisance, and his Ultimate ability allows him to charge up an attack within seconds, where a direct hit is an insta-kill. Iron Man is lethal in the sky, so it would be nice to either see his abilities have a more punishing cooldown or provide him with limited air-time. After all, he can be considered one of the best Duelists in the game when Hulk is on the same team thanks to the extra damage with the Gamma Overdrive.
 </p>
 <h2 id="storm">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Storm
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-goddess-of-weather-who-storms-the-battlefield">
  The Goddess of Weather Who Storms the Battlefield
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1527647114" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1527647114" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1527647114" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1527647114" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1527647114-img" id="article-gallery-6-1527647114">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1527647114" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-2061963680">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Role
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Duelist
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Health
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       250
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Difficulty
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3/5
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Storm was regarded as one of the worst duelists in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , but with her day-one buffs in Season 1, she has easily become one of the best. Storm is extremely deadly to fight against, and part of the reason is her primary long-range attacks of Wind Blades that can pierce through enemies, meaning those in a cluster will all feel the deadly weather attacks of Storm.
 </p>
 <p>
  Storm can also buff herself and her allies with different attacks, providing the team with support from the skies that is almost unstoppable. If Storm also uses her Omega Hurricane Ultimate, then she is practically invincible as she engulfs the area in a deadly storm that will kill anyone who touches it. While she desperately needed buffs in Season 1, the team might have gone a bit too far.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims 4 Players Make Important Realization About Sulani</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-sims-4-sulani-daily-events/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Sulani in The Sims 4 hosts daily events, like the Town BBQ and Beach Bonfire, which many fans were unaware of.
     </li>
     <li>
      Based on Polynesian and Hawaiian islands, Sulani features community-based islands and locations like the Cave of Sulani.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Sims 4 recently confirmed updates for its 25th anniversary, including new in-game items and performance enhancements.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Fans of
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Sims 4
   </strong>
  </em>
  have recently noticed a crucial detail about the island of Sulani, claiming they never noticed the location hosts daily events before.
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  was first released in 2014 by developer Maxis and publisher Electronic Arts, and the fourth main installment switched to a free-to-play model with paid DLCs in 2022. 17 expansion packs, including
  <em>
   Island Living
  </em>
  , and 12 game packs with additional features and items have been added to the game thus far, with the most recent expansion being
  <em>
   Life &amp; Death
  </em>
  released in October 2024.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  recently confirmed two major updates to the life sim to celebrate the franchise’s 25th anniversary, and the first one arrived on January 14. The updates will feature a refreshed main menu with over 70 new in-game items. Players will also be treated to redesigned townie homes, three new kits, and a Blast From The Past event featuring 2000s-inspired rewards, including a telephone and an alarm clock. Performance enhancements, covering mouse responsiveness, and better graphics rendering were other improvements, and fans can expect the second update to arrive on February 4.
 </p>
 <p>
  Posted on Reddit by Snookified, a screenshot of the Sulani map was posted in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  subreddit, highlighting the different icons populating the location. The player asked if they were the only one who didn’t know Sulani hosted daily events and also admitted they were unaware of The Pavilion’s existence. Luckily, for the uninitiated, the player posted a list of Sulani’s daily events, and some even rival the best events and parties created through
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  ’s handy mods.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-sims-4-players-discover-sulani-hosts-daily-events">
  The Sims 4 Players Discover Sulani Hosts Daily Events
 </h2>
 <p>
  The complete
  <em>
   Island Living
  </em>
  experience in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  is harnessed within the picturesque Sulani, and the community was just as clueless about the island’s daily events as the original poster. Fans now have the Town BBQ, a Beach Bonfire, a Fishing Competition, a Flowers and Music Festival, and much more to look forward to.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1116843017" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1116843017" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1116843017" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1116843017" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1116843017-img" id="article-gallery-1-1116843017">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1116843017" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-915582904">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The world of Sulani was introduced in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  ’s seventh expansion pack,
  <em>
   Island Living
  </em>
  , and is based on the Polynesian and Hawaiian Islands. The expanse has community-based islands featuring Ohan'ali Town, Lani St. Taz, and Mua Pel'amand, with an abandoned island that harbors a volcano. Completing the Cave of Sulani in
  <em>
   The Sims 4
  </em>
  is a must, as the location is nothing short of a hidden gem with plenty to explore, such as unique items and adventure, and as the Redditor discovered, there are plenty of events to teach players about the local culture.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Role-Playing Games People Are Excited For</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/new-rpg-games-upcoming/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <div class="w-table-content">
  <h3 class="title icon i-flash">
   Quick Links
  </h3>
  <div class="table-content">
   <div class="w-table-content-list">
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Citizen Sleeper 2: Starward Vector
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Avowed
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Monster Hunter Wilds
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Suikoden 1 &amp; 2 HD Remaster
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Assassin's Creed Shadows
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Atelier Yumia: The Alchemist of Memories &amp; the Envisioned Land
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       AI Limit
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       The First Berserker: Khazan
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Borderlands 4
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Vampire: The Masquerade – Bloodlines 2
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Pokemon Legends: Z-A
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Moonlighter 2: The Endless Vault
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Pathologic 3
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       The Witcher 4
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       The Elder Scrolls 6
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
    <ul class="table-content-list">
     <li class="table-content-element icon">
      <div class="table-content-link">
       Dragon Quest 12: The Flames Of Fate
      </div>
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Role-playing games have been a staple of the gaming industry for more than three decades. Each month, the genre tends to welcome a couple of noteworthy titles, be it high-profile releases such as
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Lies of P
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Octopath Traveler 2
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Baldur's Gate 3
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty
  </em>
  or more niche projects like
  <em>
   Labyrinth of Galleria: The Moon Society
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   8-Bit Adventures 2
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Little Witch Nobeta
  </em>
  . There are always
  <strong>
   new RPGs
  </strong>
  on the horizon.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Due to the ambitious nature of the genre's AAA projects, they are often announced years in advance, a practice that can result in extremely high expectations. Once the hype train gets moving, stopping it can be impossible, which has resulted in some disappointments in the past. However, when a game lives up to its potential, it is a thing of beauty. Which
  <strong>
   upcoming RPGs
  </strong>
  are the most sought-after?
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Updated January 22, 2025 by Mark Sammut:
   </strong>
   The article has been updated with two
   <strong>
    upcoming role-playing games
   </strong>
   : Citizen Sleeper 2 and AI Limit.
  </em>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="citizen-sleeper-2-starward-vector">
  Citizen Sleeper 2: Starward Vector
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-tabletop-inspired-sci-fi-rpg">
  A Tabletop-Inspired Sci-Fi RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1693359623" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1693359623" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1693359623" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1693359623" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1693359623-img" id="article-gallery-1-1693359623">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1693359623" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1735083680">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Building on the novel foundation set by 2022's
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper
  </em>
  , the sequel seems set to expand on the strengths that made its predecessor such a joy to experience. Unlike most RPGs that focus on action and combat,
  <em>
   Citizen Sleeper 2: Starward Vector
  </em>
  is all about interactivity and choice. The campaign casts players as a Sleeper trying to run a crew in the Starward Belt, all while attempting to avoid capture.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     A Sleeper is a robot with a human mind.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Compared to the previous game, which was primarily set in one location,
  <em>
   Starward Vector
  </em>
  seems to focus heavily on managing a ship and its crew, and the setting covers different locations/hubs rather than one fixed sector. As before, dice throws will play a significant role in outcomes, and players will be able to select from a range of classes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="kingdom-come-deliverance-2">
  Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="ambitious-open-world-medieval-rpg-with-a-focus-on-realism">
  Ambitious Open-World Medieval RPG With A Focus On Realism
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2029553523" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2029553523" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2029553523" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2029553523" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2029553523-img" id="article-gallery-2-2029553523">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2029553523" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-593918482">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Warhorse's
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance
  </em>
  teleports players to the Middle Ages, dropping them in a detailed and vast rendition of Central Bohemia. With slow pacing, challenging combat, and an emphasis on authenticity, the 2018 game is an impressive work of art, even if it might not appeal to everyone. The sequel will debut at the beginning of 2025, and early indications suggest that Warhorse has primarily doubled down on the original's strengths and uniqueness.
 </p>
 <p>
  Going by the gameplay footage shown so far,
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  seems set to be even more immersive than its predecessor, which is no easy feat. While the first game was a slow-burn hit that gained momentum from word of mouth, the sequel seems likely to hit the ground running, especially as more hype builds in the coming months.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="avowed">
  Avowed
 </h2>
 <h3 id="obsidian-39-s-next-action-rpg">
  Obsidian's Next Action RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-342351625" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-342351625" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-342351625" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-342351625" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-342351625-img" id="article-gallery-3-342351625">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-342351625" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-943364391">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A new Obsidian project is always a cause for celebration, and
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  seems set to be among the developer's most ambitious endeavors to date. While set in the
  <em>
   Pillars of Eternity
  </em>
  universe, the
  <strong>
   upcoming RPG
  </strong>
  should be quite a different beast. For one,
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  is a real-time action game played either from a first or third-person perspective, which stands in stark contrast with
  <em>
   PoE
  </em>
  's isometric presentation.
 </p>
 <p>
  Although only a few elements have been revealed so far, the RPG seems set to feature a robust magic system, along with skill trees that grant players some choice in how they build their characters (which makes sense considering Obsidian's track record).
 </p>
 <p>
  Obsidian has kept most of
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's story under wraps for now, only revealing that players will step into the shoes of a character who is assigned to investigate a plague. Also, companions will be part of the experience.
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  has been delayed from 2024 to 2025, but it will hopefully be worth the wait.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_24">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      The Outer Worlds 2
     </em>
     is also on the horizon and a very exciting prospect.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii">
  Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-action-adventure-game-with-rpg-mechanics">
  An Action-Adventure Game With RPG Mechanics
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-192630788" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-192630788" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-192630788" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-192630788" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-192630788-img" id="article-gallery-4-192630788">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-192630788" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-1045725796">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not a turn-based RPG like the most recent mainline entries in Sega's franchise,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  still warrants a recommendation for anyone craving a role-playing game, albeit one with beat 'em up-style action combat. For this bizarre spin-off, Goro Majima will be taking center stage, trading the yakuza life for the high seas in the process.
 </p>
 <p>
  Outlandish as this concept sounds,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  has a great track record for taking unorthodox premises and running with them, incorporating the typical fantastic writing that has come to define the entire IP. Besides returning to real-time combat,
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  looks set to allow players to piece together a crew and upgrade their ship, which they will need to do to survive battles on the sea.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="monster-hunter-wilds">
  Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <h3 id="capcom-39-s-action-epic-with-rpg-elements">
  Capcom's Action Epic With RPG Elements
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-381097522" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-381097522" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-381097522" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-381097522" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-381097522-img" id="article-gallery-5-381097522">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-381097522" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-2143544154">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A new
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  is always a cause for celebration, and
  <em>
   Wilds
  </em>
  looks primed and ready to be an impressive work of art. Capcom has confirmed that a February 2025 release is on the cards and that the game will launch on the PS5, PC, and Xbox Series X/S; consequently,
  <em>
   Wilds
  </em>
  will likely have more in common with
  <em>
   World
  </em>
  rather than
  <em>
   Rise
  </em>
  since the latter was designed around the Nintendo Switch's limitations, resulting in fairly small maps compared to its predecessor.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, an argument could be made that
  <em>
   Monster Hunter
  </em>
  exists in a unique category outside of RPGs, which is certainly fair. Still, the games always incorporate a variety of role-playing elements, and they are generally good picks for fans of the genre who want to focus on action over story.
 </p>
 <h2 id="suikoden-1-amp-2-hd-remaster">
  Suikoden 1 &amp; 2 HD Remaster
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-compilation-containing-two-jrpg-classics">
  A Compilation Containing Two JRPG Classics
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1295771606" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1295771606" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1295771606" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1295771606" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1295771606-img" id="article-gallery-6-1295771606">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1295771606" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1240272189">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Putting aside spin-offs, the last
  <em>
   Suikoden
  </em>
  games debuted in 2006, nearly two decades ago by this point. The world has gone way too long without a new mainline entry, and while a sequel does not appear to be on the horizon, Konami is at least revisiting the first two games in the form of an HD remaster compilation package.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, the revealed improvements and changes are fairly ordinary, mostly focusing on improved backgrounds, animations, and basic quality-of-life adjustments like auto-save and a fast-forward for battles. This package seems set to play things safe and mostly just preserve the base games. Fortunately,
  <em>
   Suikoden
  </em>
  and its sequel are timeless masterpieces.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="xenoblade-chronicles-x-definitive-edition">
  Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
 </h2>
 <h3 id="action-rpg-with-mecha">
  Action RPG With Mecha
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1981890276" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1981890276" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1981890276" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1981890276" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1981890276-img" id="article-gallery-7-1981890276">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1981890276" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1019399256">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Nintendo has been leaning a bit heavily on remakes and remasters in the last few years, but the games themselves are still exciting. With the arrival of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  , all the mainline entries in the series will now be available on the Nintendo Switch, making the hybrid console the definitive way to experience Monolith Soft's fantastic franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  A spin-off confined to the Wii U,
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  tends to not receive quite as much love as its numbered brethren, which is a shame as it has arguably one of the best combat systems in the series. Even in 2015, the game's open-world and visuals were very impressive, and the
  <em>
   Definitive Edition
  </em>
  seems to come with a notable upgrade. Nintendo even mentioned new story content.
 </p>
 <h2 id="assassin-39-s-creed-shadows">
  Assassin's Creed Shadows
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stealth-action-adventure-rpg">
  Stealth Action-Adventure RPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1229507578" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1229507578" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1229507578" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1229507578" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1229507578-img" id="article-gallery-8-1229507578">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1229507578" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1621919631">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While not everyone loved the shift,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  has been steadily implementing more RPG elements since
  <em>
   Origins
  </em>
  , with
  <em>
   Mirage
  </em>
  being an exception. Ubisoft's upcoming entry,
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , looks set to continue this trend, at least according to comments made in this Xbox interview by its Game Director, Charles Benoit. Set in Feudal Japan, this project will feature two protagonists, a shinobi named Naoe and a samurai called Yasuke. Except for certain missions, players will be able to swap between these characters on the fly, and they have unique skills, weapons, and playstyles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Every
  <em>
   Assassin's Creed
  </em>
  game is a big deal, but
  <em>
   Shadows
  </em>
  appears to be attracting more hype than usual. Part of that has to do with the setting, as fans have been craving a Japan-based adventure for years. The dual-protagonist structure is also compelling, especially since Naoe seems to be designed to facilitate stealth-based combat similar to the older entries in the series.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_57">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Originally scheduled for November 2024,
     <em>
      Assassin's Creed Shadows
     </em>
     was pushed back to March 20, 2025.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="atelier-yumia-the-alchemist-of-memories-amp-the-envisioned-land">
  Atelier Yumia: The Alchemist of Memories &amp; the Envisioned Land
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-new-alchemy-themed-jrpg-adventure-with-a-switch-to-real-time-combat">
  A New Alchemy-Themed JRPG Adventure With A Switch To Real-Time Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1895053700" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1895053700" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1895053700" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1895053700" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1895053700-img" id="article-gallery-9-1895053700">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1895053700" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-1973228009">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gust's
  <em>
   Atelier
  </em>
  has never enjoyed the same level of exposure and popularity as, for example,
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  or even
  <em>
   Tales
  </em>
  , but the franchise has been fairly consistent over the decades. The
  <em>
   Ryza
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Sophie
  </em>
  subseries generally performed really well, showcasing the IP at its best and arguably attracting the most attention up to this point. As tends to happen every couple of entries, Gust is preparing to launch into a new era by introducing a new protagonist, although the proposed changes seem to be far more expansive than just a new female lead.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Atelier Yumia
  </em>
  will utilize a real-time combat system rather than the traditional turn-based battles that make up the older entries. Now, to be fair,
  <em>
   Atelier
  </em>
  has focused on delivering flashy battle animations for a while, and
  <em>
   Yumia
  </em>
  's version seems to still focus quite a bit on ranged spells and combo chains; consequently, this shift might not revamp the core gameplay loop to the point of feeling like a complete departure from the status quo. Anyway, it looks pretty great, and Gust (and Koei Tecmo) deserve praise for trying something new.
 </p>
 <p>
  Naturally,
  <em>
   Atelier
  </em>
  would not be
  <em>
   Atelier
  </em>
  without a robust synthesis system, something that will almost certainly not be neglected by the
  <strong>
   upcoming 2025 RPG
  </strong>
  . Players will be spending a lot of time creating items that can be used either in battles or while exploring the world.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ai-limit">
  AI Limit
 </h2>
 <h3 id="another-anime-soulslike">
  Another Anime Soulslike
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-1190088712" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-1190088712" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-1190088712" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-1190088712" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-1190088712-img" id="article-gallery-10-1190088712">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-1190088712" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1891306321">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Soulslikes are not that exciting nowadays because they are so plentiful.
  <em>
   AI Limit
  </em>
  might just end up being another entry in an RPG subgenre that has threatened to become overexposed in recent years, destined to be forgotten within a few weeks of its debut. However, the demo is pretty decent, and the anime aesthetic sets it apart from the crowd to an extent (except for
  <em>
   Code Vein
  </em>
  , of course).
 </p>
 <p>
  Gameplay-wise,
  <em>
   AI Limit
  </em>
  sticks fairly close to the Soulslike blueprint, albeit with a few unorthodox tweaks like a transformation mechanic. Still, the game might not hold too many surprises for people who are very familiar with these types of releases, and that does not have to be a negative thing.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_72">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     <em>
      AI Limit
     </em>
     's demo is available on both Steam and the PlayStation Store.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-first-berserker-khazan">
  The First Berserker: Khazan
 </h2>
 <h3 id="action-rpg-with-intense-soulslike-combat">
  Action RPG With Intense Soulslike Combat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-11-345721609" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-11-345721609" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-11-345721609" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-11-345721609" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-11-345721609-img" id="article-gallery-11-345721609">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-11-345721609" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-11">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-11-slides-container-1558687331">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Coming from a relatively unknown studio but set within a popular international franchise (
  <em>
   Dungeon Fighter Online
  </em>
  ),
  <em>
   The First Berserker: Khazan
  </em>
  looks impressive from its gameplay footage so far, which depicts a dark fantasy world and fairly fast-paced, stylish combat (and bloody).
 </p>
 <p>
  As with any of these types of projects,
  <em>
   The First Berserker: Khazan
  </em>
  's quality will be difficult to predict without hands-on time to determine how good the gameplay feels. Fortunately, the title will be an Xbox Game Pass Day One release, so a lot of players will be able to check it out.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_79">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     <em>
      The First Berserker: Khazan
     </em>
     's demo is available on PC, Xbox, and the PlayStation Store.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h2 id="clair-obscur-expedition-33">
  Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-turn-based-rpg-with-a-dark-fantasy-setting">
  A Turn-Based RPG With A Dark Fantasy Setting
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-12-793819107" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-12-793819107" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-12-793819107" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-12-793819107" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-12-793819107-img" id="article-gallery-12-793819107">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-12-793819107" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-12">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-12-slides-container-1816047652">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  seems fascinating so far, at least based on the available footage and information. Sandfall Interactive is crafting a turn-based RPG set in a unique fantasy world that has a fascinating aesthetic that is almost surreal, with the main antagonist being a Paintress who has the power to kill anyone of a certain age. That concept is great and has an almost cosmic horror aspect to it.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a nice change of pace for a Western developer,
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  utilizes a combat system that appears to blend classic JRPG elements with real-time commands, hopefully finding a middle-ground that highlights the strengths of both styles. The game is also built in Unreal Engine 5, so it should look pretty spectacular.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_87">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     <em>
      Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
     </em>
     is expected to launch at $49.99 to make it as accessible as possible.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="borderlands-4">
  Borderlands 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="looter-shooter">
  Looter-Shooter
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-13-473324887" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-13-473324887" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-13-473324887" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-13-473324887" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-13-473324887-img" id="article-gallery-13-473324887">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-13-473324887" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-13">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-13-slides-container-1927194982">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gearbox's
  <em>
   Borderlands
  </em>
  is the definitive looter-shooter franchise, and it does not really have any major challengers. Despite garnering an array of criticisms that might not make them 100% beloved,
  <em>
   Borderlands 3
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Tiny Tina's Wonderlands
  </em>
  are still fantastic co-op shooters with more than enough RPG elements to satisfy people who want to explore different builds and loadouts.
  <em>
   Borderlands 4
  </em>
  is loosely slated for a 2025 release, although very little is known about the sequel at this point. The
  <em>
   B4
  </em>
  reveal trailer did not include too much information, and the same can be said for the available concept art.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite the lack of information, the project is still surrounded by plenty of excitement, simply due to the IP's mostly positive reputation. There are just not all that many alternatives to
  <em>
   Borderlands
  </em>
  , and the fourth entry will likely be "good" at a minimum.
 </p>
 <h2 id="vampire-the-masquerade-ndash-bloodlines-2">
  Vampire: The Masquerade – Bloodlines 2
 </h2>
 <h3 id="action-amp-social-sim">
  Action &amp; Social Sim
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-14-1051678739" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-14-1051678739" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-14-1051678739" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-14-1051678739" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-14-1051678739-img" id="article-gallery-14-1051678739">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-14-1051678739" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-14">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-14-slides-container-1799781088">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Vampire: The Masquerade – Bloodlines
  </em>
  is the definition of a cult classic. While rough around the edges, the RPG features fantastic writing and characters, along with a great deal of customization that provides players with plenty of creative freedom. It is a masterpiece that, for the longest time, seemed destined to remain a solitary project (in the video game industry, anyway); however, in 2019,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Bloodlines 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  was revealed to the world. Since then, the game has been pushed back a few times, and information regarding its production has been inconsistent. That said, a few
  <em>
   Vampire: The Masquerade
  </em>
  spin-offs have debuted over the last few years, so the IP is alive.
 </p>
 <p>
  Set in Seattle,
  <em>
   Bloodlines 2
  </em>
  will let players create a newly transformed vampire, which will involve picking things like their human background and preferred discipline.
  <em>
   Vampire: The Masquerade
  </em>
  's success can be partially credited to its deep clan system, which permits players to commit to one of the vampire groups operating in the city. This element should be present in
  <em>
   Bloodlines 2
  </em>
  . In terms of gameplay, so far, it seems like the sequel will stick close to its predecessor; therefore, expect first-person action with a heavy focus on a dialogue system.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="pokemon-legends-z-a">
  Pokemon Legends: Z-A
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-next-evolution">
  The Next Evolution
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-15-680316061" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-15-680316061" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-15-680316061" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-15-680316061" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-15-680316061-img" id="article-gallery-15-680316061">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-15-680316061" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-15">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-15-slides-container-1771207745">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At this point,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  is largely shrouded in shadow, with very little available information. Game Freak has confirmed that the project will take place in Kalos, which was introduced during the sixth generation. Similar to 2022's
  <em>
   Arceus
  </em>
  , one has to assume
  <em>
   Z-A
  </em>
  takes place well before the events of
  <em>
   X
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Y
  </em>
  . Beyond that, the sequel/successor will almost certainly expand on its predecessor's concepts, specifically an open-world and less focus on combat.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite being barely anything more than a logo at the moment,
  <em>
   Pokemon Legends: Z-A
  </em>
  is unquestionably one of the most
  <strong>
   highly-anticipated 2025 RPGs
  </strong>
  . Why? Well, it is
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  . More specifically, it is a follow-up to perhaps the franchise's best-received game of the Switch generation.
 </p>
 <h2 id="moonlighter-2-the-endless-vault">
  Moonlighter 2: The Endless Vault
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-shop-keeper-who-loves-action-rpgs">
  A Shop Keeper Who Loves Action RPGs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-16-2005886482" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-16-2005886482" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-16-2005886482" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-16-2005886482" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-16-2005886482-img" id="article-gallery-16-2005886482">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-16-2005886482" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-16">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-16-slides-container-1941859231">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A charming indie action RPG that emphasizes shop management,
  <em>
   Moonlighter
  </em>
  is not only very fun but also offers quite a bit of replay value. The 2018 release was successful enough that a sequel always seemed likely, especially since the concept certainly had room to grow. Fortunately, Digital Sun seems set to return to this universe, once again casting players as Will, a shopkeeper who needs to keep his inventory stocked by going out in the wild and collecting loot.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Moonlighter 2
  </em>
  's biggest change is the switch to a full 3D presentation, albeit presented from an isometric angle. While its predecessor's pixel art is top-notch, the sequel should be a pretty substantial upgrade in terms of visuals and presentation. Beyond that, players will get to explore a new area, Tresna, while helping a struggling village to flourish.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="pathologic-3">
  Pathologic 3
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-horror-fueled-journey">
  A Horror-Fueled Journey
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-17-1735759650" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-17-1735759650" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-17-1735759650" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-17-1735759650" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-17-1735759650-img" id="article-gallery-17-1735759650">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-17-1735759650" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-17">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-17-slides-container-8458436">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pathologic
  </em>
  is not for everyone. The series is known for cryptic storytelling, ambiguous characters, purposefully frustrating mechanics, and nightmarish world design that can be genuinely unsettling. In other words,
  <em>
   Pathologic
  </em>
  is a wonderful but acquired taste. The third entry's announcement came as a surprise since its concept was originally planned to be the Bachelor route of
  <em>
   Pathologic 2
  </em>
  , the final step in that game's episodic-style release cycle.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, to be clear,
  <em>
   Pathologic 3
  </em>
  appears set to expand greatly on the route, offering an experience that should hopefully justify its standalone presentation. Even if
  <em>
   Pathologic 2
  </em>
  is not quite as highly regarded as its predecessor, both games are very good, and there is nothing to suggest their successor will fail to maintain that high standard. Horror RPGs are extremely rare, so this series should be cherished.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-new-witcher-saga-polaris">
  The Witcher 4
 </h2>
 <h3 id="action-amp-open-world-presumably">
  Action &amp; Open-World (Presumably)
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-18-1873271962" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-18-1873271962" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-18-1873271962" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-18-1873271962" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-18-1873271962-img" id="article-gallery-18-1873271962">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-18-1873271962" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-18">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-18-slides-container-1619426853">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  CD Projekt Red has been working on a new
  <em>
   The Witcher
  </em>
  project for a few years, but the developer did not confirm that it would be the next mainline entry in the saga until The Game Awards 2024.
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  is on the horizon, and it is an exciting time to be a fan of open-world RPGs or just games in general. While
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's debut state reduced CD Projekt Red's public goodwill, the developer's post-launch commitment helped right a few of those initial wrongs, and the game is nowadays in good shape. More importantly,
  <em>
   The Witcher 3
  </em>
  is still largely regarded as one of the greatest Western RPGs of all time, and time has done very little to dull its shine.
 </p>
 <p>
  As the previous entry's DLC nicely completed Geralt's story, it had long been speculated that
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  would feature a new protagonist, and Ciri has always been the most obvious pick. Well, The Game Awards' trailer largely confirmed that rumor, with the powerful character being front and center. At this point, almost nothing is known about the sequel's direction, except for Ciri seeming to be a few years older than in
  <em>
   Wild Hunt
  </em>
  . Also, Geralt will likely make an appearance in
  <em>
   The Witcher 4
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-elder-scrolls-6">
  The Elder Scrolls 6
 </h2>
 <h3 id="open-world-presumably">
  Open-World (Presumably)
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="The Elder Scrolls 6 Landscape" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/the-elder-scrolls-6-landscape.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It was only a matter of time before
  <strong>
   <em>
    The Elder Scrolls 6
   </em>
  </strong>
  was revealed, although that is essentially all that Bethesda has done. Except for some minor details that can be surmised from the few seconds of footage that has been released so far, the game is still largely a mystery; however,
  <em>
   TES 6
  </em>
  is one of those
  <strong>
   upcoming RPGs
  </strong>
  that only needs to exist to generate hype.
 </p>
 <p>
  Realistically, Bethesda's sequel is still a few years away from a debut, and the publisher will probably not start to heavily market the project until after
  <em>
   Starfield
  </em>
  's cycle is complete. Nevertheless, it would be shocking if
  <em>
   TES 6
  </em>
  does not wind up as one of the best-selling games of all time.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dragon-quest-12-the-flames-of-fate">
  Dragon Quest 12: The Flames Of Fate
 </h2>
 <h3 id="turn-based-presumably">
  Turn-Based (Presumably)
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured-Square-Enix-JRPG-Reveal-Logo" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg" decoding="async" height="700" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Dragon-Quest-12-Announcement-Featured.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1400"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Dragon Quest 12
  </em>
  is a weird one. Since being revealed in 2021, Square Enix has barely uttered a word regarding the next mainline entry in the storied JRPG franchise.
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  's influence and popularity cannot be understated, particularly in Japan where the series is nothing short of a cultural phenomenon. While there was a fairly long dry spell after
  <em>
   DQ8
  </em>
  , the 11th mainline entry was a hit in Western countries, elevating the license to international highs it had not experienced for a while. Thanks to its predecessor's success,
  <em>
   Dragon Quest 12
  </em>
  is poised to be one of the biggest releases in the license's history outside of Japan.
 </p>
 <p>
  Perhaps, Square Enix announced
  <em>
   DQ12
  </em>
  's existence a bit prematurely or simply wanted to gauge the public's interest in a sequel; whatever the reason, the post-reveal silence has lasted slightly too long. Hopefully, the publisher will expand on the game's development at some point in the near future as the gaming world is ready for a new mainline
  <em>
   Dragon Quest
  </em>
  adventure.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Stranding 2 Has a Clear Path to Another Great PT Easter Egg</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/death-stranding-2-pt-easter-egg-paper-bag-cosmetic/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  While Easter eggs are fairly common in gaming, Hideo Kojima is one of those developers fans can expect plenty of Easter eggs from in just about any game, regardless of its genre, tone, or relevance. The same goes for one of his most recent games,
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , which included a subtle reference to
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  , a legendary interactive demo intended as a teaser for a new installment in the
  <em>
   Silent Hill
  </em>
  franchise,
  <em>
   Silent Hills
  </em>
  . The project was ultimately canceled, but
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  's influence can still be felt in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , and the same could eventually be said of its sequel,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Death Stranding 2: On the Beach
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the clearest references to
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  is a radio broadcast that can be heard during gameplay, which is reminiscent of the radio transmission heard during the first several minutes of
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  During the radio broadcast in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , players hear a DJ mention "a string of mysterious deaths" and a man turning himself in to the police, both of which are callbacks to
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  's narrative. Now, looking ahead to
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , although
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  is a very short horror experience, there is still another icon the sequel could reference from the teaser, and it could do so in both a nostalgic and humorous way if it tried.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="death-stranding-2-should-feature-p-t-39-s-talking-paper-bag">
  Death Stranding 2 Should Feature P.T.'s Talking Paper Bag
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-236023322" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-236023322" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-236023322" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-236023322" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-236023322-img" id="article-gallery-1-236023322">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-236023322" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-291567341">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-paper-bag-would-be-another-great-death-stranding-reference-to-p-t">
  The Paper Bag Would Be Another Great Death Stranding Reference to P.T.
 </h3>
 <p>
  There are plenty of memorable moments in
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  's short playtime of nearly half an hour, but one of them stands out more than many others: a mysterious talking paper bag that players encounter about three quarters of the way through the game. The bag, filled with what appears to be black blood, speaks to the player upon the encounter, delivering some cryptic message about another reality and the danger it poses. The black goo alone is enough to connect it to the black appearance of Timefall in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , thereby making it a perfect
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  Easter egg for
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h3 id="death-stranding-2-could-incorporate-the-paper-bag-in-some-creative-ways">
  Death Stranding 2 Could Incorporate the Paper Bag in Some Creative Ways
 </h3>
 <p>
  There are also some creative ways
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  could incorporate the paper bag into its gameplay, especially considering the first game's penchant for dark humor that the sequel is likely to honor. Firstly, it would be interesting to see the paper bag from
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  become a piece of cargo Sam is tasked with transporting, as it could then potentially speak to Sam during his journey for what could be a lightly humorous conversation. If it didn't speak directly to Sam, it could emit unsettling sounds, like the faint cries of a baby or whispers, much like the eerie ambiance in
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     There are plenty of memorable moments in
     <em>
      P.T.
     </em>
     's short playtime of nearly half an hour, but one of them stands out more than many others: a mysterious talking paper bag that players encounter about three quarters of the way through the game.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  On a more humorous note, the paper bag would make a great cosmetic item for Sam to wear in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  . One of the silliest cosmetic items from the first
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  is the Otter Hood, which is given to Sam by none other than a Conan O'Brien cameo, and since he's set to reappear in
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  , perhaps the paper bag could be his gift to Sam this time. Sam could then wear the paper bag on his head, just as he does the Otter Hood in
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  , bringing a little bit of lighthearted humor to players' journey through the next story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Incorporating
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  's paper bag into
  <em>
   Death Stranding 2
  </em>
  would not only pay homage to one of Kojima's best creations but also potentially highlight his skillful ability at blending horror and humor. Whether as a piece of cargo, an unsettling companion, or what could be a hilarious cosmetic item, the paper bag offers a perfect opportunity to create yet another connection to
  <em>
   P.T.
  </em>
  in the
  <em>
   Death Stranding
  </em>
  universe.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Nikki - Forced Perspective: Burning With Anger Guide</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/infinity-nikki-forced-perspective-burning-with-anger-guide/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There is never a shortage of adventures to embark on in
  <strong>
   <em>
    Infinity Nikki
   </em>
  </strong>
  , which is one of the game's many aspects that its devoted player community has appreciated since its spectacularly successful launch in December 2024. While fashion is one of Nikki's biggest priorities during her journey across Miraland, there are other types of quests that test other skills as well, such as photography with Forced Perspective quests.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One such quest in Infinity Nikki is Forced Perspective: Burning With Anger, and if you're looking to complete it, you'll need to know the best way to work Momo's camera lens to fulfill this Faewish Sprite's wish.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-complete-forced-perspective-burning-with-anger">
  How to Complete Forced Perspective: Burning With Anger
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-turaida-quest-start.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Forced Perspective: Burning With Anger
  </strong>
  is a quest within the Forced Perspective series that is unlocked in the
  <strong>
   Wishing Woods
  </strong>
  . To unlock it, you need to complete the
  <strong>
   first quest in Chapter 6
  </strong>
  of the main story questline, and then reach the
  <strong>
   Grand Tree Residential Area
  </strong>
  in the Wishing Woods.
 </p>
 <p>
  There you should find
  <strong>
   Turaida
  </strong>
  floating on a higher platform on the left side of the area near Vivienbo, which is the designated Fire Station for the Faewish Sprites. Speak to him and he'll ask Nikki to capture a photo of him "burning with anger", as the quest name suggests.
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/infinity-nikki-flower-bed-burning-with-anger.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  To accomplish this, first go and hop onto the flower bed directly opposite from Turaida, to help yourself gain some height in preparation for the photo. Now, make sure that Turaida is directly in the center of your view, and then enter
  <strong>
   Photo Mode
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-668102028" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-668102028" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-668102028" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-668102028" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-668102028-img" id="article-gallery-1-668102028">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-668102028" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-430394150">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Remove Nikki from the shot if you wish (it's not required), and you should see both Turaida and the
  <strong>
   blue
  </strong>
  <strong>
   'Burning Fire' symbol
  </strong>
  on the small building behind him highlighted in the shot, as seen above. These are your two required subjects, and you need to align them properly to get the perfect photo that Turaida desires. Using your previous experience with other photo-based challenges such as taking the perfect photo with the Sovereign of Fresh will certainly help with quests like these.
 </p>
 <p>
  Adjust the lens from a slightly lower angle and then point it upward until the Burning Fire symbol is lined up directly behind Turaida's head, giving the impression of his burning anger. You'll know you have the shot when the message 'Sprite Burning With Anger' is displayed (also seen above). Take the photo and Momo will tell Nikki to show it to Turaida.
 </p>
 <p>
  Speak to Turaida again, and Nikki's Album menu will pop up. Select the photo you just took and then hit 'Confirm'. Turaida will be pleased and thank you for your exceptional efforts by offering the following rewards:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   10 x Diamonds
  </li>
  <li>
   3 x Upgrade Packs
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Remember that
  <strong>
   Upgrade Packs
  </strong>
  are used to upgrade the three main features of Momo's camera, which include
  <strong>
   Lighting
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   Pose
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Filter
  </strong>
  . You can make these upgrades at any time by going into Photo Mode and selecting the
  <strong>
   wrench symbol icon
  </strong>
  in the top right corner of the screen.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-931476650" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-931476650" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-931476650" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-931476650" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-931476650-img" id="article-gallery-2-931476650">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-931476650" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-2102059676">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The more you level up a feature, you can unlock more options for it as well, so you can get access to several new poses for Nikki as well as lighting and filter selections.
 </p>
 <p>
  As you level up each feature, more Upgrade Packs will be required so make sure to keep a look out for every Forced Perspective quest you can find as well as your Expeditions, which you can track via Photo Mode as well. Each destination spot you visit and take a photo of will earn you 3 x Upgrade Packs, so make sure to pit-stop for those during your travels. The more options you unlock, the more you can diversify your skills with Photo Mode and take the best glamour shots in Miraland.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
