<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: How To Get The Lawless Rift Launcher (&amp; How It Works)</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-exotic-lawless-rift-launcher-location-how-to-get/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  Lawless is shaping up to be one of the biggest seasons yet, bringing a roster of heist-themed weapons and equipment, vaults to break into, and a Battle Pass filled with a variety of unique outfits. As the season progresses, even more content is being added, offering players a range of additional features to enjoy.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One of the biggest updates for
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  Chapter 6 Season 2 is the introduction of several Exotic Weapons, each with its own unique abilities—some of which have never been seen before. One of these items is the Lawless Rift Launcher, which serves as an excellent mobility tool when used. Here’s
  <strong>
   how players can get the Lawless Rift Launcher in
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
   .
  </strong>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-the-lawless-rift-launcher-in-fortnite">
  How To Get The Lawless Rift Launcher In Fortnite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1263715421" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1263715421" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1263715421" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1263715421" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1263715421-img" id="article-gallery-1-1263715421">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1263715421" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-108642941">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Following the trend of past Lawless Exotic Weapons, the Lawless Rift Launcher can be purchased from one of the many Black Markets around the map. Players will find the Lawless Rift Launcher for sale
  <strong>
   at the Rogue Repairs Black Market
  </strong>
  (northeast of Masked Meadows), located
  <strong>
   within the market's Backroom
  </strong>
  —which players can now unlock using the Common Outlaw Keycard.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here, players can
  <strong>
   purchase the Lawless Rift Launcher for one Dill Bit.
  </strong>
  Dill Bits can still be found within the various vaults around the map, like they could at the start of the season, and may also drop from Golden Llamas. However, if players have completed the Outlaw Keycard Quests to obtain the Legendary Outlaw Keycard, they can also
  <strong>
   get a Dill Bit from the Rogue Repairs Black Market Backroom
  </strong>
  by opening the keycard-locked chest found inside.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-to-use-the-lawless-rift-launcher-in-fortnite">
  How To Use The Lawless Rift Launcher In Fortnite
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2132319773" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2132319773" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2132319773" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2132319773" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2132319773-img" id="article-gallery-2-2132319773">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2132319773" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1493196660">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Lawless Rift Launcher, as the name suggests, is a weapon capable of firing Rifts—portals primarily used for transportation. The weapon
  <strong>
   holds two rounds by default
  </strong>
  but boasts unlimited ammo, as it
  <strong>
   automatically replenishes its ammunition every 22 seconds.
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  To use it, players simply need to
  <strong>
   press the shoot button to fire a Rift
  </strong>
  and then enter the Rift to be teleported into the sky, redeploying their glider. This makes the weapon a convenient means of rotating around the map, especially considering that Rifts purchased from NPCs cost 450 Gold.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the Rifts activated via the Lawless Rift Launcher can be fired from a distance, they only remain active for a few seconds, meaning players must enter the Rift quickly after firing it. Additionally,
  <strong>
   players can Rift enemies and even NPCs
  </strong>
  by firing the Rift directly at them, making it an excellent strategy for sending opponents away when caught in a pinch.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InZOI Player Spots Controversial Feature</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/inzoi-denuvo-anti-tamper-controversial-feature-against-piracy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      One InZOI: Creative Studio player has discovered evidence of the demo using Denuvo Anti-Tamper.
     </li>
     <li>
      Game Rant was unable to replicate the player's findings, and the game's Steam page doesn't mention anything in the way of DRM.
     </li>
     <li>
      Denuvo is a somewhat controversial DRM solution that has previously faced accusations of being detrimental to game performance, though its creators insist that the software can be lightweight—if implemented correctly.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    InZOI
   </em>
  </strong>
  reportedly uses Denuvo Anti-Tamper, according to one early adopter's testimony. The claim has already caused some
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  performance concerns among fans, though only time will tell whether these are well-founded.
 </p>
 <p>
  Denuvo Anti-Tamper is a digital rights management (DRM) solution that's long enjoyed widespread adoption among game developers. Over the years, Denuvo has developed a bit of a reputation as a controversial feature that's detrimental to game performance. However, its creators have insisted that this wasn't the case, and that the DRM software can have a negligible performance impact—so long as it's implemented properly rather than being treated as an afterthought.
 </p>
 <p>
  InZOI Studio may have joined the list of Denuvo adopters. According to a recent report from a Discord user who was playing the
  <em>
   InZOI: Creative Studio
  </em>
  demo, the trial version of the game implements Denuvo in a way that requires an internet connection. When the user blocked
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  in their Windows Defender Firewall, they reportedly received an error instructing them to copy a specific exception code and paste it into a text box on a Denuvo-owned website. Game Rant was unable to replicate this issue, suggesting that if
  <em>
   InZOI: Creative Studio
  </em>
  does use Denuvo, the authenticity checks it performs are sporadic and the demo doesn't need to be online at all times.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="inzoi-steam-page-makes-no-mention-of-denuvo">
  InZOI Steam Page Makes No Mention of Denuvo
 </h2>
 <p>
  To date, developer InZOI Studio hasn't said anything about implementing any kind of DRM into its upcoming life sim. The game's Steam page also doesn't mention any kind of third-party DRM being part of the package, with its only requirement notice referencing a third-party end-user license agreement (EULA). However, seeing how
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  is only slated for release on March 28, it's possible that its Steam page will be updated in the run-up to this launch. In the meantime, the
  <em>
   InZOI: Creative Studio
  </em>
  demo page also doesn't reference DRM in any capacity.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-493256381" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-493256381" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-493256381" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-493256381" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-493256381-img" id="article-gallery-1-493256381">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-493256381" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-406047636">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A vocal section of the fandom has already voiced concerns about the game's possible use of Denuvo.
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  's early access system requirements are already quite steep, leading some to wonder whether the game's apparent reliance on aggressive anti-piracy and -tampering software might have something to do with that.
 </p>
 <p>
  As is occasionally the case with early access titles,
  <em>
   InZOI
  </em>
  's system requirements could decrease over time as the developers continue optimizing the game ahead of its version 1.0 release. InZOI Studio previously said it's aiming to keep the life sim in early access for at least a year.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilization 7 Reveals What's Coming in Future Updates</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/civilization-7-future-updates-content/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Firaxis provides a developer update on Civilization 7, highlighting upcoming features and upgrades.
     </li>
     <li>
      Version 1.1.1 will focus on making quality-of-life changes and balancing adjustments.
     </li>
     <li>
      Quick Move feature will be added to speed up gameplay sessions and Restart Game button allows for map regeneration with the same faction.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  According to a message from developers at Firaxis Games, the next update to
  <strong>
   <em>
    Sid Meier's Civilization 7
   </em>
  </strong>
  will bring a number of useful changes and quality-of-life upgrades.
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  is the latest in the long-running series of turn-based empire-building strategy games.
 </p>
 <p>
  Often seen as one of the pioneering titles of strategy gaming, the
  <em>
   Sid Meier's Civilization
  </em>
  series never fails to make waves with every new installment. In fact,
  <em>
   Civilization
  </em>
  games are so influential and satisfying to players that many of the titles in the series end up competing against each other. Many consider
  <em>
   Civilization 4
  </em>
  to be among the best 4X strategy games of all time and use it as a yardstick against which past and present releases are compared.
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  is no stranger to that tendency, and its major changes to the flow of a typical
  <em>
   Civ
  </em>
  session have received a lot of scrutiny since its release in February 2025.
 </p>
 <p>
  In light of that scrutiny and a number of complaints from fans, Firaxis Games Creative Director Ed Beach released a video preview of changes coming with the game's next update, version 1.1.1. Published just a day before the update drops on March 26, 2025, the preview explains the thinking behind some of the patch's planned additions. The majority of changes will focus on improving the game's quality-of-life, making things more convenient for existing
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  players. Some new balance adjustments will also address an issue with the
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  Age system, which alters the flow of the campaign such that even longtime fans of the series see the game as a major break from tradition.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="civilization-7-version-1-1-1-patch-upcoming-changes">
  Civilization 7 Version 1.1.1 Patch Upcoming Changes
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-0cea32a2cab8e870" id="emaki-video-player-0cea32a2cab8e870">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Quick Movement
  </li>
  <li>
   Start Position Map Generation Options
  </li>
  <li>
   Renaming of Settlements and Commanders
  </li>
  <li>
   Restart Button
  </li>
  <li>
   Mt. Everest Natural Wonder
  </li>
  <li>
   Easier Bulk Buying
  </li>
  <li>
   Notifications When Cities Attacked
  </li>
  <li>
   Crisis Indicators
  </li>
  <li>
   Easier Access to Trade Lens
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved Resource Tool Tips
  </li>
  <li>
   Changes to Age Progress in Age of Exploration
  </li>
  <li>
   Increased Costs for Modern Techs and Civics
  </li>
  <li>
   Advisors Warn When Troops Unpacked
  </li>
  <li>
   Improved Trade Outpost Bonus
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  According to Beach's commentary, the
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  version 1.1.1 update is centered around improvements to the player experience. The most obvious new addition is "Quick Move," a much-requested feature that allows units to move instantly to where they're going, speeding up sessions greatly. Other speed-related updates will include the addition of a "Restart Game" button that regenerates the map with the same faction and leader choices, for players who want to optimize their starting position by re-rolling the
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  map.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1302216757" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1302216757" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1302216757" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1302216757" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1302216757-img" id="article-gallery-1-1302216757">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1302216757" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1130221121">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Another map-related update will add options to guide the game's map generation algorithm. The default behavior, which allows for creative asymmetry in starting circumstances, will be called "standard." A new "balanced" option will prioritize more equal distribution of resources, territory, and opportunity for every
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  faction on the map, to ensure an even playing field in multiplayer sessions. Another notable change will make the Modern Age last longer before transitioning by increasing the costs of its Techs and Civics.
 </p>
 <p>
  Online reaction to the version 1.1.1 preview was generally positive, with many players on Twitter, Bluesky, and Reddit praising Firaxis for its detailed communication about the upcoming update. Though some players complained that some issues still needed addressing, most reactions expressed confidence that, with time, Firaxis will improve
  <em>
   Civilization 7
  </em>
  and refine the experience to best suit fan desires.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hogwarts Legacy 2’s Customization Shouldn’t Be Contained to the Room of Requirement</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hogwarts-legacy-2-customization-more-options-social-business-management/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  A great draw of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hogwarts Legacy
   </em>
  </strong>
  —perhaps the biggest—is living within the castle walls as a student. There are probably only a handful of
  <em>
   Harry Potter
  </em>
  fans out there who haven't dreamed about getting their Hogwarts letter one day and being whisked off to a magical life. For the most part, this is what they get in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  . There are naturally several aspects that fall short, a key one being the most obvious: the overall student life itself.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Customization is also a contributing, underdeveloped aspect; it's limited to redecorating the Room of Requirement and changing one's appearance. Being able to create an avatar and having a secret room to oneself is naturally great, but there should be more to student life in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  . The dorms and common room, for starters, are where a lot happens. Players would likely feel more at home if they're able to customize their dorms in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  , if not the common room as well.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-hogwarts-legacy-2-should-make-student-life-more-personal">
  Why Hogwarts Legacy 2 Should Make Student Life More Personal
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1620500248" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1620500248" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1620500248" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1620500248" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1620500248-img" id="article-gallery-1-1620500248">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1620500248" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2054085607">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="dorm-personalization-could-turn-hogwarts-legacy-2-into-every-wizard-39-s-home-away-from-home">
  Dorm Personalization Could Turn Hogwarts Legacy 2 Into Every Wizard's Home Away From Home
 </h3>
 <p>
  Giving players the choice to customize their dorms in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  would go a long way in enabling them to experience the complete student life. A big part of living in a castle for three-quarters of the year is having a space that's entirely personal, where there are no limits to self-expression. To this end, making the furniture and the color theme fully customizable seems natural. After all, conjuring and transfiguring materials and textures to refashion a space shouldn't be limited to the Room of Requirement in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Avalanche Software could also target customization by tying it in with the loot and quest system. As fans may remember, the loot in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  is pretty decent, but it's nothing to write home about. The game could expand on this by rewarding them with tchotchkes of varied styles, depending on the quest or NPC they interact with. So, a player could choose to display various items in their dorms, whether it's something like a fuzzy plushy collection, a Chocolate Frog Card tower, a Hungarian Horntail miniature, or even a set of rudimentary class projects that they're working on.
 </p>
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  's social system is fleshed out even more, the state of the protagonist's sleeping area, the items they have, and the general comings and goings could lead to interesting dialogue exchange; a morality system of sorts that impacts their bonds with certain characters would be inspired as well. After all, it would be boring, unnatural even, if the six-to-seven people living together don't have any actual roommate actions.
 </p>
 <h3 id="hogwarts-legacy-2-can-unlock-social-potential-through-player-decisions">
  Hogwarts Legacy 2 Can Unlock Social Potential Through Player Decisions
 </h3>
 <p>
  If there's one piece of content that many players remember being disappointed about, outside the castle walls, it's the Haunted Hogsmeade shop quest in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy
  </em>
  . While the dialogues make it seem like they will get to run their own shop, that's not the case. They can't select the items that are sold, what the decor is like, or even the prices set; all they can do is buy and sell for a slightly higher profit. Ultimately, the entire thing falls short of what is seemingly promised at the start. The quest itself, however, is a particularly good one.
 </p>
 <p>
  If players gain more control over Hogsmeade in
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  , or another village for that matter, it would not only turn things around but make them even better. They could choose which shops go where, what the design and key business actions are, and perhaps even a couple of people that get hired. This will be more believable if it's not instant; rather, everything takes time, and requires a certain chunk of monetary and quest investment from players. This may help players feel more engaged in the experience, considering they actually get a worthwhile say and stand to profit, whether by way of money or story.
 </p>
 <p>
  Going from nothing to control over a group of shops or a village itself may feel like a big leap, but there's always room to explain things. Given how the first game ended,
  <em>
   Hogwarts Legacy 2
  </em>
  's story may jump forward a few years. If the player is pureblood or a halfblood, this could be a way to have them learn and expand the family business, build connections with shopkeepers and landowners, and even garner support for future actions. If the protagonist is a muggleborn, the process could be more gradual and challenging. It could help them learn more about how the magical businesses work, earn money for clothing and items, and even network for supportive actions over the campaign. While it's impossible to say what
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hogwarts Legacy 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  's story and gameplay could look like, giving players more freedom may be the best foot forward.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds: What Is The Forbidden Lands? - Bite-Size Lore</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/monster-hunter-wilds-what-is-the-forbidden-lands-bite-size-lore/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  What are the Forbidden Lands? The setting of the newest installment in the Monster Hunter series has tons of new mysteries to investigate and discover! These exotic locales showcase unique ecosystems that host their own challenges and wildlife for the Hunter to take on.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
