<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>7 Horror Games That Change Drastically Midway Through</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/horror-games-that-change-drastically-midway-through/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Horror games can dramatically change elements like protagonists, story, and environment midway to surprise players.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games like Until Dawn, Doki Doki Literature Club!, and The Forest subvert player expectations effectively.
     </li>
     <li>
      Unexpected changes in gameplay, characters, and environment in games like Dead Space and The Last Of Us: Part 2 heighten immersion.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  For a horror game to be memorable, it needs to keep things fresh throughout the nightmarish adventure to ensure players feel immersed from beginning to end. While this obviously means things like enemy and environment variety will be included to help add some diversity to the game, sometimes, developers will also decide to make a full 180 and completely change up an aspect of the game midway through, which can end up drastically changing the overall experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whether it be a sudden change to a new protagonist, bizarre story twists, or even a complete tonal flip, there are plenty of ways horror titles that have subverted players' expectations by taking the risk of making giant changes only a few chapters into the player's story. However, whether these drastic changes were pulled off successfully or not can vary, but one thing is for sure, they certainly all threw players off guard upon experiencing them for the first time.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="until-dawn">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Until Dawn
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="until-dawn-suddenly-turns-from-a-predictable-80s-horror-flick-turns-into-an-intense-fight-for-survival">
  Until Dawn Suddenly Turns From A Predictable 80s Horror Flick Turns Into An Intense Fight For Survival
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-317125631" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-317125631" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-317125631" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-317125631" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-317125631-img" id="article-gallery-1-317125631">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-317125631" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-608727608">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the beginning of
  <em>
   Until Dawn
  </em>
  , once the squabbling group of friends are able to get inside and settle down with one another, it very quickly becomes clear that a killer is on the loose, and looking to hunt down each of them one by one. For the most part, this seemed like a typical homage to horror classics of old, but what's strange is the killer is only revealed at roughly the midpoint of the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  The truth is, while Josh owns up to being the killer, since the teens arrived in the lodge, they have also become the prey of the dangerous Wendigo who roam the mountain and all of its underground tunnels. This twist threw everyone by surprise and managed to raise the stakes even higher, turning a fairly predictable 80s horror flick into a fierce fight for survival.
 </p>
 <h2 id="doki-doki-literature-club">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Doki Doki Literature Club!
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="there-39-s-no-horror-game-that-features-tonal-whiplash-quite-as-strongly-as-doki-doki-literature-club">
  There's No Horror Game That Features Tonal Whiplash Quite As Strongly As Doki Doki Literature Club!
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-2031421128" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-2031421128" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-2031421128" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-2031421128" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-2031421128-img" id="article-gallery-2-2031421128">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-2031421128" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-404439554">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Doki Doki Literature Club!
  </em>
  is a psychological thriller which first guides players into a false sense of security before then breaking the fourth wall completely, resulting in terrifying results. It's very much a game of two halves which shows its true colors a few hours in, making for one of the most unnerving horror experiences in the last few years.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite it being advertised as a horror game, the tonal whiplash in this game is unlike anything else, which is why it would became such a phenomenon during the horror-game streamer era, where viewers would flock to see the top player's reactions.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="little-nightmares">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Little Nightmares
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="six-39-s-persona-entirely-changes-thanks-to-one-eerie-moment-in-the-game">
  Six's Persona Entirely Changes Thanks To One Eerie Moment In The Game
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1634414141" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1634414141" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1634414141" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1634414141" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1634414141-img" id="article-gallery-3-1634414141">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1634414141" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1937661592">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Six, the main protagonist of
  <em>
   Little Nightmares
  </em>
  , seems like a pretty innocent character for much of the game. Though they are shown to be prone to random hunger spikes, they are ultimately just trying to get away from the grotesque monsters that they face throughout the nightmarish adventure, that is, until Six has a fateful encounter with a gnome who offers them a sausage.
 </p>
 <p>
  Rather than taking the gift, Six instead decides to chow down on the gnome like some kind of ravenous animal. This completely changes the tone of the game, making Six feel like more of a hunter rather than being the hunted, giving the rest of the game a very different feel and vibe from the first few hours.
 </p>
 <h2 id="dead-space">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Dead Space
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-are-transported-from-the-ishimura-into-an-entirely-new-ship-with-unique-enemies-halfway-through-dead-space">
  Players Are Transported From The Ishimura Into An Entirely New Ship With Unique Enemies Halfway Through Dead Space
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1176876495" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1176876495" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1176876495" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1176876495" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1176876495-img" id="article-gallery-4-1176876495">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1176876495" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-557510310">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After the Necromorphs show themselves in the first few minutes of the first
  <em>
   Dead Space
  </em>
  , the game follows a fairly streamlined path that seems like it wouldn't stray too far off course. Simply put, Isaac needed to repair numerous parts of the Ishimura to stop it from crashing, and would then need to find a way to escape in one piece, but one monster who throws a wrench into these plans is the Leviathan Remnant.
 </p>
 <p>
  After players take out this monstrosity, they are then sent flying into the USM Valor, a military ship that looks and feels entirely different to the Ishimura that players had been trapped in for so long. Even the enemies, who are able to teleport due to their Stasis packs, play differently, drastically changing the game and ramping up the intensity of its story tremendously.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-forest">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   The Forest
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-forest-39-s-story-and-environment-take-a-dramatic-turn-a-few-hours-in">
  The Forest's Story And Environment Take A Dramatic Turn A Few Hours In
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-2145993555" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-2145993555" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-2145993555" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-2145993555" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-2145993555-img" id="article-gallery-5-2145993555">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-2145993555" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1715769074">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  is a horror-themed survival game where players must try to stay alive while stalked and hunted by a group of cannibals who reside on a faraway island. Players aren't really given much to go off in terms of story for a fair few hours, at least not until they start using the keycards, which will eventually lead them to an underground lab that entirely changes around the environment, switching from a tropical island to an scientific facility.
 </p>
 <p>
  While the tone of the game entirely changes by this point, the story also takes a dramatic turn with the introduction of the Resurrection Obelisk, which instantly turns a fairly barebones story into something pretty intriguing and exciting. Though
  <em>
   The Forest
  </em>
  very well could have just ended with players escaping, this clever twist keeps them engaged throughout the experience by fleshing out the world a little more.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-last-of-us-part-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   The Last Of Us: Part 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-sudden-character-change-that-nobody-saw-coming-takes-place-halfway-through-the-last-of-us-part-2">
  A Sudden Character Change That Nobody Saw Coming Takes Place Halfway Through The Last of Us: Part 2
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-39210723" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-39210723" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-39210723" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-39210723" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-39210723-img" id="article-gallery-6-39210723">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-39210723" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-1121187476">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  For fans who had managed to avoid the leaks, the story of
  <em>
   The Last of Us Part 2
  </em>
  was a complete mystery. Though the trailers had shown scenes of Joel and Ellie together, making it appear like this would be focusing on another venture featuring the lovable duo, Joel's death at the beginning of the game switched gears to instead make this a game which, many believed, was now giving Ellie the main role.
 </p>
 <p>
  However, a few chapters into the story, players suddenly find themselves taking control of Abby, who then embarks on her own journey of redemption for what she did to Joel. Though Abby is playable for a brief period in the early game, it felt as though this was just a clever way to put players in the shoes of the villain for a few seconds, kind of like with Sephiroth in
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 7 Rebirth
  </em>
  , which is why this sudden change comes as such a surprise.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="resident-evil-code-veronica">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Resident Evil: Code Veronica
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-change-to-chris-not-long-after-claire-enters-antarctica-is-jarring-to-say-the-least">
  The Change To Chris Not Long After Claire Enters Antarctica Is Jarring, To Say The Least
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1088136161" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1088136161" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1088136161" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1088136161" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1088136161-img" id="article-gallery-7-1088136161">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1088136161" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-189301848">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the beginning of
  <em>
   Resident Evil Code Veronica
  </em>
  , players assume control of Claire Redfield, who wakes up in a mysterious prison after a failed infiltration attempt at an Umbrella base. Though Chris Redfield does appear on the front cover alongside his younger sister, many fans still assumed this would be Claire's time to shine and a standalone game that could focus on her solo adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  It certainly seems that way in-game too, since Claire plays an integral role in the story, including trying to take down Alfred and escaping with Steve to Antarctica. It's therefore jarring to say the least when, at about the halfway point of the game, players are suddenly switched over to Chris with no warning. If players don't stash a few weapons in the item box, they'll find themselves at a disadvantage when flipping over to the second protagonist, making it a pretty divisive mechanic for how unexpected it is.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoD Warzone: Every Perk, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cod-warzone-best-perks-use/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Call of Duty: Warzone
   </em>
  </strong>
  offers an extensive range of Perks that players can choose to enhance their loadouts and optimize their playstyle across all game modes, whether they’re battling it out in Battle Royale or engaging in the fast-paced action of Resurgence.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Perks are a defining feature of
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , allowing players to strengthen specific gameplay elements to improve survivability and gain an edge in combat encounters. Selecting the right Perks can significantly influence your success, which is why we’ve ranked all the available options to help you make the best choices for your loadout.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="reflexes">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Reflexes
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="react-to-enemy-explosives">
  React to Enemy Explosives
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-reflexes-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Triggered explosives have a delay when sprinting past them.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Activate challenge through the Armory
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Dodging explosives is a common strategy, particularly during late-game scenarios where such threats can significantly benefit opponents. However, the
  <strong>
   Reflexes
  </strong>
  perk is only situationally useful, offering a brief reaction window to evade enemy explosive equipment when exposed. Given its limited utility and the availability of stronger options in Perk Slot 1, Reflexes ranks as one of the least favorable choices for this slot.
 </p>
 <h2 id="quartermaster">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Quartermaster
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="equipment-always-available">
  Equipment Always Available
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quartermaster-perk-slot-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Recharge equipment over time (50 seconds).
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Available Immediately
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you’re a fan of using equipment frequently – whether to blind enemies in buildings, chip away at their health before engaging, or create a cover with smoke grenades during rotations –
  <strong>
   Quartermaster
  </strong>
  is a solid choice. However, its utility is limited by its primary function: recharging equipment every 50 seconds. Given the availability of more versatile and popular options in Perk Slot 2, Quartermaster often falls short of being a worthwhile pick.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="bomb-squad">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Bomb Squad
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="equipment-avoidance-specialist">
  Equipment Avoidance Specialist
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-cod-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-bomb-squad-perk-slot-2-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reduces incoming explosives and fire damage. Spot enemy equipment and Killstreaks through walls.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 8
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  For players who prefer an aggressive playstyle and often find themselves exposed to enemy equipment,
  <strong>
   Bomb Squad
  </strong>
  is an excellent perk choice. It increases your chances of surviving effects from tactical and lethal equipment and allows you to anticipate threats and avoid unexpected deaths from killstreaks or hidden equipment traps. Still, this option is highly situational and best suited for players who meet its narrow criteria.
 </p>
 <h2 id="cold-blooded">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Cold-Blooded
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="evade-being-easily-targeted-by-enemies">
  Evade Being Easily Targeted By Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-cold-blooded-perk-slot-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Undetectable by AI targeting and thermal optics. Prevents some enemy recon Perks and effects.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 41
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Remaining undetectable is a critical advantage in Battle Royale modes, especially when lives are limited. However, the
  <strong>
   Cold-Blooded
  </strong>
  perk, once a go-to choice for many players in earlier
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  iterations, has seen a decline in effectiveness. Few players now utilize thermal scopes, and the risk of being targeted by AI is minimal in most scenarios. While its ability to counter certain Recon Perks adds some utility, the overall benefit of Cold-Blooded feels limited. This makes it a less appealing option in most loadouts, as it doesn’t significantly impact gameplay compared to other perks available.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="sprinter">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Sprinter
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="never-stop-sprinting">
  Never Stop Sprinting
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-sprinter-perk-slot-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Can Tactical Sprint indefinitely.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 32
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Since its introduction, sprinting – especially Tac Sprinting – has been an essential tool for
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  players to move around the maps. However, with the integration of
  <em>
   Black Ops 6
  </em>
  , players can now achieve unlimited sprinting by simply equipping a knife. This makes the
  <strong>
   Sprinter
  </strong>
  perk redundant, taking up a valuable slot that could be better utilized for other, more impactful perks.
 </p>
 <h2 id="veteran">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Veteran
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="control-enemy-equipment-and-hit-effects">
  Control Enemy Equipment and Hit Effects
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-veteran-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reduce the negative effects of some enemy equipment. While aiming down sights reduce flinching and extend Hold Breath duration.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Activate challenge through the Armory
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  As its name suggests,
  <strong>
   Veteran
  </strong>
  is a perk for players who often find themselves under enemy fire or exposed to hostile equipment. It helps reduce the impact of flinching and mitigates significant health loss during engagements. Also, for those who frequently use sniper rifles, this perk proves invaluable by extending the duration of the Hold Breath mechanic, enhancing precision in long-range battles.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="gung-ho">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Gung-Ho
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="maximizing-movement">
  Maximizing Movement
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-gung-ho-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reduced movement penalties when reloading or using equipment. Reload while Tac Sprinting.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Available Immediately
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Maximizing movement in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  is essential for players focused on agility, whether disengaging from fights or rotating to better positions. While the
  <strong>
   Gung-Ho
  </strong>
  perk aims to reduce movement penalties when reloading or using equipment, its impact is minimal. Considering the highly competitive Slot 3 perks, players may find better options, but for those who value reloading on the move, it remains a niche choice.
 </p>
 <h2 id="ghost">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Ghost
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stealthy-approach">
  Stealthy Approach
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-ghost-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Undetectable by enemy Radar Pings while moving. Cannot be detected by some devices.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 17
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Once a must-have for survival, the
  <strong>
   Ghost
  </strong>
  perk has lost its edge in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  due to its revamp of perks, which now offers several strong alternatives for Slot 3. While Ghost provides radar ping immunity and stealth against certain devices while moving, its utility in Battle Royale mode is limited as the expansive maps allow for natural evasion. As for Resurgence, during intense combat the perk’s benefits rarely come into play, leading players to favor perks with more consistent and impactful advantages. Furthermore, this Perk loses its effect with players using Birdseye.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="dexterity">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Dexterity
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="moving-without-hesitation">
  Moving Without Hesitation
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-dexterity-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reduced weapon motion while jumping, sliding, and diving. Take less fall damage.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 20
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Dexterity
  </strong>
  is a widely favored Perk in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  ’s Slot 1, offering benefits like smoother movement, reduced weapon sway, and decreased fall damage. While useful, its impact is less pronounced compared to earlier iterations of the perk. Players transitioning from Mountaineer may naturally opt for Dexterity, but its current version doesn’t deliver the same game-changing effects as its original counterpart.
 </p>
 <h2 id="birdseye">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Birdseye
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="recon-expert">
  Recon Expert
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-birdseye-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       UAVs you call in are 25% larger and show the heading of the enemy for your squad. Detects players with Ghost.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 23
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  In
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , having intel on enemy positions is crucial for gaining an edge, enabling you to anticipate movements and avoid unexpected eliminations. The
  <strong>
   Birdseye
  </strong>
  perk provides significant tactical advantages to control the flow of the match and support your squad, enhancing UAV duration and revealing enemy headings to your teammates. Additionally, Birdseye can detect players using the Ghost perk, neutralizing their attempts at stealth and ensuring you’re not caught off guard by hidden opponents.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="grenadier">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Grenadier
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="explosive-survivor">
  Explosive Survivor
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-grenadier-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Explosive damage slows enemy health regeneration and movement speed. Throw equipment farther and see a previous of the trajectory.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Available Immediately
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Grenadier
  </strong>
  perk is ideal for agile players who want a tactical edge in encounters. It debilitates enemies by reducing their health recovery and movement speed, leaving them vulnerable to follow-up attacks. Additionally, it shows the precise trajectory of throwable equipment and slightly increases the throwing range, making it easier to land effective strikes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="scavenger">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Scavenger
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="avoid-running-out-of-ammo">
  Avoid Running Out Of Ammo
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-scavenger-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Start equipped with maximum reserve ammo for your primary weapon. Resupply ammo equipment, and plates from dead enemies.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 26
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Managing your ammunition is essential in a game like
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , where your weapons are your primary means of survival. While
  <strong>
   Scavenger
  </strong>
  might seem like a popular choice for its ability to restock ammo and plates from fallen enemies, it’s often unnecessary. The game provides plenty of ammunition through loot caches and automatically refills ammo after eliminating opponents, making Scavenger a less efficient use of a valuable perk slot.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="alertness">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Alertness
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="sharpened-vision-prevents-surprise-attacks">
  Sharpened Vision Prevents Surprise Attacks
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-alertness-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Sense when enemies are nearby. Tell when you are being aimed at by the enemy.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 44
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Alertness is a powerful perk for passively gathering critical intel during movement or rotations. It notifies you when enemies are nearby or aiming directly at you, similar to the popular High Alert perk from previous
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  versions. This makes it invaluable for staying aware and avoiding threats, especially when you’re exposed on the map.
 </p>
 <h2 id="survivor">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Survivor
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="never-back-down-from-a-fight">
  Never Back Down From A Fight
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-survivor-perk-slot-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Start regenerating health more quickly. Your allies revive you faster when you’re downed.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 47
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 1
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players who are constantly moving around during engagements have multiple Perk options to choose from in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , and Survivor is a top-tier pick. It boosts your health regeneration, helping you recover quickly and stay prepared to either counterattack or defend against follow-up hits. Additionally, if you’re the leader player in your squad, Survivor enables your teammates to revive you faster when downed, minimizing downtime and keeping a valuable player in the fight.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="quick-fix">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Quick Fix
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="useful-armor-and-health-boost">
  Useful Armor and Health Boost
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-quick-fix-perk-slot-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Killing enemies or inserting armor plates immediately starts health regeneration. Can insert amor plates one-handed.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 50
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 2
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  When you’re in a firefight in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  , taking out enemies and replenishing your armor are essential actions, and having a perk like
  <strong>
   Quick Fix
  </strong>
  that boosts your health regeneration when doing so can make a huge difference to your survival, as it contributes to keeping you in the fight longer. This perk enhances your ability to stay alive, giving you the edge needed to overcome threats. Moreover, being able to equip armor plates with one hand can be a game-changer during intense moments, allowing you to stay focused on the battle while staying protected.
 </p>
 <h2 id="resolute">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Resolute
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="priceless-movement-boost">
  Priceless Movement Boost
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-resolute-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Taking damage from gunfire provides a boost to movement speed for a short duration.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 5
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  If you’re someone who thrives on constant action in Battle Royale or Resurgence modes in
  <em>
   Warzone
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   Resolute
  </strong>
  is the Perk you need. It grants a temporary boost to your movement speed when you take damage, which can be crucial for both escaping tricky situations and dodging incoming fire. This advantage allows you to evade elimination by using your increased mobility to reposition, or if you prefer to keep fighting, it can help you recover enough to dodge and counterattack effectively.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="tempered">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Tempered
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="fewer-armor-plates-grant-more-action">
  Fewer Armor Plates Grant More Action
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tempered-perk-slot-3.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       Refill armor plates to full with two plates instead of three.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 35
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <strong>
   Tempered
  </strong>
  may seem like a simple perk, it has remained one of the most popular choices since its debut back in 2020's
  <em>
   Black Ops Cold War
  </em>
  . The perk lets you fully equip your armor with just two plates, making it easier to recover during a fight. This advantage allows you to stay in the fight longer, counterattack more effectively, and maintain momentum by preventing your enemy from regaining control. With Tempered, you can play more aggressively without the constant worry of spending a ton of time restoring your armor.
 </p>
 <h2 id="tracker">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Tracker
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="easily-spot-nearby-enemies">
  Easily Spot Nearby Enemies
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/call-of-duty-warzone-tracker-perk-slot-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Description
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       How to Unlock
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Perk Slot
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       See enemy footsteps. Bullets you fire briefly mark an enemy for you and your squad. Enemies that down you are automatically pinged.
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Reach Level 29
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       Perk Slot 3
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Tracker
  </strong>
  is one of the most versatile Perks in the game, providing valuable situational awareness. It highlights enemy footprints on the ground, helping you avoid surprise attacks or set up your own ambushes by knowing the enemy’s exact position. Additionally, any bullets you fire and land on enemies will briefly mark them for your team as well, allowing teammates to track enemy movements without needing mid-fight callouts. Furthermore, if you're downed by an enemy, they will be automatically pinged, allowing your squad to avenge you while also ensuring a potential revival.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honkai: Star Rail's Time Control Mechanic Explained</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/honkai-star-rail-time-control-mechanic-explained/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  When Amphoreus was first revealed, there had been rumors that
  <strong>
   <em>
    Honkai: Star Rail
   </em>
  </strong>
  would include time-bending that is said to be a core gameplay mechanic in the chapter. This was intriguing because it would be a first for
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  and there was a lot of speculation about how it would work during exploration and/or combat.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  During the recent
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  Version 3.0 Special Program stream, the developers revealed that Trailblazer will have the ability to control time in certain areas in Amphoreus. Initial snippets show how the unique mechanic works, which actually has an important role in the next arc's story.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="trailblazer-39-s-time-control-ability-is-a-big-deal-in-amphoreus">
  Trailblazer's Time Control Ability is a Big Deal in Amphoreus
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-684838764" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-684838764" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-684838764" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-684838764" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-684838764-img" id="article-gallery-1-684838764">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-684838764" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1814499068">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Amphoreus is a mysterious dystopian world that survived a millennium-long war between Titans and mortals. When the Astral Express Crew arrives, they will meet a group of heroes known as the Chrysos Heirs, whose mission is to obtain the Titans' Coreflames, so they can bring the planet back to its former glory. Amphoreus also has influences from Greek mythology, which are evident in the characters, locations, and even the gameplay.
 </p>
 <p>
  As mentioned, one of the core gameplay mechanics of
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's Amphoreus arc is the Trailblazer's ability to control time, also known as Oronyx's Prayer. Oronyx is known as the Titan of Time, who governs the past, present, and future of Amphoreus, and also safeguards memories. According to
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's devs, Trailblazer is able to use the Titan's power through a phenomenon known as Oronyx's Miracle, allowing them to recreate illusions of the past and restore certain objects to their original state.
 </p>
 <p>
  Gameplay clips from
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  's Version 3.0 Special Program stream showed the Trailblazer exploring a ruin within Castrum Kremnos and approaching a tome to activate Oronyx's Prayer, which is symbolized by an hourglass symbol at the lower right of the screen. This gives them the ability to see visions of the past that can help them rebuild accessways in order to reach certain areas and, in some cases, the timelines can converge, and the Trailblazer can see the map's past and present states.
 </p>
 <p>
  The rewind ability allows them to stop time at the right moment to create walkways, clear debris, and even stop Zagreus, a mischievous thief, from stealing a treasure chest from the overworld. This new gameplay mechanic is quite similar to
  <em>
   Life is Strange
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Life is Strange: Double Exposure
  </em>
  's time-bending powers, where players can utilize these skills to solve puzzles.
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Oronyx's Miracle:
   </strong>
   A phenomenon used by the followers of the Titan of Time to create illusions, change reality, and restore objects to their past state.
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Oronyx's Prayer:
   </strong>
   A rewinding power that the Trailblazer can use to bring back objects to their past state. This can be used on memory-laden objects, which show a ripple of energy that indicates that Oronyx's Prayer can be used there.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  It's still unknown if the time control mechanic will be available across the entirety of Amphoreus, or just a specific area similar to Penacony's Dreamscape.
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  devs also teased that there would be a special map in the Amphoreus update where the Trailblazer "can experience the past and present in all its glory."
 </p>
 <p>
  Likewise, the importance of this power is still under wraps, which could be a hint that Oronyx's presence could be a big deal in the long run. This is interesting because there is a rumor that March 7th might get a massive role in
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  Version 3.0 because of an unannounced character in her likeness known by their Divine Authority, "Oronyx, Veil of Evernight." For now, players will just have to wait until
  <em>
   Honkai: Star Rail
  </em>
  Version 3.0 launches on January 15 to find out more about Amphoreus and everything within it.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect From Split Fiction in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/split-fiction-2025-news-reveals-gameplay-release-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  After being revealed during 2024's The Game Awards and given a release date in early 2025, player expectations may already be high for Hazelight Studios' next upcoming co-op game,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Split Fiction
   </strong>
  </em>
  . With Hazelight Studios' first game,
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  , winning The Game Awards' prestigious Game of the Year in 2021, it was arguably a smart move for the developer to announce its next game,
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  , during 2024's awards show to garner players' attention. But now expectations have been set for
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  as the game builds on Hazelight Studios' co-op formula from
  <em>
   A Way Out
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  However, between
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  's official announcement in December 2024 and its release date confirmed for March 2025, this doesn't appear to leave much time for Hazelight Studios to build hype around the upcoming game. As a result, players could expect to see a surge in updates about
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  ahead of its launch to provide new information about the game, fill in any blanks players might still have, and ultimately generate interest leading up to its release.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="split-fiction-will-be-a-new-direction-for-hazelight-studios">
  Split Fiction Will Be a New Direction for Hazelight Studios
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1659701867" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1659701867" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1659701867" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1659701867" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1659701867-img" id="article-gallery-1-1659701867">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1659701867" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1235506907">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Based on Hazelight Studios' previous games,
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  is primed to follow the same co-op formula the developer has become known for. Though some players may be more familiar with Hazelight Studios thanks to its second game,
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  , winning Game of the Year in 2021, the developer has explored the potential for co-op gameplay and two-player storytelling since its first game,
  <em>
   A Way Out
  </em>
  . These games could offer players some insight into what to expect from the studio's upcoming
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  , but Hazelight Studios' next game could be a blend of both as the developer ventures into new territory.
 </p>
 <p>
  For instance,
  <em>
   A Way Out
  </em>
  was a more realistic and grounded experience than the studio's objectively more fantastical
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  , whereas
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  appears to strike a balance between the two. Based on the gameplay trailer revealed during 2024's The Game Awards and commentary made by Hazelight Studios' Director, Josef Fares,
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  will combine both science fiction and fantasy through its protagonists trapped within a simulation—how far
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  takes this hybridization of genres and what the game's larger story will be may still be unclear ahead of its launch.
 </p>
 <h3 id="split-fiction-is-expected-to-stay-true-to-hazelight-studios-39-formula">
  Split Fiction is Expected to Stay True To Hazelight Studios' Formula
 </h3>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  may be taking a new direction from Hazelight Studios' previous games in terms of tone and story, the core of its co-op gameplay seems like it will stay true to the developer's current format. For example, Fares outlined during
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  's trailer that, similar to
  <em>
   It Takes Two
  </em>
  , will feature unique mechanics exclusive to each level requiring players to work together, such as raising fantasy-based dragons or donning sci-fi suits. Moreover, Fares confirmed that
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  will continue to use the Friends Pass, meaning players can expect to share the gameplay experience with a friend.
 </p>
 <h3 id="players-should-expect-to-learn-more-before-split-fiction-39-s-release">
  Players Should Expect to Learn More Before Split Fiction's Release
 </h3>
 <p>
  Despite expectations that
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  won't stray far from Hazelight Studios' existing co-op approach, the upcoming game could still break new ground with its story, especially given that its trailer focused more on gameplay than narrative. Therefore, with an impending March 6 release date, players could expect to hear more about
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  over the coming months, such as revealing more details about the game's story, its protagonists Zoe and Mio, or its CEO antagonist of Rader Publishing. This could even include a more fleshed-out story trailer or a more in-depth gameplay demo showcasing a few of
  <em>
   Split Fiction
  </em>
  's earliest levels.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk 2077: The 18 Best Decisions V Can Make</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cyberpunk-2077-best-choices-decisions/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Certain characters and dialogue options in
      <em>
       Cyberpunk 2077
      </em>
      have a significant impact on the story and the fate of certain characters. The player must pay attention to make the best decisions.
     </li>
     <li>
      In the
      <em>
       Phantom Liberty
      </em>
      DLC, players must make important choices that affect the story and the characters. Players should consider if they can trust Songbird and if helping her is the best choice for V.
     </li>
     <li>
      Making specific choices in
      <em>
       Cyberpunk 2077
      </em>
      can lead to new endings, secret endings, and even romantic relationships. Players should choose wisely to shape V's journey in Night City.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It’s no secret that living the best life in Night City is practically impossible. However,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Cyberpunk 2077
   </em>
  </strong>
  is filled with actions and choices that directly impact V’s life and the lives of those around them. There are many ethical and moral decisions that V can make, and it all lies in the hands of the player.
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  holds many paths, and the player must choose their own.
 </p>
 <p>
  If the player is looking for the best decisions in
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  , then they need to pay close attention to certain characters and dialogue options. Although life in Night City may not be the greatest dream, it can still harbor some good moments for those who make the right choices.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Updated January 5, 2025, by Jake Fillery:
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   With so many moral decisions to make in Cyberpunk 2077, it can often be hard to figure out if players have made the right choice or not. There are some terrible decisions to be made, but the best decisions V can make in Cyberpunk 2077 will be listed below so that players can ensure that they have the most satisfying time in Night City, even if some moral conundrums prove difficult to swallow.
  </em>
 </p>
 <p>
  <span class="article-alert">
   This Article contains spoilers for Cyberpunk 2077 &amp; Phantom Liberty
  </span>
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="help-johnny-fix-his-past-mistakes">
  <span class="item-num">
   18
  </span>
  <span>
   Help Johnny Fix His Past Mistakes
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="johnny-might-be-messed-up-but-he-has-a-heart">
  Johnny Might be Messed Up, But He Has a Heart
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="johnny silverhand at the oil field" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg" decoding="async" height="1280" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/20241001152040_1-cropped.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2560"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After confiding with Johnny in Chippin' In, V's relationship with the relentless rocker boy changes, hopefully for the better. With their newfound trust, V can help Johnny make amends with some old friends, like Kerry Eurodyne and other former band members of Samurai who Johnny left behind in his crusade against Arasaka all those decades ago.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the best things V can do is to help Johnny fix the wrongdoings of his past, as it seems like the natural progression of their bond and also provides players with fun missions to experience outside of the main story. Being a pal to Johnny is a great thing for V, especially as their own mortality draws ever closer.
 </p>
 <h2 id="never-trust-arasaka">
  <span class="item-num">
   17
  </span>
  <span>
   Never Trust Arasaka
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-worst-thing-players-can-do-is-help-arasaka-rise-from-the-ashes">
  The Worst Thing Players Can Do is Help Arasaka Rise from the Ashes
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="cyberpunk 2077 yorinobu arasaka" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/cyberpunk-2077-plot-hole.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Whether it's Hanako, Takemura, or anyone working under the foot of Arasaka, none of them can be trusted. Arasaka has never proved itself as the caring corpo, and Johnny has reinforced the idea that Arasaka is the worst of the worst anytime he gets to open his mouth, so try and heed his warning for the best outcome.
 </p>
 <p>
  Trusting Arasaka breaks the relationships and moralities of many, so any choice that has Arasaka's favor in mind should be actively avoided. Arasaka will never have V's best interest at heart, and if players out there want to be free, then it's best to actively avoid helping them in any way.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="let-peralez-live-a-beautiful-lie">
  <span class="item-num">
   16
  </span>
  <span>
   Let Peralez Live a Beautiful Lie
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="jefferson-peralez-can-never-know-the-truth">
  Jefferson Peralez Can Never Know the Truth
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Jefferson Peralez Sitting Cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg" decoding="async" height="800" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Jefferson-Peralez-Dream-On-Cyberpunk.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1600"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the toughest decisions in the entire game comes from the realization that the Peralez family is having their brain patterns rewritten by unknown forces so that they are easily controlled. While it would make sense to drop this truth bomb on Jefferson, it is against his wife's wishes and also puts them in far more danger than if they would just lose their identities like they've headed down for a long nap.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's a decision with no winner, but not telling Jefferson the truth means that he is safe from Mr. Blue Eyes, and if players do tell him the truth, then he will become overly paranoid, unhealthy, and refuse to believe anyone around him to the point where it seems he might take his own life instead of leading Night City as its mayor, even if that mayor is under the thumb of higher powers.
 </p>
 <h2 id="help-joshua-attone-for-his-sins">
  <span class="item-num">
   15
  </span>
  <span>
   Help Joshua Attone For His Sins
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="don-39-t-let-his-sacrifice-be-in-vain">
  Don't Let His Sacrifice Be In Vain
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=70&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=1"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Joshua Stephenson Praying" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg" decoding="async" height="500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cyberpunk-2077-joshua-(1).jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Joshua Stephenson was a bad man, and his death sentence is for a justified reason. Joshua has hurt and killed a lot of people, but the Sinnerman side quest shows that he's had a change of faith, and he now believes in God and that he is the new Messiah. As a result, Joshua wants to sacrifice himself, but this is being exploited by corporate greed to film it as a braindance so people can experience The Passion in all its glory.
 </p>
 <p>
  Whilst some may want to save Joshua, they must know that it isn't possible, and the best way to proceed in this quest is to guide Joshua on his path, and to comfort him. If players doubt him or make him question his decision to sacrifice himself, then he will still go through with it, but with immense pain and suffering. Being gentle and affirming to Joshua will help make his sacrifice seem important, and will even move other people as he redeems himself for his past sins.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="saving-barry">
  <span class="item-num">
   14
  </span>
  <span>
   Saving Barry
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="stop-a-suicide-from-a-friend-in-need">
  Stop A Suicide From A Friend In Need
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="barry lewis" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/barry-lewis.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Life in Night City isn't easy, and in Happy Together, V's neighbor Barry is having the hardest time there is. His friend has died, and not even his colleagues at the NCPD can get through to him. If players fail to investigate Barry's condition or give him a proper talk, then he will kill himself, and his friends at the NCPD will be distraught by another good man lost to the corruptible horrors of Night City.
 </p>
 <p>
  There's a way to save Barry once players head to the Columbarium, and they will be able to find a memorial dedicated to Andrew, which is Barry's dead friend, who just so happens to be a turtle. Venturing here before talking to the cops after a conversation with Barry means that his life will be saved.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rescue-president-myers">
  <span class="item-num">
   13
  </span>
  <span>
   Rescue President Myers
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="saving-the-nusa-president-opens-up-the-phantom-liberty-dlc">
  Saving The NUSA President Opens Up The Phantom Liberty DLC
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Cyberpunk 2077 Phantom Liberty Rosalind Myers" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-rosalind-myers.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If players have purchased the
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  expansion, then they should receive a phone call from Songbird about a contract to save the NUSA President, Rosalind Myers. If players take on this quest, then they best hurry, as it's a race against time to get to Myers once her shuttle crash lands in the dangerous zone of Dogtown.
 </p>
 <p>
  Failing to reach her in time will cause the game to continue, with Songbird kicking V to the dirt and vowing to never help them again. Players can reverse this decision by loading a past save, but it's still a bad idea to let Rosalind Myers die, as it will lock them out of the amazing story from
  <em>
   Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="helping-reed">
  <span class="item-num">
   12
  </span>
  <span>
   Helping Reed
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="reed-will-save-v-39-s-life-but-at-the-cost-of-cyberware">
  Reed Will Save V's Life But At The Cost Of Cyberware
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="A screenshot of Idris Elba as Solomon Reed against a red light in Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty." data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-phantom-liberty-locked-out-solomon-reed.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As players progress through
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty
  </em>
  , they will meet the tritagonist, Solomon Reed. Reed is vitally important to the story, and his allegiance to the FIA is above all else. Despite being killed for and by his country 7 years before the events of the game, it won’t stop his loyalty, and his promise to V: Solomon Reed will save their life.
 </p>
 <p>
  By helping Solomon Reed, he will fulfill his promise to help V. Choosing the right dialogue options and making specific decisions will see Reed see V as more than just an FIA asset, and as a friend, whom he will desperately want to help, and choosing Solomon Reed will also open up a new secret ending for the base game.
 </p>
 <h2 id="have-bennett-and-jago-rule-dogtown">
  <span class="item-num">
   11
  </span>
  <span>
   Have Bennett And Jago Rule Dogtown
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="mutual-co-operation-ensures-corpos-stay-out-of-dogtown">
  Mutual Co-operation Ensures Corpos Stay Out Of Dogtown
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="kurt hansen's wake, with jago and bennett watching V as Aguilar " data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg" decoding="async" height="1500" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/collage-maker-03-oct-2023-01-12-pm-9219.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Fatal consequences strike in Phantom Liberty, and there comes a point where a new ruler must be declared for Dogtown. In the quest Run This Town, players are tasked by Mr. Hands to provide Dogtown with a new, ruthless dictator, one on par with Kurt Hansen, but with a little more restraint thanks to a loyal accountant.
 </p>
 <p>
  The quest is a lot of fun, but what’s vitally important is that players use their dialogue skills to make sure that Jago steps down from the race of Dogtown’s newest leader, and that Bennett rules supreme. However, if players are smart, they can make sure that Bennett rules and Jago lives, ensuring mutual cooperation for Dogtown to thrive under new leadership.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="killing-dodger">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Killing Dodger
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-key-figure-in-the-drug-business-in-amp-out-of-dogtown">
  A Key Figure In The Drug Business, In &amp; Out Of Dogtown
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="cyberpunk 2077 waiting for dodger walkthrough" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-waiting-for-dodger.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Receiving the Gig Waiting for Dodger, players can head through a former NCPD station in Pacifica near the Grand Imperial Mall. The objective is clear, thanks to Stella’s direction, who will tell players that they need to infiltrate the NCPD station and find her husband and his friend, two cops who have gotten themselves in a fairly bad situation involving drugs.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once players have rescued Bill and Charles, they will be cornered by Dodger, a central character involved in Kurt Hansen’s Barghest unit. Although players can talk their way out of this, killing Dodger is a great choice, as not only does it give an iconic weapon, but it also takes out one of Kurt Hansen’s important men.
 </p>
 <h2 id="give-paco-and-babs-to-panam-palmer">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Give Paco and Babs To Panam Palmer
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="save-two-innocent-barghest-soldiers-from-execution">
  Save Two Innocent Barghest Soldiers From Execution
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="cyberpunk 2077 balls to the wall paco and babs" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/cyberpunk-2077-balls-to-the-wall-walkthrough-10.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players can save Paco and Babs in Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty during the Balls to the Wall side job, as long as they call in some favors. Paco and Babs are in deep trouble with Barghest, thanks to Paco’s betrayal and desire for Eurodollars. However, Paco’s fate doesn’t need to resort to being a message to the traitors of Dogtown, and they can spare the character from his fate with a noose.
 </p>
 <p>
  All players need to do is give Panam Palmer and the Aldecaldos a text on their phone, to which she will happily assist. Panam will help Paco and Babs sneak out of Dogtown, and then out of Night City, where they can start fresh and travel the world, free from being a Kurt Hansen soldier.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="send-jackie-to-his-mother">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Send Jackie To His Mother
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="pay-respects-to-a-dear-friend-with-jackie-39-s-ofrenda">
  Pay Respects To A Dear Friend With Jackie's Ofrenda
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="jackie's ofrenda in cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/jackie-s-ofrenda-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the earliest tragedies in
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  is the death of Jackie Welles. Jackie was V’s best friend, and his life was taken during The Heist mission. When Jackie has passed, V has the decision to send his body somewhere. Players should always send Jackie home, to his mother, so that he can have a proper passing.
 </p>
 <p>
  If Jackie is sent to his mother, then players can engage in the emotional mission in which they are involved in Jackie’s Ofrenda. Not only is the funeral upsetting character building, but players can obtain Jackie’s iconic gold dual-wield pistols afterward. Sending his body elsewhere means that Jackie’s mind is trapped in Soulkiller, and he will never be at peace.
 </p>
 <h2 id="diving-with-judy">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Diving With Judy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="give-judy-the-goodbye-she-deserves">
  Give Judy The Goodbye She Deserves
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="cyberpunk 2077 project orion blank slate" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cyberpunk-2077-judy-alvarez-smoking-night-city-skyline.jpeg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Judy is another occupant of Night City who doesn’t exactly live the easiest life. She has been through a lot and has seen even worse. Night City is no friend to Judy, and the city has taken more than she could afford to give. Even when Judy tries to do good and make Clouds a place for Dolls, matters simply worsen as the Tyger Claws retaliate, killing even more people.
 </p>
 <p>
  Judy will ask V to go diving with her to help take her mind off things. Johnny objects, but this is one of the times when players should ignore him. It’s an intimate mission, and female Vs will be able to have a romantic relationship with Jud. Male Vs, on the other hand, will be able to get closure on Judy’s missions, as she will leave Night City forever afterward.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="siding-with-netwatch">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Siding With NetWatch
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-voodoo-boys-cannot-be-trusted">
  The Voodoo Boys Cannot Be Trusted
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="netwatch officer in cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/netwatch-officer-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Siding with Corpos is usually never a good idea, but when it comes to the better of two evils, players should certainly side with NetWatch when the time comes. V will be infected by Placide and the Voodoo Boys with a virus that will kill the NetWatch officer, and V, to free the Voodoo Boy agents trapped in the net. Thanks to Johnny’s chip, V will survive the attack, an attack that proves just how selfish and evil the Voodoo Boys are.
 </p>
 <p>
  With this in mind, players should side with NetWatch to eliminate all of the Voodoo Boys, and finally engage in a boss fight with the rude and disrespectful Placide. The Voodoo Boys are more of a threat than NetWatch, as the latter is simply trying to keep Rogue AIs out of the world, whereas the Voodoo Boys want to join their side for the inevitable war, making them the true enemy.
 </p>
 <h2 id="helping-panam-and-the-aldecaldos">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Helping Panam And The Aldecaldos
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="panam-is-a-loyal-ally-and-the-aldecaldos-can-be-family">
  Panam Is A Loyal Ally, And The Aldecaldos Can Be Family
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="panam palmer cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/panam-palmer-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Panam is a great character in
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  , and players should do what they can to help her, whether that’s in a revenge quest or mending her relationship with the nomad clan the Aldecaldos. In doing so, not only are players given a fun set of missions that help players and V explore a life outside of Night City, but it also opens up future opportunities.
 </p>
 <p>
  In completing the Aldecaldos missions and siding with Panam whenever possible, players will unlock a new ending for the game, as well as a romantic relationship with Panam for male Vs. Panam is a great addition and could be a great ally to all genders of V for her loyalty and determination.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-guy-who-saved-my-life">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Guy Who Saved My Life
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="create-an-inseparable-friendship-with-johnny-silverhand">
  Create An Inseparable Friendship With Johnny Silverhand
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="johnny silverhand in the oil fields" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/johnny-silverhand-in-the-oil-fields.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players who develop a friendship and trust with Johnny Silverhand will find themselves in the side mission Chippin’ In. This side mission can be accessed by letting Johnny go on his date with Rogue and onwards. During this mission, Adam Smasher’s lackey, Jeremiah Grayson, will tell V where Johnny is buried. Going to the Oil Fields with Johnny is an emotional experience. It's also a spiritual awakening for Johnny Silverhand, who realizes he never had a true friend like V.
 </p>
 <p>
  V needs to make the right dialogue choices at this point. Players need to start on the right path by writing on Johnny’s gravestone:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     The guy who saved my life
    </em>
   </strong>
   .”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     Nah, f***ed that up too
    </em>
   </strong>
   .”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     What do you want from me?
    </em>
   </strong>
   ”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     OK. But as second chances go, this is your last
    </em>
   </strong>
   .”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     You were a real d*ck in the beginning.
    </em>
   </strong>
   ”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     When you said you let down your friends…
    </em>
   </strong>
   ”
  </li>
  <li>
   “
   <strong>
    <em>
     Yeah, I’ll call Rogue
    </em>
   </strong>
   .”
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This is the only way players will get a 70% friendship with Johnny Silverhand and unlock the secret ending with their favorite dead choom.
 </p>
 <h2 id="investigating-peter-pan">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Investigating Peter Pan
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="save-a-serial-killer-39-s-child-victims">
  Save A Serial Killer's Child Victims
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="creepy peter pan video in cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/creepy-peter-pan-video-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The instinct for Johnny Silverhand may be to not trust cops, but River Ward makes a good case of why he needs help. River’s nephew is missing and is one of the comatose victims of serial killer Peter Pan. V and River should team up to solve this detective mystery, embarking on a true and unexpected thriller in
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  This mission is like no other, and it’s a delicate matter of child victims that V and the players should try their hardest to solve with River. By choosing to investigate the case with River, players will be able to save kidnapped boys and build a good relationship with River.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="incapacitating-the-cyberpsychos">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Incapacitating The Cyberpsychos
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="incapacitate-don-39-t-kill-to-try-and-find-a-cyberpsycho-cure">
  Incapacitate, Don't Kill, To Try And Find A Cyberpsycho Cure
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="cyberpsycho in cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cyberpsycho-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are plenty of Cyberpsychos in Night City thanks to the indulgence of chrome. Cyberpsychosis is an illness given to people who have too many body modifications. It causes them to lose their minds and commit themselves to a murderous rampage. There is no known cure for Cyberpsychosis, but that doesn’t mean that Regina Jones isn’t trying to solve the case herself.
 </p>
 <p>
  For Regina to gather the appropriate data and help these poor victims of circumstance, V needs to incapacitate all Cyberpsychos. It may not be easy, but it’s the moral thing to do. Beating up Cyberpsychos or using stealth for non-lethal takedowns means that Regina and her team can further research ways to cure these poor victims.
 </p>
 <h2 id="saving-takemura">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Saving Takemura
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="takemura-is-essential-to-fight-for-arasaka">
  Takemura Is Essential To Fight For Arasaka
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="takemura having a coffee in cyberpunk 2077" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" decoding="async" height="1000" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/takemura-having-a-coffee-in-cyberpunk-2077.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2000"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Although Takemura and V started as less than friends, their circumstances made them valuable allies, and eventually friends. Takemura and V kidnap Hanako Arasaka to tell her about her brother’s crimes and that Saburo was murdered by her brother, Yorinobu. However, Arasaka agents flood the hotel and attempt to kill V and Takemura.
 </p>
 <p>
  If V wants to save Takemura, players can climb up the hotel to save Takemura from the overwhelming Arasaka forces. If they leave him behind, Takemura will die and his friendship will be lost, thus ending the possibility of him appearing in several of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's many endings.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
