<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Path of Exile 2 Players Can No Longer Use One of The Game's Best Skills in 0.2.0</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/path-of-exile-2-poe2-energy-shield-es-grim-feast-op-removed-good-bad/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Path of Exile 2's Dawn of the Hunt update includes 5 new Ascendancies and over 100 Unique Items.
     </li>
     <li>
      Grim Feast, a powerful Skill Gem doubling Energy Shield, has been disabled in the game for balancing.
     </li>
     <li>
      The disabling of Grim Feast may shift the meta away from Energy Shield dominance in builds.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  There are many things that will change with
  <strong>
   <em>
    Path of Exile 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  's first major patch since its early access debut, coming out tomorrow with the new Dawn of the Hunt release alongside the new Huntress class, several Ascendancies, and much more. As is customary for action RPGs,
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  's Dawn of the Hunt update will come with a balance pass to the current items, skills, and classes while also adding several more (namely, 5 Ascendancies and over 100 Unique Items, as well as Support Gems). What is unusual is that existing elements are outright removed, but this is the case for one Skill Gem that was previously one of the best in the game, if not the.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  builds are made of many components, and Skill Gems are just one of the bigger cogs in the machine - some can be replaced, while others are "mandatory" for the build to be successful. The early access version of the game proved to be problematic when it came to some Skill Gems, to the point that some had to be nerfed soon after release, while others remained untouched until now. The patch notes for Dawn of the Hunt list all these changes, and interestingly, they also mention that Grim Feast has been removed from the game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="path-of-exile-2-is-disabling-grim-feast-for-the-foreseeable-future">
  Path of Exile 2 is Disabling Grim Feast For The Foreseeable Future
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1957480291" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1957480291" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1957480291" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1957480291" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1957480291-img" id="article-gallery-1-1957480291">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1957480291" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1276869971">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  's Grim Feast was one of the strongest skills to have in any build for a simple reason: it essentially doubled one's Energy Shield. With Energy Shield being the strongest defense in the game by a huge margin, Grim Feast could double the EHP of any Chaos Inoculation build or dramatically increase it for hybrid Life and ES builds. This is because every remnant picked up by players would add Energy Shield to the character's total, potentially overflowing ES up to double its maximum value.
 </p>
 <p>
  The result was that most builds benefited from going the Energy Shield route, and all builds that did were fundamentally miles better with Grim Feast. For these reasons, GGG is disabling Grim Feast from the Gemcutting options in
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  , and all versions of the skill will be unusable for the time being. Grim Feast is not being removed from the game permanently, though, as GGG plans on making changes to it in the future. However, it's implied that the skill will never be the same again, and players can expect a substantial rework for it.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are various reasons why Energy Shield in
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  was a meta option for builds until now, including the fact that the best builds in the game featured characters with high Intelligence or casters. This made Grim Feast all the more played, especially with Chaos Inoculation being very popular due to the itemization gap it removes by taking care of Chaos Resistance on its own. For the sake of balancing the game, since a rework of Energy Shield is much more complex and time-consuming, it seems that the next best solution was to disable Grim Feast entirely.
 </p>
 <h3 id="it-39-s-not-all-doom-and-gloom-for-path-of-exile-2-39-s-best-skill">
  It's Not All Doom and Gloom For Path of Exile 2's Best Skill
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Path of Exile 2
  </em>
  's future updates will still need to address defenses more broadly, such as improving Armour dramatically, given its current state, so it's possible that the next big patch will do all this and also mark the return of Grim Feast. For now, though, players can no longer use this incredibly powerful Gem, and builds will have to adapt moving forward. With the huge amount of nerfs in the patch, it's not impossible that a new meta will form where Energy Shield is not as dominant, which alone could bode well for the return of Grim Feast.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves - Salvatore Ganacci Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves-salvatore-ganacci-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Salvatore Ganacci character trailer
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Switch 2 Edition Feature is a Game Changer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/one-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-switch-2-edition-update-game-changer-auto-build-zelda-notes/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Nintendo Switch 2 will not only introduce new titles, but also enhanced editions of several popular Switch games. Among them are The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild and The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom, both of which will feature improved visuals and a new "Zelda Notes" function. This tool, accessible via the Nintendo Switch app, allows players to store and share information, including Auto-Build designs in Tears of the Kingdom, making it easier for players to recreate and exchange vehicle or weapon blueprints.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Titanfall 3 Coming in 2026</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/titanfall-3-2026-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Popular Apex Legends leakers claim Titanfall 3 is in development and set for a 2026 release.
     </li>
     <li>
      Respawn Entertainment may have been juggling Titanfall 3 alongside other projects like Apex Legends and Star Wars Jedi: Survivor.
     </li>
     <li>
      If rumors are true, Titanfall 3 may potentially be revealed at the 2025 Game Awards in December.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  First-person shooter fans have been clamoring for
  <em>
   <strong>
    Titanfall 3
   </strong>
  </em>
  for a long time, and it seems two
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  leakers might have some insight on the matter. Although EA developer Respawn Entertainment has largely moved on to the very successful and critically well-received
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi
  </em>
  games, a large portion of the studio's fans still want the team to take another crack at
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  , and have only heard bad news throughout the years about the prospect of a third entry in the sci-fi mech shooter franchise.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's safe to say that the
  <em>
   Titanfall
  </em>
  franchise never had it easy. The original game, one of the first ever AAA games of its era to forego a single-player story campaign to focus on its multiplayer suite, was exclusively released on the Xbox One in 2014, only a few months after the new console's disappointing launch.
  <em>
   Titanfall 2
  </em>
  followed up two years later in 2016, and while this time the sequel offered a fully-fledged single-player story campaign and was released as a multiplatform title, it was notoriously sandwiched between the releases of two multiplayer FPS behemoths in
  <em>
   Call of Duty: Infinite Warfare
  </em>
  and EA's very own
  <em>
   Battlefield 1
  </em>
  , causing it to once again fly under the radar. Despite this,
  <em>
   Titanfall 2
  </em>
  's single-player FPS campaign is remembered as one of the best of its generation, which has led to many fans calling for a third installment.
 </p>
 <p>
  Now, after EA has come out several times to debunk
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  rumors, two well-known
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  leakers have come out claiming that Respawn Entertainment is indeed working on the third
  <em>
   Titanfall
  </em>
  game. On Twitter, YOROTSUKI posted an image of a
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  logo, expressing that the "secret game" they previously mentioned was in development at Respawn is indeed
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  . Furthermore, they claim that the game is going to be revealed at the 2025 Game Awards in December with a 2026 release window. Another
  <em>
   Apex
  </em>
  leaker, Osvaldatore on Twitter, corroborated YOROTSUKI's claim.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="apex-legends-leaker-claims-titanfall-3-is-real-coming-in-2026">
  Apex Legends Leaker Claims Titanfall 3 is Real, Coming in 2026
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-976648160" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-976648160" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-976648160" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-976648160" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-976648160-img" id="article-gallery-1-976648160">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-976648160" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-411293104">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  With everything Respawn has going on with the ongoing
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  and the confirmed third
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi
  </em>
  game, it's hard to see the studio also being able to juggle
  <em>
   Titanfall 3,
  </em>
  and aim to release the game next year to boot. If these rumors are true, it could mean that
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  might have been in development alongside
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi: Survivor.
  </em>
  Respawn reportedly has three development teams, one for the
  <em>
   Star Wars Jedi
  </em>
  games, one for
  <em>
   Apex Legends
  </em>
  , and another that works on VR experiences. Out of them, it would be safe to assume this rumored
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  is the
  <em>
   Apex
  </em>
  team's game, since they share a universe.
 </p>
 <p>
  If
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  does happen to get revealed at The Game Awards in December, it would likely mean that the game would be looking at a Fall or Holiday 2026 release window. However, since this is all still rumor and speculation, fans will have to wait and see for themselves whether Respawn really is working on
  <em>
   Titanfall 3
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk 2077: The Case for Project Orion to Follow the Devil Ending</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/cyberpunk-2077-project-orion-the-devil-ending-good-interesting-story/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Cyberpunk 2077
   </em>
  </strong>
  , despite its innumerable faults at launch, is a truly special game, and one can only assume that
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , its codenamed sequel, will solidify its nascent legacy. But while
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  is full of potential—especially considering what CD Projekt Red has hopefully learned from
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's disastrous release—its premise is a big mystery.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-warning" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom warning" id="custom_block_1">
   <div class="custom_block-content warning">
    <p>
     Major spoilers ahead for
     <em>
      Cyberpunk 2077
     </em>
     .
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Perhaps the greatest question mark surrounding
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  is how exactly it will connect to the story of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  . After all, CDPR's sci-fi opus features several distinct endings, most of which result in V's demise. Canonizing an ending in an RPG series is always messy business, but the fact that
  <em>
   Cyberpunk
  </em>
  is, for the most part, a self-contained narrative, changes things as well. It's not like, say,
  <em>
   Mass Effect
  </em>
  , where each entry leads into the next one, and all of them come together to form a single narrative. Having said that, if CD Projekt Red is indeed going to make
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  some sort of direct sequel to
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  , it has to choose one ending to write in stone, and The Devil could be the right choice.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077-arguing-for-the-devil-to-be-the-canon-ending">
  Cyberpunk 2077: Arguing for The Devil To Be the Canon Ending
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1429563839" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1429563839" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1429563839" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1429563839" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1429563839-img" id="article-gallery-1-1429563839">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1429563839" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-668031199">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="the-devil-is-cyberpunk-39-s-darkest-ending">
  The Devil Is Cyberpunk's Darkest Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  It's not exactly surprising that The Devil is almost unanimously cited as
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  's worst ending. It involves V selling out to Arasaka—a corporation that is presented as, if not wholly evil, a symbol of everything wrong with the game's hyper-capitalist, unregulated world. Arasaka is the player's enemy for most of the game: it created the engram that set Johnny and V on their trail of destruction in the first place, and its crimes against humanity in general are well documented. Put plainly, they are not a fan-favorite faction.
 </p>
 <p>
  But like so many uber-powerful organizations, they can be a corrupting force. They make V a tantalizing offer: they can save their life, in a sense, by copying their consciousness onto a personality engram of their own. This engram can then theoretically be implanted into any vessel, organic or cybernetic, which effectively makes V immortal. Of course, this all comes at the cost of working for Arasaka, aiding their ultimate, shadowy goals and selling V's soul, but this is a deal many would likely take in the real world. Even though it's just a copy of V's persona, the idea of continued life has widespread appeal; as sad as it is to admit, the lofty ideals of many would likely crumble when faced with such an offer, especially if the alternative is a slow and painful death.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The Devil ending has an alternate branch, wherein V helps Arasaka and still chooses to die, though this doesn't have much potential when it comes to a sequel—it's mostly just depressing and fruitless.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="project-orion-could-do-a-lot-with-the-devil-ending">
  Project Orion Could Do a Lot With The Devil Ending
 </h3>
 <p>
  Despite being dark, depressing, and not exactly loved by fans, The Devil is a particularly fitting ending. The violent and unjust corporate world of
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  is hard to escape uncorrupted, and V abandoning any semblance of morals or integrity for the chance at everlasting life is definitely thematically resonant, if rather disappointing. Moreover, following this concept to its conclusion could allow for a great degree of narrative potential.
 </p>
 <p>
  If CD Projekt Red wants to make V the protagonist of
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , then The Devil is one of the only endings that could be canonized, since V is sentenced to death in most others. Maybe
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  could be about V rectifying this decision, as players could assume the role of the "engram V," who regrets siding with Arasaka and chooses to fight them to undo their
  <em>
   Frankenstein
  </em>
  -esque fate, even if it means their death. Alternatively, V could be an antagonist in
  <em>
   Project Orion
  </em>
  , serving as a puppet of their corporate overlords.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
