<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Shouts Out Hollow Knight: Silksong</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xbox-hollow-knight-silksong-mention/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Hollow Knight: Silksong, the highly anticipated sequel, is confirmed for a day one Xbox Game Pass launch.
     </li>
     <li>
      The ID@Xbox director mentioned Silksong, creating excitement among fans.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans speculate Silksong may finally release in 2025, following years of silence from Team Cherry.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hollow Knight: Silksong
   </strong>
  </em>
  has recently been mentioned by the head of ID@Xbox alongside a handful of other games that are confirmed to be releasing this year. It's been widely accepted since the game's 2017 release that the original
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  is one of the greatest indie games ever made. A brutally challenging 2D Metroidvania,
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  garnered near universal praise, with its Nintendo Switch port achieving a 90 on Metacritic.
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  began development as DLC for the original game, but later grew into a fully fledged sequel.
 </p>
 <p>
  With six entire years passing since
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  's initial reveal back in 2019, the sequel has achieved a unicorn-like reputation, leaving fans in the dark for years on end, popping out every few years with a small update. Its largest update by far was at Xbox's 2022 Summer Game Fest showcase, where
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  debuted an all-new trailer and confirmed its day one Xbox Game Pass launch. This same showcase promised all its games would be out in the next 12 months, insinuating
  <em>
   Silksong
  </em>
  would be out by June 2023. However, as the deadline neared, developer Team Cherry announced
  <em>
   Silksong
  </em>
  's indefinite delay, and fans have heard nothing but radio silence from the team ever since.
 </p>
 <p>
  The director of ID@Xbox, Guy Richards, made reference to
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  in a new Xbox Wire post. In addition to talking about some of the program's recent successes, such as last year's indie hits
  <em>
   Neva
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Another Crab's Treasure
  </em>
  , Richards also looked ahead at some of Xbox's indie partnerships fans can be excited about this year. Richards went on to name games like turn-based fantasy RPG
  <em>
   Clair Obscur: Expedition 33
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Descenders Next,
  </em>
  and Remedy Entertainment's co-op FPS,
  <em>
   FBC Firebreak
  </em>
  . In that same breath, Richards unexpectedly name-dropped
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong,
  </em>
  creating much buzz and excitement among fans online.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="hollow-knight-silksong-mentioned-by-id-xbox-39-s-guy-richards">
  Hollow Knight: Silksong Mentioned by ID@Xbox's Guy Richards
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-415966847" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-415966847" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-415966847" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-415966847" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-415966847-img" id="article-gallery-1-415966847">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-415966847" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-519300593">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It's very interesting how each of the three games that preceded
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  in Guy Richards' comment all have 2025 release dates or windows. Both
  <em>
   Descenders Next
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Expedition 33
  </em>
  are releasing next month, on April 9 and 24 respectively, and
  <em>
   FBC Firebreak
  </em>
  is expected to land at some point in 2025. Since
  <em>
   Silksong
  </em>
  already had a release window that it missed two years ago, it doesn't seem too unlikely that the game will finally see its long-awaited and highly anticipated release by the end of this year. Still, some
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  fans aren't holding their breath after six years of near-complete silence from Team Cherry.
 </p>
 <p>
  With Nintendo's Switch 2 Direct right around the corner on April 2, some
  <em>
   Hollow Knight: Silksong
  </em>
  hopefuls are thinking it might show up there. However, it seems
  <em>
   Silksong
  </em>
  might already have some sort of marketing partnership in place with Xbox and Game Pass. Furthermore, Nintendo might only want to focus this upcoming Direct on the new Switch 2 console and its own first-party games. As usual,
  <em>
   Hollow Knight
  </em>
  fans will just have to tune in to see whether the planets are aligned for
  <em>
   Silksong.
  </em>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite Issues Refund That Could Indicate Major Changes to a Type of Cosmetic</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fortnite-cosmetics-refunds-march-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players who own the Rap Boy Reloaded skin and the Air Jordan 3 SE Unite Kicks in Fortnite are getting refunds.
     </li>
     <li>
      This has led some players to hypothesize that every pair of shoes would soon count as Kicks and be added to Fortnite's in-game Locker.
     </li>
     <li>
      It's unclear when, or if, this will happen, as Epic Games hasn't released a statement.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fortnite
   </em>
  </strong>
  has refunded players who acquired a skin wearing a purchasable set of kicks, generating a rumor that shoes will soon be offered as separate cosmetics like Back Blings.
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  introduced players to Kicks back in November 2024, and while some found it to be a strange addition at first, it didn't take long before it grew on many, especially once more options became available. The Jordan Air 1s were the first pair of Kicks to make it to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  as a reward for those who completed the Dynamo TNTina Quests, available through the Chapter 2 Remix Battle Pass. However, not long after they became available, more pairs of kicks were released in the Item Shop.
 </p>
 <p>
  Nowadays, there are dozens of Kick options in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  . Most gamers have grown used to seeing them rotate in and out of the
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  Item Shop when it refreshes. However, there has always been some controversy regarding the price of Kicks. The cheapest pairs of Kicks cost 600 V-Bucks, but those that have more complex designs or are a result of collabs tend to cost between 800 and 1,000 V-Bucks, meaning gamers must spend the equivalent of $10 to buy a pair of digital shoes.
 </p>
 <p>
  The Air Jordan is one of the most popular models of Kicks in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , and there are several of its variants that gamers can acquire in the Item Shop. Many Air Jordans in the Shop cost 1,000 V-Bucks, and this includes the Air Jordan 3 SE Unit Kicks. The Rap Boy Reloaded skin, one of the several Eminem skins in
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  , rocks this exact model of shoes in-game, allowing players to wear them without owning them as Kicks. Oddly enough, players who purchased both the Rap Boy Reloaded skin as well as the Air Jordan 3 SE Unit Kicks recently got a refund of 1,000 V-Bucks, which led to discussion and speculation among fans.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="who-received-a-refund-in-fortnite">
  Who Received a Refund in Fortnite?
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Players who owned the Rap Boy Reloaded skin and the Air Jordan 3 SE Unite Kicks.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Since the refund only applies to users who own a skin that features the Air Jordan 3 SE Unite shoes, players began to speculate that this could mean every pair of shoes would soon count as Kicks and be added to
  <em>
   Fortnite
  </em>
  's in-game Locker. This would mean that players are receiving a refund because, since the Rap Boy Reloaded is wearing these shoes, they should be included as skins when purchasing his full skin and not as a separate item.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-758090979" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-758090979" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-758090979" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-758090979" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-758090979-img" id="article-gallery-1-758090979">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-758090979" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2110310466">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  It may sound confusing at first, but the trick is to look at it like a removable cosmetic, such as Back Blings. If this scenario becomes a reality, players will be able to freely mix and match most of their owned skins' shoes, as they will be accessible in the Kicks tab. It is unknown if this will happen in the future, and if it does, there are no leaks to indicate when it will become the norm. Nevertheless, this theory would explain why players were issued a refund for owning these two items simultaneously. Thankfully, they were only given back the currency in V-Bucks and were able to keep both cosmetics.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best Games About Surfing The Web</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-games-about-surfing-the-web/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Mundane tasks such as browsing the internet are given an exciting spin in these titles.
     </li>
     <li>
      Internet-based games offer intriguing storytelling and interactive experiences.
     </li>
     <li>
      Games such as Her Story and The Roottrees Are Dead task the player with navigating the web to uncover the truth.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Games always have their players accomplishing tasks of varying scope, be it just passing their school exams to saving their world from a deadly dragon. It all depends on the story they want to tell, but most games opt more towards the latter, tending to stay away from the mundane every day, or if they do tread there, putting their own spin on things.
 </p>
 <p>
  A few of these games task their players with surfing the web, visiting various web pages and completing activities, whether it is the whole game or just a portion of it. With the internet such a known quality almost everyone accesses daily, these developers have done their best to make these games truly intriguing, and massively fun to play.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-v">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto V
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="occasionally-the-player-might-need-to-log-online">
  Occasionally, the Player Might Need to Log Online
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-2018483954" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-2018483954" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-2018483954" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018483954" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-2018483954-img" id="article-gallery-1-2018483954">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-2018483954" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1573839710">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Grand Theft Auto 5
   </strong>
  </em>
  is without a doubt one of the biggest games of all time, giving players a massive map to explore, and so much to see and do. This freedom gives players the choice to partake in side-quests, tour around the city to see the sights, and cause all sorts of mischief that can grab the wrong sort of attention.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once introduced in the game, players have the freedom to access it whenever they wish to choose, as their protagonist's smartphone can be used as a web surfing tool. There is quite a lengthy list of websites they can access, from sites deciding to outing cults to purchasing cars. Every website is interactive, unlike previous entries in the franchise, hugely expanding on what players can do on the internet, and ensuring players will open up their phones occasionally.
 </p>
 <h2 id="simulacra">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Simulacra
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="solve-a-missing-person-39-s-case-using-a-smartphone">
  Solve a Missing Person's Case Using a Smartphone
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-685442338" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-685442338" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-685442338" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-685442338" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-685442338-img" id="article-gallery-2-685442338">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-685442338" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1637053988">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms:
   </strong>
   PC, Android, iOS, PS4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   October 26th, 2017
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developers:
   </strong>
   Kaigan Games
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genres:
   </strong>
   Horror
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  The player character finds a smartphone, which, as it turns out, belongs to a missing girl named Anna. Upon booting it up, players see a message crying for help before a video pops up showing her terrified and begging no one to come looking for her. Of course, the player is going to completely disregard the message and dive right into the mystery, helped or hindered by other characters such as best friend Ashley, ex-boyfriend Greg, and Taylor, who she met on a dating app.
 </p>
 <p>
  Alongside messaging these characters, the player also needs to gain access to certain apps on Anna's phone, such as her email, Jabbr, Spark and Surfer, which are all online apps, of course. By looking through Anna's accounts, they gain new information needed to progress, coming one step closer to finding her.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="kinitopet">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   KinitoPET
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="this-virtual-assistant-is-not-all-what-it-seems">
  This Virtual Assistant is Not All What It Seems
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-1577936543" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-1577936543" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-1577936543" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-1577936543" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-1577936543-img" id="article-gallery-3-1577936543">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-1577936543" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2034262976">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms:
   </strong>
   PC
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   January 9th, 2024
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developers:
   </strong>
   troy_en
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genres:
   </strong>
   Horror
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  What if Microsoft's Clippy was a lot more sinister in nature? Well, this is a question rarely asked, but one
  <strong>
   <em>
    KinitoPET
   </em>
  </strong>
  answered nonetheless. An unassuming virtual desktop assistant that promises smart technology to talk and adapt to the users' actions, in order to give them some friendly and intelligent company while going about their business online.
 </p>
 <p>
  But, this is a horror game, and not everything is going to remain innocent and normal.
  <em>
   KinitoPET
  </em>
  soon devolves into a nightmare, with the pet wanting their experience to be everlasting, and maybe it won't remain shackled to the internet. What's more, it can even alter some computer settings to make players feel like they are the ones truly being stalked by KinitoPET.
 </p>
 <h2 id="her-story">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Her Story
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="view-her-story-through-short-clips-and-transcripts">
  View Her Story Through Short Clips and Transcripts
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1384798626" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1384798626" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1384798626" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1384798626" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1384798626-img" id="article-gallery-4-1384798626">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1384798626" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-355029295">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Missing person Simon turns up dead some time later, and it would seem he was murdered. Suspicions are immediately placed on Hannah, his wife, who confirms they did argue before he went missing. Her interviews are uploaded to the database as short clips for the player to watch through to determine the truth of her story.
 </p>
 <p>
  The player must navigate through the database to watch these clips and order them correctly using the software on the computer, while they can also plug in keywords or phrases to find more clips to gain more insight into Hannah's story. There are also transcripts so they can read back anything they watched, allowing players to step into the shoes of a detective. Careful attention must be placed while playing so they can know the truth.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="the-roottrees-are-dead">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   The Roottrees Are Dead
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="navigate-the-90s-web-to-piece-together-the-family-tree">
  Navigate the 90s Web to Piece Together the Family Tree
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1736883963" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1736883963" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1736883963" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1736883963" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1736883963-img" id="article-gallery-5-1736883963">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1736883963" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-105097325">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In the late 90s, a private plane crashed, and on it were a few members of an old and prestigious family the Roottrees's that had a net worth in the billions. Due to a will penned by the great-great-grandfather, the money must be evenly distributed to those that are a Roottree by birth, not through marriage. This is where the player comes in, who must cobble together a sprawling family tree to correctly identify the blood relatives of all Roottrees, to ensure the money goes to the right people.
 </p>
 <p>
  In order to succeed in their task, players will spend most of their time scouring the internet for clues, plugging in names and scraps of information into the search engine to learn more about all the family members. It is a tough task, as information is not spoon-fed to the player, and they will have to rely on what they know so far, and a little bit of thinking skills in order to succeed.
 </p>
 <h2 id="home-safety-hotline">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Home Safety Hotline
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="read-through-the-entries-to-identify-the-threat">
  Read Through the Entries to Identify the Threat
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-372105313" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-372105313" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-372105313" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-372105313" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-372105313-img" id="article-gallery-6-372105313">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-372105313" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-979260312">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  In a world where strange creatures and events occur to everyday people, the Home Safety Hotline was founded, an emergency line for those dealing with these bizarre occurrences. Those manning the line, specifically the player protagonist, must take calls and navigate through the online database to corroborate the information given with the entries in the database, and send the correct one over to the caller so they know exactly what to do.
 </p>
 <p>
  The internet functionality is limited in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Home Safety Hotline
   </strong>
  </em>
  , as outside of checking emails, players will be limited to the database. But every call will have them double-checking entries, even after they are an hour or so in and think they have most of it memorized. To make it more difficult, sometimes the database goes offline for maintenance, so players better hope they memorized enough to make it through.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="welcome-to-the-game-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Welcome to the Game 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="hunt-for-codes-on-the-deep-web">
  Hunt For Codes on the Deep Web
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1261415223" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1261415223" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1261415223" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1261415223" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1261415223-img" id="article-gallery-7-1261415223">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1261415223" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-131384390">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Platforms:
   </strong>
   PC
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Released:
   </strong>
   April 3rd, 2018
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Developers:
   </strong>
   Reflect Studios
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Genres:
   </strong>
   Horror
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  After watching a stream of a young girl begging to be saved, the main character takes it upon themselves to try and gain access to the Red Room to see if they can save her, given some pointers by the mysterious Adam who gives them the low-down on the deep web they will be exploring, along with the various dangers of doing so. After a brief tutorial, players are thrown into the deep end, and left to find Amalia themselves.
 </p>
 <p>
  Along with navigating various websites and hunting for URLs to other deep web pages and scraps of code needed to access the red room, players also need to contend with threats such as the police, Noir, Lucas, and the Breather, all who can catch the player unaware while completing their tasks. They must also combat hacks by winning minigames, as if they didn't have enough to worry about. One of the toughest horror games out there with some truly shocking and disgusting websites,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Welcome to the Game 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  is not for the faint of heart.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hypnospace-outlaw">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Hypnospace Outlaw
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="explore-and-monitor-the-early-age-internet">
  Explore and Monitor the Early Age Internet
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1073259895" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1073259895" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1073259895" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1073259895" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1073259895-img" id="article-gallery-8-1073259895">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1073259895" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1228232566">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  If anyone was on the internet in the late 90s and early 2000s,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hypnospace Outlaw
   </strong>
  </em>
  will be the ultimate nostalgia trip. As a moderator on hypnospace, an internet service people can access while sleeping thanks to the HypnOS headband, players must navigate through various web pages that include some MySpace-like pages, and report any bannable offenses they find. Players will receive emails including what particular violations they are on the lookout for, and will gain access to further zones the more they progress.
 </p>
 <p>
  As such, Hypnospace Outlaw has no other gameplay then tabbing through varying websites, yet still manages to create a phenomenal simulation puzzle game that is at times puzzling, funny, and even dark when Y2K hits, killing users who were in hypnospace at the time. Those looking for a solid web-surfing experience or feeling nostalgic for the internet of yore, they need to check out
  <em>
   Hypnospace Outlaw
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB The Show 25: How to Make Tons of Stubs</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/mlb-the-show-25-stubs-how-to-make-get-tons-free-easy/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Stubs are a virtual currency in
  <strong>
   <em>
    MLB The Show 25
   </em>
  </strong>
  that players can use to buy cards and to participate in Battle Royales and Showdowns. While it is possible to buy Stubs with real world money, there are absolutely opportunities to earn them through gameplay. This guide is here to detail some of the best of those opportunities, and it will help players start accumulating Stubs in
  <em>
   MLB The Show 25
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_1">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players can use Stubs to buy packs, though doing so is not generally recommended.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-make-stubs-in-mlb-the-show-25">
  How to Make Stubs in MLB The Show 25
 </h2>
 <h3 id="collections">
  Collections
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-137537100" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-137537100" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-137537100" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-137537100" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-137537100-img" id="article-gallery-1-137537100">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-137537100" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-751856232">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players will receive Stubs as they work through the various
  <strong>
   collections
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   MLB The Show 25
  </em>
  's Diamond Dynasty mode, and they should make a habit of occasionally taking these actions in order to claim those rewards:
 </p>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Navigate to "Collections" under the "Collect" tab.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select one of the collection categories, like "Starter Collections."
  </li>
  <li>
   Select one of the collections within the category, like "Collect Common Players."
  </li>
  <li>
   Select cards that have been obtained but not yet "collected." Those cards will be in color, but they will not have "Collected" written on top of them.
  </li>
  <li>
   Press the "Advance" input that is displayed at the bottom of the screen to "collect" the selected cards and progress along the collection's reward track, which may feature Stubs and is shown on the right side of the screen.
  </li>
  <li>
   Repeat Steps 2-5 for all the categories and collections.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_8">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players will also receive
     <strong>
      packs
     </strong>
     as they work through collections, which will, in turn, grant cards that can be used to make further collection progress. Alternatively,
     <em>
      MLB The Show
     </em>
     players can
     <strong>
      sell the cards
     </strong>
     that they pull from these packs through the in-game Marketplace for even more Stubs.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="diamond-quest">
  Diamond Quest
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1835310852" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1835310852" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1835310852" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1835310852" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1835310852-img" id="article-gallery-2-1835310852">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1835310852" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1246389104">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   Diamond Quest
  </strong>
  game mode is a great place to earn Stubs, as it allows players to repeatedly earn a selection of Diamond cards, which they can then repeatedly
  <strong>
   sell through the Marketplace
  </strong>
  . This guide to
  <em>
   MLB The Show 25
  </em>
  's Diamond Quest mode will help players pursue those Diamond card rewards, and they all have sell values of more than 4,400 Stubs at the time of writing.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Players will also earn
     <strong>
      packs
     </strong>
     as they complete Diamond quests. Once again, those packs will award cards that can be used to complete collections, and they can also be sold through the Marketplace for fast Stubs.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="conquest">
  Conquest
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2041576674" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2041576674" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2041576674" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2041576674" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2041576674-img" id="article-gallery-3-2041576674">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2041576674" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-69903141">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The Conquest game mode provides another good opportunity to earn Stubs, as many of the maps feature
  <strong>
   goals
  </strong>
  that award the currency when completed. Notably, many of these goals do not even require players to capture Strongholds, which means that they can, essentially, simulate their way to free Stubs.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_16">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     There are also packs to be earned by completing goals on many of the Conquest maps, and players should make sure to collect or sell the cards that they pull from them. There are many hidden Conquest rewards in
     <em>
      MLB The Show 25
     </em>
     as well, giving players even more opportunities to earn packs with contents that can be turned into Stubs.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="marketplace">
  Marketplace
 </h3>
 <p>
  While this has already been hinted at several times, it is worth emphasizing that players should absolutely be selling cards through the in-game Marketplace, as it is a great way to earn Stubs. At the very least, players should be selling their
  <strong>
   duplicates
  </strong>
  , and here is a quick overview of how to sell something through the Marketplace:
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1928639255" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1928639255" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1928639255" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1928639255" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1928639255-img" id="article-gallery-4-1928639255">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1928639255" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-2015079546">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Navigate to "My Inventory" under the "Collect" tab.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select the category from which you wish to sell something.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select the card you wish to sell, and click "View In Market."
  </li>
  <li>
   Select the entry that appears, and click "Buy/Sell Options."
  </li>
  <li>
   Click "Sell," and sell the card for the highest number of Stubs currently being offered for it (the highest entry on the right chart). Alternatively, create a Sell Order and assign a price to the card. It is recommended that the price be near the lowest number of Stubs currently being asked for the card (the highest entry on the left chart).
  </li>
 </ol>
 <h3 id="flipping-cards">
  Flipping Cards
 </h3>
 <p>
  Players can make a lot of Stubs in
  <em>
   MLB The Show
  </em>
  by flipping cards through the Marketplace, though doing so requires a good amount of monitoring and maintenance. Here is a simple flipping strategy that is often recommended, and players may want to try incorporating it into their Stubs-earning strategies:
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1802225063" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1802225063" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1802225063" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1802225063" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1802225063-img" id="article-gallery-5-1802225063">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1802225063" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-413026249">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Navigate to "Marketplace" under the "Shop" tab.
  </li>
  <li>
   Select either MLB Players or Equipment, as these are the types of cards that are currently considered best for flipping. If you selected MLB Players, set the Rarity filter to Gold.
  </li>
  <li>
   Look through the listings for cards where there is a big gap between the "Buy Now" and "Sell Now" prices. Players can find more details about what sort of gap is neccessary for a flip to be profitable below.
  </li>
  <li>
   Enter the listing's Buy/Sell Options, click on "Buy," and create a Buy Order. Set the price just above the highest number of Stubs currently being offered for the card (the highest entry on the right chart).
  </li>
  <li>
   Once the order is complete, return to the listing, click "Sell," and create a Sell Order. Set the price just below the lowest number of Stubs currently being asked for the card (the highest entry on the left chart).
  </li>
  <li>
   Wait for the item to sell, adjusting the price over time if necessary.
  </li>
 </ol>
 <p>
  To note, sellers are taxed 10% upon selling a card through the Marketplace, which means that the margins for flipping a card can be quite small. To determine if a card is a good target for a flip, players should take these actions:
 </p>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="mlb the show 25 make stubs" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg" decoding="async" height="2160" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/mlb-the-show-25-flip-comparison.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="3840"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ol>
  <li>
   Look at the left chart in the card's Buy/Sell options.
  </li>
  <li>
   Take the top number from this chart (the lowest price the card is currently being sold for), multiply it by 0.1, and subtract the product from the initial number. For example, if the card's lowest sell price is 1,000 Stubs, players would subtract 100 (10%) from 1,000 to get 900 Stubs. This means that if they sold the card for 1,000 Stubs, they would receive 900 Stubs.
  </li>
  <li>
   Look at the top number on the right chart (the highest price the card is currently being bought for). If this number is less than the number that was determined in Step 2, there is a potential profit to be made. To continue with the above example, if the highest buy price for the card is 880 (20 less than the 900 Stubs that would be earned by selling it for 1,000), then there is a potential profit of 20 Stubs per flip.
  </li>
 </ol>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Berserker: Khazan - Release Time and Date</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/the-first-berserker-khazan-release-time-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    The First Berserker: Khazan
   </em>
  </strong>
  follows Khazan, a fallen hero seeking vengeance in a brutal, war-torn world. The game features stunning 3D cel-shaded visuals, bringing its dark fantasy setting to life. Boss fights are intense and demand skill, requiring precise timing and strategy. Players must master combat mechanics to survive the game’s unforgiving challenges.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   The First Berserker: Khazan
  </em>
  is set to release on all major platforms, including
  <strong>
   Xbox
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   PlayStation
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   PC
  </strong>
  . However, some players will have the chance to jump in up to three days early before the official launch.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="the-first-berserker-khazan-global-release-times">
  The First Berserker: Khazan Global Release Times
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Release Times For The First Berserker Khazan" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/release-times-for-the-first-berserker-khazan.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The release date for
  <em>
   The First Berserker: Khazan
  </em>
  is March 27, 2025, as confirmed by a post on the game's official website. The game will launch simultaneously worldwide, meaning Xbox players cannot use the New Zealand trick to gain early access ahead of other platforms.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_6">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     You can check the chart below to see when
     <em>
      The First Berserker: Khazan
     </em>
     will be available in your country or region.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="table-container">
  <table align="" border="1" cellpadding="1" cellspacing="1" style="" summary="">
   <thead>
    <tr>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Time Zone
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Release Date
      </p>
     </th>
     <th scope="col">
      <p>
       Release Time
      </p>
     </th>
    </tr>
   </thead>
   <tbody>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       PDT (U.S.)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       8:00 a.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       CDT (U.S.)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       10:00 a.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       EDT (U.S.)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       11:00 a.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       BRT (Brazil)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       12:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       GMT (U.K.)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       CEST (Jordan)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       SAST (Africa)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       5:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       EEST (Greece)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       AST (Saudi Arabia)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       MSK (Russia)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       6:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       GST (Dubai)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       7:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       UTC +7 (Thailand)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       10:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       UTC +8 (China)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       11:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       SGT (Singapore)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 27, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       11:00 p.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       KST (Korea)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 28, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       12:00 a.m. (midnight)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       JST (Japan)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 28, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       12:00 a.m. (midnight)
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       AEST (Australia)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 28, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       1:00 a.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
     <td>
      <p>
       NZST (New Zealand)
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       March 28, 2025
      </p>
     </td>
     <td>
      <p>
       3:00 a.m.
      </p>
     </td>
    </tr>
   </tbody>
  </table>
 </div>
 <h2 id="how-to-play-the-first-berserker-khazan-early">
  How To Play The First Berserker: Khazan Early
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="How to Play The Firstt Berserker Khazan Early?" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2025/03/how-to-play-the-firstt-berserker-khazan-early.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Players wanting to play the game early can purchase the
  <strong>
   Digital Deluxe Edition
  </strong>
  , which comes with
  <strong>
   72-hour Early Access
  </strong>
  . This means that players in most regions can play the game on March 24th. The Deluxe Edition of
  <em>
   The First Berserker: Khazan
  </em>
  is priced at
  <strong>
   $69.99 USD
  </strong>
  on
  <strong>
   Steam
  </strong>
  ,
  <strong>
   PS5
  </strong>
  , and
  <strong>
   Xbox Series X/S
  </strong>
  . Purchasing this edition will not only get early access but also include the following:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Hero's Weapon Set
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Hero's Dual Wield
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Spear
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Greatsword
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Hero's Armor Set
   </strong>
   <ul>
    <li>
     Hero's Helm
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Wristguards
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Pauldrons
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Leggings
    </li>
    <li>
     Hero's Combat Boots
    </li>
    <p>
    </p>
   </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Digital Artbook
   </strong>
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
