<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>PS Plus March 2025 Player Count Takes a Big Hit</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/ps-plus-march-2025-free-games-player-count-down/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The free PS Plus games for March 2025 were not as popular as the January or February offerings.
     </li>
     <li>
      Data from True Trophies and Game Trends suggests a 15.2% drop compared to February.
     </li>
     <li>
      There was also a drop compared to the January free games.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  It seems as though not as many
  <strong>
   PlayStation Plus
  </strong>
  subscribers were as interested in the March 2025 free games as they were in the February 2025 lineup. PlayStation Plus subscribers, regardless of tier, are treated to a fresh batch of free games at the beginning of every month. The free games vary wildly in genre, budget, and popularity, which makes it difficult to predict what's going to be free from one month to the next.
 </p>
 <p>
  There have been three sets of free PS Plus games given away in 2025 so far. The free PS Plus games for January 2025 were
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Need for Speed: Hot Pursuit Remastered
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   The Stanley Parable: Ultra Deluxe
  </em>
  , while the February 2025 free games were
  <em>
   Payday 3
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   High on Life
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Pac-Man World: Re-Pac
  </em>
  . The March 2025 free games, which are still available for subscribers to claim for their digital libraries, are
  <em>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Sonic Colors: Ultimate
  </em>
  , and
  <em>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Cowabunga Collection
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  One would assume that the free PS Plus games for March 2025 would prove to be the most popular so far. After all,
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League
  </em>
  was a massive flop when it first released, as was
  <em>
   Payday 3
  </em>
  .
  <em>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </em>
  , while not a commercial success, did at least earn mostly positive reviews and is only a few months old. Not to mention,
  <em>
   Sonic Colors: Ultimate
  </em>
  is generally considered one of the best 3D
  <em>
   Sonic
  </em>
  games and
  <em>
   The Cowabunga Collection
  </em>
  includes a bunch of classic
  <em>
   TMNT
  </em>
  games for the nostalgia-minded gamer. Indeed, the March 2025 PS Plus free games lineup seems like the strongest this year so far, but it has apparently experienced a drop in player count compared to both the February and January offerings.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="free-ps-plus-games-for-march-2025">
  Free PS Plus Games for March 2025
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1291920233" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1291920233" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1291920233" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1291920233" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1291920233-img" id="article-gallery-1-1291920233">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1291920233" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-248722964">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   Dragon Age: The Veilguard
  </li>
  <li>
   Sonic Colors: Ultimate
  </li>
  <li>
   Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Cowabunga Collection
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  This was reported by True Trophies and Game Trends. According to their data, the free PS Plus games for March 2025 saw a 15.2% player count drop compared to the February games, and a 10.8% player count drop compared to the January 2025 free games. It seems the March 2025 free games being generally better-received titles did nothing for their player counts.
 </p>
 <p>
  It will be interesting to see if this downward trend continues with the April 2025 free games or if there's a rebound of sorts. We won't know what the free PS Plus games for April 2025 will be until next week, though we do know that PS Plus Extra is getting a day one game on April 10 in the form of
  <em>
   Blue Prince
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Finals - Season 6 Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/the-finals-season-6-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Season 6 of The Finals
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumor: Xenoblade Chronicles X Could Be Coming to the Switch 2</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/xenoblade-chronicles-x-nintendo-switch-2-rumor/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition has a hidden 60 FPS mode, but trying to enable it on the Switch leads to issues.
     </li>
     <li>
      Some now speculate that this setting may be reserved for use with the Nintendo Switch 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      More details about the Switch 2 will be revealed on April 2.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
   </em>
  </strong>
  has a hidden 60 FPS mode, discovered by a modder speculating that it might be a setting reserved for the Switch 2. There's a chance this 60 FPS mode was just an initial idea from Monolith Soft that got scrapped during the remastering process, but it may also be an indication that a version of
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  is being prepped for the Switch 2.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  is an expanded and remastered version of the
  <em>
   Xenoblade
  </em>
  title released for the Wii U in 2015. This enhanced version brings visual improvements and various quality-of-life changes to the interface and exploration, especially to compensate for the lack of the GamePad. It also makes some battle adjustments, such as removing BLADE and Field Levels. For veterans,
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  features new story content accessible in the post-game, expanding the lore even further with a new Skell pilot character and a new enemy faction.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  officially launched on March 20 for the Nintendo Switch, and rumors are already circulating that a version of the game is planned for the Switch 2. Modder masagratordev shared information on Twitter about the RPG's dynamic resolution range and the existence of a hidden 60 FPS mode. According to masagratordev, enabling this feature on the Switch causes weird issues in the game, such as gameplay being rendered every second frame at a 60 FPS output, but the player only gets 30 usable frames. The modder notes that no other
  <em>
   Xenoblade
  </em>
  title has this hidden setting.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="xenoblade-chronicles-x-hidden-settings-raises-speculation-about-a-switch-2-version">
  Xenoblade Chronicles X Hidden Settings Raises Speculation About a Switch 2 Version
 </h2>
 <p>
  The modder and other users speculate this could be the groundwork for
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  to launch on the Switch 2. Technically speaking, many professionals already consider the fact that a massive open-world game like
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X
  </em>
  ran on the Wii U to be a miracle, crediting this achievement to Monolith Soft's expertise. It's possible that, at first, the studio tried to make the Definitive Edition run at 60 FPS on the Switch but realized it was unlikely and abandoned the attempt halfway through. However, the fact that this setting remains in the game and wasn't outright removed leaves room for speculation about a potential Switch 2 patch that could run it at 60 FPS.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1521774876" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1521774876" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1521774876" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1521774876" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1521774876-img" id="article-gallery-1-1521774876">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1521774876" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-455919795">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Even though
  <em>
   Xenoblade Chronicles X: Definitive Edition
  </em>
  doesn't hit 60 FPS, the game is still a technological marvel. Given its vast expansiveness and the sheer freedom of an entirely connected planet, it was considered one of the best Wii U games ever released. On the Switch, the game's ambition and scope remain intact, now with high-resolution graphics, an enhanced soundtrack, and various contemporary quality-of-life improvements to please modern players.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardew Valley Fan Spots Game Reference In Unexpected Place</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/stardew-valley-reference-usa-today-crossword-puzzle/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley's presence expands beyond gaming with a reference in a USA Today crossword puzzle.
     </li>
     <li>
      The beloved indie title continues to gain recognition in unexpected ways outside of video games.
     </li>
     <li>
      Fans celebrate the inclusion of Stardew Valley in mainstream media like USA Today.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The beloved farming sim
  <strong>
   <em>
    Stardew Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  continues to expand its presence beyond gaming, as one player spotted a reference to the game in a USA Today crossword puzzle.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has recently offered a live concert series that has drawn in audiences outside the video game's fandom, and now the indie title is getting recognition in even more unexpected ways.
 </p>
 <p>
  Since it first launched in 2016,
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has become a pillar of the life-sim video game genre and cemented its legacy as one of the best indie titles of all time. Over the years, fans have spotted a number of exciting
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  references in real life, ranging from menu items at cafes to handcrafted collectibles at small shops, and a recent crossword clue about the game has fans celebrating.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fan hoshluml spotted a reference to the farming sim game in the March 19, 2025 edition of the USA Today crossword puzzle. The clue was given for section 40-Across and requires puzzle-solvers to know a four-letter word that describes "items that can be smelted in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  ." Players will quickly be able to answer with the correct solution of "ores," which can be purchased from the blacksmith
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="640746" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/stardew-valley-clint.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Clint
  </span>
  or gathered in the Mines in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . These ores are then combined with coal and placed into a
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="638579" style="color: #9242ff; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2024/05/stardew-valley-furnace.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Furnace
  </span>
  which then smelts the ores into metal bars. Mining and smelting play a major role in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , as metal bars are needed to upgrade the player's farmer character's tools, including the Axe, Hoe, Watering Can, and Pickaxe. For
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  fans, the crossword puzzle hint is very easy, but even non-gamers could use general knowledge of smithing to find the correct answer.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="stardew-valley-reference-in-usa-today-crossword-puzzle">
  Stardew Valley Reference in USA Today Crossword Puzzle
 </h2>
 <p>
  A representative from USA Today, Nikol, responded to the Reddit post, thanking hoshluml for enjoying the crossword puzzle. Fellow fans were incredibly happy to see an indie game like
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  getting recognition from a major media outlet, showcasing the title's impact beyond the video game community. One commentor noted that the March 19 USA Today crossword puzzle also included a hint that referenced the hit indie game
  <em>
   Balatro
  </em>
  , showing that many solo-developed titles like
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  can have a big impact outside their own player base.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1503940398" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1503940398" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1503940398" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1503940398" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1503940398-img" id="article-gallery-1-1503940398">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1503940398" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-787528327">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Indie games have been growing in popularity in recent years, and many have been delighted to see games like
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  getting their time in the spotlight beyond the realm of computers and consoles. As the farming title continues to develop its cultural presence, interested fans can stay tuned for more community shares and official updates for
  <strong>
   <em>
    Stardew Valley
   </em>
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomfall - Pre-Launch Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/atomfall-pre-launch-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Atomfall launches on March 27, 2025
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
