<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Smite 2 Free-to-Play Launch Date Announced Alongside New Character</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/smite-2-free-to-play-launch-date/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Smite 2's free-to-play open beta is scheduled to begin on January 14.
     </li>
     <li>
      Aladdin, the first God from the Tales of Arabia pantheon, will launch on the same date.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new update will add popular Gods from the original Smite, new game modes, quality-of-life improvements, and much more.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Smite 2
   </strong>
  </em>
  will kick off its free-to-play open beta on January 14, kicking off a new chapter for the third-person action MOBA. Entering its Alpha stage in early 2024,
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  is promising new modes, Gods, Aspects, and much more as it prepares to introduce even more players to the new generation of
  <em>
   Smite
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  A sequel to the 2014 free-to-play MOBA
  <em>
   Smite
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  was revealed almost a decade after its predecessor's release, promising an entirely revamped experience built using Unreal Engine 5. Like the original title,
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  invites players to take on the guise of various legendary figures and Gods based on real-world pantheons, from Greek mythology to traditional Japanese deities. By the end of August 2024, players could choose from 23 Gods, with that number promising to swell to 50 by the end of January 2025. Now, more information about what players can expect has been revealed, with more than a new character on the docket for this year.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  's developers have announced that the game will begin its free-to-play open beta on January 14, giving players a chance to see how the title truly differs from the original game. Along with this exciting news, Aladdin, the first God from the Tales of Arabia pantheon, will launch on the same date, further bolstering
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  's already impressive roster. Aladdin's Role is that of a Magical Assassin and Jungler who is able to run on walls and trap enemies in his lamp. Fans can also expect to see the return of Mulan, Geb, Ullr, and Agni from the original
  <em>
   Smite
  </em>
  , though the characters will see some changes to their skillsets.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="when-does-the-smite-2-f2p-open-beta-begin">
  When Does the Smite 2 F2P Open Beta Begin?
 </h2>
 <div class="display-card video large no-badge">
  <div class="w-adsninja-video-player">
   <div class="an-ignore">
    <div class="adsninja-video-player emaki-video-player emaki-video-player-5307dfa64d571158" id="emaki-video-player-5307dfa64d571158">
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <ul>
  <li>
   January 14, 2025
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  A new 3v3 game mode, Joust, has also been announced for the F2P open beta. Featuring an Arthurian-themed area, players will be able to traverse the map using Teleporters, with Stealth Grass making it possible to surprise enemies. The same map will be used for Duel, a new 1v1 mode. Additionally, the new Aspects feature will offer a new twist on gameplay, with players able to trade a certain facet of their God's build in exchange for a powerful boon. For example, with Aspects enabled, Athena can no longer teleport to an Allies side to shield them, but she can instead teleport to foes to weaken them. During the open beta period, 20 of
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  's 45 dynamic Gods
  <em>
  </em>
  will feature Aspects, with more being added in the future.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-97565611" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-97565611" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-97565611" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-97565611" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-97565611-img" id="article-gallery-1-97565611">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-97565611" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-161557432">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A number of quality-of-life features are also coming to
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  , including Role Guides, helpful messages to aid new players, PC text chat, item store improvements, death recaps, and much more. The first
  <em>
   Smite 2
  </em>
  esports tournament finale is scheduled to take place at the HyperX Arena in Las Vegas from January 17-19, further shining a light on this new MOBA experience. The title is available for PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series X/S.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Argument for Haunted Chocolatier to Take the Opposite Approach to Romance as Stardew Valley</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/haunted-chocolatier-romance-opposite-stardew-valley-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Haunted Chocolatier, like Stardew Valley, features romance mechanics but may benefit from taking an opposite approach.
     </li>
     <li>
      Stardew Valley's romance mechanics may feel predictable and repetitive in Haunted Chocolatier, potentially dulling the experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      Haunted Chocolatier's business-management premise allows for a unique approach to romance, making it an integral part of gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  While romance is not everything in ConcernedApe's
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , it's at least a significant contributor to the game's heart and soul, effectively encompassing a sizable portion of the "life" part of the farm life sim genre it calls home. Not only is it a great way to get to know many of
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's NPCs on a deeper level, it's an opportunity for players to have the comfort of someone waiting at home for them after a long day's work, and even someone who helps out around the farm. In light of that, it's good news that ConcernedApe's upcoming chocolate confectionery store sim,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Haunted Chocolatier
   </strong>
  </em>
  , includes romance in its gameplay as well.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's inclusion of romance mechanics is all well and good, but there remains an argument for the whole system to take the opposite approach to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's romance.
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  may look, sound, and feel a lot like
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , but its similarities don't need to cross over into its romance mechanics.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="why-haunted-chocolatier-39-s-romance-should-be-opposite-to-stardew-valley-39-s">
  Why Haunted Chocolatier's Romance Should Be Opposite to Stardew Valley's
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-289135992" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-289135992" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-289135992" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-289135992" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-289135992-img" id="article-gallery-1-289135992">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-289135992" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1135902858">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="stardew-valley-39-s-romance-mechanics-might-feel-too-predictable-in-haunted-chocolatier">
  Stardew Valley's Romance Mechanics Might Feel Too Predictable in Haunted Chocolatier
 </h3>
 <p>
  One of the main reasons
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  might want to move in the opposite direction to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  when it comes to its romances is that the mechanics might feel too familiar to those who have already spent plenty of time playing the farm life sim.
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  has now been out for nearly 9 years, which means players have had more than enough time to familiarize themselves with the ins and outs of its romance mechanics. As such, those same players who plan on migrating over to
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  once it launches may find its romance mechanics to be devoid of the challenge they once posed in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , should they be similar.
 </p>
 <p>
  Incorporating
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's romance mechanics into
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  might also feel too repetitive for some, thereby taking the joy of discovery out of the whole experience. Heading into
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  , players would then immediately know what they would need to do in order to effectively romance their favorite characters — speak to them regularly, find out what their favorite things are and gift them those things, and visit them as often as possible to ensure no Heart Events are missed.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_9">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Of course, players would initially still need to put in the work to discover what their favorite NPCs enjoy, but the mechanics, being too similar to
     <em>
      Stardew Valley
     </em>
     's, might nonetheless be too repetitive.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="haunted-chocolatier-39-s-premise-allows-for-an-unconventional-approach-to-romance">
  Haunted Chocolatier's Premise Allows for an Unconventional Approach to Romance
 </h3>
 <p>
  Another reason
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's romance might want to move away from
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's romance mechanics boils down to
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's business-management premise. Unlike
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , which revolves around players building a farm and simply living their life in Pelican Town,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  sees players managing a chocolate confectionery store. Presumably, this premise will be a bit more demanding of players than the farm they were tasked with developing in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , as running a successful business might be a taller order than managing a farm.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-pullquote">
  <div class="emaki-custom pullquote" id="custom_block_12">
   <div class="custom_block-content pullquote">
    <p>
     Another reason
     <em>
      Haunted Chocolatier
     </em>
     's romance might want to move away from
     <em>
      Stardew Valley
     </em>
     's romance mechanics boils down to
     <em>
      Haunted Chocolatier
     </em>
     's business-management premise.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  In light of that, players will need plenty of help running their shop, as they can't hope to do it by themselves. According to some of
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's screenshots, players will be able to hire ghosts to assist them in the everyday operations of their chocolate confectionery store, but this mechanic could be applied to the game's romances as well. Whereas
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  essentially encourages players to pursue a romance with any NPCs they find interesting,
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's romanceable NPCs could come with traits that directly benefit the player's store, should they court and even marry those NPCs.
 </p>
 <p>
  This would make
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's romance an integral part of its gameplay, rather than more of an optional activity, as it is in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  . Players would be far more encouraged to pursue romantic relationships with
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's NPCs, and that alone would set it apart from
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  's romance. However, regardless of whether
  <em>
   Haunted Chocolatier
  </em>
  's romance mechanics remain the same or move in the opposite direction to
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  , at least there will be another opportunity for players to personalize their experience and optimize their virtual lifestyle, just as they can in ConcernedApe's acclaimed farm life sim.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper Light Breaker Devs Detail the Story and Universe of the Franchise</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/hyper-light-breaker-story-universe-interview/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker's
   </em>
  </strong>
  Early Access release is nearly here, providing a sequel to indie darling
  <em>
   Hyper Light Drifter
  </em>
  after nearly a decade.
  <em>
   Hyper Light Breaker
  </em>
  will differ significantly from its predecessor, evolving not only aesthetic and gameplay aspects, but story and worldbuilding elements as well.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Despite the widely beloved status of
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  ,
  <em>
   Hyper Light Breaker
  </em>
  will pivot greatly from what's been established previously in the franchise. The game will be an open-world roguelike and will take advantage of a cel-shaded art style that brings
  <em>
   Risk of Rain 2
  </em>
  to mind. With these sweeping changes to the core experience, it follows that changes will come to how the game's world and story are built. To learn more about how
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  will evolve the series' narrative, Game Rant sat down with members of the Heart Machine team—including lead producer Michael Clark, narrative director Laura Michet, senior gameplay engineer Chris Forseth, and art director Danny Moll.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-hyper-light-breaker-will-build-on-the-world-of-drifter">
  How Hyper Light Breaker Will Build On The World Of Drifter
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1295066282" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1295066282" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1295066282" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1295066282" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1295066282-img" id="article-gallery-1-1295066282">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1295066282" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-288165902">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: How did you approach building upon the world/lore of
   <em>
    Hyper Light Drifter
   </em>
   for
   <em>
    Breaker
   </em>
   given that it’s not strictly a sequel/prequel?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  The
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  ’s experience takes place much later than
  <em>
   Hyper Light Breaker
  </em>
  —but they spend much of their time walking through the history of past events. We started with that shared history, expanding the world and the various warring factions and opportunistic groups that sought power.
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  is a new story with a lot to discover—I don’t want to spoil it—but over the course of early access, players will learn more about what happened here, how the world changes, when the Abyss King gained his power, and who the Abyss King and his Crowns were, are, and aspire to be.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Michet:
  </strong>
  When we created the story for
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  , we focused on the characters who are in
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  —the
  <em>
   Breakers
  </em>
  themselves, and the Crowns in particular. They have their own experience of the world and their own goals, fears, and relationships with one another. The story focuses on these things.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   will feature up to 3 player co-op. How does this play into the story versus the single-player experience?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Forseth:
  </strong>
  I don’t believe this is really any difference. It is the same game, same story, just with friends.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Michet:
  </strong>
  The story isn't affected by how many players are in your session. Each player makes their own progress through the story at their own pace.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Are there any particularly fun or favorite NPCs that you are excited for players to get to know?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  I think players are going to be very eager to learn everything they can about Pherus Bit.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Michet:
  </strong>
  I agree—Pherus Bit is my favorite character as well!
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q: Can you talk a little bit about the benefits of using comic book panels to communicate information? What does this add to the overall storytelling?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  Showing and not telling a story draws players into the narrative and asks that they pull the story from the imagery, rather than just reading text. It operates on a different level than text or speech, and plays very well into the worlds we create. We create deep, interesting worlds, and our players enjoy discovering them and discussing them.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Michet:
  </strong>
  In
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  , we wanted to try and lean on and extend the storytelling techniques from
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  in
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  . We think that there are some cool structural opportunities available in breaking up the story this way and in challenging the player to speculate and investigate as they start to put the story together from different perspectives.
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  also told its story with enigmatic images representing the perspectives of different characters, so that gave us an opportunity to try and use those techniques in new ways in
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-162087649" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-162087649" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-162087649" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-162087649" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-162087649-img" id="article-gallery-2-162087649">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-162087649" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1815840463">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    Drifter
   </em>
   had more isolationist, solitary themes, but
   <em>
    Breaker
   </em>
   is more co-op-focused. How do the themes shift and change between games, and how does that impact its storytelling?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Clark:
  </strong>
  I’m hesitant to delve too much into this because I want players to experience it in-game, but if
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  is more solitary,
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  is more social in its themes.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Michet:
  </strong>
  Players will discover this as they play
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Q:
   <em>
    Hyper Light Drifter
   </em>
   was so unafraid to be bold with its use of color. How does
   <em>
    Hyper Light Breaker
   </em>
   incorporate this—did you keep any of the same color palette choices from
   <em>
    Drifter
   </em>
   , or go with different color palettes to establish a different world?
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   Moll:
  </strong>
  A key part of
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  ’s color identity is its use of gradients and impressionistic color variation. The
  <em>
   Breaker
  </em>
  art team has worked hard to translate these kinds of treatments into 3D space to vivid effect. In most cases, we've targeted unique color palettes, but in some places (that
  <em>
   Drifter
  </em>
  fans will recognize) we've referenced things more directly. The sky color, just to name one.
 </p>
 <p>
  <strong>
   [END]
  </strong>
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Direct Date Announced</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/like-a-dragon-direct-date-2025/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  fans who are eager to learn more about
  <strong>
   <em>
    Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
   </em>
  </strong>
  before its February release can tune into a Like a Dragon Direct later this week. Unlike the recent mainline
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  RPGs,
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  will allow players to enjoy the fluid, real-time combat the original Kiryu saga was known for. This time, Goro Majima is in the driver's seat, as
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  follows his story in and around Hawaii after the events of last year's
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  isn't all developer Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio has going on, as the acclaimed studio showed up big time at last month's 2024 Game Awards with two massive reveals in
  <em>
   Virtua Fighter 6
  </em>
  and a new IP codenamed
  <em>
   Project Century
  </em>
  . It was a surprise to many to learn about RGG Studio taking the reins of Sega's long-dormant fighting game franchise, but it's
  <em>
   Project Century
  </em>
  that garnered even more attention. The
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  -like action brawler
  <em>
  </em>
  is set in 1915 Japan, and since its reveal, fans have been left wondering about its unconfirmed ties to the
  <em>
   Yakuza/Like a Dragon
  </em>
  universe, with some believing it could potentially chronicle the beginnings of the Omi Alliance.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the lead-up to
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  , which is set to release on February 21, RGG Studio has announced a Like a Dragon Direct focused on the game. Fans can tune in to the YouTube or Twitch livestream on Thursday, January 9 at 12 PM Eastern Time. RGG goes on to mention that fans can expect to see new gameplay features without needing to worry about too many narrative details being spoiled.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="rgg-studio-reveals-like-a-dragon-direct-date-amp-time">
  RGG Studio Reveals Like A Dragon Direct Date &amp; Time
 </h2>
 <ul>
  <li>
   January 9
  </li>
  <li>
   12 PM EST
  </li>
  <li>
   YouTube, Twitch
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  RGG Studio has already shown off plenty of
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  since its reveal last year. With many of the game's combat features and minigames having already been revealed, it'll be interesting to see what RGG has up its sleeve for the upcoming stream. RGG exclusively mentioned
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  in its announcement of the Like a Dragon Direct, but fans are speculating that they may get a tease of one of the studios' many other projects, like the all-but-confirmed
  <em>
   Yakuza 3 Kiwami
  </em>
  remake. Perhaps another look at
  <em>
   Project Century
  </em>
  is on the table, though considering the event's title, "Like a Dragon Direct," it likely won't be involved, especially since it's only been a month since its initial reveal.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-36990691" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-36990691" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-36990691" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-36990691" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-36990691-img" id="article-gallery-1-36990691">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-36990691" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1965497674">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  is setting sail on Xbox, PlayStation, and PC on February 21, and will surely be wacky enough to stand out among the other big February games like
  <em>
   Monster Hunter Wilds, Assassin's Creed Shadows
  </em>
  , Obsidian Entertainment's
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  , and others. What more RGG Studio has to show of the game is a mystery, but fans don't need to wait long to find out.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Bayonetta Origins Director Joins Sony's Housemarque</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/bayonetta-origins-director-returnal-housemarque-platinum-games/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The director of Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon has left PlatinumGames for a lead game designer role at Returnal developer Housemarque.
     </li>
     <li>
      PlatinumGames has seen the departures of some key developers recently, raising some worries about the studio's current direction.
     </li>
     <li>
      Housemarque has been working on a new IP since the launch of Returnal in 2021.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The director of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon
   </strong>
  </em>
  has exited PlatinumGames to join
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  developer Housemarque. This update comes amid a purportedly tumultuous time for PlatinumGames, and the departure of the lead creative behind
  <em>
   Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon
  </em>
  lends further credence to the uncertainty around the studio's current direction.
 </p>
 <p>
  Back in September 2023, PlatinumGames' most prominent developer, Hideki Kamiya, announced his departure from the Osaka-based studio. To explain his decision, the famed
  <em>
   Bayonetta
  </em>
  creator cited the dissonance between the direction PlatinumGames was heading in compared to his own inclinations as a game developer. One year later, Kamiya was surprisingly announced to be leading development on Capcom's
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  sequel at The Game Awards 2024, complete with a revived Clover Studio. However, this long-awaited reveal gave rise to concerns about the future of PlatinumGames.
 </p>
 <p>
  Shortly after the
  <em>
   Okami
  </em>
  sequel announcement, some of PlatinumGames' top developers were rumored to have left the studio as they'd wiped all mentions of it from their social media profiles. One of these developers was Abebe Tinari, the director of 2023's
  <em>
   Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon
  </em>
  , who revealed that he'd left Japan and moved to Helsinki, Finland. Tinari's LinkedIn profile has now spilled the beans on his decision to move to Helsinki, as the
  <strong>
   former PlatinumGames developer has taken up a lead game designer role at Housemarque
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="bayonetta-origins-director-now-working-on-housemarque-39-s-new-ip">
  Bayonetta Origins Director Now Working on Housemarque's New IP
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-205751383" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-205751383" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-205751383" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-205751383" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-205751383-img" id="article-gallery-1-205751383">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-205751383" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1763191330">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Housemarque's last release was its critically-acclaimed roguelike shooter
  <em>
   Returnal
  </em>
  in May 2021, following which the Helsinki-based studio was acquired by PlayStation. Ever since then, Housemarque has been chipping away on a new IP, and it seems all too likely that Tinari will be lending his talents to the same. It's yet to be determined when Housemarque plans to reveal its next game, but many fans don't expect an announcement until at least 2026.
 </p>
 <p>
  As for PlatinumGames, it's too soon to ascertain how much of an impact the recent high-profile developer exits will have on the studio's future projects. Recently, PlatinumGames announced a year-long celebration for
  <em>
   Bayonetta
  </em>
  's 15th anniversary, which might include the announcement of a new entry in the series as well. Other than a potential new
  <em>
   Bayonetta
  </em>
  game, PlatinumGames has also been working on a new IP dubbed
  <em>
   Project GG
  </em>
  since 2020. However,
  <em>
   Project GG
  </em>
  was being helmed by Hideki Kamiya, and now that he's no longer at PlatinumGames, there's no telling how much the game's development may have slowed down.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
