<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Rivals Reveals Gameplay of ‘King of Spartax’ Costume for Star-Lord</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/marvel-rivals-gameplay-king-of-spartax-new-costume-skin-star-lord/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The new King of Spartax skin for Star-Lord is scheduled to release on April 11.
     </li>
     <li>
      Emma Frost will also be receiving a new skin called X-Revolution with the launch of Season 2.
     </li>
     <li>
      During Season 2: Hellfire Gala, players will be able to earn the free Chaos Gown outfit for Scarlet Witch.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Marvel Rivals
   </em>
  </strong>
  has released new gameplay footage that gives players their first glimpse at gameplay of the upcoming King of Spartax costume for the Duelist Star-Lord. NetEase Games recently announced that Season 2 of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  will release on April 11, which will introduce Emma Frost as the hero shooter's newest Vanguard.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent developer update, NetEase Games revealed that it will be changing the way seasons work in the near future. Starting with Season 3, seasons will only last two months, but they will still include the same amount of content. This means players can expect to see new heroes added to
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  every month instead of every six weeks. The developers have claimed that this is all part of a strategy to keep the community engaged with the popular hero shooter. It will also give gamers the ability to play as more of their favorite Marvel heroes and villains without having to wait as long between updates.
 </p>
 <p>
  In a recent post on Twitter, NetEase Games showcased fresh gameplay of the upcoming King of Spartax skin for Star-Lord in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  , which is set to release on April 11 with the launch of Season 2: Hellfire Gala. In keeping with the theme of the upcoming season, the costume shows Star-Lord in a regal black and gold outfit with a blue sash and belt. The outfit features many small details, such as golden buttons and a matching pin of the Guardians' iconic crest.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="marvel-rivals-showcases-star-lord-rsquo-s-upcoming-lsquo-king-of-spartax-rsquo-costume">
  Marvel Rivals Showcases Star-Lord’s Upcoming ‘King of Spartax’ Costume
 </h2>
 <p>
  Star-Lord isn't the only hero receiving a new set of cosmetics, as
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  ' Emma Frost will also be getting a black and gold makeover when her X-Revolution skin releases in the shop on April 11. The somewhat revealing costume shows the hero with a longer haircut that features a large swoop in the front. Emma Frost can also be seen wearing a diamond ring in the shape of an "X," which matches a similar design on the back of her outfit. NetEase Games has not announced how much each skin will cost when they enter the shop.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-942708717" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-942708717" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-942708717" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-942708717" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-942708717-img" id="article-gallery-1-942708717">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-942708717" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-501144836">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Gamers interested in claiming free skins in
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  will have the opportunity to earn the new Chaos Gown costume for Scarlet Witch by playing nine matches during Season 2. Players who participate will also receive a nameplate featuring the popular Duelist. Leakers have also suggested that Namor could be receiving a new Will of Galacta skin as part of upcoming Twitch Drops associated with Season 2: Hellfire Gala. With a whole new season releasing on April 11 and even more content on the way, many fans are feeling optimistic about the future of
  <em>
   Marvel Rivals
  </em>
  .
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far Cry Primal Could Be the Right Blueprint for a Far Cry New Dawn Sequel</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/far-cry-new-dawn-sequel-potential-fc-primal-similar-good-why-how/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Far Cry New Dawn and Far Cry Primal offered different experiences in the franchise with unique settings and mechanics.
     </li>
     <li>
      A potential Far Cry New Dawn sequel could benefit from incorporating some of Primal's survival-based and beast-taming systems.
     </li>
     <li>
      A sequel that overhauls New Dawn's weapon tier system to mirror Primal's in a new iteration of its Survival Mode could work well for both story and gameplay.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Released in 2019,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Far Cry New Dawn
   </strong>
  </em>
  was a more divisive entry in Ubisoft's flagship FPS action franchise. After the generally well-received fifth numbered installment, it followed up with a spin-off that was also sort of a half-sequel. A strange situation to be sure, but
  <em>
   Far Cry New Dawn
  </em>
  signaled that the studio was still willing to try different things, even if they didn't always pan out. Prior to
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  , it had heavily experimented with 2016's
  <em>
   Far Cry Primal
  </em>
  , with the results more positively received.
 </p>
 <p>
  With the studio having been silent for a lengthy period about what might be coming next for
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  , rumors and leaks have stepped in to suggest some significant changes to the formula. Whether this turns out to be true remains a waiting game for now, but Ubisoft has surprised fans before, and it could do so again by revisiting
  <em>
   Far Cry New Dawn
  </em>
  's world and premise in a sequel while looking to
  <em>
   Primal
  </em>
  for some of the best ways to inform and improve upon how one might work.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_3">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Earlier this year, Ubisoft released an unexpected update for
     <em>
      Far Cry New Dawn
     </em>
     , adding in a 60 FPS patch.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="far-cry-primal-might-be-the-best-inspiration-for-a-potential-new-dawn-sequel">
  Far Cry Primal Might Be the Best Inspiration for a Potential New Dawn Sequel
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-270114710" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-270114710" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-270114710" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-270114710" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-270114710-img" id="article-gallery-1-270114710">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-270114710" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1280292534">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <h3 id="far-cry-primal-and-far-cry-new-dawn-39-s-visions">
  Far Cry Primal and Far Cry New Dawn's Visions
 </h3>
 <p>
  As the two entries set the farthest back in the past and future respectively,
  <em>
   Primal
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  are outliers in
  <em>
   Far Cry'
  </em>
  s output that offered players a different experience compared to most other entries. Both their settings were a bigger shakeup, with the former being set in the Stone Age instead of an exotic modern locale, and
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  taking place roughly a generation after the nuclear apocalypse at the conclusion of
  <em>
   FC5
  </em>
  . Though seemingly lying at opposite ends of the scale, they also mirror each other in notable ways and were similarly experimental with various mechanics. With
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  <em>
   Primal
  </em>
  often the better-received entry, it might thus serve as the best template for a
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  sequel.
 </p>
 <h3 id="how-a-far-cry-new-dawn-sequel-based-on-far-cry-primal-39-s-designs-could-work">
  How a Far Cry New Dawn Sequel Based on Far Cry Primal's Designs Could Work
 </h3>
 <p>
  <em>
   Far Cry
  </em>
  has long had crafting and upgrade systems, and
  <em>
   Far Cry Primal
  </em>
  's Survival Mode turned things up a notch by making some of these more costly and introducing more difficult parameters. Having another title set after The Collapse could see players managing resources and building more elaborate settlements from the ground up, much like
  <em>
   Far Cry Primal
  </em>
  's Wenja village. A
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  sequel that leans into these survival-based mechanics by having specialized NPCs for players to unlock that provide increasingly better bonuses to help survive in a harsher world would fit naturally within the framework.
 </p>
 <p>
  ​​​​​​​
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Far Cry Primal
  </em>
  's beast taming was another standout element, and could be tweaked to allow fans to do so again in a post-apocalyptic setting. Ubisoft also worked with experts to create an authentic-sounding fictional primitive language for
  <em>
   Primal,
  </em>
  an idea that could be revived in a second
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  , in a future where a new tongue may be developing. While this is perhaps more on the extreme end, it was nevertheless an interesting inclusion that would benefit from a new take.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of its least-liked features was
  <em>
   Far Cry New Dawn
  </em>
  's weapon tier system. This could be overhauled by altering it to work more closely like
  <em>
   Primal
  </em>
  's for a followup, allowing a greater range of playstyle preferences while keeping some of
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  's core intact. Combined with a modified version of
  <em>
   Primal
  </em>
  's Survival Mode, both could integrate well, playing into the setting and narrative while evolving the established formulas. Although there are currently no known plans for such a project,
  <em>
   Far Cry Primal
  </em>
  has numerous aspects that could serve as a good jumping-off point for a possible
  <em>
   New Dawn
  </em>
  sequel.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Games That Let You Grow A Garden</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-games-gardening-grow-garden-flowers/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Hokko Life offers a unique gameplay experience focused on crafting over similarities to Animal Crossing.
     </li>
     <li>
      Hello Kitty Island Adventure provides a cozy, relaxing atmosphere with gardening, baking, and bug collecting activities.
     </li>
     <li>
      Final Fantasy 14's casual gameplay contributes to making the MMO feel like home, with gardening as a rewarding and engaging activity.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Whether it's an open-world game, an RPG, or a life simulator, there is no doubt that having lots of side activities can add to the immersion and offer a much-needed change of pace. Some players might like the stealth and thrill of hunting, and others may prefer the less intense pastime of baking. While many of such activities reward players for their patience, few do more than gardening.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are plenty of games that allow players to cultivate their own life, be it flowers, vegetables, or some unknown alien flora. Usually, this also means that players get to reap the benefits of getting their hands dirty, harvesting their veg to eat, or picking flowers for decorations.
  <strong>
   These are some of the best games that let players grow a garden
  </strong>
  , perfect for green-thumbed adventurers.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_4">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     This list focuses on gardens, rather than farms. Games where gardening is the main premise/core gameplay have not been included (e.g.
     <em>
      Garden Life
     </em>
     ,
     <em>
      Viva Piñata
     </em>
     ).
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="hokko-life">
  <span class="item-num">
   10
  </span>
  <span>
   Hokko Life
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="not-just-an-animal-crossing-dupe">
  Not Just An Animal Crossing Dupe
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1041095091" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1041095091" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1041095091" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1041095091" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1041095091-img" id="article-gallery-1-1041095091">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1041095091" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-898180369">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Because of its visuals,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hokko Life
   </strong>
  </em>
  is often compared to
  <em>
   Animal Crossing
  </em>
  , but players willing to give it a try will find a distinct title with its own unique gameplay. While there are some similarities between the two as casual sims,
  <em>
   Hokko Life
  </em>
  focuses on crafting more-so than its counterpart.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once players have a shovel and some seeds, they can
  <strong>
   plant flowers pretty much anywhere
  </strong>
  and any time, as they thrive in every season. Planting flowers is done to improve the town, but there's nothing stopping the player from designing a garden outside their house.
 </p>
 <h2 id="hello-kitty-island-adventure">
  <span class="item-num">
   9
  </span>
  <span>
   Hello Kitty Island Adventure
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="explore-make-friends-and-complete-puzzles">
  Explore, Make Friends, And Complete Puzzles
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1950580418" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1950580418" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1950580418" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1950580418" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1950580418-img" id="article-gallery-2-1950580418">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1950580418" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1026234305">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Hello Kitty Island Adventure
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a life sim based on Sanrio's iconic anthropomorphic cast of characters. With lots of places to explore, players can travel and solve puzzles, making friends along the way. They can also jump into multiplayer and enjoy some co-op adventuring.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Hello Kitty Island Adventure
  </em>
  is a very cozy game, with a relaxing pastel aesthetic and plenty of chill activities to do. Players can bake, decorate, and collect bugs, as well as
  <strong>
   grow their own garden
  </strong>
  . The variety of flowers can even be bred to produce new colors and patterns.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-tip" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom tip" id="custom_block_17">
   <div class="custom_block-content tip">
    <p>
     Unlocking the greenhouse via the "Grand Garden Gathering" quest allows players to house region/event-specific plants.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-14">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 14
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-biggest-comebacks-in-mmo-history">
  One Of The Biggest Comebacks In MMO History
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-2015233288" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-2015233288" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-2015233288" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-2015233288" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-2015233288-img" id="article-gallery-3-2015233288">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-2015233288" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1952229785">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <strong>
   <em>
    Final Fantasy 14
   </em>
  </strong>
  had a big turnaround when the reboot
  <em>
   A Realm Reborn
  </em>
  was released, overhauling the initial disaster into an essentially new game.
  <em>
   FF14
  </em>
  isn't just an action-packed, monster-slaying MMO; there's also plenty of casual gameplay that helps make the server feel like home.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once players have acquired a property, they can get to
  <strong>
   work on their garden patch
  </strong>
  (purchased from Housing Merchants). Flower growth will depend on soil and fertilizer, and as in real-life, failing to tend to the patch will cause them to wither, but it's satisfying to see the hard work bloom.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-sims-4">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   The Sims 4
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="players-can-become-whoever-they-want-to-be">
  Players Can Become Whoever They Want To Be
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1039779898" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1039779898" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1039779898" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1039779898" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1039779898-img" id="article-gallery-4-1039779898">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1039779898" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-143457570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    The Sims 4
   </strong>
  </em>
  is over a decade old now, and admittedly, it's beginning to show its age — a concern given away when EA made the game free to play in 2022. That said, the game is still drawing in new and existing players with the amount of freedom it gives to pursue pretty much anything they want.
 </p>
 <p>
  Character creation and house-building are two of the main appeals of
  <em>
   The Sims 4,
  </em>
  <strong>
   gardening being one hobby
  </strong>
  that can be leveled while also making the home's exterior more aesthetic. Players have to water the plants, maybe even weed and bug spray them, but it pays off; veg can be eaten and flowers displayed.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_31">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     The
     <em>
      Cottage Living
     </em>
     expansion is great for gardening and farming enthusiasts.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="no-man-39-s-sky">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   No Man's Sky
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="plenty-of-strange-and-surprising-planets-to-explore">
  Plenty Of Strange And Surprising Planets To Explore
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-1452148724" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-1452148724" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-1452148724" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-1452148724" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-1452148724-img" id="article-gallery-5-1452148724">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-1452148724" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1565007308">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  While
  <em>
   <strong>
    No Man's Sky
   </strong>
  </em>
  was a relatively empty game when it was first released, there is no denying that it has since had a dramatic glow-up in terms of both content and gameplay. This space exploration-slash-survival game has something for fighters, explorers, and survivalists alike.
 </p>
 <p>
  If players choose to set up base on a planet, they can build with a degree of freedom (provided they have the resources). This includes
  <strong>
   the ability to create a garden
  </strong>
  . Cosmetic flora can be purchased from quicksilver merchants, while a wide variety of crops can be planted and harvested, even if it's merely for aesthetic purposes.
 </p>
 <h2 id="the-elder-scrolls-5-skyrim-special-edition">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   The Elder Scrolls 5: Skyrim (Special Edition)
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="embark-on-epic-quests-or-don-39-t">
  Embark On Epic Quests (Or Don't)
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-1088797158" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-1088797158" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-1088797158" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-1088797158" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-1088797158-img" id="article-gallery-6-1088797158">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-1088797158" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-657019416">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Part of why
  <strong>
   <em>
    Skyrim
   </em>
  </strong>
  remains a popular RPG is its combination of possible playthroughs and nostalgic (if clunky) mechanics. Whether players decide to pursue a career as the Dragonborn or settle down with a family on their own personal homestead,
  <em>
   Skyrim
  </em>
  has something for everyone.
 </p>
 <p>
  If players decide to build a house with the
  <em>
   Hearthfire
  </em>
  DLC (included in
  <em>
   Special Edition
  </em>
  ), they can
  <strong>
   add a garden onto their property
  </strong>
  to grow ingredients. Likewise, they can
  <strong>
   build a greenhouse
  </strong>
  that grows both food and ingredients; particularly useful for making valuable potions without needing to venture out for the components.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="subnautica">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Subnautica
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="an-underwater-survival-horror-full-of-dangers">
  An Underwater Survival Horror Full Of Dangers
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1669122722" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1669122722" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1669122722" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1669122722" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1669122722-img" id="article-gallery-7-1669122722">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1669122722" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-213007046">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Subnautica
   </strong>
  </em>
  is a staple underwater open-world game that blends story, survival, and horror almost seamlessly. Stranded on an alien planet, the player must figure out why they crashed and find a way to escape before the aquatic terrors get their way. Between the mysteries, though, there is plenty of scavenging and crafting to be done to make the ocean feel a little less hostile.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players can use
  <strong>
   interior or exterior grow beds
  </strong>
  to plant seeds (the required grow bed depending on the species). Some of the flora are weird and beautiful, making for some aesthetic additions to players' bases. As an added bonus, most can be harvested for food or crafting ingredients.
 </p>
 <h2 id="stardew-valley">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Stardew Valley
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="create-the-farmstead-of-dreams">
  Create The Farmstead Of Dreams
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-824768565" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-824768565" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-824768565" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-824768565" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-824768565-img" id="article-gallery-8-824768565">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-824768565" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-882982469">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Stardew Valley
   </strong>
  </em>
  is the epitome of farm life sims, loved for its cozy vibes with both chill and grindy gamers enjoying what it has to offer. The game
  <em>
   <strong>
   </strong>
  </em>
  is primarily known for its focus on farming, but that's not to say that players can't carve out a bit of time to focus on making their farmhouse a bit more homely.
 </p>
 <p>
  Flowers in
  <em>
   Stardew Valley
  </em>
  have a number of purposes; they can be used for crafting, cooking, as gifts, and to encourage bees to make honey. While they do have a seasonal life,
  <strong>
   keeping a flower garden is both an aesthetic and fruitful
  </strong>
  , adding a bit of extra color to players' land.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="minecraft">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Minecraft
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="build-and-survive-in-an-endless-sandbox-world">
  Build And Survive In An Endless Sandbox World
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-9-1180462489" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-9-1180462489" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-9-1180462489" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-9-1180462489" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-9-1180462489-img" id="article-gallery-9-1180462489">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-9-1180462489" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-9">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-9-slides-container-307722415">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Minecraft
   </strong>
  </em>
  is one of the best-selling video games of all time, and a franchise complete with books, spin-offs, and as of recently, a film. There's no confusion as to why it's still so popular, with its blocky sandbox worlds offering players the opportunity to build almost anything, from cottages to castles.
 </p>
 <p>
  There are a range of diverse biomes in
  <em>
   Minecraft,
  </em>
  each with their own flora and fauna to harvest. So long as there's a dirt block, players can simply
  <strong>
   place hand-picked flowers in their garden,
  </strong>
  <strong>
   or throw down bonemeal for random plant growth
  </strong>
  . They can also plant various seeds for a
  <strong>
   veg patch,
  </strong>
  providing the dirt is tilled and has a water supply.
 </p>
 <h2 id="animal-crossing-new-horizons">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Animal Crossing: New Horizons
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-cozy-social-sim-with-lots-of-freedom">
  A Cozy Social Sim With Lots Of Freedom
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-10-355109016" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-10-355109016" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-10-355109016" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-10-355109016" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-10-355109016-img" id="article-gallery-10-355109016">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-10-355109016" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-10">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-10-slides-container-1073490791">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Starting with a humble tent,
  <em>
   <strong>
    Animal Crossing: New Horizons
   </strong>
  </em>
  lets players establish themselves as part of the community on a desert island at whatever pace they like. Players are pretty much free to do as they please, be it upgrading their house, restoring the island, or collecting wildlife.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the many cozy activities in the game is
  <strong>
   creating a garden
  </strong>
  . Flowers can be dug up and
  <strong>
   re-planted or grown from seeds
  </strong>
  , and they can be crossbred to create new colors. Picked flowers can be used to decorate and craft with or wear, making it not just a cozy and pretty pastime but a useful one. One of the unique elements of the game is its real-time seasonal gameplay; flower seed availability at Nook's Cranny will depend on the month and hemisphere.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumo 2 - Official Announcement Teaser Trailer</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/video/lumo-2-official-announcement-teaser-trailer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  Lumo 2 is an isometric puzzle and platform game developed by Triple Eh? Ltd. See the official announcement teaser trailer here.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves Newest Guest Character Leaves Fans Frustrated</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves-salvatore-ganacci-fans-frustrated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points" data-nosnippet="">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      DJ Salvatore Ganacci joins Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves' roster, shocking fans and is considered a bizarre choice.
     </li>
     <li>
      Ganacci is known for frequenting Saudi Arabian music festivals, his viral performances at Tomorrowland, and his songs Take Me To America and Step-Grandma
      <em>
       .
      </em>
     </li>
     <li>
      Fatal Fury fans noted Ganacci’s inclusion as one of the worst, as several social media users didn’t even know who the DJ was.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The upcoming fighting game
  <strong>
   <em>
    Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves
   </em>
  </strong>
  has added a surprising character to the roster, and the announcement has left the fandom quite perplexed. Unlike its predecessor
  <em>
   Garou: Mark of the Wolves
  </em>
  , which featured a roster of brand-new characters,
  <em>
   City of the Wolves
  </em>
  will see the return of several characters from the
  <em>
   Fatal Fury
  </em>
  franchise and its sister series
  <em>
   Art of Fighting
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <p>
  Developed and published by SNK,
  <em>
   City of the Wolves
  </em>
  is the first entry in the franchise after a 26-year hiatus, with the last release being
  <em>
   Mark of the Wolves
  </em>
  in 1999.
  <em>
   Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves
  </em>
  ’ open beta previously ran back in February 2025, featuring eight characters within four stages for players to conquer, and the full release is planned for April 24, 2025, on PC, PlayStation, and Xbox Series consoles.
 </p>
 <p>
  Announced by SNK on social media, it was confirmed through a live-action trailer and gameplay showcase that the real-life and world-famous DJ, Salvatore Ganacci, would be joining the line-up. Ganacci is known for frequenting Saudi Arabian music festivals, confirmed to perform at this year’s 1001 Festival in Riyadh on the same day as
  <em>
   City of the Wolves
  </em>
  ’ launch, and became prominent in the music community for his viral performances at Tomorrowland and his songs
  <em>
   Take Me To America
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Step-Grandma
  </em>
  . The DJ’s addition has been regarded as a weird choice, so much so that Ganacci has managed to join the strangest guest characters in fighting games list.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves-welcomes-dj-salvatore-ganacci-to-the-roster">
  Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves Welcomes DJ Salvatore Ganacci to the Roster
 </h2>
 <p>
  <em>
   Fatal Fury
  </em>
  fans noted Ganacci’s inclusion as one of the worst, as several social media users didn’t even know who the DJ was, and some players even apologized for complaining about Terry Bogard’s confirmation prior. One Redditor went a step further to apologize for complaining about
  <em>
   Street Fighter 6
  </em>
  's guest characters and
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 16
  </em>
  ’s Clive Rosfield’s addition to
  <em>
   Tekken 8
  </em>
  , and asked for Ganacci’s addition to make sense. Unlike the DJ’s announcement,
  <em>
   Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves
  </em>
  ’ confirmation that popular soccer player Cristiano Ronaldo would be joining the roster was met with a much warmer reception.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-438702302" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-438702302" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-438702302" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-438702302" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-438702302-img" id="article-gallery-1-438702302">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-438702302" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-618418130">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Joining the fighting game’s previously confirmed roster, consisting of 17 fighters like Billy Kane, Rock Howard, and Chun-Li from
  <em>
   Street Fighter
  </em>
  , a
  <em>
   Fatal Fury: City of the Wolves
  </em>
  dataminer may have uncovered more base characters and some DLC additions. Kim Jae Hoon, Freeman, and Hokutomaru were among the names mentioned in the leak, alongside Abel “Grant” Cameron, Blue Mary, Rick Strowd, Alfred, Ryo Sakazaki, Duck King, and Wolfgang Krauser.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
