<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii Should Not Be Afraid to Use Majima’s Full Range</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii-majima-character-serious-funny/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  The launch of
  <em>
   <strong>
    Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
   </strong>
  </em>
  is almost here, and this upcoming title from Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio is getting attention for many reasons. Not only is the premise of the game quite unique, even by the standards of the wacky franchise of which it is a part, the project is also crucially centered around fan-favorite figure Goro Majima, who serves as the main protagonist.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  This focus on Majima in
  <em>
   Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  marks the first time the character has appeared as a main protagonist in the franchise since 2015's
  <em>
   Yakuza 0
  </em>
  , a game that is renowned for its captivating and layered narrative. While the wild premise of
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  is set to offer some hilarious moments, it is important that Majima is not relegated to simply providing comic relief, a role that he often takes. It seems that developer RGG may be reluctant to lean into the seriousness of Majima's character for
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza
  </em>
  , and that could lead to a missed opportunity for the title.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="majima-39-s-full-personality-can-still-shine-in-like-a-dragon-pirate-yakuza-in-hawaii">
  Majima's Full Personality Can Still Shine in Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1262203045" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1262203045" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1262203045" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1262203045" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1262203045-img" id="article-gallery-1-1262203045">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1262203045" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1455735312">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The story of
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  sees Goro Majima wash up on the shores of the tropical islands, confused by his situation due to a bout of amnesia. In classic
  <em>
   Like a Dragon
  </em>
  style, Majima quickly finds himself as the captain of his very own pirate ship, and with a tiger cub companion, which allows the title to offer ship combat, exploration, and customization.
 </p>
 <p>
  The land combat in
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza
  </em>
  goes back to the classic beat-em-up mechanics of prior
  <em>
   Yakuza
  </em>
  titles. There are some more-supernatural special abilities, though, which are a testament to the mind-bending moves that Majima has used over the years. This respect for Majima's history should extend across every aspect of his portrayal in
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza
  </em>
  , especially since the project could be the last time the character appears in such a prominent role.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_7">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     With Majima being 60 years old during the events of
     <em>
      Pirate Yakuza
     </em>
     , it is possible that RGG could phase the character out of playable roles going forward, making a great portrayal in the forthcoming game all the more important.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Some fans have shown concern about recent statements that have been made by RGG, with the studio's chief producer, Hiroyuki Sakamoto, suggesting that a "really rounded emotional story" cannot be made with Majima as the central focus. While Majima has always been well-suited to some of the more eccentric elements of the franchise's gameplay and story, the extremely-positive response to
  <em>
   Yakuza 0
  </em>
  was largely due to the spotlight that it shone on the raw and dramatic side of Majima's character.
 </p>
 <h3 id="a-heightened-sense-of-drama-and-comedy-could-make-pirate-yakuza-the-perfect-majima-game">
  A Heightened Sense of Drama and Comedy Could Make Pirate Yakuza the Perfect Majima Game
 </h3>
 <p>
  A lot of Majima's eccentricities are almost a way for him to escape from the suffering that he has experienced in the past, and
  <em>
   Yakuza 0
  </em>
  found a fantastic way to balance the conflicting aspects of his personality in order to create a dramatic and captivating story with a fitting level of comic relief. The amnesia that Majima is experiencing in
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza
  </em>
  could be an excellent vehicle for dramatic beats, and trailers for the game even portray a showdown between Majima and his sworn brother Saejima due to the confusion caused by the former's memory loss.
 </p>
 <p>
  A slow recollection of Majima's memories throughout the story of
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza
  </em>
  could be a fantastic way to give a level of grounded emotion to the game, and Majima could potentially revisit his past like Kiryu has in recent titles like
  <em>
   Infinite Wealth
  </em>
  . It does make sense for
  <em>
   Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
  </em>
  to lean further into the comedic and outlandish gameplay elements of the franchise, yet the game should not be afraid to utilize the full breadth of Majima's persona. Giving the story both dramatic flair and lighthearted moments would be the perfect way to do this.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Great Open-World Games With No Loading Screens</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-open-world-games-no-loading-screens/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Star Wars Outlaws blends seamless transitions without traditional load screens, enhancing the open-world experience.
     </li>
     <li>
      Elite Dangerous offers a jaw-dropping outer space adventure with minimal hidden load screens during hyperspace travel.
     </li>
     <li>
      Red Dead Redemption 2 impressively covers vast terrains with no traditional load screens, a masterpiece of open-world gaming.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  First, let's get this caveat out of the way: zero loading screens is pretty much impossible. Players will always encounter them when respawning, fast traveling, or just booting up the game. So naturally, some of the games on this list have brief loading screens. But outside of those instances, they offer a largely uninterrupted experience.
 </p>
 <p>
  Yes, hidden loading screens are a thing, but we won’t dwell on the most egregious examples. This is a list of open-world games players can seamlessly jump into and explore.
 </p>
 <p>
  But before we begin, let’s have a moment of silence for the open-world games that couldn't make the list:
  <em>
   Breath of the Wild, Tears of the Kingdom, Hogwarts Legacy, The Witcher 3,
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Kingdom Come: Deliverance 2
  </em>
  . While these games boast minimal loading screens, they still slip up whenever players enter shrines or travel back and forth between areas. Rules are rules!
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="star-wars-outlaws">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Star Wars Outlaws
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="hidden-load-screens-are-rare-but-forgiven">
  Hidden Load Screens Are Rare But Forgiven
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1068092649" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1068092649" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1068092649" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1068092649" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1068092649-img" id="article-gallery-1-1068092649">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1068092649" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1318205721">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Billed as the first-ever open-world
  <em>
   Star Wars
  </em>
  game (much to the dismay of
  <em>
   Galaxies
  </em>
  fans),
  <em>
   Star Wars Outlaws
  </em>
  is the very definition of a 7/10 game. It’s a fun ride that leaves neither lasting impressions nor regrets.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of its standout features, however, is its near-absence of load screens. Sure, there are hidden ones, but they’re so seamlessly integrated that it’s hard to complain. These sneaky transitions only serve to enable smooth planetary flying between the game’s open-world areas, a concession most spacefaring adventurers are happy to make.
 </p>
 <h2 id="elite-dangerous">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   Elite Dangerous
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="cross-the-milky-way-with-no-interruptions">
  Cross The Milky Way With No Interruptions
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-552749165" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-552749165" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-552749165" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-552749165" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-552749165-img" id="article-gallery-2-552749165">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-552749165" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-1582958128">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  When it comes to open worlds,
  <em>
   Elite Dangerous
  </em>
  takes the cake—and then some. It’s a 1:1 representation of the entire Milky Way galaxy. It’s truly a sight to behold. What makes it even more jaw-dropping is the absence of traditional load screens.
 </p>
 <p>
  Sure, there are hidden load screens during hyperspace travel, but they’re pulled off so seamlessly that players barely notice. Pilots watch the star they’re approaching, take in the cockpit details, or even sit back and twiddle their thumbs. Regardless of what players do, hyperspace travel remains a mesmerizing experience that never gets old.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="saints-row-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Saints Row 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-gta-clone-that-also-borrowed-its-approach-to-cut-scenes">
  A GTA Clone That Also Borrowed Its Approach To Cut Scenes
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-100072974" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-100072974" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-100072974" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-100072974" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-100072974-img" id="article-gallery-3-100072974">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-100072974" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-1147957327">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A surprising entry on this list is
  <em>
   Saints Row 2
  </em>
  . This off-color sequel shrugged off pace-killing load screens so seamlessly that most players didn't even notice their absence. But, as
  <em>
   Futurama
  </em>
  so wisely puts it: "When you do things right, people won't be sure you've done anything at all."
 </p>
 <p>
  Arguably the peak of the franchise,
  <em>
   Saints Row 2
  </em>
  fully embraced the ridiculousness that set it apart from
  <em>
   GTA
  </em>
  . It was about as crass as things could possibly get for a 2008 game — a year that cursed cinemas with the likes of
  <em>
   Meet the Spartans
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Harold &amp; Kumar Escape from Guantanamo Bay
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 id="cyberpunk-2077">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="not-a-loading-screen-in-sight-in-night-city">
  Not A Loading Screen in Sight in Night City
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1982975117" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1982975117" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1982975117" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1982975117" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1982975117-img" id="article-gallery-4-1982975117">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1982975117" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-611193617">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  After clawing back its tattered reputation following a rocky launch, CD Projekt Red managed to transform
  <em>
   Cyberpunk 2077
  </em>
  into a pretty damn respectable game. Once players were finally given a fully functioning experience, praise flowed in.
 </p>
 <p>
  One of the game’s biggest accolades is its stunning open world. With a mix of dusty deserts and sprawling sci-fi cityscapes, Night City offers seamless exploration without a load screen in sight. That’s a remarkable feat, especially considering the jaw-dropping visuals, meticulously detailed interiors, and streets teeming with NPCs.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-san-andreas">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="one-of-the-first-open-worlds-to-do-it">
  One of the First Open-Worlds To Do It
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-751717111" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-751717111" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-751717111" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-751717111" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-751717111-img" id="article-gallery-5-751717111">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-751717111" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-1136201190">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The granddaddy of no loading screens (aside from its iconic starting screens),
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas
  </em>
  is as iconic as it gets. Previous entries in the franchise featured splash screens when moving between regions, but
  <em>
   San Andreas
  </em>
  waved goodbye to that era.
 </p>
 <p>
  From CJ’s iconic BMX ride at the beginning to the game’s climactic finale, players rarely encounter loading screens. The game pulls some clever tricks to achieve this, dynamically loading environments as players traverse the sprawling map. The closest thing to a break is the brief fade to black when entering buildings — a small price to pay for seamless exploration.
 </p>
 <h2 id="grand-theft-auto-5">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Grand Theft Auto 5
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="explore-the-paradise-of-san-andreas-without-a-single-break">
  Explore the Paradise of San Andreas Without a Single Break
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-256266501" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-256266501" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-256266501" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-256266501" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-256266501-img" id="article-gallery-6-256266501">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-256266501" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-273451762">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Grand Theft Auto V
  </em>
  is still impressive well over a decade past its launch. For a game that originally graced the PS3 and Xbox 360, it’s dumbfounding how Rockstar managed to pull it off. But they did — and the result is a technical marvel worthy of praise.
 </p>
 <p>
  Zooming across San Andreas in a fighter jet or speeding through Los Santos in a supercar wouldn't hit the same if players were constantly greeted by static load screens filled with tips and character models. But for those masochistic enough to crave loading screens, there's always
  <em>
   GTA Online
  </em>
  .
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="red-dead-redemption-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-true-masterpiece-without-time-outs">
  A True Masterpiece Without Time-Outs
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-656446746" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-656446746" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-656446746" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-656446746" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-656446746-img" id="article-gallery-7-656446746">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-656446746" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-1991477589">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The scope of
  <em>
   Red Dead Redemption 2
  </em>
  is truly awe-inspiring. Spanning five fictitious U.S. states, traveling across its vast terrain reportedly takes around 3 hours and 14 minutes. And with that much ground to cover, players never encounter a single load screen.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is an astounding achievement for a game with such painstaking attention to detail. No wonder Rockstar poured over eight years into crafting this masterpiece. Sure, a few savvy players might point out one of the game’s rare loading screens, but we’ll ignore it to avoid spoilers—and because this title more than earns its place on the list.
 </p>
 <h2 id="marvel-rsquo-s-spider-man-2">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Marvel’s Spider-Man 2
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="swing-from-one-end-of-the-map-to-the-other-instantaneously">
  Swing From One End of the Map to the Other Instantaneously
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1120036560" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1120036560" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1120036560" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1120036560" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1120036560-img" id="article-gallery-8-1120036560">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1120036560" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1292232600">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Swinging into first place with a flawless open-world experience is
  <em>
   Marvel’s Spider-Man 2
  </em>
  . Even fast travel in this game doesn’t have loading screens—players simply select their destination and boom, they’re there. All thanks to the PS5’s impressive loading capabilities.
 </p>
 <p>
  Some players were skeptical, suggesting hidden loading screens were behind the seamless transitions. But Insomniac’s director of core technologies, Mike Fitzgerald, shut down the speculation with a mic-drop response: “That's a hold-to-confirm prompt, not hiding a load. If anyone wants to check, they can look at how late it's possible to cancel it out when they're playing.”
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2's Heresy Iron Banner is Going to Be Tinasha's Mastery All Over Again</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/destiny-2-heresy-iron-banner-warlords-spear-farming-rewards-bad-why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Heresy's release captivates players with an engaging story, seasonal weapons, and new activities.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new Iron Banner weapon, Warlord's Spear, will likely spark a farming frenzy with strong perks, but may face controversy.
     </li>
     <li>
      Farming Iron Banner for PvE weapons can be frustrating, and the same issues with Tinasha's Mastery in Revenant may surface.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  One could argue that despite all the issues that Episode 2 had leading into Heresy,
  <strong>
   <em>
    Destiny 2
   </em>
  </strong>
  's newest release managed to instantly captivate players with its story, seasonal weapons, the new secret Exotic quest, The Nether as its main activity, as well as the return of the Dreadnaught itself. This, combined with a complete overhaul of
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  's Trials of Osiris for PvP, is already making Heresy the best Episode so far, even in the face of some issues tied to the launch of the Sundered Doctrine Dungeon and voice acting. Even though the premise is great, there is a chance the upcoming Iron Banner will cause another controversy similar to the one in Revenant.
 </p>
 <p>
  Episode Revenant was one of the lowest points in the franchise's history, and that's because of many contributing factors that had varying impacts. Among them was the debacle of Iron Banner offering one of the best weapons in the game for PvE, but gating it behind a PvP activity, random rolls with no crafting, and a Glimmer issue. As such, even if Tinasha's Mastery was one of the best weapons in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  , with many players grinding for it, only a few Guardians got the god roll. This may all happen again next week when Iron Banner returns in Heresy.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="destiny-2-39-s-new-warlord-39-s-spear-trace-rifle-is-caught-between-a-rock-and-a-hard-place">
  Destiny 2's New Warlord's Spear Trace Rifle is Caught Between a Rock and a Hard Place
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-607410854" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-607410854" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-607410854" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-607410854" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-607410854-img" id="article-gallery-1-607410854">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-607410854" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-639530570">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Heresy will introduce a new Iron Banner weapon in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  , called Warlord's Spear. This is an Adaptive Frame Arc trace rifle that will have some incredibly strong PvE perk combinations, meaning it will once again spur players to farm Iron Banner to get the weapon. Still, no changes have been announced to the formula, meaning that players will still most likely have to get Warlord's Spear with random rolls, paying one Engram and 25,000 Glimmer for every focusing attempt. This made the farming process a slog, and without protection from duplicates or some kind of perk-focusing, it's entirely up to RNG to get a god roll.
 </p>
 <p>
  On top of that, Tinasha's Mastery was in the Reputation Track in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  last Episode, but it was not there all the time. As such, those who had already claimed that specific reward from Lord Saladin couldn't get that specific Tinasha's Mastery roll afterward, at least not in a guaranteed way. This upset many players who had been grinding for the gun when Iron Banner first came out, and the same thing may happen again in Heresy.
 </p>
 <h3 id="why-destiny-2-players-should-farm-iron-banner-in-heresy">
  Why Destiny 2 Players Should Farm Iron Banner in Heresy
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Tinasha's Mastery Destiny 2 Side (1)" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tinasha-s-mastery-destiny-2-side-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As it stands, there is a good chance that Warlord's Spear will be a meta weapon even in Heresy with no trace rifle mods so far, though more Artifact mods will be unlocked with Act 2 and Act 3. The reason is that this weapon will be able to roll with the new Detonator Beam perk, which is currently available on the new Strand trace rifle Unsworn from
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  's Sundered Doctrine Dungeon. Dungeon weapons are not easily available as god rolls, so Warlord's Spear may be easier to farm. It's also an Arc gun with a few perks that synergize with the Arc focus of Heresy, making it all the more worthwhile to get.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_11">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Heresy's Iron Banner will return to its original one-week schedule as opposed to two weeks in a row. The first Iron Banner week will run from February 18 to February 25, and the next will be on April 1.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <h3 id="farming-iron-banner-for-warlord-39-s-spear-is-history-repeating-itself">
  Farming Iron Banner For Warlord's Spear is History Repeating Itself
 </h3>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="Guardians wearing Iron Banner armor and standing in front of Lord Saladin" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg" decoding="async" height="900" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/destiny-2-iron-banner-season-of-the-seraph.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="1800"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Assuming the conditions for farming this new trace rifle in
  <em>
   Destiny 2
  </em>
  's Iron Banner remain the same, it's likely that Warlord's Spear will be as controversial as Tinasha's Mastery, which is bad press that Heresy doesn't need at the moment. It can be particularly difficult to balance the issue with Reputation Track rewards, as they change weekly, so it's likely that a good roll of Warlord's Spear will appear at some point. Players may be wise to not claim Reputation Track rewards unless they are about to reset Saladin's Rank, but this is not a long-term solution. Only time will tell if Bungie is making the right choice, but Warlord's Spear does seem enticing enough to warrant farming Iron Banner even for PvE players.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Trading Card Game Has New Batch of Promo Cards to Collect</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-trading-card-game-promo-cards-illustration-contest/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      The Pokemon TCG is gearing up to roll out its newest set of promo cards, featuring the winners of the 2024 Illustration Contest.
     </li>
     <li>
      The new batch of promo cards will feature fan-created artworks of Feraligatr, Pikachu, and Toxtricity ex at participating retailers and through the Pokemon Center webste.
     </li>
     <li>
      The Pokemon TCG has seen plenty of hype among collectors lately, with multiple highly sought-after sets like Surging Sparks and Prismatic Evolutions.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  The
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon Trading Card Game
   </em>
  </strong>
  has rolled out a brand-new promotional event with exclusive cards, celebrating the winners of last year's "Illustration Contest" for the TCG. The beloved trading card game based on the long-running monster-catching franchise has often featured special promo cards, with some fetching particularly high prices on the secondary market. Franchise mascot Pikachu has seen some particularly valuable promos, with cards like the "Mario Pikachu" and Pikachu's XY-era "Poncho" cards fetching thousands of dollars. Now, a new set of exclusive promo cards are on the way soon.
 </p>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  's annual "Illustration Contest" event has been a fan-favorite among Pokemon enthusiasts and collectors, rewarding the franchise's most talented fans. The contest features thousands of pieces of Pokemon artwork submitted by fans from around the world, with the chance for their art to be featured on a special promo
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  card. Last year's edition of the contest did see some major controversy surrounding some submissions, with several entrants being disqualified for using AI art. However, the winners have now been chosen and the newest Illustration Contest promos have been revealed.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="pokemon-tcg-reveals-illustration-contest-2024-promos">
  Pokemon TCG Reveals Illustration Contest 2024 Promos
 </h2>
 <p>
  As reported by ComicBook, The Pokemon Company has officially revealed the three promo cards for the 2024 Illustration Contest. The cards feature two classic Pokemon as well as one newer entry, with Feraligatr, Pikachu, and Toxtricity ex appearing as the newest batch of promo cards. The Pokemon Company also revealed how fans can get their hands on the new promo cards, available at participating local game stores, through the Pokemon Center website with a special promo code, and at Pokemon Day League celebration events. The promotional event is set to begin late next week on February 21.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-927552621" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-927552621" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-927552621" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-927552621" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-927552621-img" id="article-gallery-1-927552621">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-927552621" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-260560375">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  The
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  's newest promotional event comes as
  <em>
   Pokemon
  </em>
  collecting has hit a fever pitch throughout recent months. New sets like "Surging Sparks" and "Prismatic Evolutions" have seen massive hype from fans, with many retailers experiencing shortages of the hyped new sets. Prismatic Evolutions, in particular, has sent collectors into a frenzy with stunning Special Illustration Rare cards for all the Eeveelutions, with Umbreon fetching well over $1,500 USD. The excitement, combined with supply issues, even caused some retailers like GameStop to limit sales of Prismatic Evolutions.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  's recent hype was joined by the overwhelming success of the card game's newest mobile version.
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG Pocket
  </em>
  released in October of last year to massive early numbers, earning over $120 million within just weeks of its official launch. The mobile TCG also recently shipped a major update to the game, introducing its first new expansion set with the release of "Space-Time Smackdown."
  <em>
   Pokemon TCG
  </em>
  fans will soon have the chance to pick up some exciting new promos with Pokemon Day just around the corner.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avowed's Graphics and Performance Are Getting a Lot of Praise</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/avowed-graphics-performance-praise/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Avowed's graphics and performance in its early access release are receiving tons of praise for utilizing Unreal Engine 5.
     </li>
     <li>
      Digital Foundry praised Avowed's performance on Unreal Engine 5, calling it one of the best showcases of the modern engine.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Following
  <em>
   <strong>
    Avowed
   </strong>
  </em>
  's recent early access release for Premium Edition owners, the game's graphics and performance are coming in for tons of praise.
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  utilizes the power of Unreal Engine to bring the stunning world of Eora to life.
 </p>
 <p>
  Overall, the reviews for
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  <em>
  </em>
  have been pretty positive. Obsidian's latest RPG currently holds an 81 Top Critic Average on review score aggregator Open Critic, with frequent praise for its combat and commitment to player choice. However, some criticism has been aimed at its story and world, with some feeling the NPCs feel too robotic, as opposed to fully-fledged characters in the story. At the moment, the game remains in its early access period for Premium Edition owners only, so it remains to be seen if the general player reception reflects this, too.
 </p>
 <p>
  In Digital Foundry's tech review for
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  , the outlet reserved tons of praise for its performance on Unreal Engine 5. "Performance is thankfully solid across the 30fps and 40fps modes, with only occasional hiccups on both Series X and Series S... Even so, this is Obsidian's best-performing console game by far - not perfect, but good enough." It also claims it "leverages Unreal Engine 5's latest features, almost without fault," describing it as "one of the best showcases of a modern Unreal Engine 5 title." It seems that
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  's smaller scope, instead choosing to set the game in several small areas as opposed to one open world, has paid off.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="avowed-39-s-ue5-graphics-and-performance-praised-after-early-access-launch">
  Avowed's UE5 Graphics and Performance Praised After Early Access Launch
 </h2>
 <p>
  Unreal Engine 5 has come in for plenty of criticism from gamers. There are tons of major titles using Unreal Engine 5, some of which have had major technical flaws in the past. However, it's easy to succumb to confirmation bias here, noticing the UE5 games that struggle while ignoring the ones that run well.
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  is another example of why it's not entirely down to Unreal Engine 5, but rather the individuals using Epic's popular game engine.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-633407964" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-633407964" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-633407964" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-633407964" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-633407964-img" id="article-gallery-1-633407964">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-633407964" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1639717065">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Hopefully, the release of
  <em>
   Avowed
  </em>
  proves to be a success for Obsidian, as it's always exciting to see a developer take a chance on something fresh. Just recently, Obsidian confirmed it has ambitious objectives going forward, with the end goal to still be developing games 100 years from now. Obsidian is still one of the biggest names in the RPG genre, having developed
  <em>
   Star Wars Knights of the Old Republic 2: The Sith Lords
  </em>
  and
  <em>
   Fallout: New Vegas
  </em>
  . While it's perhaps unfair to constantly compare the studio to its previous works, it undoubtedly exists in the large shadow of what came before.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
