<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Arkham Games Might Never Be the Same If Rocksteady’s Batman Beyond Rumor is True</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/batman-arkham-batman-beyond-rumor-cape-glide-gadgets-detective-mode/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  More than rhythmic freeflow combat and cape-gliding traversal, the
  <em>
   Arkham
  </em>
  series of
  <strong>
   <em>
    Batman
   </em>
  </strong>
  games has always had an inspired suite of gadgets at its core. Besides
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Shadow
  </em>
  , every
  <em>
   Arkham
  </em>
  game has taken place over the course of a single night and thus necessitated the use of a tighter inventory or improvisational tools as Batman is faced with unique obstacles. Still, gadgets such as the Batclaw, Cryptographic Sequencer, Explosive Gel, and Batarangs are mainstays that Batman always has equipped in his utility belt by the end of each game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Appropriately so,
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Knight
  </em>
  pushed the envelope on gadgets to accommodate for how much more high-tech the series had suddenly become. This is apparent in
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Knight
  </em>
  ’s Battle Mode-ready Batmobile and V8.03 Batsuit alone, even only nine months after the events of
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham City
  </em>
  . It is unknown how much time may pass now between
  <em>
   Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League—
  </em>
  which is set five years after
  <em>
   Knight—
  </em>
  and Rocksteady’s reportedly upcoming Batman game. But, if rumors are true, it will be fascinating to see what arsenal of futuristic gadgets players may have at their disposal if Rocksteady is indeed developing an Arkhamverse-adapted
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  game.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="bruce-wayne-rsquo-s-trusty-gadgets-should-feel-outdated-in-a-batman-beyond-game">
  Bruce Wayne’s Trusty Gadgets Should Feel Outdated in a Batman Beyond Game
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1824484277" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1824484277" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1824484277" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1824484277" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1824484277-img" id="article-gallery-1-1824484277">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1824484277" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-362596467">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_5">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Batman’s gadgets are obviously advanced in terms of real-life modern-day standards and yet they’ve arguably never been wildly science-fiction-inspired or unfathomable beyond the technology in the cowl lenses that allow him to activate Detective Mode to view skeletons and see through structures, summarily analyze blood samples and chemical residue, or rewind and fast-forward an augmented-reality simulation of a crime scene via contextual environmental evidence.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <p>
  Otherwise, more or less everything Batman is somehow able to stash away and retrieve from his utility belt would likely need to be abandoned in a
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  retelling that would presumably take place decades into the Arkhamverse’s future. Batman’s Cryptographic Sequencer should be hilariously antiquated by the time Terry McGinnis dons a Batsuit, for example. To be fair,
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham Knight
  </em>
  does have some cutting-edge technology, including a Remote Hacking Device and a Voice Synthesizer. That said, if the Arkhamverse is going to define its next era in Neo-Gotham it’ll need an even larger overhaul.
 </p>
 <h3 id="what-a-batman-beyond-game-rsquo-s-gadgets-could-look-like">
  What a Batman Beyond Game’s Gadgets Could Look Like
 </h3>
 <p>
  Interestingly, Terry McGinnis’ Batman gadgets aren’t all that high-tech or unrealistic for 2039, and this gives Rocksteady an opportunity to stretch its imagination regarding what tools players gradually obtain throughout the course of the game. Batarangs and a Batclaw are sure to be reprised, but it would be riveting to see how Detective Mode may have evolved.
 </p>
 <p>
  Batman’s V8.03 Batsuit being designed with a titanium-dipped tri-weave so he can absorb impacts and take out multiple foes in quick succession means Terry’s Batsuit, as sleek and understated as the black-and-red, capeless bodysuit should be, will hopefully exhibit far greater capabilities. Jet thrusters in the
  <em>
   Batman Beyond
  </em>
  suit’s boots mean players would theoretically be capable of flight, for instance, and seemingly fundamentally change how players traverse if they won’t be relying solely on cape- or wingsuit-gliding and grapnel-boosting.
 </p>
 <p>
  This Batsuit does traditionally have underarm glider wings, though—as seen in
  <em>
   Batman: Arkham City
  </em>
  ’s astonishingly faithful and exceptional ‘Batman Beyond Batman’ skin—and could likely sustain the Arkhamverse’s most iconic traversal mechanic, but with jet thrusters there’d be no meaningful reason to grapnel-boost or create momentum with dive-bombs in the same capacity and thus gameplay would undeniably be a mere shade of what it used to be. Still, this new era, if legitimate, could be a treasure trove of nostalgia with Bruce Wayne’s old gadgets displayed in the Batcave for players to reminisce about.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Best JRPGs With Very Little Backtracking, Ranked</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/best-jrpgs-with-little-backtracking-ranked/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Final Fantasy 6 innovatively discards backtracking, focusing on unfolding a fresh narrative in a changed world.
     </li>
     <li>
      I Am Setsuna presents a linear JRPG experience, avoiding unnecessary backtracking, and maintaining a streamlined pace.
     </li>
     <li>
      Lost Odyssey prioritizes storytelling over exploration, restricting grinding, and preventing backtracking to maintain a linear adventure.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Players hate backtracking in the majority of video games they play, even if it may be a necessary evil to pad out the runtime. Even the most beautiful environments can become stale after a point if players cross these locations way too many times.
 </p>
 <p>
  This is especially true in JRPGs, where a bunch of sidequests and secrets involve a fair bit of exploration backtracking. This is why players will love the games in this genre that respect a player's time and don't make them explore the same areas over and over again until they lose their impact.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_4">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Games will be ranked based on how much backtracking (if any) is involved.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-6">
  <span class="item-num">
   8
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-fact-that-the-entire-world-changes-in-a-flash-shows-that-backtracking-isn-39-t-a-priority">
  The Fact That The Entire World Changes In A Flash Shows That Backtracking Isn't A Priority
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1601007916" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1601007916" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1601007916" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1601007916" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1601007916-img" id="article-gallery-1-1601007916">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1601007916" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-1027046857">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 6
  </em>
  is one of the greatest video games ever made that fans still can't get enough of. The game's intense pacing and some gutsy decisions have led to its universal appeal, ensuring that players don't have to backtrack at any point in the game unless they want to find a few secrets.
 </p>
 <p>
  The World of Balance is discarded after a point in a risky move as players embark on another adventure in a new, ruined world to help the heroes reunite and take out Kefka once and for all. Aside from helping Gau learn Rages or filling out the dances that Mog can learn, there's no reason to backtrack and visit older areas, which is something that
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  fans will appreciate.
 </p>
 <h2 id="i-am-setsuna">
  <span class="item-num">
   7
  </span>
  <span>
   I Am Setsuna
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-fairly-linear-jrpg-that-doesn-39-t-give-players-too-many-reasons-to-revisit-areas">
  A Fairly Linear JRPG That Doesn't Give Players Too Many Reasons To Revisit Areas
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-452421093" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-452421093" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-452421093" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-452421093" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-452421093-img" id="article-gallery-2-452421093">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-452421093" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-524046656">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  A beautiful and short JRPG that serves as an ode to
  <em>
   Chrono Trigger
  </em>
  , players will love
  <em>
   I am Setsuna
  </em>
  as long as they don't mind the game's obvious inspirations, with
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 10
  </em>
  being an easy mention here. The snow-covered world and melancholic story enhance the title's mature storytelling.
 </p>
 <p>
  Players will love ensuring Setsuna's safety every step of the way before eventually deciding to fight back against fate. Aside from fighting the game's superboss, there's no reason to backtrack and visit environments that players have already visited previously.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-13">
  <span class="item-num">
   6
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy 13
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-linearity-of-this-jrpg-is-infamous">
  The Linearity Of This JRPG Is Infamous
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-3-497867050" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-3-497867050" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-3-497867050" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-3-497867050" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-3-497867050-img" id="article-gallery-3-497867050">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-3-497867050" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-3">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-3-slides-container-2049947109">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  One of the most divisive JRPGs of all time, fans still can't make up their mind when it comes to
  <em>
   Final Fantasy 13
  </em>
  . While the game's visuals are off the charts, the experimental gameplay splits fans down the middle, and the game's focus on linearity can get under a player's skin.
 </p>
 <p>
  It's not until players reach Gran Pulse that the world opens up somewhat and players can explore. This is the only time when they'll need to backtrack in what is otherwise an oppressively linear experience.
 </p>
 <h2 id="lost-odyssey">
  <span class="item-num">
   5
  </span>
  <span>
   Lost Odyssey
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="the-game-focuses-on-telling-a-well-paced-story-instead-of-prioritizing-exploration">
  The Game Focuses On Telling A Well-Paced Story Instead Of Prioritizing Exploration
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-4-1524956242" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-4-1524956242" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-4-1524956242" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-4-1524956242" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-4-1524956242-img" id="article-gallery-4-1524956242">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-4-1524956242" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-4">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-4-slides-container-947281468">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Lost Odyssey
  </em>
  decided to place a major emphasis on telling a riveting, well-paced story that dealt with the idea of becoming immortal and outgrowing friends and lovers. This means that exploration took a backseat, letting players enjoy a linear adventure where backtracking went against the game's approach.
 </p>
 <p>
  In fact, the game actively prevents players from grinding by reducing any XP rewards after a point. Players must follow the intended path as quickly as possible to not bog down the pacing, making for a linear JRPG that many fans enjoy for its strengths.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="parasite-eve">
  <span class="item-num">
   4
  </span>
  <span>
   Parasite Eve
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="a-short-and-sweet-jrpg-with-excellent-pacing-and-little-to-no-backtracking">
  A Short And Sweet JRPG With Excellent Pacing And Little To No Backtracking
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-5-806190350" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-5-806190350" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-5-806190350" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-5-806190350" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-5-806190350-img" id="article-gallery-5-806190350">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-5-806190350" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-5">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-5-slides-container-90868105">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike the many JRPGs that released on the PS1 back in the day,
  <em>
   Parasite Eve
  </em>
  aimed for a short and riveting experience with barely any avenues for exploration. Players explore various areas in New York City as they hunt Eve down, with the climax arriving in no time.
 </p>
 <p>
  Even the Chrysler Building, an additional dungeon accessible in New Game+, doesn't encourage backtracking as players are focused on crossing every floor before reaching the game's superboss. This makes it clear why
  <em>
   Parasite Eve
  </em>
  is praised by the masses as an incredible and unique JRPG that more fans need to check out.
 </p>
 <h2 id="fire-emblem-three-houses">
  <span class="item-num">
   3
  </span>
  <span>
   Fire Emblem: Three Houses
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="strategy-jrpgs-usually-don-39-t-feature-backtracking-and-this-game-is-no-exception">
  Strategy JRPGs Usually Don't Feature Backtracking, And This Game Is No Exception
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-6-742672121" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-6-742672121" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-6-742672121" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-6-742672121" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-6-742672121-img" id="article-gallery-6-742672121">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-6-742672121" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-6">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-6-slides-container-22102293">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Unlike traditional Japanese role-playing games, strategy JRPGs follow a mission-based structure with little to no avenues for exploration. Every stage is a one-and-done affair that can't be accessed after the mission is completed.
 </p>
 <p>
  Most
  <em>
   Fire Emblem
  </em>
  games fit this bill, and
  <em>
   Three Houses
  </em>
  is no exception. It's one of the most accessible and beloved strategy JRPGs that takes players on a wild ride where they can enjoy an epic story that shows the series at its very best.
 </p>
 <div class="ad-even">
  <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 </div>
 <h2 id="triangle-strategy">
  <span class="item-num">
   2
  </span>
  <span>
   Triangle Strategy
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="there-39-s-little-to-no-exploration-involved-in-this-strategy-jrpg">
  There's Little To No Exploration Involved In This Strategy JRPG
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-7-1859296004" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-7-1859296004" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-7-1859296004" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-7-1859296004" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-7-1859296004-img" id="article-gallery-7-1859296004">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-7-1859296004" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-7">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-7-slides-container-317121933">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  <em>
   Triangle Strategy
  </em>
  is a surprisingly great tactical JRPG that shouldn't be judged by its trivial name. The game's beautiful HD-2D visuals are a joy to witness as players are whisked away on an epic adventure.
 </p>
 <p>
  Despite some cutscenes overstaying their welcome,
  <em>
   Triangle Strategy
  </em>
  's story is epic and exactly what fans want from a strategy JRPG. There's no backtracking involved in this game as players move from one mission to the next as the conflict between the three countries of the continent features many twists and turns.
 </p>
 <h2 id="final-fantasy-tactics">
  <span class="item-num">
   1
  </span>
  <span>
   Final Fantasy Tactics
  </span>
 </h2>
 <h3 id="arguably-the-best-final-fantasy-spinoff-of-all-time-with-a-mission-based-structure">
  Arguably The Best Final Fantasy Spinoff Of All Time With A Mission-Based Structure
 </h3>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-8-1994931648" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-8-1994931648" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-8-1994931648" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-8-1994931648" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-8-1994931648-img" id="article-gallery-8-1994931648">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-8-1994931648" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-8">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-8-slides-container-1954450385">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Many fans consider
  <em>
   Final Fantasy Tactics
  </em>
  to be the best spinoff title in this series, which is hefty praise given the quality of other spinoff
  <em>
   Final Fantasy
  </em>
  games. Most players were introduced to the world of Ivalice in this hard yet rewarding title where players controlled Ramza Beoulve and his allies in an adventure for the ages.
 </p>
 <p>
  The mission-based structure is prevalent here, although players are encouraged to grind from time to time if they want to make the most of the job system and surpass some of the game's biggest difficulty spikes. Still, this doesn't involve any backtracking, ensuring that players are taken on a ride that never lets up.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Wilds: How To Use Auto-Crafting</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/monster-hunter-mh-wilds-how-use-auto-crafting/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  There are a lot of items to find and craft in
  <em>
   <strong>
    Monster Hunter Wilds
   </strong>
  </em>
  and only a few inventory slots to manage. A lot of the materials you find can be crafted into something useful right then and there, but opening up the crafting menu in a hunt can be dangerous.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  Auto-crafting is a great tool for instantly picking up an item and crafting it into what you need it to be. Here's how auto-crafting works along with how to turn it on and off for individual items.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-turn-auto-crafting-on-amp-off-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  How To Turn Auto-Crafting On &amp; Off In Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-554146863" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-554146863" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-554146863" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-554146863" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-554146863-img" id="article-gallery-1-554146863">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-554146863" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-2106495164">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Auto-crafting is turned on and off for each individual item, so you can choose which ones you want to auto-craft in case one material is used in multiple recipes. If you want auto-crafting turned off across the board, you will need to go in and
  <strong>
   individually turn it off for every item
  </strong>
  . To control auto-crafting, open up the main menu and select the Crafting List. Here you'll see a list of all the things you can craft, and when hovering over an item press:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PlayStation
   </strong>
   - R3
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Xbox
   </strong>
   - Press Right Joystick
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    PC
   </strong>
   - Tab
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Pressing this button will toggle the bar to the right side of that item in the menu. When the
  <strong>
   circle is to the right side and the bar is green, auto-crafting is turned on
  </strong>
  for that item, and vice versa. Not every item can have auto-crafting turned on, but just about every consumable that heals you or restores a status ailment can be, and they are almost all worth having on at all times.
 </p>
 <h2 id="how-does-auto-crafting-work-in-monster-hunter-wilds">
  How Does Auto-Crafting Work In Monster Hunter Wilds
 </h2>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-2-1872885416" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-2-1872885416" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-2-1872885416" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-2-1872885416" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-2-1872885416-img" id="article-gallery-2-1872885416">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-2-1872885416" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-2">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-2-slides-container-348832216">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  As long as the item you want to craft has auto-crafting turned on, you'll automatically craft that item whenever you pick up the second item in the recipe. If you have
  <strong>
   both items already in your inventory, the system won't auto-craft anything
  </strong>
  that you already have. This means you'll only auto-craft
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3432286" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/03/mega_potion_item_healing_support_mhwilds_wiki_guide_85px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Mega Potion
  </span>
  whenever you pick up Honey, and not if you just have
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3432301" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/03/honey_item_ingredient_mhwilds_wiki_guide_85px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Honey
  </span>
  already in your inventory. When you auto-craft, a notification will appear along the right side of the screen letting you know what you crafted, the same as when skills activate.
 </p>
 <p>
  This means you'll still have to do a bit of manual crafting, but the main benefit to auto-crafting is the ability to immediately make consumables in combat, such as
  <span class="display-card-hyperlink" data-id="3432291" style="; ;">
   <img loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/sharedimages/2025/03/potion_item_healing_support_mhwilds_wiki_guide_85px.png?fit=contain&amp;h=22&amp;w=22"/>
   Potion
  </span>
  . You'll also need to make sure you
  <strong>
   have an inventory slot for the new item to go when auto-crafting
  </strong>
  . If you're at your pouch's capacity and pick something up that you can auto-craft with and not require a new inventory slot for, you'll still auto-craft what you can before getting the usual menu asking you to drop something.
 </p>
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-note">
  <div class="emaki-custom note" id="custom_block_13">
   <div class="custom_block-content note">
    <p>
     Example: If your pouch is full but you only have one Mega Potion and a few potions, picking up Honey will still auto-craft the Mega Potions since there is a slot for the resulting Mega Potions to go.
    </p>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the Most Likely Reason Pokemon GO Doesn't Let Players Evolve Kubfu Yet</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/pokemon-go-cant-evolve-kubfu-why-when-theory/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <section class="emaki-custom-block emaki-custom-key-points">
  <div class="emaki-custom key-points" id="custom_block_0">
   <h3 class="title icon i-list">
    Summary
   </h3>
   <div class="custom_block-content key-points">
    <ul>
     <li>
      Players speculate Urshifu may be introduced later in the current Pokemon GO season.
     </li>
     <li>
      Urshifu's potential inclusion in the game could follow a similar pattern to past Pokemon introductions in Pokemon GO events.
     </li>
     <li>
      Pokemon GO fans anticipate the release of Urshifu's different forms, as well as the upcoming addition of Nickit and Thievul in March events.
     </li>
    </ul>
   </div>
  </div>
 </section>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Pokemon GO
   </strong>
  </em>
  players have a theory about the absence of Kubfu's evolution in the game, speculating that Urshifu could be added later in the season.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  is expected to debut more Pokemon from Generation 8 in the coming months.
 </p>
 <p>
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  's newest season, called Might and Mastery, kicked off globally on March 5, and with it came the debut of the Gen 8 bear Pokemon Kubfu. Players can currently obtain Kubfu for free in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  by completing the season's permanent Special Research or through the limited Power Potential Event, which lasts until March 10. However, players who have already unlocked Kubfu in their Pokedex may have noticed that the creature cannot evolve into Urshifu.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  teased Urshifu in its latest Might and Mastery official trailers, so fans were certain that the Pokemon would be available sooner rather than later. The absence of Urshifu has disappointed players, but some fans have a theory of how the monster will eventually debut in the game.
 </p>
 <p>
  In the
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  Reddit community, user ZaxAlchemist shared their frustration over their Dynamax Kubfu not being able to evolve. It also cannot be transferred or traded. Under the post, fellow
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  fan beejalton suggested that Urshifu will likely be available later during the Might and Mastery season as part of a new research quest. Another player, Legitimate_Load_6841, theorized that Urshifu's debut could be similar to Naganadel's in 2024. Players might remember how the Ultra Beast Poipole was added at the start of
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  's 14th season World of Wonders in March 2024. Its evolution, though, wasn't introduced until late May 2024 through a special event. Since then, players have had the chance to evolve their Poipole into Naganadel in
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . In this way, it is possible that Urshifu's debut would follow the same formula, and players would have to wait until a later event centered around it.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="kubfu-39-s-evolution-might-be-available-in-pokemon-go-through-an-event">
  Kubfu's Evolution Might Be Available in Pokemon GO Through an Event
 </h2>
 <p>
  It is worth noting that Urshifu can have two forms, Single Strike Style and Rapid Strike Style, so many players may want to collect more than one Kubfu to have both variants. Moreover, Urshifu has both Dynamax and Gigantamax forms.
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  's latest trailers confirmed that Dynamax Urshifu is planned for the current season, so there's a chance that Urshifu Max Battles could launch in the future. It remains to be seen if Gigantamax Urshifu will also be added. On the other hand, developers have recently confirmed that Nickit and Thievul are coming to
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  . Both Gen 8 fox Pokemon will be featured during the Deep Depths event on March 19.
 </p>
 <div class="valnet-gallery">
  <div class="article__gallery type-gallery" data-article-gallery="article-gallery-modal-1-1948281597" data-gallery-id="main-carousel-1-1948281597" data-gallery-lightbox="gallery-modal-1-1948281597" data-gallery-thumbnail-id="gallery-thumbnails-1-1948281597" data-gallery-thumbnail-img-class="gallery-thumbnails-1-1948281597-img" id="article-gallery-1-1948281597">
  </div>
  <div class="gallery-lightbox" id="gallery-modal-1-1948281597" style="display: none">
   <button class="lightbox__exit-btn icon i-close">
    <span class="txt">
     Close
    </span>
   </button>
   <div class="lightbox">
    <div class="lightbox__swipper" id="swipper-1">
     <div class="swiper-wrapper" id="gallery-modal-1-slides-container-723657041">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-next icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
     <div class="swiper-button-prev icon i-arrow-1">
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  There are several
  <em>
   Pokemon GO
  </em>
  events launching in March 2025, including the upcoming Fuecoco Community Day on March 8.
  <strong>
   <em>
    Pokemon GO
   </em>
  </strong>
  's Might and Mastery season will end on June 3.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fisch: How to Get Rod of the Zenith</title>
      <link>https://gamerant.com/fisch-how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="content-block-regular">
 <p>
  In
  <strong>
   <em>
    Roblox's
   </em>
  </strong>
  <em>
   <strong>
    Fisch
   </strong>
   ,
  </em>
  all Mariana's Veil fishing rods are great for catching luck-based fish, whether it's Banana, Lovestorm Eel, or the trench exclusives. However, most of them fall short in resilience and control, and
  <strong>
   Rod of the Zenith
  </strong>
  is no exception.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <p>
  However, like all Mariana's Veil rods, this one comes with a special passive ability—one that convinces most Fischers to get it. If you're planning to reach the deepest parts of the trench, you'll eventually encounter this rod, but obtaining it isn't as simple as the Volcanic Rod or Challenger's Rod. This guide will show you
  <strong>
   how to get the Rod of the Zenith in
   <em>
    Fisch
   </em>
   ,
  </strong>
  its overall stats, and whether it's worth buying.
 </p>
 <!-- Not injecting Ads due to No-Ads mode. -->
 <h2 id="how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch">
  How To Get Rod Of The Zenith In Fisch
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get rod of the zenith in fisch" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-1.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  Rod of the Zenith can be found near the
  <strong>
   fishing pond of the Abyssal Zenith
  </strong>
  in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  . It's the third area of the Mariana's Veil trench, which unlocks after completing the Submarine Ice Upgrade at Challenger's Deep. Once your submarine is upgraded, hop into the ocean side of the trench and keep descending while navigating the obstacles. Finding Abyssal Zenith is one thing, but the real challenge begins at the entrance; you'll have to make your way through tunnels while dodging Anglerfish guards before finally reaching the main area. Fischers struggling to reach the Abyssal Zenith fishing area can check out this guide.
 </p>
 <p>
  Luckily, Abyssal Zenith doesn't have any temperature or warmth problems, so you can roam around without worrying about your character's survival, unlike in Volcanic Vents or Challenger's Deep. To get the Rod of the Zenith in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  ,
  <strong>
   head southeast
  </strong>
  from the Inn Keeper and buy it for
  <strong>
   10,000,000 in-game currency.
  </strong>
  It’s got a blue glow, making it easy to spot, but if you're having trouble, check behind the Back to Surface portal in Abyssal Zenith. Just a heads-up: You don’t need to complete any bestiary to obtain this rod, unlike the Ethereal Prism Rod, which makes you finish the Veil of the Forsaken Bestiary first.
 </p>
 <h2 id="rod-of-the-zenith-39-s-stats-in-fisch">
  Rod Of The Zenith's Stats In Fisch
 </h2>
 <div class="body-img landscape">
  <div class="responsive-img image-expandable img-article-item" data-img-caption='""' data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg" data-modal-container-id="single-image-modal-container" data-modal-id="single-image-modal">
   <figure>
    <picture>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 768px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=825&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 481px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=800&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <source data-srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2" media="(min-width: 0px)" srcset="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg?q=49&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=500&amp;dpr=2"/>
     <img alt="how to get rod of the zenith in fisch" data-img-url="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg" decoding="async" height="1100" loading="lazy" src="https://static0.gamerantimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/how-to-get-rod-of-the-zenith-in-fisch-2.jpg" style="display:block;height:auto;max-width:100%;" width="2200"/>
    </picture>
   </figure>
  </div>
 </div>
 <p>
  At the time of writing, the Rod of the Zenith is the second most expensive rod in
  <em>
   Fisch
  </em>
  , right behind the Ethereal Prism Rod. For the price you’re paying, it doesn’t offer anything too special. Its resilience and control are pretty low, so you’ll need to pair it with Controlled, Resilient, or Mythical to make it useful for catching valuable fish.
 </p>
 <p>
  Here’s what the Rod of the Zenith offers:
 </p>
 <ul>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Luck:
   </strong>
   145%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Lure Speed:
   </strong>
   85%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Resilience:
   </strong>
   15%
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Strength:
   </strong>
   Infinite Kg
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Control:
   </strong>
   0.15
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Passive Ability:
   </strong>
   Triggers a second fishing mini-game, and keeping the fishing line in the bar boosts your mutation chances from 0.1x to 10x on the hooked fish. However, it also lowers resilience.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p>
  Rod of the Zenith has a cool passive ability, but if you’re after valuable mutations instead of random ones, the Ethereal Prism Rod is a better grind. It gives a 50% chance of a Prismize mutation, which increases your fish’s price by 8x.
 </p>
</div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
