<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>PATAPON 1+2 REPLAY</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2383200/PATAPON_12_REPLAY/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 PATAPON 1+2 REPLAY
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   SAS CO.,LTD.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Bandai Namco Entertainment Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2383200/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 PATAPON is an action adventure where players use the rhythm of 4 Mystical Drums to command cute and mysterious eyeball-like creatures known as Patapons.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 All Patapons have unique characteristics and classes (jobs) such as the Hatapon who stands in the center of the squadron waving its flag and leading its allies, the Tatepon who protects others with its large shield, and the Yumipon who attacks by shooting arrows. The role of each Patapon during battle varies with their class, allowing you to create a unique and well-rounded army to take on the various challenges that await!
 <br/>
 As the player, you are the God of the Patapons and lead them on a grand adventure to Earthend!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   PATAPON and PATAPON 2 are now a packaged set!
  </strong>
 </h2>
 <div class="bb_img_ctn">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2383200/extras/①.PATAPON_GIFs_Steam_PACKAGE_SET.gif"/>
 </div>
 <br/>
 The two games, released in 2007 and 2008, are back as a remastered set!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   The game involves 2 elements: simple controls and strategic combat!
  </strong>
 </h2>
 <div class="bb_img_ctn">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2383200/extras/②.PATAPON_GIFs_Steam_CONTROL_STRATEGIC_COMBAT.gif"/>
 </div>
 <br>
  The controls are incredibly simple, comprised of the rhythmic beating of four drums [Pata(←), Pon(→), Don(↓), Chaka(↑)].
  <br>
   <br>
    At the same time, there are many strategic elements, such as using the right battle commands during the right situation, and creating an army comprised of the classes (jobs) of Patapons, creating a game that is easy to understand while still offering a challenge!
    <h2 class="bb_tag">
     <strong>
      A Game full of Challenges and Variety!
     </strong>
    </h2>
    <div class="bb_img_ctn">
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2383200/extras/③.PATAPON_GIFs_Steam_CHALLENGES_AND_VARIETY.gif"/>
    </div>
    <br>
     Patapons can be made or enhanced using various items. On top of that, even stronger Patapons can be created by gathering materials from stages and minigames. The game contains 400 weapons and equipment to enhance and upgrade your Patapons!
     <br/>
     Customize your army to your heart’s content and create a one-of-a-kind squadron to take on the various enemies and challenges this game has to offer!
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      <strong>
       New support features!
      </strong>
     </h2>
     <div class="bb_img_ctn">
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2383200/extras/④.PATAPON_GIFs_Steam_NEW_SUPPORT.gif"/>
     </div>
     <br/>
     While the original game elements remain unchanged, new support features have been added for a more enjoyable gaming experience!
     <br/>
     Newly implemented features found in this version allow players to adjust the standard difficulty between Easy, Normal, and Hard, adjust the timing of button presses, and keep the drum icon displayed at all times!
     <br/>
     Enjoy the original PATAPON, made better with all-new features!
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i3-3225 / AMD A6-7400K
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Intel Arc A580 / AMD Radeon R7 370 / GeForce GTX 750Ti
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        3 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Mouse control is not supported. Estimated performance: 1080p/60fps with graphics settings at "Low". Framerate might drop in graphics-intensive scenes. When playing with Steam Deck, please set the console's refresh rate to a fixed 60 FPS.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i5-7600K / AMD Ryzen 3 3100
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Intel Arc A750 /AMD Radeon RX 5700 XT / GeForce GTX 1660 Super
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        3 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Mouse control is not supported. Estimated performance: 1080p/60fps with graphics settings at "High". Framerate might drop in graphics-intensive scenes. Windows 10 (Version 1809 or later) and a 4GB VRAM GPU (graphics board or video card) are required for DirectX 12 API. When playing with Steam Deck, please set the console's refresh rate to a fixed 60 FPS.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISLANDERS: New Shores</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368930/ISLANDERS_New_Shores/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 ISLANDERS: New Shores
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   The Station
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Coatsink
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Thunderful Publishing
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2368930/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <div class="bb_img_ctn">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2368930/extras/IslandersNewShores_SteamGIFs_01.gif"/>
 </div>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 The next chapter in the beloved minimalist city-building franchise is here. ISLANDERS: New Shores invites you back to a world of tranquil creativity, now reimagined with expanded gameplay, stunning visuals, and a host of fresh features that build on the charm of the original.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Whether you're a longtime fan or a newcomer, prepare to explore, build, and strategise like never before.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Build Your Dream Cities Across 50 Unique Levels
  </strong>
 </h2>
 Explore over 44 building types across 6 diverse biomes, each available in 4 vibrant colour variations, letting you customise your strategy and create truly unique cities.
 <br>
  <br>
   Choose your mode of play;
   <strong>
    High Score Mode
   </strong>
   for those who love a competitive twist, or
   <strong>
    Sandbox Mode
   </strong>
   to let your creativity run wild.
   <br>
    <br>
     <div class="bb_img_ctn">
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2368930/extras/IslandersNewShores_SteamGIFs_02.gif"/>
     </div>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      <strong>
       Experience a World of New Features
      </strong>
     </h2>
     <strong>
      Photo Mode
     </strong>
     - Capture and share your stunning island creations with customisable filters and a turntable camera.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Expanded Soundtrack
     </strong>
     - Enjoy 75 minutes of original music that sets the perfect mood for your building adventures.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Dynamic Scoring Systems
     </strong>
     - Master innovative scoring methods - such as line of sight, distance bonuses, and inter-island strategies - to enhance your gameplay.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Boons
     </strong>
     - Unlock single-use power-ups that give you unique tactical advantages as you progress.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Twitch Integration
     </strong>
     - Streamers can now engage their audiences directly with interactive features built into the game.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <div class="bb_img_ctn">
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2368930/extras/IslandersNewShores_SteamGIFs_03.gif"/>
     </div>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      <strong>
       A Visual Overhaul That Elevates the Experience
      </strong>
     </h2>
     With a complete reimagining of the minimalist aesthetic, ISLANDERS: New Shores delivers a visual feast that complements its deep, strategic gameplay. Whether you’re here to relax or to challenge your building skills, every new shore offers a fresh canvas for creativity.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      <strong>
       Key Features
      </strong>
     </h2>
     - Two modes: High Score and Sandbox (with separate saves)
     <br/>
     - 44 unique building types and 7 island properties
     <br/>
     - 50 dynamic island generators offering endless variety
     <br/>
     - Photo Mode with filters and a turntable camera
     <br/>
     - 75 minutes of original, immersive music
     <br/>
     - Boons: new one-time power-ups for strategic gameplay
     <br/>
     - Advanced scoring systems that reward clever tactics
     <br/>
     - Twitch integration for an interactive streaming experience
     <br/>
     <br/>
     ISLANDERS: New Shores - where every island is a new adventure, and every build is a chance to create something extraordinary.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims™ 4 Enchanted by Nature Expansion Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3199780/The_Sims_4_Enchanted_by_Nature_Expansion_Pack/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 The Sims™ 4 Enchanted by Nature Expansion Pack
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Maxis
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Electronic Arts
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   The Sims™
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3199780/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 Live surrounded by the magic of nature in The Sims™ 4 Enchanted by Nature Expansion Pack*. Embrace a free-spirited lifestyle where you Forage and sleep under the stars, or bring nature’s gifts inside with versatile gardening pots. A charming world is waiting where you can craft Elixirs, cure Ailments, meet Mother Nature herself, and even become a Fairy!
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Purchase now to get the Fairy Garden bonus items, available through August 21, 2025**. Give your lot a fantastical touch! Make your yard feel like a magical forest with the Lofty Leaf Pond, give new meaning to “natural light” with the Luminous Mycena Lantern, and provide Fairies with their own secret spot with the Disguised Dwelling Fairy Home.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  KEY FEATURES:
 </strong>
 <br>
  <br>
   <ul class="bb_ul">
    <li>
     <strong>
      Life Among the Trees:
     </strong>
     — Step outside and make yourself at home in nature. With the Natural Living Skill, Sims can meet their needs outdoors without beds or plumbing! The natural world has a lot to offer, and Sims can Forage to uncover what’s hidden. Find everything from crystals to frogs to food! This way of life is perfect for Sims with the new Nature Nomad Aspiration. Sims can even bring the great outdoors inside with new pots for gardening on tables, counters, shelves, and more. The 3 new traits — Plant Lover, Mystical, and Disruptive — play a role in how Sims relate to their world.
     <br>
      <br/>
     </br>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Fairest Folk:
     </strong>
     — Do you feel nature’s mystical pull? Embark on a special journey and become a Fairy! Fairies can develop abilities that let them nurture plants, change the moods of others, and a whole lot more. The new Fairy Stories Aspiration will have you choosing between Harmonious and Discordant Fairy paths! Create Fairy Sims with wondrous wings and make them unique by painting! Plus, add whimsical accessories, glowing tattoos, and more. Non-Fairy Sims can also have magical fun by using Fairy Dust to enchant plants, bring Gnomes to life, and more.
     <br/>
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      A Balanced Lifestyle
     </strong>
     — Prolonged negative emotions cause imbalance, and imbalance can lead to Ailments with strange effects. They aren’t always bad (maybe you like lots of Gnomes at your house!), but if you want a Cure, you can turn to the new Apothecary Table and hone your Apothecary Skill. There’s a Cure for every one of the 8 Ailments, plus 14 more recipes with other fantastical effects. Sims who enjoy the Apothecary skill can become Naturopaths, a new 10-level career where you can cure Sims at home. They may also take on the Elixir Enthusiast Aspiration. Make sure to watch your Luck, which affects everything from cooking well to developing Ailments.
     <br/>
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      A Land of Enchantment
     </strong>
     — Innisgreen is a beautifully lush, green world where Sims live in harmony with nature. There are 3 neighborhoods: a quiet waterfront town called Coast of Adhmor where they’re all about Gnomes, Sprucederry Grove where nature and civilization blend together, and the magical forest of Everdew. From meeting Mother Nature and starting your journey towards fairydom to using the Glaswood Tree statue to summon Spruce Almighty, spectacular adventures are waiting!
    </li>
   </ul>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system OS: 64 Bit Required. Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        3.3 GHz Intel Core i3-3220 (2 cores, 4 threads), AMD Ryzen 3 1200 3.1 GHz (4 cores) or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        128 MB of Video RAM and support for Pixel Shader 3.0. Supported Video Cards: NVIDIA GeForce 6600 or better, ATI Radeon X1300 or better, Intel GMA X4500 or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        26 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system OS: 64 Bit Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel core i5 (4 cores), AMD Ryzen 5 or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        1 GB of Video RAM, NVIDIA GTX 650, AMD Radeon HD 7750, or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        51 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mycopunk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3247750/Mycopunk/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Mycopunk
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Early Access
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Pigeons at Play
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Devolver Digital
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Devolver Digital
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3247750/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 A ragtag squad of robot rejects is hired by the SAXON corporation and given one last shot at profitable glory (and avoiding the scrap heap). They are the New Atlas Hazard Crew, a ramshackle squad of exterminators sent to uncover the mysteries behind a planet-wide fungal catastrophe.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Embark on a series of dangerous planet-side missions to drive back the mycological menace. Could this be a simple natural disaster like they claim? And did SAXON really misfile your taxes? Or was that your own fault?
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <div class="bb_img_ctn">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3247750/extras/01_-_FUNGICIDAL_TENDENCIES.gif"/>
 </div>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  FUNGICIDAL TENDENCIES
 </h2>
 Choose from an outrageous arsenal of advanced futuristic weaponry (and some power tools), then supercharge them in a one-of-a-kind grid-based upgrade system to create the ridiculous sci-fi super-weapon of your dreams.
 <br>
  <br>
   <div class="bb_img_ctn">
    <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3247750/extras/02_-_BREAK_THE_MOLD.gif"/>
   </div>
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    BREAK THE MOLD
   </h2>
   Slaughter hordes of enemies as they corrupt and weaponize the planet's technology against you. Pick crawlies apart piece by piece — but be wary, whatever they drop could be grabbed up by another enemy.
   <br>
    <br>
     <div class="bb_img_ctn">
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3247750/extras/03_-_VISIBLE_RESULTS.gif"/>
     </div>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      VISIBLE RESULTS IN 1-2 MISSIONS
     </h2>
     Alone, these rickety robots aren’t up to much, but together they become more than the sum of their parts. Combine upgraded abilities and customised weapons to create synergistic builds and achieve strategic co-op mayhem. Or just shoot each other.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <div class="bb_img_ctn">
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3247750/extras/04_-_ROACH_MOTEL.gif"/>
     </div>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ROACH MOTEL
     </h2>
     Let off steam between missions in an orbital dropship packed with toys and games. Hang out with your friends, uncover more about the galaxy, and shoot the breeze with the insectoid SAXON veteran Roachard Cox.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 x64 Bit
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i3-610 / AMD FX-8350
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GeForce GTX 960 / Radeon R9 380 / Arc A380
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        10 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Low Quality setting, in 1080p, producing 30 FPS
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 11 x64 Bit
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i7-6700K / AMD Ryzen 5 1500X
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Geforce RTX 2080 / Radeon RX 5700 XT / Arc A750
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        10 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        High Quality setting, in 1080p, producing 60 FPS
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ground of Aces</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308690/Ground_of_Aces/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Ground of Aces
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Free To Play
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Early Access
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Blindflug Studios AG
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Blindflug Studios AG
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 10, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2308690/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Welcome to GROUND OF ACES
  </strong>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/landing_steam_optimized.gif"/>
  </div>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  It is the dawn of
  <strong>
   World War II
  </strong>
  , and you
  <strong>
   take command
  </strong>
  of a
  <strong>
   remote military air base
  </strong>
  .
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Prepare for missions, send out pilots and fend off attacks
  </strong>
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/nightattack_steam_optimized.gif"/>
  </div>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Engulf yourself in the Second World War and experience its battles from the perspective of your air base crew. It is your responsibility to make sure everybody is physically and mentally prepared to fulfil their duties.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Plan, build and shape your very own air base
  </strong>
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/buildup_blur.gif"/>
  </div>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Build up and manage a World War II air base. Your personal home for your planes and your crew members. Complete freedom of how you want to build. You will plan and place every wall.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Manage iconic World War II aircraft
  </strong>
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/lancaster_steam_optimized.gif"/>
  </div>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Enjoy a variety of accurate fighter airplanes. A joy for aviation aficionados who know the difference between a Hurricane and a Spitfire. But consider: bigger airplanes will need bigger infrastructure. So make sure you can house some of WW2's most impressive airplanes.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Take care of your pilots and crew
  </strong>
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/barbuildup_steam_optimized.gif"/>
  </div>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Experience personal stories of your air base crew members. On your base every person matters and has their own personality. The game takes huge inspiration of the everyday life of airplane bases in remote locations and how it felt to live there, in good and bad times.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   In the style of Franco-Belgian bande dessinée
  </strong>
  <div class="bb_img_ctn">
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308690/extras/steam_spitfire_optimized.gif"/>
  </div>
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The game is built from the ground to look like a living and breathing comic book, bringing the style of these timeless art pieces to life. From Bergèse to Hergé, the attention to detail and love for planes of the old masters is what we strive for.
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
