<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Victoria 3: Sphere of Influence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2411231/Victoria_3_Sphere_of_Influence/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Victoria 3: Sphere of Influence
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Paradox Development Studio
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Paradox Interactive
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Victoria
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2411231/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2411231/extras/En.png"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Put your diplomatic skill to the ultimate test in
 <i>
  <strong>
   Sphere of Influence
  </strong>
 </i>
 , a new expansion to
 <i>
  Victoria 3
 </i>
 . Pull other nations into your orbit through diplomatic skill, economic leverage or straightforward bribery. Building a durable international faction of like-minded governments, pursuing common goals for a common good and the glory of your power.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Paradox Interactive’s grand strategy simulation of the Victorian Age offers new ways to impose your will on the world. A coalition of reactionary powers can form blocs to work against the threat of liberal forces in other nations. Use your economic might to co-opt or coerce other regimes, spreading the banner of your ideology wherever your fleets might sail. Resist or embrace domestic pressure to change your traditional foreign policy, as economic and ideological agitators push you to build new coalitions of power.
 <br>
  <br>
   <i>
    Sphere of Influence
   </i>
   adds many new actions and systems to illustrate the quick moving nature of diplomatic relations in this dramatic era, including new content specifically about The Great Game - the decades long competition between the British and Russian Empires for pre-eminence in North India and Central Asia.
   <br>
    <br>
     Features of
     <i>
      <strong>
       Victoria 3: Sphere of Influence
      </strong>
     </i>
     includes:
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       <strong>
        Fierce Competition:
       </strong>
       Use your Prestige to become a Great Power and create your own Power Bloc! Dominate other nations in a diplomatic arrangement to pursue common economic or ideological goals, whether promoting open trade around the world or spreading specific values to other nations.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Power Bloc Customization:
       </strong>
       Choose the identity and principles of your loose alliance, whether it be a group promoting ideological concerns like the Comintern, or an economy-oriented bloc pushing for cross-border market integration like the Zollverein. You can even customize colors and emblems for your bloc!
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        “The Great Game”:
       </strong>
       New events, journal entries and decisions inspired by the Russian and British rivalry in Central Asia, and a new Objective - you can play as any of the powers central to that conflict, including Persia and Afghanistan. A newly redrawn map highlights the many competing interests in this frontier between empires.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Foreign Investment:
       </strong>
       Invest in the economic development of countries outside of your direct influence, making a profit from their financial success.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Nationalization:
       </strong>
       Start a Diplomatic Play to seize foreign assets in your country and prevent your wealth from going overseas.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Subject Interactions:
       </strong>
       Adjust the payments from your vassals and protectorates, meddle in their internal politics and more!
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Interest Group Lobbies:
       </strong>
       Domestic interest groups will pursue foreign policy objectives, promoting amicable relations with some countries and hostility with others nations or even influence the development of friendly lobbies in other nations.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        Power Bloc Monuments:
       </strong>
       Build majestic monuments to emphasise your bloc’s influence and domination over world events.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       <strong>
        New Historical Flavor:
       </strong>
       New historical characters and companies, most centered on the Great Game content, as well as more events, new journal entries, Lobby related content, new clothing and event art.
      </li>
     </ul>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626860/Dragon_Eclipse/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Dragon Eclipse
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Early Access
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Fardust
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Awaken Realms
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 24, 2024
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2626860/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Important information to consider before purchasing this game in early access:
  </strong>
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   The game is still in development. You might encounter various smaller or bigger bugs, balance issues, and a lack of final polish.
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   We’re open to any feedback. We believe that together, we can create the best deckbuilding experience possible!
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Your saved data may become corrupted or wiped with large patches and version changes.
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Gamepads may not work properly (which will be changed in the future), so a keyboard + mouse setup is strongly recommended.
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   The game is playable on Steam Deck, but as gamepad controls are not finished, you will have to use the trackpad frequently.
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Right now, only English is supported, but in the future, we’ll expand the list of available languages
  </li>
 </ul>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  <strong>
   Experience a new and unique twist on the deck-building roguelite genre!
  </strong>
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/2Experience-a-new-and-unique-twist-on-the-deck-building-roguelite-genre.gif"/>
 <br/>
 In Dragon Eclipse, you'll discover and collect magical Mystlings—creatures you can befriend and use in battle. Not only will you craft your deck of cards, but you'll also assemble a team of three Mystlings, each with unique stats, abilities, and dedicated cards. As you progress, your Mystlings will grow stronger and evolve! Utilize their abilities in deckbuilding to create breathtaking combos with every run. But beware—the Eclipse is coming!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  A fresh take on a beloved formula
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/2A-fresh-take-on-a-beloved-formula.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Combining team battler mechanics with deck-building strategy opens up endless fun and inventive combinations. After every run, you'll unlock new Mystlings, cards, and higher difficulty levels, keeping the game exciting for a long time. Experiment with different setups, create amazing combos, boost your stats, and engage each team member uniquely to achieve the impossible!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Choose a tamer
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/Choose-a-tamer.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Your choice of tamer determines your starting deck and pool of cards. Each tamer has a distinct playstyle and unique specialization, so choose wisely to face whatever destiny awaits!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Choose your Mystlings
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/Choose-your-Mystlings.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Every Mystling has unique stats, abilities, and a starting card for your deck. Strategically balance your team, make them your loyal companions, and together, fight against the encroaching evil.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Train and evolve your Mystlings
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/Train-and-evolve-your-Mystlings.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Mystlings level up and evolve during combat, gaining powerful new abilities. You’ll have to discover and harness their potential. They may look sweet, but in the hands of a skilled tamer, they can become deadly weapons able to dominate the battlefields!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Create your deck
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/Create-your-deck.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Throughout your journey, you'll construct a powerful deck full of great combos. Acquire new cards from various sources, engage in battles, complete side quests, and meet intriguing characters to ensure your deck is tailored to your combat needs and preferences.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Time is of the essence
 </h2>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2626860/extras/Time-is-of-the-essence.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Time is crucial in gameplay. The Eclipse is approaching, limiting the time you have to gather cards and resources. Make strategic decisions and choose your path wisely, as some valuables will have to be sacrificed for the greater good.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Ready to become the best tamer out there? Start your journey now!
 </h2>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_full">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS *:
        </strong>
        Windows 7/8/10 64-bit
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel® Core™ i5-4500K
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GTX 750 / Radeon HD 7770
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        4 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_note">
     <strong>
      *
     </strong>
     Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dice &amp; Fold</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693930/Dice__Fold/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Dice & Fold
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Tinymice Entertainment
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Rogue Duck Interactive
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Gamersky Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   RDI Strategy Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2693930/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <strong>
  Dice & Fold
 </strong>
 is a game that combines the strategic depth of turn-based dungeon crawlers with the thrill of chance inherent in dice games. Players unfold cards to face the creature cards and try to beat the card and fold it. Reminiscent of classic table-top RPGs and Solitaire, the game adds a simple layer of strategy.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch" rel="" target="_blank">
  <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/Olexa.png"/>
 </a>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  SOLITAIRE WITH A DICE?
 </h2>
 The core mechanic of the game revolves around dice rolling. Players engage in combat by rolling a dice, with the outcome directly influencing the strength of their attacks. The higher the roll, the more damage inflicted on the enemies.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/gif3.gif"/>
 <br>
  <br>
   You must strategize the best use of their dice rolls to maximize damage and control the battlefield, while also anticipating the counterattacks from monster cards at the end of each turn. The game offers a compelling risk-reward system, challenging players to balance aggressive tactics against the need for self-preservation.
   <br>
    <br>
     Adding to the complexity, the game features 20+ distinct classes, each with unique abilities and playstyles. This diversity allows for varied approaches to beating the dungeon, encouraging replayability and experimentation.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ROGUELIKE & DECKBUILDING
     </h2>
     With the generative dungeon system, reminiscent of the branching pathways in
     <strong>
      Slay the Spire.
     </strong>
     This element of choice ensures that each journey through the dungeons is a unique experience, filled with unexpected challenges and rewards. As the player you will choose the enemy and upgrade cards you want to keep in your next turn.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/gif.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Between stages, players have the opportunity to choose items, similar to the mechanics in
     <strong>
      Vampire Survivors.
     </strong>
     These upgrades range from enhancing dice rolls and bolstering class abilities to gaining new effects that can turn the tide in challenging encounters.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     If a player is defeated, the game doesn’t end in frustration. Instead, players are rewarded with meta upgrades and currencies that can be used to strengthen their character for subsequent runs. This progressive system ensures a continual sense of advancement and achievement, even in defeat.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/gif2.gif"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      CREATE CRAZY COMBOS
     </h2>
     With its blend of strategy, chance, and RPG elements,
     <strong>
      Dice & Fold
     </strong>
     offers an engaging and ever-evolving gameplay experience that appeals to both fans of dungeon crawlers and players who enjoy the unpredictability of dice-based games. Its unique combination of mechanics, and expansive upgrade system, offers a lot of replayability and fun!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Important Note:
     </strong>
     Dice & Fold will be doing a full release, but we will keep the content of the game updated with new items, new heroes and companions. Keep an eye on the new content updates.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/wishlist.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693930/Dice__Fold/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">
      https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693930/Dice__Fold/
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
      <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/join_discord.png"/>
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2693930/extras/ContentRoadmap.png"/>
     <br/>
     <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693930/Dice__Fold/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">
      https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693930/Dice__Fold/
     </a>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gladiator Guild Manager</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1043260/Gladiator_Guild_Manager/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Gladiator Guild Manager
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Entertainment Forge
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   GrabTheGames
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Gamera Games
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   UpgradePoint
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   GrabTheGames Publishing
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 22, 2024
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Oct 13, 2021
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1043260/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Hire your first gladiators and begin your adventure in this epic fantasy world.
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Map3.png"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Compete in Arena Championships
 </h2>
 Choose gladiators for each fight, position them, and instruct their behavior.
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/2vs2_instuctions_fight.png"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 The battle will play out on its own, showing you the results of your strategy. Keep a close watch on your enemy, understand their moves, and figure out how to best counter them.
 <br>
  <br>
   Your goal is to win all the arena championships.
   <br>
    <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Audience_Roaring.png"/>
    <h2 class="bb_tag">
     Grow Your Team
    </h2>
    As you progress, you’ll be able to build new types of buildings that will let you hire new types of gladiators, including warriors, rangers, beasts, mages, and more, allowing you to form unique teams.
    <br>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Shopping.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Gladiators have traits that determine their bonuses and additional abilities. You can find great deals in the market or teach and upgrade traits as you form the strategy for your team.
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Traits_Scroll_600p.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Unleash your creativity by growing your unique team. Level them up, upgrade traits, and equip them with powerful items, all while planning carefully how to build the most efficient team of gladiators that work well together.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Various Battles
     </h2>
     Between monthly championships, you should maximize your profit and growth to gain an edge in the next tournament.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Enter weekly Ring of Death arenas that offer different challenges.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Take advantage of changing weather conditions that affect gladiators to gain the upper hand on your opponents.
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Weather_and_Arenas.png"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Quests and World
     </h2>
     A variety of quest offers will come from different factions in need of your deadly gladiator services outside of the arena. Build or destroy reputations with them.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Help out the poor, support the district and the kingdom, or aid the progress of magic, depending on the main allegiance you choose.
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Necromancer_Quest.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Change the fate of this region and kingdom, or get involved in silly side plots.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Once you’re ready to put your gladiators' power to the ultimate test, accept challenging quests where your team will fight horrifying boss monsters.
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Spider_Boss_Fight.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Replayability
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Each time you play, you can choose a different main allegiance, resulting in different main quests and endings while you try different team strategies.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Tournament Mode
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Once you finish the main campaign, try yourself in endless tournament mode where gameplay is simplified into rounds. Enemies get stronger and stronger, and you play until you lose. Leave your score on the Steam leaderboard to compare with other players or friends.
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/Tournament_Fight.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Community
     </strong>
     <br/>
     We’d love to have you in our
     <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
      Discord
     </a>
     community and hear your feedback and experience with the game.
     <br/>
     <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
      <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1043260/extras/DiscordPROMO.png"/>
     </a>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   Game contains a lot of cartoony gore and violence during the automatic gladiator battles.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_full">
        <ul>
         <strong>
          Minimum:
         </strong>
         <br/>
         <ul class="bb_ul">
          <li>
           <strong>
            OS:
           </strong>
           10.7.0 or later
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Processor:
           </strong>
           4.0GHz
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Memory:
           </strong>
           6 GB RAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Graphics:
           </strong>
           256mb Video Memory, capable of Shader Model 2.0+
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Storage:
           </strong>
           2 MB available space
          </li>
         </ul>
        </ul>
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Go! My Harem Farm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659960/Lets_Go_My_Harem_Farm/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Let's Go! My Harem Farm
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   XO_PROJECT
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   OTAKU Plan
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 21, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2659960/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
  <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2659960/extras/social_banner_discord.png"/>
 </a>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2659960/extras/22.png"/>
 <br/>
 You are a young man living in the city. Every day, you were busy with work, leading a hectic life.
 <br/>
 Tired of such a lifestyle, you began to yearn for a slow life in a place rich in nature. At that time, you heard that a ranch in a certain rural village was being sold cheaply, so you decided to buy the ranch to start a second life.
 <br/>
 However, the village chief you met seems to have a favor to ask of you...?
 <br>
  <br>
   "Could you possibly have children with the young women in the village?"
   <br>
    <br>
     This game is a farm life simulation game.
     <br/>
     Players will control this young man, growing vegetables, raising livestock, and after work, go out to the village to get along with the women.
     <br/>
     As you get closer, events that deepen the relationship occur, and eventually, they may wish to have your children.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2659960/extras/33.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       Slow Life
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Farm Life Simulation
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       16 Romanceable Characters
      </li>
     </ul>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   Some scenes in the game will appear bare and sexually suggestive content that is not suitable for minors, Pleasedecide whether to play or not.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        7 / 8 / 8.1 / 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        3+ GHz Processor
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        DirectX 11/OpenGL 4.1 capable GPU
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        1 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        3+ GHz Processor
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        OpenGL ES 2.0 hardware driver support required for WebGL acceleration. (AMD Catalyst 10.9, nVidia 358.50)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        2 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
