<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader Kings III: Roads to Power</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671070/Crusader_Kings_III_Roads_to_Power/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Crusader Kings III: Roads to Power
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Paradox Development Studio
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Paradox Interactive
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Crusader Kings
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2671070/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 The glory and might of the Byzantine Empire are yours to command in this Major Expansion to
 <i>
  Crusader Kings III
 </i>
 . The unique politics and cultures of the heir to the Roman Empire are on display through a new governing system, new ways for characters to progress up the societal ladder, and new activities for them to engage in. You can also explore a new exciting lifestyle as a landless Adventurer, seeking fame and glory across a living map of the medieval world.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2671070/extras/steam_byz_zoomout_01.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <strong>
    Administrative Government:
   </strong>
   Experience medieval rule outside of the feudal system with a new style of empire management. A web of Governors jockeys for position in the empire with intrigue and power, sometimes rewarding merit and sometimes rewarding perfidy. Only a truly skilled Emperor can keep these squabbling forces in line.
   <br>
    <br/>
   </br>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    The Family Estate:
   </strong>
   Run and manage a powerful Family Estate, the seat of your House’s power, even when you hold no other land. Construct new buildings and improvements to further your power and influence within an administrative empire.
   <br>
    <br/>
   </br>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Influence System:
   </strong>
   Build up a character’s influence within an administrative empire to climb the rungs of bureaucracy. Raise your status in the realm and gather more power for yourself. Start as a landless noble on an estate, and compete for valuable provinces to govern before making your bid for the Purple.
   <br/>
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    A Life of Adventure:
   </strong>
   Freely roam the map, untied to any realm or holding, going wherever the winds of fortune blow you. Fulfill contracts as a landless adventurer, even through the generations, building up a reputation of your own. Earn gold, prestige and fame traveling the globe until you decide to settle down and claim land you have earned through merit.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2671070/extras/steam_byz_camp_02.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <strong>
    Choose Successor or Caesar:
   </strong>
   Spend the influence you have gathered to determine the course of the Empire and get the successor you want, whether a royal family member, a powerful noble, a martial hero, or any other candidate you can rally the people behind. The Emperor can even opt to co-rule if the burden of the throne is too much for one person.
   <br/>
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    New Byzantine Flavor Content:
   </strong>
   New events, monuments and activities built around the Byzantine theme, including chariot racing.
   <br/>
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   <strong>
    Cosmetic Additions:
   </strong>
   A Byzantine-themed UI skin and new court fashions for your characters, new 2D event art, new on-map monuments of the Byzantine world, new on-map holding designs, and a Byzantine throne room for Royal Court sessions, among other aesthetic improvements. New music inspired by Orthodox holy chants is also included.
  </li>
 </ul>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2671070/extras/steam_barbershop_03.gif"/>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remnant II® - The Dark Horizon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384075/Remnant_II__The_Dark_Horizon/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Remnant II® - The Dark Horizon
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Gunfire Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Arc Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2384075/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 A return to N’Erud uncovers a mysterious place preserved in time, where alien farmlands are tended by robots for inhabitants who have long since perished. But time corrupts all, and rogue AI and robotic creations threaten at every turn while travelers search for the secrets of the colossal entity that dominates the skyline.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  FEATURES
 </strong>
 <br/>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   New storyline, dungeons and area based in the world of N’Erud
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   New Archetype - The Warden
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Many items and powerful weapons that enhance gameplay
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   New bosses, characters and fearsome creatures
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   Gameplay revolves around intense fights against humanoid, non-humanoid, and fantastical creatures with gunplay and melee weapons. In certain circumstances, critical hits can cause enemies to become decapitated. Mild use of language when characters are under duress.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Win 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i5-7600 / AMD Ryzen 5 2600
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GeForce GTX 1650 / AMD Radeon RX 590
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        80 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Win 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel i5-10600k / AMD R5 3600
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GeForce RTX 2060 / AMD Radeon RX 5700
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        80 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ara: History Untold</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2021880/Ara_History_Untold/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Ara: History Untold
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Oxide Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Xbox Game Studios
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2021880/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Build a nation and lead your people throughout history to the pinnacles of human achievement as you explore new lands, develop arts and culture, conduct diplomacy, and go head-to-head with your rivals to prove you are the greatest ruler ever known. It's Your World Now.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Ara: History Untold is an evolution in historical grand strategy, featuring beloved classic PC strategy mechanics alongside innovative gameplay like a national crafting economy, true simultaneous turn resolution, a non-linear technology tree, and cloud-backed synchronous/asynchronous multiplayer - all with an expansive and vibrant presentation where you can zoom out from surveying the very edges of your empire all the way down to your citizens living their daily lives. In Ara, there are no pre-set paths to victory, leading to endless possibilities. Your choices will define the world you create, your experience, and your legacy.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Join the Ara History: Untold Insider Program today! As an Insider you’ll join a passionate community of strategy game fans that receive exclusive updates, invitations to provide feedback, and opportunities to play the game before it is released. Sign up today at
 <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
  arahistoryuntold.com
 </a>
 .
 <br>
  <br>
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/City.png"/>
   <br>
    <br>
     <strong>
      Explore an Immersive Living World:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Explore a dynamic living world filled with life and charm across sweeping landscapes ranging from tropical jungles to sand-swept deserts as you discover the resources you need to develop your nation. Witness the world come to life in vivid, realistic detail as citizens move throughout the world and react dynamically to times of health and sickness, war and peace, wealth and despair with unique biomes, cultures, and eras representing the diversity of the human experience.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/EnvironmentCombo5_616px.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Build Your Nation:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Serve your people and grow your prestige with numerous Improvements, from forges to libraries, citadels to cathedrals, public parks to industrial factories - as well as a global variety of the greatest architectural Triumphs ever conceived and built by human hands.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/CityMenus.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Guide your people through the eras of human discovery:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Nurture your people’s brilliance and invention as you progress your Nation through twelve unique Technology Eras, making the hard choices about where to focus your Nation’s greatest minds. As you near the end of each Era, you’ll have to decide how fast to push your scientists along the path to the future - at the risk of the present.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/Technology.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Oversee a rich and detailed national economy:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Harvest the bounty of the natural world and deploy the labor of your people with a depth-filled National Crafting system. Will you manufacture Amenities - like lavish feasts - to provide your cities and citizens with powerful benefits, or invest in the creation of Equipment - the weapons of war - to prepare your Armies to defend your nation or conquer your rivals? Whatever paths you choose you’ll need to carefully optimize your resources and production to achieve the most efficient systems if you want to outpace your rivals to fortune and lasting glory.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/Amenity.png"/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/CreatingArmy.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Rule Your Way:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Choose from dozens of history's most influential figures to embody as you reshape the world through your choices. The unique and varied global Leaders and Nations in Ara emphasize a wide variety of different playstyles. Experiment with gameplay-impacting Traits and powerful Leader Abilities drawn from the effect they had on world history. Whether friend or foe, each Leader has a distinct personality based on their historical background that informs their AI behaviors.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/Leader.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Experience True Simultaneous Turns:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Every turn each nation's actions and choices resolve simultaneously, leading to suspense, anticipation, unique outcomes, and surprising twists on the classic turn-based formula. The fate of your people will be determined by your decisions and your ability to predict your opponent’s next move, putting your skill as a leader to the ultimate test.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2021880/extras/SimultaneousTurns_616px.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Defend your people by land, sea, and air:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Warfare in Ara is presented in the Living World, as thousands of years of military conflict reflect the progress and martial prowess of your people. Develop technologies to advance your weaponry against your rivals, hone your wartime economy and industry to gain the edge, and outthink your opponent’s strategies as maneuvers resolve authentically at once thanks to the power of True Simultaneous Turns.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Prove Your Worth in Online Multiplayer:
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Combining the speed and surprise of True Simultaneous Turns with the power of the cloud - multiplayer in Ara is fast, seamless, and able to be enjoyed asynchronously with a wide range of options to tailor you and your friend’s experience to the way you want to play together.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     A Microsoft Account is required to play online multiplayer.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 (20H1) or later
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        AMD Ryzen 5 2400G – Intel i5-5300U
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        AMD Radeon RX 480 – Nvidia GeForce GTX 970
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        50 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 (20H1) or later
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        AMD Ryzen 5 3600 – Intel i5-6400
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        AMD RX Vega 64 – Nvidia GeForce GTX 1080Ti
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        50 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2951990/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Void_Shadows/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Owlcat Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Owlcat Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Warhammer
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2951990/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 “Void Shadows” is the first DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, offering a massive amount of content with about 15 hours of fresh gameplay and a new romanceable companion. Fully integrated into the game’s main story, this DLC will allow players to delve into the depths of their voidship first-hand in an enthralling new story that will pit them against an unfamiliar enemy trying to bring ruin to the von Valancius dynasty from within.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2951990/extras/1.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  A new story
 </strong>
 — a tense 15 hours of adventures on board the von Valancius voidship, filled with unexpected threats, various quests, unique equipment, and additional lore content, all of it fully integrated into the main campaign.
 <br>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2951990/extras/2_1.gif"/>
  <br>
   <br>
    <strong>
     А new companion
    </strong>
    — Kibellah, a Death Cult Assassin, who is ready to pledge her life in service of the von Valancius dynasty just as her predecessors did for generations before, even possibly developing a strong personal bond with the Lord Captain.
    <br>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2951990/extras/3.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      А new looming threat
     </strong>
     arising from within the deepest and darkest bowels of the player’s very own voidship — the malignant Genestealer Cult — a horrific breed of xenos who operate from the shadows, infecting your crew with their genetic code to convert them, slowly twisting their faith in the Emperor to carry out their wretched designs.
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2951990/extras/4.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      New crew members
     </strong>
     — high-level officers integral to voidship operations, numbering thousands upon thousands of souls, stand ready to serve the Lord Captain.
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2951990/extras/5.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      New locations to explore
     </strong>
     — the sheer magnitude of the voidship hides many distant nooks and crannies where no Lord Captain has gone before.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo Point Nova</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1836730/Echo_Point_Nova/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Echo Point Nova
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Greylock Studio
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Greylock Studio
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 24, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1836730/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 From the team that brought you Severed Steel, dive into a vast open-world FPS designed for both solo and 4-player cooperative play!
 <br/>
 <br/>
 You play as an explorer with exceptional combat skills who crash-lands on a mysterious planet. This planet is dominated by a ruthless mercenary force exploiting ancient technology to craft devastating weapons. Pursue the main quest to dismantle their operations, or explore the world at your own pace!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Explore a Seamless Open World
 </h2>
 Every distant vista is within reach. Traverse a completely seamless world using your grapple hook, hoverboard, and a variety of unlockable powers.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1836730/extras/2big4.gif"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Epic Battles and Colossal Bosses
 </h2>
 Embark on a main quest to encounter towering colossi or stumble upon these foes during your explorations. Battle against diverse enemy classes such as pyromancers launching area attacks, elusive sappers planting turrets, and helicopters raining down rockets.
 <br>
  <br>
   <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1836730/extras/fball.gif"/>
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    Flexible Singleplayer and Co-op Gameplay
   </h2>
   Jump into cooperative play from the start with no mandatory tutorials. Progress on the same save whether in solo or co-op mode, and tailor individual difficulty settings within the same multiplayer session. Note: Co-op play is supported through Steam Friends invites (random matchmaking is not available).
   <br>
    <br>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1836730/extras/coop.gif"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Unlock Secrets and Power-Ups
     </h2>
     Echo Point Nova is filled with hidden weapons, character enhancements, and stylish cosmetics. Collect agility orbs to enhance your mobility, and unlock weapon attachments by racking up kills.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1836730/extras/surfd2.gif"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      An Accessible Game
     </h2>
     Echo Point Nova's default settings and recommended difficulty are pretty hard core! But there's loads of options for all players to set things up the way they like.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      A Growing Game
     </h2>
     Our last game, Severed Steel, received new game modes, weapons, maps, and more for many months after launch. We pay lots of attention to our community and plan on a steady flow of content, quality of life improvements, and gameplay tweaks. Join our Discord or post in the Steam community to get in on the action!
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This game contains stylized first person gun and melee combat, with blood splashes and blood wound decals on enemy character bodies.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Quad-Core 64-bit Intel or AMD processor
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA 1050 or equivalent
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        4 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
