<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Creeper World IXE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2257010/Creeper_World_IXE/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Creeper World IXE
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Knuckle Cracker
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Knuckle Cracker
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Creeper World
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 12, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2257010/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/What2Banner.jpg"/>
  Creeper World IXE is a real-time strategy game in the Creeper World franchise with groundbreaking pixel-level simulation. Command a squad of ships, coordinate your tactics, and fight back the alien menace known as "The Creeper," an all-consuming fluid enemy that has already devoured thousands of colonies.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/image002.gif"/>
  Your mission: stop the Creeper's endless advance or all life in the universe will perish. Unlike previous encounters, humanity now possesses a technological advantage that you can harness not only to survive, but to dominate the galaxy.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/Gameplay2Banner.jpg"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  In Creeper World IXE you will liberate and explore hundreds of worlds in this real-time strategy game where the enemy is a fluid and every pixel of the terrain is simulated. Terraform through dozens of terrain types to use gravity and nature against the enemy. Bring awesome new weapons to use against chambers of compressed Creeper that explode outwards with ripple and wave mechanics.
  <br/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/image006.gif"/>
  Combine sand, particle, and creeper fluid simulations to open up new strategies and threats. Bring multi-weapon units to a dynamic battlefield as you explore worlds for secrets of the Creeper. Gain experience from your victories and unlock new and amazing technologies to help in your fight.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Create and play custom maps with new and original units made by the community or yourself! 2D-pixel graphics are married with a detailed and robust custom map and unit creation system, so nearly anyone with an idea can make a unit or a mission and share it with others. Use built-in control modules, or craft your own with robust built-in RPL scripting.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/Creeper2.jpg"/>
  The Creeper is an ancient fluid-like enemy that relentlessly spreads across terra-formable terrain; engulfing and destroying anything that crosses its path. With sufficient firepower, you can push back the Creeper. But, in most cases it cannot be killed entirely by simply shooting at it. It is a foe that constantly regenerates through Creeper Emitters in its never-ending goal of consuming all living matter.
  <br/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/image004.gif"/>
  The only way to stop the creeper is to find and destroy the emitters and destroy the IXE Cores on each planet. Only by finding all of the cores and activating them simultaneously will The Creeper be destroyed and the planet saved. Achieving this goal will be no easy task. Command your squad of ships carefully.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Explore each planet while making sure you hold your ground. Locate, activate and destroy the IXE Cores. As easy as this might seem, at first glance, The Creeper will constantly push to thwart your efforts and attack in surprising ways to throw you off balance. Keep a cool head, be prepared, and use the environment to your advantage. That is the key to your success.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2257010/extras/Features2Banner.jpg"/>
 </p>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   Embark on story and campaign missions as you fend off the Creeper for galactic domination
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Sand physics terrain where every pixel is simulated allowing the use of gravity and terrain as part of your strategy
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Enhanced Creeper fluid simulation with waves creating new Creeper behavior
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Particle system for new and greater threats
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Use terrain chemistry and terraforming to gain the advantage over your enemy
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Extensive custom unit support with scripting where the community can craft their units, missions and control modules.
   <br/>
  </li>
  <li>
   Online map database for endless fun and new challenges
  </li>
 </ul>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  AI Generated Content Disclosure
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe how their game uses AI Generated Content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   Some background and character art extended and enhanced using Photoshop generative fill. Some audio help narration done using an in-house cloned voice for clarity. Some audio narration done using professionally licensed cloned voice.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 or later
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Quad Core 2.5Ghz
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        6 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Dedicated GPU
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        2 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 or later
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Six Core 3Ghz
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        nVidia RTX 20 series / AMD RX 580 series equivalent or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        4 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Skulltaker – Omens of Destruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130750/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Skulltaker__Omens_of_Destruction/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Total War: WARHAMMER III - Skulltaker – Omens of Destruction
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   CREATIVE ASSEMBLY
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Feral Interactive
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   SEGA
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Total War
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Warhammer
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 12, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3130750/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The Skulltaker DLC pack for Total War: WARHAMMER III introduces Khorne’s Immortal Champion and the greatest of all Bloodletters, Skulltaker, as a playable Legendary Lord alongside a deadly host of new battle units, gameplay features and objectives to be experienced in the immense Immortal Empires campaign or Custom Battles.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  Skulltaker relentlessly seeks worthy skulls for his master. Constantly scanning the battlefield for the strongest opponents, he issues a thunderous challenge before swiftly ending their lives. Embodying Khorne’s unyielding fury, he takes immense pride in his martial abilities and views himself as an unstoppable force.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  Campaign Feature:
  <br>
   ● Cloak of Skulls: As the champion of Khorne, Skulltaker must seek-out and defeat powerful enemy lords across the heroic pantheon of the Warhammer World and add their skulls to his infamous cloak. With each new skull he earns ‘Champions Essence’ allowing him to unlock new bonuses or upgrade existing ones, granting powerful new abilities and traits that increase his proficiency in combat.
   <br>
    <br>
     Battle Playstyle:
     <br>
      ● Few daemons ascend to the exalted position of Khorne’s Champion and those who do are assured to be lethal in almost every regard. This is true for Skulltaker, a force of daemonic destruction, he excels at hunting down and duelling enemy lords before cleaving through ranks of troops with his two-handed Slayer Sword. His Cloak of Skulls passive ability grants increasing spell resistance and ward saves the more he kills.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      New Units:
      <br/>
      ● Nine new units from the Blood God’s domain enter the fray, including two Legendary Heroes; Skarr Bloodwrath ‘the bloodthirsty butcher’ and Scyla Anfingrimm ‘the rage of Khorne’, followed by a host of acolytes including the Bloodspeaker, Slaughterbrute, Bloodbeast, Wrathmongers, Skullreapers, and Khorngors.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      Content Overview:
      <br/>
      ● 1 Legendary Lord
      <br/>
      ● 2 Legendary Heroes
      <br/>
      ● 1 Lord
      <br/>
      ● 5 Battle Units
      <br/>
      ● 3 Regiments of Renown
      <br/>
      ● New Gameplay Mechanics and Features
      <br/>
      ● Playable in Immortal Empires and Custom Battles Only
     </br>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_full">
        <ul>
         <strong>
          Minimum:
         </strong>
         <br/>
         <ul class="bb_ul">
          <li>
           <strong>
            OS:
           </strong>
           macOS 12.5
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Processor:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (8‑Core CPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Memory:
           </strong>
           8 GB RAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Graphics:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (7‑Core GPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Storage:
           </strong>
           125 GB available space
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Additional Notes:
           </strong>
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The game is officially supported on all Mac models released since November 2020 with an Apple M1 chip or better. To check your Mac model and when it was released, select About This Mac from the Apple menu on your menu bar.
           </ul>
           ———
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The following Macs are capable of running the game but do not consistently meet the standards required for official support:
            <li>
             * All Mac models with an AMD GPU that support macOS 12.5
            </li>
           </ul>
          </li>
         </ul>
        </ul>
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Golgfag – Omens of Destruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130740/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Golgfag__Omens_of_Destruction/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Total War: WARHAMMER III - Golgfag – Omens of Destruction
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   CREATIVE ASSEMBLY
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Feral Interactive
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   SEGA
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Total War
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Warhammer
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 12, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3130740/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The Golgfag Maneater DLC pack for Total War: WARHAMMER III introduces one of the most successful Ogre Mercenaries, Golgfag Maneater, as a playable Legendary Lord alongside a deadly host of new battle units, gameplay features and objectives to be experienced in the immense Immortal Empires campaign or Custom Battles.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  A weathered veteran, there are few foes in the world Golgfag hasn’t faced, having fought across continents and cultures the world over. He’ll take any job, kill anyone, and steal anything as long as the price is right, and his loyalty is strictly for hire, lasting only as long as the deal does. Boisterous and larger-than-life, Golgfag is also a top guzzler of Bugman’s ale.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  Campaign Feature:
  <br>
   ● Mercenary Contracts: As an internationally renowned mercenary, Golgfag helps client factions throughout the WARHAMMER world settle their warring disputes by taking on all their wars. When a contract is signed, he must earn points by making acts of aggression against the enemy within a specified turn-limit and after reaching his target the contract is complete, granting a payout and rewards such as Meat, Maneater Banners and culture unique Ancillaries.
   <br>
    <br>
     Playstyle:
     <br>
      ● A fearsome reputation such as Golgfag’s isn’t forged through the showing of mercy, and on the battlefield, he ensures that any fools who stand in his way regret it. A proficient anti-infantry killer, he cuts through foes like a sharp knife through stale Old-World butter, but can also call upon some deadly abilities such as Dead Eye in in which he fires a powerful single shot that deals significant ranged and armour piercing damage.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      New Units:
     </br>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  ● New units joining Golgfag’s mercenary brigade include the Legendary Hero Bragg the Gutsman, the self-proclaimed executioner of the Ogre Kingdoms, as well as the Ogre Paymaster, Bruiser, Golgfag’s Maneaters, Pigback Riders, Blood Vultures, Yhetees and Thundertusk.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Content Overview:
  <br/>
  ● 1 Legendary Lord
  <br/>
  ● 1 Legendary Hero
  <br/>
  ● 1 Lord and 1 Hero
  <br/>
  ● 5 Battle Units
  <br/>
  ● 3 Regiments of Renown
  <br/>
  ● New Gameplay Mechanics and Features
  <br/>
  ● Playable in Immortal Empires and Custom Battles Only
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_full">
        <ul>
         <strong>
          Minimum:
         </strong>
         <br/>
         <ul class="bb_ul">
          <li>
           <strong>
            OS:
           </strong>
           macOS 12.5
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Processor:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (8‑Core CPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Memory:
           </strong>
           8 GB RAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Graphics:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (7‑Core GPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Storage:
           </strong>
           125 GB available space
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Additional Notes:
           </strong>
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The game is officially supported on all Mac models released since November 2020 with an Apple M1 chip or better. To check your Mac model and when it was released, select About This Mac from the Apple menu on your menu bar.
           </ul>
           ———
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The following Macs are capable of running the game but do not consistently meet the standards required for official support:
            <li>
             * All Mac models with an AMD GPU that support macOS 12.5
            </li>
           </ul>
          </li>
         </ul>
        </ul>
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Gorbad – Omens of Destruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574900/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Gorbad__Omens_of_Destruction/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Total War: WARHAMMER III - Gorbad – Omens of Destruction
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   CREATIVE ASSEMBLY
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Feral Interactive
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   SEGA
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Total War
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Warhammer
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 12, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2574900/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The Gorbad Ironclaw DLC pack for Total War: WARHAMMER III introduces one of the most infamous of all Orc Warbosses, Gorbad Ironclaw, as a playable Legendary Lord alongside a deadly host of new battle units, gameplay features and objectives to be experienced in the immense Immortal Empires campaign or Custom Battles.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  One of the most infamous of all Orc Warbosses, Gorbad knows but one language and that is war. Unique amongst his race due to his rare mix of brain and brawn, he has become an inspiration amongst his kind for "invasions done propa".
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Campaign Feature:
  <br/>
  ● Da’ Plan: A tenacious tactician, Gorbad must experiment with unique battle strategies such as matching different units in his army roster to unlock powerful synergistic bonuses such as abilities, attributes, and campaign perks. Each tactic can progress in level by completing challenges, encouraging creative army compositions and rewarding strategic thinking.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  Battle Playstyle:
  <br/>
  ● Riding into battle atop his fierce Warboar, Gnarla, Gorbad penetrates the enemy lines with devastating charges before engaging in close combat with his mighty axe, Morglor ‘the Mangler’. His ‘Da Great Leader’ ability which activates when troops are in his vicinity, granting increased melee attack and defence.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  New Units:
  <br/>
  ● New units joining Gorbad’s Waaagh! include the legendary hero Snagla Grobspit accompanied by a motley crew of warriors such as the Savage Orc Great Shaman, Night Goblin Big Boss, Black Orcs (Axe & Shield), mangler squigs, Colossal Squig, Arachnarok (Flinger), and Bolt Throwa.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Content Overview:
  <br/>
  ● 1 Legendary Lord
  <br/>
  ● 1 Legendary Hero
  <br/>
  ● 1 Lord and 1 Hero
  <br/>
  ● 5 Battle Units
  <br/>
  ● 3 Regiments of Renown
  <br/>
  ● New Gameplay Mechanics and Features
  <br/>
  ● Playable in Immortal Empires and Custom Battles Only
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_full">
        <ul>
         <strong>
          Minimum:
         </strong>
         <br/>
         <ul class="bb_ul">
          <li>
           <strong>
            OS:
           </strong>
           macOS 12.5
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Processor:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (8‑Core CPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Memory:
           </strong>
           8 GB RAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Graphics:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 (7‑Core GPU) or better
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Storage:
           </strong>
           125 GB available space
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Additional Notes:
           </strong>
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The game is officially supported on all Mac models released since November 2020 with an Apple M1 chip or better. To check your Mac model and when it was released, select About This Mac from the Apple menu on your menu bar.
           </ul>
           ———
           <ul class="bb_ul">
            The following Macs are capable of running the game but do not consistently meet the standards required for official support:
            <li>
             * All Mac models with an AMD GPU that support macOS 12.5
            </li>
           </ul>
          </li>
         </ul>
        </ul>
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hatsuyuki Sakura</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3171460/Hatsuyuki_Sakura/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Hatsuyuki Sakura
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   SAGA PLANETS
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   HIKARI FIELD
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   NekoNyan Ltd.
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 12, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3171460/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  "Hatsuyuki Sakura" is one of the most popular works by SAGA PLANETS, a popular Japanese developer for visual novels.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Experience Hatsuyuki Sakura for the first time in 1080p!
  </strong>
  <br/>
  This version includes the English, Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese, and Japanese versions. It supports Steam Achievements and Trading Cards, along with additional content.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3171460/extras/story.png"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3171460/extras/Chara-01steam.png"/>
  <br/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3171460/extras/Chara-02steam.png"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3171460/extras/Chara-03steam.png"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.fastly.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3171460/extras/Chara-04steam.png"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This work contains depictions of the protagonist’s alcohol abuse and use of coarse language, which may not be suitable for some users. Please ensure you are aware of this information before making a purchase.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        2.66GHz
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        512M
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 9.0c
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        11 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Sound Card:
        </strong>
        PCM
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
