<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Heroes: Trails through Daybreak II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668430/The_Legend_of_Heroes_Trails_through_Daybreak_II/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 The Legend of Heroes: Trails through Daybreak II
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Nihon Falcom
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   PH3 GmbH
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   NIS America, Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   The Legend of Heroes
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 14, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2668430/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 No longer threatened by the mafia organization Almata, the people of Calvard have returned to their peaceful lives. But one day, a shocking series of murders involving a mysterious crimson beast sets the wheels of fate in motion once again. Various factions spring into action – both those who abide by the law to uncover the truth and those looking to capitalize on any new developments wherever possible, no matter how sinister.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2668430/extras/van_1_s.png"/>
 <br/>
 With chaos once again looming on the horizon, the spriggan Van Arkride receives an unexpected visitor, prompting his own investigation. Who is behind the murders, and what is their goal? The sands of time bring old and new faces together for this thrilling second installment in the Trails through Daybreak saga.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  STORY
 </h2>
 Year 1209 of the Septian Calendar.
 <br/>
 <br>
  The threat posed by Almata has passed. Peace has finally returned to Calvard. And, for a time, that peace goes uninterrupted—until a CID special forces unit is slaughtered by an unknown assailant.
  <br>
   <br>
    With authorities working to contain the situation, criminal forces take the chance to make their own moves.
    <br>
     <br/>
     Meanwhile, a spriggan by the name of Van Arkride begins his own investigation—after prompting from an unexpected visitor.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Who could be responsible for this massacre? What was their objective? And how does it all relate to Agnès' search for the eighth Genesis?
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2668430/extras/agnes_2_s.png"/>
     <br/>
     A crimson beast's roar. A chance meeting with a boy and girl, both embroiled in a mysterious search. These are the circumstances that lure Arkride Solutions down the trail of an inescapable fate.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      SYSTEM
     </h2>
     <strong>
      Battle System
     </strong>
     <br/>
     The game builds on the seamless transition between field battles and command battles introduced in the previous game with new mechanics that can be used in both: Cross Charge & EX Chains! Mastering the use of these two combo mechanics can provide you with overwhelming firepower to use against your opponents.
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2668430/extras/Exchain_02_s.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       Cross Charge
      </li>
     </ul>
     If you manage to Perfect Dodge an enemy's attack during a field battle, the Cross Charge icon will appear! Pushing the correct button while the icon is on-screen will swap in another party member, who will simultaneously execute a charge attack on your foe! As a bonus, the party member that you swap in will have enhanced attack power for a period of time.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       EX Chains
      </li>
     </ul>
     EX Chains can be activated by fulfilling specific conditions during command battles. Once these conditions have been met, using a craft or normal attack against a stunned enemy will automatically activate an EX Chain! This allows party members with SCLM activated to launch a simultaneous attack that will also impact nearby enemies, dealing massive damage.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Choose Your Chapters
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2668430/extras/Chapter_main_s.png"/>
     <br/>
     Van and his collaborators will not always travel together during the events of Trails through Daybreak II. At times, some of the group may split off in order to take care of tasks in different areas of Calvard concurrently. Because of this, each act contains multiple chapters you can play in any order. Progress the story in the order you choose! Each chapter features a different cast of characters as we see their side of the act's story play out.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Once you've completed your chosen chapter, the next one will start up automatically.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Unique Missions
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Certain chapters will feature missions that utilize the unique skillsets of the characters in that chapter's party. For example, directly controlling the holo core AI, Mare, to hack the orbal network, or using Swin to silently tail a suspicious individual.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      CHARACTERS
     </h2>
     <strong>
      Van Arkride
     </strong>
     <br/>
     The man at the head of Arkride Solutions. A lover of sweets, saunas, and orbal cars. Due to his job as a spriggan, Van has a tendency to take on legally-questionable jobs. However, the fact that he occasionally walks on the edge of the law does not preclude him from doing good by others—as is evidenced by his numerous personal contacts. While tracking down the Oct-Geneses at Agnès' request, Van developed the ability to transform into an armored form known as the Grendel with the help of Mare, the holo core installed within his combat orbment. It was with this new ability that he was able to fend off the mafia group known as Almata. Having once terrorized the entirety of the Republic, Almata was eventually brought to its knees by the Arkride Solutions team during the fight for the Oct-Geneses. Upon the quelling of this threat, however, they decided to temporarily go their separate ways. Now left to himself in a less-than- lively office, Van is free to return to his lone-wolf lifestyle once more.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Agnès Claudel
     </strong>
     <br/>
     A first-year at the prestigious Aramis Academy who currently serves on its Student Council. Despite her polite manner of speaking and at times meek demeanor, Agnès has shown great strength and determination while employed at Arkride Solutions—especially when facing off against the seedy underbelly of society. Agnès first met Van while searching for eight prototype orbments known as the Oct-Geneses, which she inherited from her great-grandfather. As thanks for taking on her request, she began working as one of Arkride Solution's part-time assistants. At present, Agnès has recovered seven of the eight Geneses. Unfortunately, while continuing her search for the last remaining Genesis, she's had no choice but to also divide her time between preparing for the Aramis Academy Festival and periodically helping out around Arkride Solutions. Regarding her relationship with Van, she both respects and admires him as her employer. However, she seems to be harboring some more amorous feelings for him as well...
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Elaine Auclair
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2668430/extras/elaine_1_s.png"/>
     <br/>
     An A-rank bracer affiliated with the Calvard branch of the Bracer Guild. She is occasionally referred to by the moniker 'Beauty's Blade.' Due to her dignified beauty and masterful skill with a sword, Elaine tends to catch the eye of the media more often than not. Unfortunately, this also leads to talent agencies offering her contracts for modeling and acting—she always declines. Outside of being the poster girl for the Bracer Guild, Elaine has no present interest in joining the world of entertainment. During her high school years, she enjoyed a brief and fleeting romance with Van before he suddenly vanished without so much as a word. It was only recently, after seven years, that the two were able to reunite. Although their lingering feelings for each other have left their current relationship a bit tense, their time fighting Almata together was able to strengthen their bond once more. Some time after the events involving Almata and the Oct-Geneses, Elaine received word that the Central Intelligence Department's elite Gamma Squad had been brutally murdered by an unknown assailant, and that a 'crimson' monster was spotted at the scene of the crime...
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      WORLD
     </h2>
     <strong>
      The Republic of Calvard
     </strong>
     <br/>
     A large country located in the central region of the Zemurian continent. Its current leader is President Roy Gramheart. Due to the unfortunate circumstances created by the desertification of eastern Zemuria, Calvard has a substantial history of receiving both immigrants and refugees. The resulting mixture of cultures and ethnicities has made the country into something of a melting pot. One hundred years ago, Calvard was under the heel of its monarchal rulers. It was only after Sheena Dirke and her compatriots brought about a democratic revolution that the nation was transformed into a democratic republic. Though in constant conflict with Erebonia over the control of bordering regions, Calvard has recently been on the receiving end of reparations from the empire following the Battle of Jormungandr. These reparations enabled Calvard to enter a period of rapid growth and development, leading to its eventual overtake of Erebonia as the most powerful nation on the continent. Regarding the region's recreational interests, recent technological advancements in orbal vehicles and filmmaking have caused a boom in both the motorsports and orbal cinema industries.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Messeldam
     </strong>
     <br/>
     A moderate-sized city located in the north of Calvard. Due to its long-standing role as one of the Northern Sea’s major trading ports, Messeldam was often tasked during the days of monarchal rule with the delivery of imports to the capital of Oración—along with fresh seafood, of course. Although the port remains active to this day, developments in airship technology have greatly diminished its significance. The city itself, however, remains an important gateway to Remiferia and its surrounding nations. Unlike Langport, Messeldam possesses very few tourist destinations. That being said, the townscape's architecture tends to be quite popular with visitors, as its design has seen little change in the past century. The city’s Eastern and Central Eastern populations are fairly meager due to its geographical location. As such, it lacks a community that values cultural traditionalism. This has, fortunately, been a boon for Messeldam, as new art movements and customs are accepted with relative ease. It was this very attitude that led to the city serving as the venue for the Orbal Film Festival for a number of years, until its relocation to Tharbad in 1208.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      + Wishlist
     </strong>
     your copy today! We hope you look forward to the continuation of the Calvard arc!
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   Rare occurrences of violence against bound hostages.
   <br/>
   Discrimination against fictional minorities.
   <br/>
   Usage of Fantasy Drugs.
   <br/>
   Insinuation of child prostitution.
   <br/>
   Depiction of Suicide
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        AMD Ryzen 5 1600
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1050
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        22 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Settings: 1080p, 30 FPS, Performance Graphics Profile
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i5-10400
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1650
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        22 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Settings: 1440p, 60 FPS, High Graphics Profile
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider IV-VI Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2525380/Tomb_Raider_IVVI_Remastered/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Tomb Raider IV-VI Remastered
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Aspyr
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Crystal Dynamics
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Aspyr
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Aspyr
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Tomb Raider
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 14, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2525380/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <strong>
  Her legacy lives on!
 </strong>
 <br/>
 Play the next series of Tomb Raider adventures in this remastered collection of the Darkness Trilogy.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  Included Game Titles
 </strong>
 <br>
  Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation – Lara Croft discovers the lost tomb of the Egyptian God Set, unwittingly unleashing him and fulfilling an ancient prophecy—one that plunges mankind into darkness.
  <br>
   <br>
    Tomb Raider: Chronicles – Following the events of The Last Revelation, Lara Croft is buried in an Egyptian tomb and is presumed dead. At her memorial, those closest to her reminisce about secrets from her past.
    <br>
     <br/>
     Tomb Raider: The Angel of Darkness – Accused of murder, Lara becomes a fugitive on the run, while uncovering a sinister conspiracy involving alchemical experiments and the search for ancient artifacts.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Key Features
     </strong>
     <br/>
     See the Classic & Remastered Visuals: Play with the original polygonal models or swap to the remastered graphics at any time
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Travel the Globe: Follow Lara Croft around iconic locales including Cairo, Rome, Paris, and many more
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Experience Lara’s Darkest Adventures: Uncover the secrets of Lara Croft’s past and shed light on the mystery of her disappearance
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10+
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel i3 / AMD FX-4100
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GeForce GT 620 1gb / Radeon HD 8670D
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10+
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel i7 / AMD Ryzen 7 5800
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDA RTX 2080 / Radeon RX 6750
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARK: Astraeos</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3483400/ARK_Astraeos/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 ARK: Astraeos
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Massively Multiplayer
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Studio Wildcard
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Studio Wildcard
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Snail Games USA
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Snail Games USA
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 13, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3483400/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Content
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Embark on your next epic odyssey within the world of ARK with Astraeos! Explore and immerse yourself in an elysian land of colossal proportions, steeped in Greek mythology where majestic mountain ridges and marble-like cliffs give way to white sand beaches and a paradise of cherry blossoms in full bloom. At over 260km², this massive new map is overflowing with stunning scenery, ancient ruins and sacred temples. Face off against powerful new bosses, alpha dino variants with enhanced loot, and a fearsome miniboss lurking in mysterious caves.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11 with updates
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        AMD Ryzen 5 2600X, Intel Core i7-6800K
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        AMD Radeon RX 5600 XT, NVIDIA GeForce 1080
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        70 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        SSD Required
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11 with updates
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        AMD Ryzen 5 3600X, Intel i5-10600K
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        32 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        AMD Radeon RX 6800, NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3080
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        70 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        SSD Required
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns of Fury</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3099000/Guns_of_Fury/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Guns of Fury
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Gelato Games Ltd
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Gelato Games Ltd
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 13, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3099000/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Guns of Fury is a retro-inspired action platformer that combines the run & gun and Metroidvania genres. Explore a vast interconnected world, gain new abilities and weapons, battle epic bosses and stop the plans of an evil corporation before it’s too late!
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3099000/extras/boss3.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  THE STORY
 </strong>
 <br>
  <br>
   In the near future, the world is in an energy crisis. When all hope has been lost, world famous scientist Dr. Klaus makes a surprise announcement: the discovery of the "Tetra Cell". Its incredible energy-producing properties could be used for the good of mankind. However, 24 hours later, he mysteriously disappears and his lab is destroyed in an explosion. The industrialist A. Easton, President of Easton Industries is suspected to have kidnapped Dr. Klaus and that he intends to use the Tetra Cell to create a new type of super weapon.
   <br>
    <br>
     You assume the role of Vincent Fury, a special operative on a mission to infiltrate the top secret research facility of Easton Industries, rescue Dr. Klaus and recover the missing Tetra Cell before it’s too late!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3099000/extras/mech3.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Explore a huge world as you face the private army of evil industrialist A. Easton and his gang of top executives.
     <br/>
     As you advance through the game, you will discover new items and abilities, as well as gain money to purchase new equipment from merchants, which will help you access new areas and battle more powerful enemies, including fearsome bosses.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3099000/extras/grenade.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      FEATURES
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       Explore a vast interconnected world and uncover new areas using newly acquired skills and equipment
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Exhilarating run and gun action
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Beautiful hand-crafted 16-bit pixel art
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Hundreds of unique items to discover, including guns, melee weapons, bombs and accessories
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       10+ bosses and tons of enemy types
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Acquire new abilities in an authentic Metroidvania experience
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Take control of a variety of different mechs, each with its own array of attacks and abilities
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Discover secrets in breakable walls and acquire loot and powerful new equipment
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Destructible environments
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Alternate endings
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Incredible soundtrack by Dominic Ninmark
      </li>
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/3099000/extras/village3.gif"/>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_note">
     <strong>
      *
     </strong>
     Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS *:
        </strong>
        Windows 7+, 64 bit only
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core 2 Duo E8400 or AMD Phenom II X2 550
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        2 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GeForce 9600 GT or Radeon HD 3870
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        300 MB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawnfolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308630/Dawnfolk/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Dawnfolk
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Darenn Keller
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Astra Logical
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Astra Logical
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Darenn Keller
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 13, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2308630/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  In a world of darkness, you are the ruler of a kingdom lost to shadows. On a quest to save your people, you have found the mythical creature called “Lueur,” a fiery companion who will light your way. But what kind of ruler will you be?
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageHeaders_VentureIntoDarkness.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageGif_Illuminate.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  In Dawnfolk, you will explore an uncharted medieval fantasy world, manage resources, build cities, and survive against many dangers.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Minigames add a unique challenge to supporting your people. The better you are at the minigames, the more resources you get and the more likely your community will weather the darkness.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Every choice matters as you explore different strategies and play styles in Dawnfolk.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageHeaders_SatisfyingSessions.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageGif_CityMiniGames.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Not everyone has time to invest hundreds of hours into learning how to play a grand strategy game. You can dive right in and start building your settlement immediately, going from a handful of tents to a big city in less than an hour.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Dawnfolk was designed to feel familiar, yet unlike any building strategy game you’ve ever played before. Unwind and play with ease, whether you’re at home or on the go, with your gamepad, keyboard, or handheld console. Go back to the roots of gaming, where exploration and experimentation are the key to fun and discovery.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageHeaders_AWorldBroken.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageGif_Storm.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Decades ago, titanic obsidian monoliths rained down from the sky. A raging tempest of unfathomable darkness gathered around them, slowly crawling across the world and consuming all in its path. You are the ruler of this land, once mighty and resolute, now broken and wounded. But not defeated! You intend to reclaim the realm and bring back light to the world.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  After years of wandering, your story begins as you finally find the Lueur, a mythical creature able to radiate a powerful enough brightness to dissipate darkness. It is time to explore the shadows and rebuild your realm.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageHeaders_Created_ByThisOneGuyNamedDarenn.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageGif_Darenn.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  This darkly cute survival city-builder has been created with much love by a very French developer named Darenn Keller.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  After working in the game industry for a few years, Darenn set off on an adventure into indie dev land. Originally called Lueur and then Lueur and the Dim Settlers (as Darenn’s initial goal was to make non-French-speakers sound like complete morons attempting to say the name of the game), the idea for Dawnfolk came about in the LOWREZJAM in 2022 as the challenge was to make a game in one week with a resolution of 64x64 pixels.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Darenn has chosen all elements of creative direction and design. He has mixed the music, molded the sprites, and shaped the game to be reflective of his game design philosophy. But no game is made in a vacuum - Dawnfolk wouldn’t be the amazing game it is without the support of the playtesters and community. The game continues to grow and evolve thanks to players like you so check out the Discord for ways to provide feedback straight to Darenn!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageHeaders_ShapeYourStory.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2308630/extras/SteamPageGif_DifficultChoice.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Your choices determine the fate of your realm and its inhabitants.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Will you turn a blind eye to impending disasters, or will you face them head-on? How will you handle the tough moral choices that define your legacy? Can you grow and optimize your cities not just survive, but to thrive as a shining beacon for future settlers?
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Will you succeed in bringing light back to the world?
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_note">
        <strong>
         *
        </strong>
        Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
       <div class="sys_req_full">
        <ul>
         <strong>
          Minimum:
         </strong>
         <br/>
         <ul class="bb_ul">
          <li>
           <strong>
            OS:
           </strong>
           macOS 10.12
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Processor:
           </strong>
           Apple M1 or Intel Core M
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Memory:
           </strong>
           8 GB RAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Graphics:
           </strong>
           2 GB VRAM
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Storage:
           </strong>
           2 GB available space
           <br/>
          </li>
          <li>
           <strong>
            Additional Notes:
           </strong>
           Support for OpenGL 3.3
          </li>
         </ul>
        </ul>
       </div>
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     Linux
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
