<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Wreckfest 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1203190/Wreckfest_2/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Wreckfest 2
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Racing
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Early Access
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Bugbear
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   THQ Nordic
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Wreckfest
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   THQ Nordic
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 20, 2025
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 20, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1203190/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Ascend to the throne of full-contact racing by breaking the rules - and everything else - on your way to victory! Developer Bugbear went all out, rebuilding its true-to-life physics simulation engine to take full advantage of modern hardware. Wreckfest 2 features even higher crash fidelity, more intricate component damage simulation and many more improvements across the board!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Get ready to witness the absolute best-in-class car destruction and truly epic moments of chaos, all with the signature vehicle handling from Wreckfest!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Destruction awaits on the ultimate driving playground!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Unmatched racing experience
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Brace yourself for the most phenomenal full-contact racing action with no rules, just jaw dropping moments of chaos and destruction, powered by the overhauled physics engine. Race in intense head-to-head fights on courses featuring high-speed circuits, crazy courses with obstacles & jumps, intersections and oncoming traffic, or go for demolition domination in derby mode.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  More and more tracks & arenas will be added during the Early Access phase.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Awesome & customizable cars
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Forget pristine supercars: Our cars are old, dented and patched together. Each of them tells a story, and you can tell your own by customizing your ride. Over the course of early access, more and more customization options will be added to the game. They will not only unlock your creative desires, but also contain new armor and component types that support certain playstyles. And later during Early Access, you can also share your designs with other racers and wreckers!
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Fully revamped game modes
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Launching into early access with the base game modes of Racing, Derby and multiplayer mode. During the Early Access phase, we will add a completely revamped career mode that adapts to your individual playstyle and guides you on your journey to become a true champion! For online racers there will be new skill-based matchmaking system and server queues coming as well!
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Challenges
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Another highlight during the Early Access phase will be special challenges, putting you behind the steering wheel of unconventional vehicles that were definitely never supposed to end up on a racetrack! Various bite-sized scenarios will keep you hooked as you battle for the highest scores.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Mod Support
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  During the Early Access phase, mod support will be added so you can really mess with this game by installing various mods from the Steam Workshop.
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 or 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Core i5 8600 / Ryzen 5 3500 or equivalent 6 core CPU
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        GTX 1060 / RX 580
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        15 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        For 1080p - 30 FPS at low graphics preset. These requirements will be lowered during the early access phase.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 or 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Core i7 9700 / Ryzen 5 3600X or equivalent 6 core CPU
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        RTX 3070 / 6800 XT
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        15 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        For 1080p 60 FPS at high graphics preset. These requirements will be lowered during the early access phase.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cataclismo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1422440/Cataclismo/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Cataclismo
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Digital Sun
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Hooded Horse
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Hooded Horse
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 20, 2025
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Jul 22, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1422440/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/IMG_1_Loop.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Lead the last survivors in the aftermath of the Cataclismo as a corrupted world seeks to destroy all that remains of humanity. Build fortresses brick by brick, designing intricate, towering structures of wood and stone to fend off waves of Horrors as they attempt to overwhelm your band of survivors. Command powerful units in their stalwart defense, coordinating their varied capabilities as you race from breach to breach. Lead forays into the unknown to secure the vital resources needed to grow your military might and construction capabilities as you hold fast against the ever-growing onslaught – siege after siege, night after night.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/english_Headline_1.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/IMG_2_Loop.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Far from the relative safety of the Last City, your citadels and outposts hold back the hordes of Horrors before they can strike at the heart of humanity. Build impregnable fortresses across multiple biomes using an intricate building system that allows you to design your defenses with full freedom and strategic creativity, adapting your plans to the surrounding environment. Take advantage of natural chokepoints, height advantages, and local resources as you strategize for the challenge of each upcoming night’s attack.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    A highly modular building system allows you to design your fortresses exactly as you desire – one piece at a time, with blueprints you have designed in advance, or using community creations shared by other players. Use your hard-earned resources to build structures that grant access to previously unreachable parts of the map, or construct fortifications that deny the Horrors access and provide your troops safe vantage points.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    Build cheaply and quickly using wood, or establish quarries and use durable stone to better withstand the onslaught. Keep an eye on structural integrity and load-bearing columns as falling pieces will kill friend and foe alike, often creating unique opportunities to crush numerous enemies with cleverly placed vulnerabilities.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    Adapt your fortress to growing needs as you acquire new tools and expand in an attempt to secure all the resources needed to sustain a powerful defensive force. Optimize the path from resource deposits to your warehouses with well placed structures and use rooftop construction to make the most of your limited space.
   </p>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/english_Headline_2.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/IMG_3_Loop.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Though the Horrors may test your defenses during the day, only at night do they pour forth in full force. Spend your days exploring the world and pursuing the growth of your fortress, but as the sun starts to set, you would be wise to position your forces in preparation for the night’s onslaught.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    Skillfully command soldiers ranging from sharp-eyed bowmen to explosive cannoneers to respond to an ever-evolving situation as new Horrors emerge. Draw the enemy into chokepoints lined with devastating traps and ambush them raining down fire arrows and pots of poison flung from your battlements. Maneuver your troops into precise tactical positions to take advantage of special traits and abilities made available as they upgrade, positioning them at heights that let them perform at their best – a wise architect can design fortresses that allow for a tiered defense.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    Build vital structures to sustain your defenses against the growing threat and unlock higher levels of prosperity alongside new technologies. Resource gathering outposts, unit recruitment centers, and housing for your citizens all directly and indirectly support your troops in their efforts. Should the walls falter, even your citizens' homes can be used as a secondary layer of defense – you must protect the citadel at all costs.
   </p>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/english_Headline_3.png"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/IMG_4_Loop.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Cataclismo contains all three of: an epic single-player narrative campaign; a skirmish mode featuring hand-crafted maps; and an endlessly replayable challenge mode that puts you to the test on procedurally generated maps where you fend off increasingly dangerous waves of Horrors. A complex map editor gives you the ability to design and share skirmish maps of your own to challenge the community while the intricate construction system will allow the architecturally inclined to build and share blueprints and help others in their defense against the Horrors.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The Cataclismo left the world devastated. But all hope is not lost – lead humanity through the darkness to a bright future as you design grand fortresses and command troops in real-time battles against a seemingly endless horde that will stop at nothing to see your people destroyed.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1422440/extras/IMG_5_Loop.gif"/>
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows® 10 (64-bit)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel® Core™ i7-4770 (quad-core) / AMD® FX-Series™ FX-9590 (quad-core)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA® GeForce® GTX 760 (2 GB) / AMD® Radeon™ R9 270X (2 GB)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        10 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows® 10 (64-bit)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel® Core™ i7-6700 (quad-core) / AMD® Ryzen™ 5 1500X (quad-core)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        12 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA® GeForce® GTX 1050 Ti (4 GB) / AMD® Radeon™ RX 570 (4 GB)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        10 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MySims™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3328900/MySims/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 MySims™
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Maxis
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Electronic Arts
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   The Sims™
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 18, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3328900/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Explore a new world with MySims™ — it's your world to transform in this retro re-release with updated graphics! Move to a town that has been struggling lately. With a little creativity and some help from the locals, you can make this place thrive. Improve the town to attract characters, from Chef Gino Delicioso and DJ Candy Supergroove to arcade owner, Vic Vector and Cap'n Ginny, the town pirate. Discover what the residents want and need, so that you can help them enjoy life in your Sims' new town. Design a hot tub or jukebox from scratch, build homes and businesses from the roof to the front door. Uncover special decorations and patterns as you explore the growing town. From the furniture and objects to the buildings to the town as a whole – each of your creations is unique. In MySims, what you make... makes all the difference!
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  Build and customize an entire town
 </strong>
 — Your town is your own unique creation, from the design of the flower shop to the layout of a Mad Scientist’s laboratory, and beyond.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
  Shape the community
 </strong>
 — It's your call who lives there and who moves out! Who will you befriend? Who will you ignore?
 <br>
  <br>
   <strong>
    A whole world to explore
   </strong>
   — Socialize with the locals and uncover all sorts of useful and surprising treasures hidden throughout the town.
   <br>
    <br>
     <strong>
      Create your own Sim
     </strong>
     — Personalize your Sims' appearance from head to toe. Unlock cool clothing as you befriend the neighbors.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Design your own stuff
     </strong>
     — Decorate with your very own furniture and accessories, then customize your creations with things you can grow, harvest, or discover around town.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        64-bit Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        i3 3220 / Ryzen 3 1200 / AMD FX6300 or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        6 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Nvidia GT 730 / Radeon R7 240 / Intel HD Graphics 620 (SM 6.0) or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        16 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Internet connection : Required for game activation, optional for game updates and cloud saves.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        64-bit Windows 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        i3 4130 / Ryzen 3 1300X or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Nvidia GT 1030 / Radeon RX 550 (SM 6.0) or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        16 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        Internet connection : Required for game activation, optional for game updates and cloud saves. For best experience we recommend the following aspect ratios and resolutions -Common 16:9 resolutions: 1280x720, 1600x900, 1920x1080, 2560x1440, 3840x2160. -Common 16:10 resolutions: 1280x800, 1440x900, 1680x1050, 1920×1200 -Common 21:9 resolutions: 2560x1080, 3440x1440.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 26</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3116890/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_26/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Out of the Park Baseball 26
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Sports
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Out of the Park Developments
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Out of the Park Developments
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Out of the Park Baseball
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 14, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3116890/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  We are thrilled to introduce Out of the Park Baseball 26 - the 26th edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Fans around the world have fallen in love with Out of the Park Baseball, recognizing its unique place in the intersection of video games and sport!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Develop and discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Here are some of the new features coming to Out of the Park Baseball 26, building on the foundation of the franchise:
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   For the first time ever - The Road To The World Baseball Classic(
  </strong>
  TM)
  <strong>
   !
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  We are thrilled to announce that, for the first time in Out of the Park Baseball history, the authentic World Baseball Classic(TM) will be in the game! Starting this season with the World Baseball Classic(TM) Qualifiers, including the clubs and players, and continuing into next year, the
  <strong>
   real
  </strong>
  World Baseball Classic(TM) clubs, participants, schedules, and more will be here. This single-player-mode feature allows everyone to experience the best of international baseball in true OOTP fashion.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Player Development Lab 2.0!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Our popular new single-player feature gets bigger and better this season! New progress bars improve clarity and allow you to track your players even more closely. Midterm progress reports now also give you a better idea on how your players are performing and allow you to be even more hands-on. Have a guy struggling to improve his plate discipline and don’t want to keep him in the lab for any longer? You can now cut your losses and free up the space for someone else. With new game settings, refined programs, fun news from around the league, and more, experience the development lab on a whole new level!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   New and improved MLB Draft!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  The importance of the draft cannot be overstated and in OOTP 26 we have greatly expanded upon the experience. An all new draft combine allows you to follow top prospects, develop strong relationships with them, and see what other organizations are thinking. Get the opinion of experts on the draft class in a new Draft Pipeline. With a new Draft Central screen and even more refinements, make your choices and see how you can transform your club into a powerhouse!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Beautiful new dynamic scoreboards with in-game live information!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  OOTP 26’s visuals jump off the screen and deliver great information in real time! Updated in real-time with information from the game you’re managing, put yourself in the stands like you’re sitting in the ballpark.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Drive for the Pennant is back
  </strong>
  -
  <strong>
   now for any season in baseball history
  </strong>
  !
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Our popular new mode returns - now letting you explore any year in the entire history of the sport in this unique, streamlined single player challenge! Execute important choices at crucial times, be transported to the manager’s seat in the last inning of a no-hitter, make a key pitching decision late in a game, and much more! No longer limited to just the current season, Drive For The Pennant is an incredible way to explore the rich and vast history of Major League Baseball, and focus your game on the big decisions for your team.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Licensed leagues return!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  MLB, the complete minor leagues, the KBO in Korea and licensed leagues from the UK and the Netherlands are all here for you to explore in depth. Jump into the MLB or KBO season at any point, all season long, with up-to-the-minute rosters, trades, injuries, transactions, and more!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   The National Baseball Hall of Fame!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Our amazing partnership with the National Baseball Hall of Fame continues this season in new and fascinating ways! Hall of Fame players, artifacts, and experiences will pepper OOTP 26 all season long across the entire experience.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   2025 Rosters and rules!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2025 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 26 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Tons of upgrades big and small!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Overhauled player scouting model, with scouts giving you more details than ever before about your players
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Improved historical ratings engine, to ensure the best historical play ever
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     A Military Service system to replicate the real club decision making process needed for the KBO
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Improved UI experience
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Updated AI for all number of systems, player evaluation, and minor league management
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Much more!
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Perfect Team returns with new ways to compete online against your friends and the world!
  </strong>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring upgrades that come directly from our amazing community, this year’s Perfect Team is set to take players to all-new heights.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Perfect Team 26 features:
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     New Clubhouse Rewards Shop, to give you the most control of your rewards
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     New league promotion systems and league play incentives
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     Updates to give you more control over your team than ever before
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <i>
     New licensed legendary players
    </i>
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    New content all season long - and beyond! All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.
   </p>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Out of the Park Baseball 26 runs on PC/Mac/Linux and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Major League and Minor League Baseball trademarks and copyrights are used with permission of Major League Baseball. Visit
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Officially Licensed Product of MLB Players, Inc. MLBPA intellectual property rights may not be used without the written consent of MLBPA or MLBPI.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Out of the Park Developments © Copyright 2026. All Rights Reserved
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Bringer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2334170/Metal_Bringer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Metal Bringer
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   ALPHAWING Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   PLAYISM
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   PLAYISM
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 11, 2025
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2334170/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 In this roguelike action-adventure, control humanoid "Labor" and giant "Arms" to uncover the mysteries of the world.
 <br/>
 A young girl named Suria wakes up in a laboratory and finds out that she has been put in cryosleep for 1000 years without her knowledge.
 <br/>
 In order to search for the rest of humanity, she builds Labor with her trusty Buds, and sends them off to investigate...
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Highly Customizable Player Characters and Arms
 </h2>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2334170/extras/01_01.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Build and control android soldiers called "Labor", or have them pilot giant machines called "Arms". Each and every Labor and Arms you build is highly customizable. You can change the color and appearance of their features, or swap out parts to change their fighting styles. Create and fight with the mech of your dreams!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Effortlessly Wipe Out Hordes of Enemies
 </h2>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2334170/extras/02.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Labor can be strengthened by installing different types of apps. App disks can be obtained by defeating enemies, but you lose all installed apps when you fall in battle.
 <br>
  <br>
   However, by analyzing an app's data, you can use it when you customize your next Labor, allowing you to perform better each run until you can freely trample all over your opponents with ease.
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    Obtain Enemy Arms Parts on the Go
   </h2>
   Even the most powerful Arms will eventually wear down, but when that happens, you can use Arms parts left behind by the enemy.
   <br>
    <br>
     What's more, you can analyze the blueprints of powerful Arms parts over the course of the game, which unlocks various customization options. Find out what kind of gear suits you best to build the ideal mech.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Ray Tracing and Ever-Changing Music
     </h2>
     This game uses the same retro art style as Samurai Bringer, but just like Samurai Bringer, it also implements a real time pixel art generating system, and will also feature the newest raytracing technology for beautifully lit environments.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     The music too is made with the newest technology, as it is played in real time and changes according to the situation.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      The Story
     </h2>
     The sky is blue, infinitely high, and infinitely vast...
     <br/>
     Whose words were these again...?
     <br/>
     Ah, I remember... It was about a virtual reality Rudra told me about.
     <br/>
     A fairy tale.
     <br/>
     How many years has it been since humanity took refuge underground?
     <br/>
     No one alive has ever seen a blue sky.
     <br/>
     And now, I'm trapped in the depths, in a small, lifeless room.
     <br/>
     Just how long have I been here...?
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows10 64bit
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        INTEL E3-1230v2 / AMD FX-8350
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GTX960(4G)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows10 64bit
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        INTEL i7-4790K / AMD FX-9590
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GTX1060(6G)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        (Normal Ray Tracing)：NVIDIA RTX 3060
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
