<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<item>
			<title>F1® 24</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2488620/F1_24/</link>
			<description><![CDATA[<style>
						.sys_req_container {
								display: flex;
								flex-wrap: wrap;
								margin-bottom: 10px;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
								flex: 1;
								padding: 10px;
								box-sizing: border-box;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col {
								border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.sys_req_right_col {
								border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
								display: flex;
								justify-content: center;
						}
						.ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
								margin-top: 1px;
						}
						[dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
								border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
						}
						</style>
		<div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
	Title:
 </b>
 F1® 24
 <br/>
 <b>
	Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
	<a>
	 Racing
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Sports
	</a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Developer:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Codemasters
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Publisher:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Electronic Arts
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Franchise:
	</b>
	<a>
	 EA Sports
	</a>
 </div>
 <b>
	Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2488620/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
	About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2488620/extras/F124_Highlights_REVEAL.png"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Be One of the 20 with EA SPORTS™ F1® 24, the official video game of the 2024 FIA Formula One World Championship™. Unleash your champion in pursuit of a legacy-defining F1® Career, the mode’s first major update since 2016. Drive like the greatest and feel at one with the car through the all-new EA SPORTS Dynamic Handling System. Ignite your passion by connecting to your favorite teams and drivers while proving that you have what it takes across new modes and experiences.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	KEY FEATURES
 </strong>
 <br>
	<ul class="bb_ul">
	 <li>
		<strong>
		 Unleash Your Champion
		</strong>
		— Discover the newly innovated Driver Career mode with new gameplay rooted in the sport, or team up with a friend in 2-player career.
		<br>
		 <br/>
		</br>
	 </li>
	 <li>
		<strong>
		 EA SPORTS Dynamic Handling
		</strong>
		— Get to grips with more authentic handling. The latest physics gives you more control over how your personal driving style impacts your car’s performance and race strategy.
		<br>
		 <br/>
		</br>
	 </li>
	 <li>
		Challenge Career is a new, interactive feature in the F1® season that offers episodic competitive play with unique events and challenges, allows community members to compete for high scores, and invites them to influence future content by voting on social media.
		<br/>
		<br/>
	 </li>
	 <li>
		<strong>
		 Ignite your passion with Fanzones.
		</strong>
		These allow you to support your favorite team and driver, collaborate with other fans to achieve goals, raise your profile in the standings, and unlock unique rewards and items.
	 </li>
	</ul>
	<img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2488620/extras/F124_ProductFeatures_REVEAL.png"/>
	<br/>
	<br/>
	This game includes optional in-game purchases of virtual currency that can be used to acquire virtual in-game items.
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
	System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
	<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Windows
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="sys_req_container">
		<div class="sys_req_left_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Minimum:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 10 64-bit Version 21H1 or newer
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				Intel Core i3-2130 | Core i5-9600k (VR) or AMD FX 4300 | Ryzen 5 2600X (VR)
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				8 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				NVIDIA GTX 1060 (6GB) | GTX 1660Ti (VR) | RTX 2060 (RT) // AMD RX 480 (8GB) | RX 590 (VR) | 6700XT (RT) // Intel Arc A380 (VR/RT)
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 DirectX:
				</strong>
				Version 12
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Network:
				</strong>
				Broadband Internet connection
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				100 GB available space
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Sound Card:
				</strong>
				Direct X Compatible
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 VR Support:
				</strong>
				Steam VR. Keyboard and mouse required
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Additional Notes:
				</strong>
				GPU must support D3D_SHADER_MODEL_6_6.
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
		<div class="sys_req_right_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Recommended:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 10 64-bit Version 21H1 or newer
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				Intel Core i5-9600k or AMD Ryzen 5 2600X
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				16 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				NVIDIA RTX 2070 (+VR) | RTX 3070 (RT) // AMD RX 6600XT | RX 6700XT (VR) | RX 6800 (RT) // Intel Arc A580 (VR/RT)
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 DirectX:
				</strong>
				Version 12
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Network:
				</strong>
				Broadband Internet connection
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				100 GB available space
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Sound Card:
				</strong>
				Direct X Compatible
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 VR Support:
				</strong>
				Steam VR. Keyboard and mouse required
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Additional Notes:
				</strong>
				GPU must support D3D_SHADER_MODEL_6_6.
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
	 </div>
	</div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Selaco</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1592280/Selaco/</link>
			<description><![CDATA[<style>
						.sys_req_container {
								display: flex;
								flex-wrap: wrap;
								margin-bottom: 10px;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
								flex: 1;
								padding: 10px;
								box-sizing: border-box;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col {
								border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.sys_req_right_col {
								border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
								display: flex;
								justify-content: center;
						}
						.ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
								margin-top: 1px;
						}
						[dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
								border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
						}
						</style>
		<div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
	Title:
 </b>
 Selaco
 <br/>
 <b>
	Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
	<a>
	 Action
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Adventure
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Early Access
	</a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Developer:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Altered Orbit Studios
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Publisher:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Altered Orbit Studios
	</a>
 </div>
 <b>
	Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
 <b>
	Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1592280/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
	About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1592280/extras/INFO.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Selaco is a brand new original shooter running on GZDoom, featuring thrilling action set pieces, destructibility, smart AI and a fleshed out story taking place within an immersive game world. It draws inspiration heavily from F.E.A.R. in terms of action set pieces, while mixing traditional retro-FPS elements from QUAKE and DOOM, along with some more modern features. Together with professional artists who work in the industry, several having worked on successful throwback FPS games in the past, Selaco is a fully fleshed out world full of character, action, and mystery.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1592280/extras/STORY.png"/>
 <br/>
 The story takes place during a violent invasion of Selaco, the underground facility that's home to the surviving refugees after the fall of Earth. You play as Dawn, an ACE Security Captain who, with her recent promotion and high level security clearances, is digging deep into the truth behind Selaco's murky history. Before she can finish her investigation, Selaco is rocked by explosions and armed invaders. While Selaco may take place in a large-scale conflict, much of it will be the personal story of Dawn, the center-piece of the game.
 <br>
	<br>
	 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1592280/extras/FEATURES.gif"/>
	 <br>
		<ul class="bb_ul">
		 <li>
			A lengthy story-driven campaign
		 </li>
		</ul>
		Selaco is a story-driven experience, and we don't say that lightly. A dedicated writer has been brought on board to assist with creating an engaging and believable sci-fi story and world.
		<br>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Intense Action set pieces
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 Turn the entire world into confetti with the destructive power of your weapons. Every single bullet will react properly with any materials or objects you hit. Our artists have created many different variations for each (voxel)object to ensure that the aftermath of each encounter is palpable. That once lavish office space now nothing but a pile of rubble with broken paintings, smashed tables, screen, chairs, smoke, and chunks of debris.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Custom AI
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 With our FEAR influence, writing proper AI was a goal from the get go. The enemy is fully aware of each other's presence and work together to take you down. They will keep their distance if you apply constant pressure on them, will rush you if you hide or run out of bullets, toss grenades if you use the same cover for too long, and much more. Hundreds of custom lines have been written and acted out, providing hints to the player about their current plans and tactics.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Full soundtrack
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 Selaco is accompanied by a full length original soundtrack composed by an experienced musician who has worked on many games in the past.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Professional voice-acting.
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 To help immerse players in the story and atmosphere of Selaco, professional voice actors have been brought on board. Dawn will be voiced by the incredibly talented Melissa Medina, with other casting choices revealed at a later date.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Extra Gamemodes
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 Completing levels allows you to replay that level in Incursion Mode, an expanded version of that map where your skills will be tested against a near endless onslaught of enemies. Win incursion maps to gain bonuses to aid you throughout the campaign. New exclusive Incursion Levels and new mutators will also be unlocked as the campaign progresses.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1592280/extras/modding.gif"/>
		 <br/>
		 <ul class="bb_ul">
			<li>
			 Full open-source modding support
			</li>
		 </ul>
		 Mod it till it breaks! Create new campaign experiences, modify or create your own content, port your favorite GZDoom mods. Anything goes!
		</br>
	 </br>
	</br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
	Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
	The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
	<i>
	 Depictions of violence and Gore
	 <br/>
	 Contains profanity
	</i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
	System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
	<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Windows
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
		<div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
		 <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
			<div class="sys_req_container">
			 <div class="sys_req_note">
				<strong>
				 *
				</strong>
				Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
			 </div>
			</div>
		 </div>
		</div>
	 </div>
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Linux
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
		<div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
		 <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
			<div class="sys_req_container">
			</div>
		 </div>
		</div>
	 </div>
	</div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mutant Football League 2</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1657320/Mutant_Football_League_2/</link>
			<description><![CDATA[<style>
						.sys_req_container {
								display: flex;
								flex-wrap: wrap;
								margin-bottom: 10px;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
								flex: 1;
								padding: 10px;
								box-sizing: border-box;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col {
								border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.sys_req_right_col {
								border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
								display: flex;
								justify-content: center;
						}
						.ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
								margin-top: 1px;
						}
						[dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
								border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
						}
						</style>
		<div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
	Title:
 </b>
 Mutant Football League 2
 <br/>
 <b>
	Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
	<a>
	 Action
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Casual
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Indie
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Sports
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Early Access
	</a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Developer:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Digital Dreams Entertainment
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Publisher:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Digital Dreams Entertainment
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Franchise:
	</b>
	<a>
	 Mutant Football League
	</a>
 </div>
 <b>
	Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
 <b>
	Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1657320/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
	About This Game
 </h2>
 <strong>
	Welcome to the MFL!
 </strong>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	Mutant Football League 2
 </strong>
 , is an arcade style football game that is a rollercoaster ride of thrills, strategy, and unbridled action brought to you by the designer/creator of the original Sega Genesis classic
 <strong>
	Mutant League Football
 </strong>
 and
 <strong>
	Mutant League Hockey
 </strong>
 .
 <strong>
	MFL2
 </strong>
 delivers deep strategic 8-on-8 gameplay, with bone-shattering hits and maniacal mutants that parody your favorite players.
 <br/>
 Prepare yourself for the most outrageously brutal football you’ll ever experience. Enter diabolical arenas teeming with deadly traps that set the stage for mayhem and destruction. Victory can be achieved by achieving the highest score or obliterating your opponents, aided using special "
 <i>
	Dirty Tricks
 </i>
 " plays that will leave your foes reeling and bleeding. Get ready to outwit, cheat, and decimate your way to victory.
 <br/>
 Whether you're a die-hard sports enthusiast or a casual gamer seeking exciting entertainment,
 <strong>
	MFL2
 </strong>
 promises an experience filled with unpredictable mayhem that will leave you breathless.
 <br/>
 Get ready to unleash your inner mutant on the field of mayhem!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
	<strong>
	 MFL2 Features
	</strong>
 </h2>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
	Blood and Guts
 </h2>
 Brace yourself for exploding body parts, comically horrific deaths, and blood splatters that paint the field red in a spectacle of carnage that distinguishes MFL2 from conventional sports games. Whether it's a player getting blitzed by a rampaging monster or succumbing to a trap-laden end zone, every game is a symphony of unpredictable mayhem. In the
 <strong>
	MFL
 </strong>
 , you have two paths to triumph: scoring the most points in classic football fashion or racking up a body count that leaves the opposition in tatters, causing them to forfeit.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
	Multiplayer Mayhem
 </h2>
 Two-player online mayhem. The rowdiest, dirtiest, most insane online Multiplayer you’ll ever experience with across-the-board graphical and technical improvements for a deeper, more vibrant mutated world to battle in. Extensive leaderboards and popularity rankings let everyone in the league know whose ruling the day.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
	Over 40 Mutated MFL Teams
 </h2>
 Choose from over 40 MFL teams made up of maniacal mutants including wisecracking Skeletal Deadheads, Armored Bruiserbots, Mutated Humans, and Monstrous Orcs among other ghoulishly fiendish species.
 <br>
	<ul class="bb_ul">
	 <li>
		32 pro-league teams like the Karcass City Creeps, Killadelphia Evils, and Blitzburgh Steelheads. Includes updated team rosters and player ratings for every new season.
		<br/>
	 </li>
	 <li>
		16 minor league teams like the Orcs of Hazards and Tokyo Terminators.
		<br/>
	 </li>
	 <li>
		Create your own outlandish MFL team!
	 </li>
	</ul>
	<h2 class="bb_tag">
	 Player Personalization and Skins
	</h2>
	Your players will evolve before your very eyes as they are upgraded, sporting larger armor and unlocking mind-blowing levels of customization to enhance their visual style and unleash their unique brand of badassery.
	<br>
	 <ul class="bb_ul">
		<li>
		 Different armor sets based on players XP level
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Gross facial mutations and deformations
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Stand out from the crowd with outrageous player skins
		</li>
	 </ul>
	 <h2 class="bb_tag">
		Dynasty Supreme
	 </h2>
	 MFL’s franchise mode. It is a single-player experience where you become the coach and GM of your favorite Mutant Football League team or create your own unique team. You’ll start in the minor league and claw and fight your way into the pro league, turning a group of scrub and rookie players into legendary champions. Win multiple Mayhem Bowls over several seasons to become the league’s next dynasty.
	 <br/>
	 Dynasty Supreme features include:
	 <br/>
	 <ul class="bb_ul">
		<li>
		 Create your own Dynasty Team
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Multiple Seasons
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Player Drafts
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 2 leagues (minor and pro)
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Player Cards (unlock player trades and free agents)
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Hilarious and entertaining player management
		</li>
	 </ul>
	 <h2 class="bb_tag">
		MFL Player Cards
	 </h2>
	 Player Cards unlock free agents and player trades, add historic hall of maim legends, and gain the power to replace weaker players with stronger ones on your team's roster, instantly boosting their overall effectiveness on the field.
	 <br/>
	 <ul class="bb_ul">
		<li>
		 Current
		 <strong>
			MFL
		 </strong>
		 Player (5 grades of cards)
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Rookie class
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Historic Players from the greatest MFL ever
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Historic Legends
		</li>
	 </ul>
	 <h2 class="bb_tag">
		Dirty Tricks
	 </h2>
	 Each team comes equipped with its own arsenal of twisted special plays known as
	 <i>
		Dirty Tricks
	 </i>
	 .
	 <i>
		Dirty Tricks
	 </i>
	 are the game-changers that can turn the tide of any match.
	 <br/>
	 <ul class="bb_ul">
		<li>
		 Bribe a ref play and turn the tables with a questionable call that puts the odds back in your favor.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Throw a bomb to take out the opposing team's All-Star defensive back.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Rile up the home crowd into a murderous frenzy, turning the stadium into a cauldron of hostility.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Go all-in with Shotguns and Chainsaws, equipping your players with deadly weapons to inflict maximum carnage against the unsuspecting competition while you make a break for the end zone.
		</li>
	 </ul>
	 Mastering when and how to use your Dirty Tricks becomes a strategic gamble, as you outwit and outmaneuver your opponents with diabolical flair.
	 <h2 class="bb_tag">
		The Killing Fields
	 </h2>
	 In the
	 <strong>
		Mutant Football League
	 </strong>
	 , each stadium is a battlefield with its own unique set of deadly traps and hazards.
	 <br/>
	 <ul class="bb_ul">
		<li>
		 As you sprint towards the end zone, be wary of buzz saws that can slice through mutants like a hot knife through butter.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Watch your step to avoid land mines that could turn a promising play into a fiery disaster.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Mutant worms await the unsuspecting, ready-to-swallow players whole.
		 <br/>
		</li>
		<li>
		 Fire geysers erupt unpredictably, turning the field into a hellish landscape.
		</li>
	 </ul>
	 These hazards aren't just obstacles; they're strategic elements that can be used to your advantage adding another layer of depth and strategy to the game.
	</br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
	Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
	The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
	<i>
	 Mutant Football League 2 and its addons features violence, blood and gore (including exploding body parts, comically horrific deaths, and blood splatters) and some strong language.
	</i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
	System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
	<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Windows
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="sys_req_container">
		<div class="sys_req_left_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Minimum:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 10
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				Intel Core i3-6100 3.7GHz
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				8 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				Nvidia 1060
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				10 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
		<div class="sys_req_right_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Recommended:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 11
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				Ryzen 5 5700X
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				16 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				Nvidia RTX 2060
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				10 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
	 </div>
	</div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>PANICORE</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695940/PANICORE/</link>
			<description><![CDATA[<style>
						.sys_req_container {
								display: flex;
								flex-wrap: wrap;
								margin-bottom: 10px;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
								flex: 1;
								padding: 10px;
								box-sizing: border-box;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col {
								border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.sys_req_right_col {
								border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
								display: flex;
								justify-content: center;
						}
						.ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
								margin-top: 1px;
						}
						[dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
								border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
						}
						</style>
		<div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
	Title:
 </b>
 PANICORE
 <br/>
 <b>
	Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
	<a>
	 Action
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Adventure
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Indie
	</a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Developer:
	</b>
	<a>
	 ZTEK Studio
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Publisher:
	</b>
	<a>
	 ZTEK Studio
	</a>
 </div>
 <b>
	Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2695940/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
	About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2695940/extras/finditems.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2695940/extras/opening.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2695940/extras/findnotes.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 In
 <strong>
	PANICORE
 </strong>
 , players take on the role of urban explorers drawn to dangerously abandoned places. For these people, it is exciting to discover lost arts, lost treasures and abandoned buildings, schools and other abandoned places.
 <br>
	<br>
	 But when they discover a spooky place - one that even the authorities advise against visiting - their adventures take a terrifying turn. The explorers are determined to learn the dark secrets of the abandoned place, so they ignore the warnings and follow their curiosity into its depths.
	 <br>
		<br>
		 But an unforeseen turn of events quickly puts a stop to their exploration. They unexpectedly find themselves trapped in the abandoned building, with unknown forces blocking their way out. The explorers must work together to endure the horrors within and find a way out before it is too late, as fear sets in and they realize they are not alone.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 Players must use all their bravery to solve puzzles, navigate the dangerous corridors and outwit the monster that wants to trap them in its evil clutches while time is of the essence.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <strong>
			Multiple Escape Routes:
		 </strong>
		 Confront a challenge with multiple distinct escape routes.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <strong>
			Dynamic Co-op Gameplay:
		 </strong>
		 Team up with friends in intense cooperative gameplay. Try to escape alone or together.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <strong>
			Relentless Pursuit:
		 </strong>
		 Face a relentless AI-driven monster that can hear your every step.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <strong>
			Immersive Hide-and-Seek:
		 </strong>
		 Utilize your surroundings for survival. Hide in cabinets, under tables, and in the shadows to outsmart the lurking terror. Every decision could mean the difference between life and a gruesome demise.
		 <br/>
		 <br/>
		 <strong>
			Find Items and Escape:
		 </strong>
		 To escape you have to find the right items that are distributed around the location and use them at the right place. Can you make it before it gets you?
		</br>
	 </br>
	</br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
	System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
	<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Windows
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="sys_req_container">
		<div class="sys_req_left_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Minimum:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 10 (64 Bit)
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				AMD Ryzen 3 1200 ／ Intel Core i5-7500
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				8 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				AMD Radeon RX 470 with 4GB VRAM ／ NVIDIA GeForce GTX 960 with 4GB VRAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 DirectX:
				</strong>
				Version 11
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Network:
				</strong>
				Broadband Internet connection
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				13 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
		<div class="sys_req_right_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Recommended:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				Windows 10 (64 bit)
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				AMD Ryzen 5 3600 ／ Intel Core i7 8700
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				16 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				AMD Radeon RX 5700／ NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1070
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 DirectX:
				</strong>
				Version 12
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Network:
				</strong>
				Broadband Internet connection
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				13 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
	 </div>
	</div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mysterious Voyage:Set sail</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2983380/Mysterious_VoyageSet_sail/</link>
			<description><![CDATA[<style>
						.sys_req_container {
								display: flex;
								flex-wrap: wrap;
								margin-bottom: 10px;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
								flex: 1;
								padding: 10px;
								box-sizing: border-box;
						}
						.sys_req_left_col {
								border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.sys_req_right_col {
								border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
						}
						.ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
								display: flex;
								justify-content: center;
						}
						.ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
								margin-top: 1px;
						}
						[dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
								border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
						}
						</style>
		<div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
	Title:
 </b>
 Mysterious Voyage:Set sail
 <br/>
 <b>
	Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
	<a>
	 Action
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Adventure
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Casual
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Indie
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 RPG
	</a>
	,
	<a>
	 Free to Play
	</a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Developer:
	</b>
	<a>
	 泽渔
	</a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
	<b>
	 Publisher:
	</b>
	<a>
	 BD Games
	</a>
 </div>
 <b>
	Release Date:
 </b>
 May 31, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2983380/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
	About This Game
 </h2>
 <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
	<img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/dss.png"/>
 </a>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	The difference between the prologue and the official version:
	<br/>
	The prologue unlocks the entire sea map.
	<br/>
	Maps: 1.5 in the prologue, at least 3 in the official version (estimated to be 70+ islands).
	<br>
	 Ships: 4 in the prologue, 10+ in the official version.
	 <br>
		Hero crew: 136 in the prologue, 200+ in the official version.
		<br>
		 Products/props: 104 types in the prologue, 192+ types expected in the official version.
		 <br>
			Missions/plots: The official version will add more missions/plots.
			<br/>
			Archive: Please note that the official version cannot inherit the archive progress of the prologue!
			<br/>
			The game system may change in the official version!
		 </br>
		</br>
	 </br>
	</br>
 </strong>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/1y.png"/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/1z.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	Welcome to a seafaring world full of adventure and wonder!
	<br/>
	Here you are free to pilot your ship and explore the endless oceans in search of hidden islands and treasures!
	<br/>
	You can follow the clues of treasure maps, solve ancient puzzles, and discover lost civilizations and riches!
	<br/>
	You can also engage in fierce sea battles with pirates, defeating them and capturing their loot!
	<br/>
	You can also trade between islands, acquire islands, and build your own trade network!
 </strong>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/2y.png"/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/2z.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	This is a vast sea full of opportunities and challenges.
	<br/>
	You'll need to build your own fleet, travel between ports, kill pirates or plunder merchant ships.
	<br/>
	Fortunately, there are also many friendly merchants and ports here.
	<br/>
	You can trade with them and buy or sell various items and information.
	<br/>
	You can trade the treasures you find at sea or on the island for gold or equipment.
 </strong>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/3y.png"/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2983380/extras/3z.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <strong>
	Here, you can be both the bounty hunter and the hunted.
	<br/>
	If you want to fight for justice, you can accept bounty missions issued by the Navy and hunt down those notorious pirate leaders.
	<br/>
	If you want to fight for freedom, you can challenge the navy and other forces to become the most powerful pirate king.
	<br/>
	But no matter what, when you rise to fame, you will be targeted!
	<br/>
	Only death will free you from everyone!
 </strong>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
	System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
	<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
	 <center>
		<h3>
		 Windows
		</h3>
	 </center>
	 <div class="sys_req_container">
		<div class="sys_req_left_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Minimum:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				win7
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				I5 - 10400
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				4 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				RTX 1060
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				2 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
		<div class="sys_req_right_col">
		 <ul>
			<strong>
			 Recommended:
			</strong>
			<br/>
			<ul class="bb_ul">
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 OS:
				</strong>
				win10
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Processor:
				</strong>
				I5 - 10400
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Memory:
				</strong>
				8 GB RAM
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Graphics:
				</strong>
				RTX 2060
				<br/>
			 </li>
			 <li>
				<strong>
				 Storage:
				</strong>
				4 GB available space
			 </li>
			</ul>
		 </ul>
		</div>
	 </div>
	</div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
