<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Natsu no Sagashimono ~What We Found That Summer~</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2997980/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_What_We_Found_That_Summer/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Natsu no Sagashimono ~What We Found That Summer~
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Casual
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   pekoge-sutagio
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Kagura Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Kagura Games
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 27, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2997980/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png"/>
 </a>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_1_EN.png"/>
 <br/>
 Summer vacation is finally here! Our story follows Natsu, a timid, effeminate young man who embarks on a family trip to the countryside to visit his aunt Misaki. But just as everyone's getting settled in, a mix-up at his father's workplace forces Natsu's parents to hop right back in the car and drive home, leaving him to spend the remainder of his summer break out in the sticks. Misaki is more than happy to take him in, of course, and so begins a peaceful, relaxing few weeks where absolutely nothing out of the ordinary threatens to disturb his tranquil everyday routine... Bwahahaha, as if!
 <br/>
 <br>
  It isn't long before a self-proclaimed magical girl named Chitose worms her way into Natsu's life, but her boisterous intrusion is the least of his problems. An eccentric candy seller, an insecure wanna-be teacher, a pink-haired loudmouth... Not to mention, his aunt's strange behavior around the topic of the outdoors. Surrounded by misfits, it soon becomes apparent that Natsu's real summer homework is to learn more about the women around him and help them with their problems. And yet, with only 30 days until his parents pick him up, is this one assignment he's fated to flunk, or will he pass with flying colors?
  <br>
   <br>
    <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_2_EN.png"/>
    <br>
     Have a blast fishing, catching bugs, taking in the sights, and collecting other bits and bobs as you go around talking to the locals. Get insight into not just the town, but the girls that live there as you work toward the conclusion of their individual stories. Just make sure to keep an eye on that calendar! It may seem like you have all the time in the world, but if you aren't careful, summer will pass by in the blink of an eye. Make the most out of every day and work hard to make this the best summer vacation ever!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_3_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_01_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_02_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_03_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_05_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2997980/extras/Natsu_no_Sagashimono_~What_We_Found_That_Summer~_Description_4_EN.png"/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      A Plethora of Collectibles
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Obtain a gaggle of items, including capsule toys, bugs, and fish! You can even give them to the girls and impress them with your collecting abilities!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Chit-Chat with the Townsfolk
     </strong>
     <br/>
     This colorful cast of characters always has something to say! Depending on where they are, what time of day it is, and where you are in the story, they'll all have something interesting to divulge. Really get to know them over your summer break!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Pixel Goodness
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Everything you see, from the gorgeous scenery to the girls' adorable smiles, is hand-drawn, original pixel art. It's nostalgic and full of charm... A perfect fit for a summer tale.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_note">
     <strong>
      *
     </strong>
     Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS *:
        </strong>
        Windows® 8/8.1/10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core2 Duo or better
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        DirectX 9/OpenGL 4.1 capable GPU
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 9.0
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        1 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        1280x768 or better Display. Lag may occur from loading menus or maps. Turn off other programs before running the game.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS *:
        </strong>
        Windows 11/10/8
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        2+ GHz Processor
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        OpenGL ES 2.0 hardware driver support required for WebGL acceleration. (AMD Catalyst 10.9, nVidia 358.50)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 9.0
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        4 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        1280x768 or better Display. Lag may occur from loading menus or maps. Turn off other programs before running the game.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isle of Swaps</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2294160/Isle_of_Swaps/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Isle of Swaps
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Fuzz Force
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Fuzz Force
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Fuzz Force
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 27, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2294160/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 The worldwide phenomenon of Critters has the world in its grip and the newest collectable, the Critter Trading Card Game, has just been released!
 <br/>
 Dina is Critter mad and has been begging her parents for a week to get her some cards. Yesterday they relented and have bought her a starter deck and a lovely binder to keep them in but it's not enough, she wants all the Critter Cards.
 <br/>
 It's finally lunch time and everyone rushes out to play some more Critter Challenges.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2294160/extras/Header_BattleGif.gif"/>
 <br>
  It's Critter Combat! Build up energy with weaker Skill cards and spend it to play stronger cards. With each Critter having varied stats, abilities, Weakness and Resistances, making a varied team is key. You don't want your whole team to be weak to Blaze attacks do you?
  <br>
   But Skill cards can only be used by Critters of the same element, so maybe using multiple Critters of the same type is a good strategy? You wouldn't want your Aqua Critter to be defeated and then not be able to use your Aqua Skill Cards.
   <br>
    <br>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2294160/extras/Header_DeckbuildingGif.gif"/>
     <br/>
     Build your deck by swapping with the characters you beat in battle. Got some doubles? Swap as many times as you like and are able, no limits here. Any cards are added to your binder to change up your Battle Deck at any time. Equip Stickers for passive bonuses but be aware that using rarer Critters limits how many Stickers you can use. Balance your deck between Critters, Skills and Stickers to claim victory!
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2294160/extras/Header_ChallengesGif.gif"/>
     <br/>
     Proceed through Challenges by picking one of 3 map cards but if you're feeling brave, unflipped cards award money that can be used to buy Booster Packs. A victory in a Challenge adds the cards in your battle deck to your permanent Master Binder, letting you customise the starting Critter in future runs. Create decks from the Master Binder to take on the Critter Championship and put your deckbuilding to the test. And the next Challenge run? Totally different. With 6 different areas that can appear in any order, you never know what you'll run into next time.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Game Features
     </h2>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      <li>
       A number of artists have illustrated hundreds of cards to collect and store lovingly in your binder
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       A whole bunch of Skill cards and passive ability Stickers to come up with an array of strategies.
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Swap with characters you beat to build your deck instead of 'pick 1 of 3 cards'. Swap those dupes!
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Each run is made up from 3 of the 6 Areas and can be played in any order, doing acts in the same order is pretty boring, right?
       <br/>
      </li>
      <li>
       Collect cards between runs in the Master Binder and use Master Decks to take on the toughest fights in the Critter Championship.
      </li>
     </ul>
     <br/>
     This is a game inspired by a single dev's experience of when the pokemon trading card game took over school playgrounds, swapping every breaktime and having illustrated cardboard consume his life.
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_full">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        2.0 Ghz
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        2 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        512 Mb Video Memory
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        600 MB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REYNATIS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738750/REYNATIS/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 REYNATIS
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   FURYU Corporation
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   NIS America, Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 27, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2738750/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Liberate your world
 </h2>
 <br/>
 REYNATIS is a full-blown action-packed magical RPG in which two people with different perspectives fight for their ideals in a realistic recreation of modern-day Shibuya, Tokyo.
 <br/>
 <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/1.gif"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  ■World/Story
 </h2>
 The year is 2024. In Shibuya, Tokyo, the Criminal Magic Response Act has issued an order barring citizens from going out at night. However, it was quickly disregarded, and few enforce it.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Marin Kirizumi is a wizard who grew up oppressed by others due to his magic. “If you become the strongest, you'll be set free." Following those words left by his father, he arrives in Shibuya at night.
 <br>
  <br>
   When Sari Nishijima discovered her magic, she decided to use her powers to maintain order. She follows her own sense of justice to protect Shibuya from forces with dangerous ideals and illegal drugs that turn people into monsters.
   <br>
    <br>
     Marin, who seeks liberation. Sari, who treats the oppression of wizards as justice. The story of REYNATIS begins when the two meet in Shibuya, a place where cultures and ideas mix.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ■Battle
     </h2>
     By properly utilizing Suppressed and Liberated states, anyone can easily execute show-stopping actions.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     In Suppressed Mode, you are unable to attack, but you can avoid any enemy attacks with the press of a single button.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     In Liberated Mode, you can go all out with your attacks, but you will be unable to defend, so timing is essential.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Players can instantly switch between up to three different characters in the middle of battle. Each character comes with their own unique abilities. Pick your characters depending on the situation to gain the upper hand!
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/2.gif"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ■Exploration
     </h2>
     The real city of Shibuya has been painstakingly recreated in REYNATIS. Walk around the city to find everything from famous landmarks such as SHIBUYA109 to hole-in-the-wall joints that only the savviest will know.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     While in Suppressed Mode, your identity and actions are concealed. As long as people don’t find out you’re a wizard, you can talk with normal civilians. During these conversations, you may receive exploration tips, as well as new quests.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     In Liberated Mode, you can use your magic to explore and move more quickly. However, there's a chance civilians will report you to the M.E.A., who will come after you in full force.
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ■Another
     </h2>
     Pockets of Shibuya contain Fog, gateways to an alternate magical world called Another that only wizards can access.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     This clandestine realm is managed by the anti-government organization known as the Guild. Those who cannot wield magic are unable to enter, and monsters run rampant due to the magic in the air. The expanse of Another contains not only forests and wilderness, but things resembling factories and museums, as well. What lies in its deepest recesses remains unknown.
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/3.gif"/>
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      ■Lastly
     </h2>
     When Marin and Sari’s paths cross, a darkness that will transform the world descends.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Wishlist REYNATIS today! We hope you'll look forward to the release!
     <br/>
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/4.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Scenario / Kazushige Nojima
     <br/>
     Music / Yoko Shimomura
     <br/>
     Character Design / Yasutaka Kaburagi
     <br/>
     Creative Producer / TAKUMI
     <h2 class="bb_tag">
      Steam Version Features
     </h2>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      4K Resolution and High Frame Rate
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Experience REYNATIS in 4K resolution and smooth high frame rates up to 120fps. Enjoy every scene with enhanced clarity and precision.
     <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/Action4.jpg"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Keyboard and Mouse Control Support
     </strong>
     <br/>
     Customize your playstyle with full keyboard and mouse controls, offering greater flexibility and precision in combat and exploration.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      Selected Graphics Options
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <p class="bb_paragraph">
      Tailor your visual experience with a variety of graphics settings, ensuring the game runs optimally on your hardware.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      <strong>
       Playable on Steam Deck
      </strong>
      <br/>
      Take your Shibuya action-packed experience on the go! REYNATIS is compatible with Steam Deck, delivering a smooth gaming experience wherever you are.
      <br/>
      <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2738750/extras/Steamdeck1crop.jpg"/>
     </p>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i5-4460 or above, AMD FX-6300 or above
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GeForce GTX 760 (2GB) / AMD Radeon R7 260x (2GB) or above
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        12 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i7-3770 or above, AMD FX-9590 or above
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 (6GB) / AMD Radeon RX 480 (8GB) or above
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        12 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REYNATIS Ultimate Edition (Launch)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/sub/1112795/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    Informații despre dezvoltator indisponibile.
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About the Game
 </h2>
 <p>
  Maximize your enjoyment of REYNATIS with the limited-time Ultimate Edition! This special launch edition includes an increased early purchase discount of 25%, up from the usual 10%. Plus, you'll receive the following items:
  <br/>
  - Soundtrack
  <br/>
  - Mini Art Book
  <br/>
  <br/>
  You will also enjoy all the items included in the standard Ultimate Edition:
  <br/>
  - REYNATIS (Base game)
  <br/>
  - Wizard's Gift α
  <br/>
  - Wizard's Gift β
  <br/>
  - Ultimate Wizard Items
  <br>
   - Clear Bonus Early Unlock DLC
   <br>
    - "Another" Color Costumes
    <br>
     - Art Book
     <br>
      <br>
       Get this limited-time Ultimate Edition to take your experience in the enchanting world of REYNATIS to greater heights!
      </br>
     </br>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.Cerințe de sistem indisponibile.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwarven Realms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2015240/Dwarven_Realms/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Dwarven Realms
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Indie
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Crater Studios
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Crater Studios
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Sep 27, 2024
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Dec 16, 2022
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2015240/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <strong>
   Dwarven Realms
  </strong>
  is an innovative blend of classic ARPG depth and intense mob-slaying action, offering a fresh take on the genre. Built by a passionate indie team, this action-packed ARPG delivers complex systems inspired by traditional ARPGs, combined with the sheer mob density of rogue-lite survivor games.
 </p>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Key Features:
 </h2>
 <ul class="bb_ul">
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <strong>
     Deep Customization
    </strong>
    : Master hundreds of unique skills, abilities, and off-hand options to create your ultimate build. Every character has multiple paths to power, offering endless replayability.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <strong>
     High-Intensity Combat
    </strong>
    : Fight through colossal hordes of enemies, using explosive abilities and strategic positioning to survive overwhelming odds.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <strong>
     Epic Loot & Crafting
    </strong>
    : Find and craft powerful gear, upgrade your weapons, and fine-tune your build to dominate the battlefield.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <strong>
     Seasonal Content & Challenges
    </strong>
    : Join the race for seasonal leaderboards, test your skills in chaotic ruptures, and unlock exclusive rewards.
   </p>
  </li>
  <li>
   <p class="bb_paragraph">
    <strong>
     Community-Driven
    </strong>
    : Our small, dedicated team has been building this game alongside a passionate community. We value player feedback and continuously refine the experience based on it.
   </p>
  </li>
 </ul>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  With fast-paced gameplay, evolving content, and robust customization,
  <i>
   Dwarven Realms
  </i>
  is the perfect blend of action and strategy. Whether you're new to ARPGs or a veteran, there's always something new to discover in the ever-expanding Dwarven Realms.
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  Join us in the ultimate quest for glory and survival!
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2015240/extras/Skill-Tree-K-and-Cards-GIF.gif"/>
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2015240/extras/imbue.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2015240/extras/archer_2.gif"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2015240/extras/items-steam-banner.png"/>
 </p>
 <p class="bb_paragraph">
  <img class="bb_img" src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/2015240/extras/mining-steam-banner.png"/>
 </p>
</div>
Descrierea conținutului pentru adulți indisponibilă.
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        64-bit Windows
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel CPU Core i3-2120 (3.3 GHz) / AMD CPU FX-6300 (3.5 GHz)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        Nvidia GeForce GTX 760 (2 GB) / AMD Radeon HD 7850 (2 GB)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        10 GB available space
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
