<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Sins of a Solar Empire II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1575940/Sins_of_a_Solar_Empire_II/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Sins of a Solar Empire II
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Simulation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Ironclad Games Corporation
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Stardock Entertainment
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Stardock Entertainment
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Stardock
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Sins of a Solar Empire
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Aug 15, 2024
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1575940/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Sins of a Solar Empire II is the sequel to the critically acclaimed space strategy game that seamlessly blends real-time battle tactics with the depth of 4X. As both emperor and battle commander you must lead one of six playable factions to victory against the threat of extinction!
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Real-time Tactics meets 4X Depth
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1575940/extras/Advent_orbital.gif"/>
 <br/>
 There are no turns. There is no battle mode. There is no strategic mode. It's all one mode and it's all in real-time.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Instantly zoom in to control tactical engagements where every missile, turret, and ship is fully simulated and an important part of the battle. Instantly zoom back out to manage your empire where every asteroid, moon, and planet orbits its parent in a slowly evolving strategic landscape.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Unparalleled Gameplay Experiences
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1575940/extras/Space_Battle.gif"/>
 <br/>
 Sins of a Solar Empire II delivers sprawling empires, huge fleets, and completely new and exciting gameplay moments that can only be found in Sins II.
 <br>
  <br>
   <ul class="bb_ul">
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Surprise:
     </strong>
     Build a secondary fleet on a rogue asteroid and launch a devastating surprise attack when its orbit brings it behind the enemy's back line.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Body Block:
     </strong>
     Stall an enemy's home planet bombardment by using your massive titan to body block swarms of missiles attempting to knock out your starbase and its critical planetary shield.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Screen:
     </strong>
     Advance a screen of point defense flak frigates to protect your fragile long-range cruisers by intercepting incoming bombers and missiles.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Swarm:
     </strong>
     Maneuver your faster moving ships to pick apart unescorted larger ships. Their powerful but slow-moving turrets simply can't track your agile strike force.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Influencer:
     </strong>
     Influence a hostile expansionist Minor Faction to secure your border while reserving enough Influence to win an auction for a powerful item to install on your best capital ship.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      The Backstab:
     </strong>
     Protect yourself from a backstab by establishing a time locked alliance. But pay attention to the time - your “ally” may move his fleet to your doorstep just as the lock expires!
    </li>
   </ul>
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    Features
   </h2>
   <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1575940/extras/Kol_CloseUp.gif"/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    A Dynamic Galaxy:
   </strong>
   Planets orbit their stars in real-time causing the galaxy's structure to slowly change, creating new battle fronts and new opportunities. Players can view the state of the galaxy up to an hour in the future to prepare their strategies.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    3 Unique Races:
   </strong>
   It's War Year 35 and the emergent TEC, alien Vasari, and deviant Advent have been forced to adapt and evolve to survive.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <ul class="bb_ul">
    <li>
     <strong>
      TEC:
     </strong>
     The inhabitants of this region of the galaxy, the TEC are humans who have joined together as the Trader Emergency Coalition to combat the alien Vasari empire. They rely heavily on trade to support their industrial base and augment resource income.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      Vasari:
     </strong>
     Ten thousand years ago, the Vasari Empire once ruled over hundreds of planets and dozens of sentient species. Now on the run from an unknown enemy they use their mastery of phase space to conquer and acquire resources to continue their exodus.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      Advent:
     </strong>
     A civilization of humans who were forcibly outcast by the Traders over a thousand years ago, the deviant Advent have returned with technologically amplified psionics and the power of the Unity - a devastating expression of their collective will.
    </li>
   </ul>
   <br/>
   Each race features unique starting conditions, gameplay mechanics, units, abilities, items, and technologies. Their game changing new Empire Systems add a whole new level of strategic capabilities:
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <ul class="bb_ul">
    <li>
     <strong>
      TEC Trade:
     </strong>
     The new TEC trade system enables them to dynamically adapt their economy by adjusting the allocation of traded resources on demand.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      Vasari Phase Resonance:
     </strong>
     Strategically placed structures collect Phase Resonance allowing the Vasari to customize their global phase mastery effects.
     <br/>
    </li>
    <li>
     <strong>
      Advent Unity:
     </strong>
     Enables the Advent to harness the collective will of their population, unlocking the full potential of the Unity's global abilities.
    </li>
   </ul>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    6 Playable Factions:
   </strong>
   The parent races are further differentiated by unique sub-factions each with their own unique features and play styles that reflect their motivations and goals. For example, the TEC: Primacy is a xenophobic 'human first' empire focused on aggression and the Vasari: Exodus is willing to destroy planets to fuel their mobile empire.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Combat Simulation:
   </strong>
   A detailed combat simulation adds incredible depth to tactical gameplay. Turrets with their own pitch and tracking speeds make firing solutions important in battles. Fully simulated missiles can be blocked by ships or destroyed by point defense. New mechanics around shields, armor and hull points give greater depth to units and tactical decisions.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Empire Management:
   </strong>
   All planets and ships can now be easily analyzed, customized, and upgraded in one place without the tedium of finding and clicking through all units in your empire. The Intelligent Construction system will queue up the entire chain of prerequisites to fulfill any item, research, or unit build request.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Fleet Management:
   </strong>
   The new fleet system includes the ability to request specific reinforcements on the fly. Requested units are automatically queued from the optimal factory and rallied to the fleet. Combined with Intelligent Construction this allows you to focus on the important tactical decisions and big picture strategy.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Unit Customization:
   </strong>
   Planet surfaces can now be customized with special items that vary by race and planet type. Capital ships, titans and starbases can also be customized with race specific items to fill gaps in the fleet's composition or target specific strategies.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Minor Factions:
   </strong>
   Numerous minor factions now inhabit the galaxy offering trade, auctions for rare items, and with enough influence, access to their most powerful abilities. Will you befriend them or annihilate them to keep your enemies from turning them against you?
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Diplomacy:
   </strong>
   New features include a new offer / counteroffer system, the ability to give or demand planets, and the game changing time locked cease-fires that prevent your 'ally' from backstabbing you until it expires - but keep on eye on the time!
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Multicore 64-bit Engine:
   </strong>
   The Sins II engine can utilize all available cores and RAM to maximize performance, now and into the future. Dynamic lighting, physically based rendering, higher resolution textures and more create a beautiful tapestry.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    10-Player Multiplayer Support:
   </strong>
   A cloud based online system supports both 'join codes' and lobbies to make it easier than ever to play with others. Games can now be rejoined in progress if a player drops or has to leave; humans can even take over for AI players if a friend joins late.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    In-game Mod Support:
   </strong>
   Mod support has been integrated into the game, making it easy to discover, install, and share mods. Custom maps are automatically shared for multiplayer games, preventing the hassle of everyone downloading ahead of time.
   <br/>
   <br/>
   <strong>
    Easy to Learn; Hard to Master:
   </strong>
   With an elegant and intuitive user interface Sins II is easy to pick up and play. However, mastering your chosen faction will take true skill.
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  AI Generated Content Disclosure
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe how their game uses AI Generated Content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This game used AI to help quickly iterate through designs for some UI elements using our own artwork as a baseline. AI is also used to help translate the game.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 v1607+ / 11 (64-bit)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        4-core Processor (Intel Core i5 5th-generation or AMD Ryzen 2x00 series)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        3D Video Card w/2GB VRAM (Nvidia GeForce 950 / AMD Radeon RX 450)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        20 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        1920x1080 minimum screen resolution
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        8-core Processor (Intel Core i7 9th-generation or AMD Ryzen 3x00 series)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        3D Video Card w/4GB+ VRAM (Nvidia GeForce 1060 or AMD Radeon 580)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        20 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        1920x1080 minimum screen resolution
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELDEN RING</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1245620/ELDEN_RING/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 ELDEN RING
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   FromSoftware, Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   FromSoftware, Inc.
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Bandai Namco Entertainment
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Feb 24, 2022
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1245620/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1245620/extras/ER_Steam_Gif_616x260.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 THE NEW FANTASY ACTION RPG.
 <br/>
 Rise, Tarnished, and be guided by grace to brandish the power of the Elden Ring and become an Elden Lord in the Lands Between.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  • A Vast World Full of Excitement
 </h2>
 A vast world where open fields with a variety of situations and huge dungeons with complex and three-dimensional designs are seamlessly connected. As you explore, the joy of discovering unknown and overwhelming threats await you, leading to a high sense of accomplishment.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  • Create your Own Character
 </h2>
 In addition to customizing the appearance of your character, you can freely combine the weapons, armor, and magic that you equip. You can develop your character according to your play style, such as increasing your muscle strength to become a strong warrior, or mastering magic.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  • An Epic Drama Born from a Myth
 </h2>
 A multilayered story told in fragments. An epic drama in which the various thoughts of the characters intersect in the Lands Between.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  • Unique Online Play that Loosely Connects You to Others
 </h2>
 In addition to multiplayer, where you can directly connect with other players and travel together, the game supports a unique asynchronous online element that allows you to feel the presence of others.
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This Game may contain content not appropriate for all ages, or may not be appropriate for viewing at work: Frequent Violence or Gore, General Mature Content
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        INTEL CORE I5-8400 or AMD RYZEN 3 3300X
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        12 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GEFORCE GTX 1060 3 GB or AMD RADEON RX 580 4 GB
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        60 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Sound Card:
        </strong>
        Windows Compatible Audio Device
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10/11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        INTEL CORE I7-8700K or AMD RYZEN 5 3600X
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        16 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        NVIDIA GEFORCE GTX 1070 8 GB or AMD RADEON RX VEGA 56 8 GB
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 12
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        60 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Sound Card:
        </strong>
        Windows Compatible Audio Device
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldur's Gate 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Baldur's Gate 3
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Adventure
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Strategy
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Larian Studios
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Larian Studios
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Baldur's Gate
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Aug 3, 2023
 <br/>
 <b>
  Early Access Release Date:
 </b>
 Oct 6, 2020
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1086940/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/Final_Keyart_BG3.gif"/>
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Gather your party and return to the Forgotten Realms in a tale of fellowship and betrayal, sacrifice and survival, and the lure of absolute power.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Mysterious abilities are awakening inside you, drawn from a mind flayer parasite planted in your brain. Resist, and turn darkness against itself. Or embrace corruption, and become ultimate evil.
 <br>
  <br>
   From the creators of Divinity: Original Sin 2 comes a next-generation RPG, set in the world of Dungeons & Dragons.
   <br>
    <br>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/Gather_new.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Choose from 12 classes and 11 races from the D&D Player's Handbook and create your own identity, or play as an Origin hero with a hand-crafted background. Or tangle with your inner corruption as the Dark Urge, a fully customisable Origin hero with its own unique mechanics and story. Whoever you choose to be, adventure, loot, battle and romance your way across the Forgotten Realms and beyond. Gather your party. Take the adventure online as a party of up to four.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/An_expansive_original_story.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Abducted, infected, lost. You are turning into a monster, but as the corruption inside you grows, so does your power. That power may help you to survive, but there will be a price to pay, and more than any ability, the bonds of trust that you build within your party could be your greatest strength. Caught in a conflict between devils, deities, and sinister otherworldly forces, you will determine the fate of the Forgotten Realms together.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/Next_Gen_new.gif"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     Forged with the new Divinity 4.0 engine, Baldur’s Gate 3 gives you unprecedented freedom to explore, experiment, and interact with a thriving world filled with characters, dangers, and deceit. A grand, cinematic narrative brings you closer to your characters than ever before. From shadow-cursed forests, to the magical caverns of the Underdark, to the sprawling city of Baldur’s Gate itself, your actions define the adventure, but your choices define your legacy. You will be remembered.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/Experience_Depth.png"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     The Forgotten Realms are a vast, detailed, and diverse world, and there are secrets to be discovered all around you – verticality is a vital part of exploration. Sneak, dip, shove, climb, and jump as you journey from the depths of the Underdark to the glittering rooftops of Baldur’s Gate. Every choice you make drives your story forward, each decision leaving your mark on the world. Define your legacy, nurture relationships and create enemies, and solve problems your way. No two playthroughs will ever be the same.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/01_Bullets_points.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      allows you to combine your forces in combat and simultaneously attack enemies, or split your party to each follow your own quests and agendas. Concoct the perfect plan together… or introduce an element of chaos when your friends least expect it. Relationships are complicated. Especially when you’ve got a parasite in your brain.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/02_Bullets_points.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      7 unique Origin heroes offer a hand-crafted experience, each with their own unique traits, agenda, and outlook on the world. Their stories intersect with the overarching narrative, and your choices will determine whether those stories end in redemption, salvation, domination, or one of many other outcomes. Play as an Origin and enjoy their stories, or recruit them to fight alongside you.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/03_Bullets_points.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      based on the D&D 5e ruleset. Team-based initiative, advantage and disadvantage, and roll modifiers join an advanced AI, expanded environmental interactions, and a new fluidity in combat that rewards strategy and foresight. Three difficulty settings allow you to customise the challenge of combat. Enable weighted dice to help sway the battle, or play on Tactician mode for a hardcore experience.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/04_Bullets_points_Unprecedented.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      featuring 31 subraces on top of the 11 races (Human, Githyanki, Half-Orc, Dwarf, Elf, Drow, Tiefling, Halfling, Half Elf, Gnome, Dragonborn), with 46 subclasses branching out of the 12 classes. Over 600 spells and actions offer near-limitless freedom of interactivity in a hand-crafted world where exploration is rewarded, and player agency defines the journey. Our unique Character Creator features unprecedented depth of character, with reactivity that ensures whomever you are, you will leave a unique legacy behind you, all the way up to Level 12. Over 174 hours of cinematics ensure that no matter the choices you make, the cinematic experience follows your journey – every playthrough, a new cinematic journey.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/05_Bullets_points_Romances.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      With the looming threat of war heading to Baldur’s Gate, and a mind flayer invasion on the horizon, friendships – though not necessary – are bound to be forged on your journey. What becomes of them is up to you, as you enter real, vibrant relationships with those you meet along the way. Each companion has their own moral compass and will react to the choices you make throughout your journey. At what cost will you stick to your ideals? Will you allow love to shape your actions? The relationships made on the road to Baldur’s Gate act as moments of respite at camp as much as they add weight to the many decisions you make on your adventure.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/06_Bullets_points_Customise.png"/>
     <br/>
     <ul class="bb_ul">
      so that when you hit ‘go live’, your stream isn’t interrupted by a bear, swear, or lack of underwear. Baldur’s Gate 3 has 3 different levels of streamer-friendly customisation. You can disable nudity and explicit content separately (or together), and you can enable Twitch integration to interact directly with your audience, just as we do at our Panel From Hell showcases! You’ll be able to stream Baldur’s Gate 3 without any problems, regardless of how you play, thanks to these options.
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/1086940/extras/Final_Image_new.gif"/>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This Game may contain content not appropriate for all ages. It contains General Mature Content, and may include Nudity or Sexual Content.
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
   <center>
    <h3>
     MacOS
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
    <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
     <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
      <div class="sys_req_container">
      </div>
     </div>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/230410/Warframe/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Warframe
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   RPG
  </a>
  ,
  <a>
   Free To Play
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Digital Extremes
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Digital Extremes
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Mar 25, 2013
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/230410/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 Confront warring factions throughout a sprawling interplanetary system as you follow the guidance of the mysterious Lotus and level up your Warframe, build an Arsenal of destructive firepower, and realize your true potential across massive open worlds in this thrilling, genre-defining third-person combat experience.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/230410/extras/WF_DiscordBannerGif_FNL.gif"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  BECOME A POWERFUL WARRIOR
 </h2>
 Enter your Warframe: a bio-metal suit of untold power. Unleash its Abilities and wield a vast array of devastating weaponry to effortlessly annihilate hordes of enemies on sight. And when the slaughter is over, you can earn or instantly unlock 40+ different Warframes - each with a unique suite of powers - to re-experience the mayhem any way you want.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  BATTLE ALONGSIDE FRIENDS
 </h2>
 Form a Squad with your friends and earn valuable bonus Rewards when you complete Missions together via highly collaborative, co-op gameplay. Utilize your Warframe’s Abilities to heal allies, redirect enemy fire, and achieve your objectives. Stuck on a particular challenge? In-game matchmaking makes it easy to connect with friendly Tenno whenever you need an extra hand.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/230410/extras/ExploreOpenWorlds_600x127.gif"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  EXPLORE A MASSIVE SYSTEM
 </h2>
 Deftly maneuver through ground-based Missions with your Warframe’s mesmerizing parkour skills, or take to the stars and engage in massive ship-to-ship battles in your very own customizable spacecraft. Lose yourself within mysterious open-world landscapes and discover a system teeming with fascinating lifeforms - both friendly and hostile.
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  DISCOVER AN EPIC STORY
 </h2>
 Marvel at the sweeping history of the Origin System as you experience Warframe’s massive cinematic narrative spanning 5 separate expansions and 30+ story-based Quests. Discover the power within and experience your first taste of invincibility with one of three original Warframes before you begin your journey, develop your skills and seek out the truth behind your awakening.
 <br>
  <br>
   <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/230410/extras/NinjasPlayFree_600x127.gif"/>
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    MASTER YOUR ARSENAL
   </h2>
   Your starter Weapons are just the beginning. Craft hundreds of destructive armaments, plus vehicles, Companions and more. Level them up and experiment until you find the right combination of gear that suits your unique playstyle. Fashion your weaponry for a fearsome look to compliment your custom-designed loadout.
   <h2 class="bb_tag">
    CUSTOMIZE ENDLESSLY
   </h2>
   Entering the Origin System means joining legions of friendly Tenno, each with their own personalized Warframes, Weapons and gear. With a staggering number of Customization options available to enhance your Loadout, designing the perfect look for your Warframe makes for an endlessly rewarding challenge for you and your Squad.
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This Game may contain content not appropriate for all ages, or may not be appropriate for viewing at work: Frequent Violence or Gore, General Mature Content
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_full">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS *:
        </strong>
        Windows 7 64-Bit (32-bit not supported)
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i7 860, Intel Core i5 750, or AMD FX-4100 (SSE 4.2 support required)
        <br>
        </br>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Video:
        </strong>
        DirectX 11+ capable Graphics Card
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        4 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        50 GB available HD space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Internet:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet Connection Required
       </li>
      </ul>
      <br/>
      Note: There is no Mac or Linux client currently available.
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_note">
     <strong>
      *
     </strong>
     Starting January 1st, 2024, the Steam Client will only support Windows 10 and later versions.
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/381210/Dead_by_Daylight/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<style>
            .sys_req_container {
                display: flex;
                flex-wrap: wrap;
                margin-bottom: 10px;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col, .sys_req_right_col {
                flex: 1;
                padding: 10px;
                box-sizing: border-box;
            }
            .sys_req_left_col {
                border-right: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .sys_req_right_col {
                border-left: 1px solid #ccc;
            }
            .ipsQuote_citation, .ipsSpoiler_header {
                display: flex;
                justify-content: center;
            }
            .ipsSpoiler_header [data-action='toggleSpoiler'] {
                margin-top: 1px;
            }
            [dir='ltr'] .ipsQuote, [dir='ltr'] .ipsSpoiler, [dir='ltr'] .ipsStyle_spoiler {
                border-width: 0 4px 0 4px;
            }
            </style>
    <div class="details_block" id="genresAndManufacturer">
 <b>
  Title:
 </b>
 Dead by Daylight
 <br/>
 <b>
  Genre:
 </b>
 <span data-panel='{"flow-children":"row"}'>
  <a>
   Action
  </a>
 </span>
 <br/>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Developer:
  </b>
  <a>
   Behaviour Interactive Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Publisher:
  </b>
  <a>
   Behaviour Interactive Inc.
  </a>
 </div>
 <div class="dev_row">
  <b>
   Franchise:
  </b>
  <a>
   Dead by Daylight
  </a>
 </div>
 <b>
  Release Date:
 </b>
 Jun 14, 2016
 <br/>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/381210/" width="850">
</iframe>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
 <h2>
  About This Game
 </h2>
 <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/381210/extras/DeadbyDaylight_anime_Intro_Steam.jpg"/>
 <h2 class="bb_tag">
  Death Is Not an Escape.
 </h2>
 <br/>
 Dead by Daylight is a multiplayer (4vs1) horror game where one player takes on the role of the savage Killer, and the other four players play as Survivors, trying to escape the Killer and avoid being caught, tortured and killed.
 <br/>
 <br/>
 Survivors play in third-person and have the advantage of better situational awareness. The Killer plays in first-person and is more focused on their prey.
 <br/>
 <br>
  The Survivors' goal in each encounter is to escape the Killing Ground without getting caught by the Killer - something that sounds easier than it is, especially when the environment changes every time you play.
  <h2 class="bb_tag">
   Key Features
  </h2>
  •
  <strong>
   Survive Together… Or Not
  </strong>
  - Survivors can either cooperate with the others or be selfish. Your chance of survival will vary depending on whether you work together as a team or if you go at it alone. Will you be able to outwit the Killer and escape their Killing Ground?
  <br>
   <br>
    •
    <strong>
     Where Am I?
    </strong>
    - Each level is procedurally generated, so you’ll never know what to expect. Random spawn points mean you will never feel safe as the world and its danger change every time you play.
    <br>
     <br/>
     •
     <strong>
      A Feast for Killers
     </strong>
     - Dead by Daylight draws from all corners of the horror world. As a Killer you can play as anything from a powerful Slasher to terrifying paranormal entities. Familiarize yourself with your Killing Grounds and master each Killer’s unique power to be able to hunt, catch and sacrifice your victims.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <img src="https://shared.akamai.steamstatic.com/store_item_assets/steam/apps/381210/extras/DBD_HillB_Trapper_Wraith_anime_Steam.jpg"/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     •
     <strong>
      Deeper and Deeper
     </strong>
     - Each Killer and Survivor has their own deep progression system and plenty of unlockables that can be customized to fit your own personal strategy. Experience, skills and understanding of the environment are key to being able to hunt or outwit the Killer.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     •
     <strong>
      Real People, Real Fear
     </strong>
     - The procedural levels and real human reactions to pure horror makes each game session an unexpected scenario. You will never be able to tell how it’s going to turn out. Ambience, music, and chilling environments combine into a terrifying experience. With enough time, you might even discover what’s hiding in the fog.
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <strong>
      WARNING: PHOTOSENSITIVITY/EPILEPSY SEIZURES - READ THIS NOTICE BEFORE PLAYING
     </strong>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <i>
      A very small percentage of people may experience epileptic seizures or blackouts when exposed to certain kinds of flashing lights or light patterns. These persons, or even people who have no history of seizures or epilepsy, may experience epileptic symptoms or seizures while playing video games. If you or any of your relatives has an epileptic condition or has had seizures of any kind, consult your physician before playing any video game.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      IMMEDIATELY DISCONTINUE use and consult a physician if you or your child experience any of the following symptoms: dizziness, altered vision, eye or muscle twitching, involuntary movements, loss of awareness, disorientation, or convulsions. Parents should watch for or ask their children about the above symptoms.
      <br/>
      <br/>
      You may reduce risk of photosensitive epileptic seizures by taking the following precautions: sit farther from the screen, use a smaller screen, play in a well-lit room, do not play when you are drowsy or fatigued.
     </i>
    </br>
   </br>
  </br>
 </br>
</div>
<div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_content_descriptors">
 <h2>
  Mature Content Description
 </h2>
 <p>
  The developers describe the content like this:
 </p>
 <p>
  <i>
   This Game may contain content not appropriate for all ages, or may not be appropriate for viewing at work: Frequent Violence or Gore, General Mature Content
  </i>
 </p>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>
 <h2>
  System Requirements
 </h2>
</center>
<div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
 <div class="ipsSpoiler" data-ipsspoiler="">
  <div class="ipsSpoiler_contents ipsClearfix">
   <center>
    <h3>
     Windows
    </h3>
   </center>
   <div class="sys_req_container">
    <div class="sys_req_left_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Minimum:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 64-bit Operating System
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i3-4170 or AMD FX-8120
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        DX11 Compatible GeForce GTX 460 1GB or AMD HD 6850 1GB
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        50 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Sound Card:
        </strong>
        DX11 compatible
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Additional Notes:
        </strong>
        With these requirements, it is recommended that the game is played on Low quality settings.
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="sys_req_right_col">
     <ul>
      <strong>
       Recommended:
      </strong>
      <br/>
      <ul class="bb_ul">
       <li>
        Requires a 64-bit processor and operating system
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         OS:
        </strong>
        Windows 10 64-bit Operating System
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Processor:
        </strong>
        Intel Core i3-4170 or AMD FX-8300 or higher
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Memory:
        </strong>
        8 GB RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Graphics:
        </strong>
        DX11 Compatible GeForce 760 or AMD HD 8800 or higher with 4GB of RAM
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         DirectX:
        </strong>
        Version 11
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Network:
        </strong>
        Broadband Internet connection
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Storage:
        </strong>
        50 GB available space
        <br/>
       </li>
       <li>
        <strong>
         Sound Card:
        </strong>
        DX11 compatible
       </li>
      </ul>
     </ul>
    </div>
   </div>
  </div>
 </div>
</div>
<br/>
<br/>
<center>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
