<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live Now: Inferno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961123852</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New In-Game Event: Inferno</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The streets of Tertium are aflame. Whether by heretic plot or over-zealous Imperial enforcement makes no real difference. Missions must still run, so be careful down there. You're literally dropping into a hot zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Inferno condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will start on Monday, June 23. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic portrait frame.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5fc488e1e9c4f7d418798f824c92a7cd7ca3ff54.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/48ebf065d7f8058c2c24aaecda294d00b32284fe.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Update: Battle for Tertium - Out Now! (Patch Notes)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961123617</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Upcoming New Class: Adeptus Arbites</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Darktide’s first Class DLC is soon available to all players! The release of the DLC is planned for later in the afternoon (June 23rd), <b>around 16:00 CEST - 07:00 PDT</b>. Get the Arbites Class on all platforms today at the price of $11.99 / €11.99.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> [dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d846a0ad5d8dc966d34f07b734659eff2f41325.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b><u>Free Update: Battle for Tertium</u></b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"> <img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e1eaaf207f64427e750d3ee704a8abff37e7793b.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">The Battle for Tertium</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The core player experience has been reworked to provide a new clearer narrative focus, following the conflict of the Battle for Tertium. Players will now experience a linear campaign with new mission debriefs and embedded cinematics. This new progression path is designed to ease in new players and gradually unlock features that were previously gated by character level.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/41f4ff6d56fd7030ba34047f87d4dbdd979bfb1a.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While previously each new player’s experience was completely random, the Battle for Tertium narrative presents maps, enemies and characters in a specific order, allowing players to discover all aspects of the game at a much better pace.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The story missions play the same as regular missions, except that these missions have a more tight control over which enemies spawn. You might also hear some new VO lines during missions, and some brand new mission debrief cinematics when completing each mission.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Existing players with characters at level 10 or higher can choose to skip the story or play it from the beginning.</b> Players who change their minds about playing the campaign can opt out by using the Personality Scourge at the Barber-Chirurgeon. <b>Note</b>: If you decide to skip the story when you first log-in with this update, <i>you cannot revert this decision. The only way to play the story after choosing to skip it is to create a new character.</i> <b>Additional note</b>: The option to replay story missions at any time is still in progress. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>It is worth noting that the Arbites’ arrival takes place after the events of the Battle for Tertium,</b> so while you can absolutely play as an Arbites through the new campaign (once the class releases, later today!), some of the story scenes will not be addressed to your type of character. For this reason, we suggest playing the Battle for Tertium for the first time with one of the core characters.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Mission Board Rework</div><p class="bb_paragraph">A new mission board system will be bringing several changes to how you engage with missions and difficulties. <b>Missions are no longer tied to a specific difficulty, allowing you to select a mission and then choose the difficulty you want.</b> This will effectively increase the amount of mission options available for players of all difficulty levels. While most circumstances remain consistent across difficulty levels, some are disabled on lower difficulties. <b>Notably, Maelstrom missions are exclusive to the Heresy and Auric difficulties.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5a7678117e2d8e5f33643296c61a91c71467da2c.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, the difficulty system has also been overhauled. <b>You now unlock new difficulties by completing missions rather than leveling up your characters.</b> You must prove your skills at your current maximum difficulty to unlock access to the next one. We intend to create a motivation for new players to master the game step by step, and for veteran players to feel assured that their teammates have earned the right to be there.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">You will make progress by playing missions at your current maximum difficulty. Completing missions advances your progress. Mission Failures reduce your progress slightly but you will never be demoted to a lower difficulty. Higher difficulties will require you to complete more missions to unlock them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>For existing characters, your difficulty progression will be migrated based on their character level and completed missions.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Auric is now a standalone difficulty tier</b>, placed above Damnation. We felt that Auric Heresy fell in an awkward spot compared to Damnation, with the increased mission options per difficulty, we decided it was best to turn Auric into its own difficulty level. Additionally, <b>we have removed Sedition difficulty and made a few minor changes to Uprising to take its place</b>, as we felt there was too much downtime with too few enemies between hordes. These changes aim to keep you in the action more often.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Mortis Trials</b></div><div class="bb_h2"><b>The Secrets of the Shipmistress</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Sefoni’s indiscretions are getting worse! During Mortis Trials, keen-eared Rejects now have the opportunity to sift pieces of Shipmistress Brahms’ past from the psychic chatter. How did she inherit the Mourningstar? What is she hiding? Is she really on the same side as Grendyl, let alone his irksome busybodies? Delve deeper into all these and more across dozens of new memory echoes, unlockable by claiming victory in the Mortis Trials!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>If you've ever wanted to relisten to the memory echoes you've unlocked in the Mortis Trials, you should take a look behind the pillars in the Meat Grinder.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>New difficulty for Mortis Trials</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Since the release of Mortis Trials we have noticed people requesting a higher challenge in Mortis Trials! So, we are adding a new difficulty, Auric, as well as some other small changes.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There will now be a shorter time in between waves.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Waves will now have more enemies and enemy types increasing variety.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We are changing the base difficulty to match an Auric difficulty mission.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>New In-Game Event: Inferno</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The streets of Tertium are aflame. Whether by heretic plot or over-zealous Imperial enforcement makes no real difference. Missions must still run, so be careful down there. You're literally dropping into a hot zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Inferno condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will start on Monday, June 23. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic portrait frame.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5fc488e1e9c4f7d418798f824c92a7cd7ca3ff54.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/48ebf065d7f8058c2c24aaecda294d00b32284fe.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>New Havoc Campaign</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Havoc Maintenance: </b><i>With the upcoming release of this update, Havoc will be unavailable from June 23, 2025 from 00:00 to approximately 12:00 UTC.</i></p><div class="bb_h2">New Mission Pool</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Power Matrix HL-17-36</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Magistrati Oubliette TM8-707</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Archivum Sycorax</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dark Communion</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Refinery Delta-17</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Smelter Complex HL17-36</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Chasm Station HL-16-11</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Excise Vault Spireside-13</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Consignment Yard HL17-36</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Chasm Logistratum</i></p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Mutators</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Pus-Hardened Skin</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Final Toll</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heinous Rituals</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Encroaching Garden</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rampaging Enemies </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The in-game event condition, Inferno, will temporarily be available during the first rotation in this campaign, as well.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Quality of Life Changes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased maximum number of operatives to 8.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased maximum number of weapon loadouts to 8.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a total of ~900 new banter conversations, both between the original cast and Arbites.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Weapon Balance Changes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><div class="bb_h2">Catachan "Devil's Claw" Swords</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This batch of changes for the Devil’s Claw swords aims at further reinforcing the crowd control and reliability of the family.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We increased the offensive properties of the Light attack profiles, while also significantly increasing the <b>armour damage modifiers (“adm” from now on)</b> of the Heavy Strikedown and Special Riposte profiles against specific armour types.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> We improved the base Stamina statistic, reduced the minimum Block time (the amount of time that the Block stance must be maintained after performing the input) and allowed for most attacks and attack starts to be performed while sprinting. This will make the weapon snappier and more responsive in different situations.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, we took a pass on all attacks to tweak active windows, ranges and hitboxes to be better aligned with their animations. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk I</b>, we added a new Heavy Strikedown attack, only reached from Light 3. In turn, the Light 3 attack is now reachable also from the Push action, and has an increased baseline power multiplier.  </p><p class="bb_paragraph">These additions will grant additional options to a mark which was lacking in single target attacks. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk IV</b>, we raised the power level multiplier of the Light 4 attack as it was very far into the attack chain and not particularly enticing. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk VII</b>, we increased the power level multiplier of the Pushfollow and Light 3 attacks while also changing the possible combos after a Riposte attack. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now after a successful Special Parry, the combo will chain into the Pushfollow attack instead of Light 3; as the Pushfollow attack still chains into Light 3, this will give the mark a new unique chain. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Catachan "Devil's Claw" Swords</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Vanguard</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {40, 80} to {60, 100}.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The change will also affect the Turtolsky Heavy Swords Special followup Light attacks.</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Strikedown / Light Strikedown Stab</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Maniac from 1 to 1.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {100, 200} to {115, 230}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">2nd target damage from {25,60} to {40,80}.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The changes will also affect the Turtolsky Heavy Swords Pushfollow attacks and the Maccabian Mk V Duelling Sword Light 3 attack.</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Unarmoured from 1 to 1.1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Unyielding from 0.75 to 1.25.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Riposte</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Unarmoured from 1 to 1.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Unyielding from 1 to 1.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Carapace armour from 0.25 to 0.5.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Allowed during sprint to most attacks and attack starts.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Block minimum time from 0.3 to 0.225.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stamina template update:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Base Stamina from 4 to 4.5.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked damage windows, hitboxes and ranges for several attacks.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated Inspect screen to correct some attack gestalt icons (visual only change).</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk I</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a new Heavy Strikedown attack with 540 power level multiplier .</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This attack will chain only from Light 3.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light 3 chains now to Light 2 / new Heavy Strikedown instead of Light 1 / Heavy 1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Push chains now to Light 3 / Heavy 1 instead of Light 1 / Heavy 1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy 2 chain time to Start attack from 0.55 to 0.5.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Push chain time to Start attack from 0.35 to 0.3.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 545 power level multiplier to Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 535 power level multiplier to Pushfollow attack (from default 500).</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk IV</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy 1 windup from secondary start from 0.56 to 0.46.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 550 power level multiplier to Light 4 (from default 500).</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk VII</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Pushfollow damage profile from Light Strikedown to Light Strikedown Stab.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Riposte chains now to Pushfollow / Heavy 1 instead of Light 3 / Heavy 1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 535 power level multiplier to Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 525 power level multiplier to Pushfollow attack (from default 500).</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Atrox Tactical Axes</div><p class="bb_paragraph">While sporting overall good mobility, the Tactical Axes had only average Sprint values. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We significantly improved their Sprint profile, while also allowing for most attacks and attack starts to be performed while sprinting. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We also significantly raised the damage of the Special attacks and added a new profile for the Heavy Strikedowns with a vertical or uppercut direction, with increased damage and Carapace armour modifier. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, we took a pass on all attacks to tweak active windows, ranges and hitboxes to be better aligned with their animations. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk II</b>, we added a power level boost to the Light 3 attack, as it is further into the attack chain, and to both Special attacks, as they are slower compared to the other two marks. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk IV</b>, we upgraded the damage profile for both Heavy attacks and slightly lowered their chain timings, as they are both performed in a vertical or uppercut direction. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk VII</b>, we added a power level boost to all Light attacks, as they inflict a higher movement speed penalty compared to the Lights of the other marks, and changed the Heavy 2 profile to the new Heavy Strikedown. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Atrox Tactical Axes</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Assassin</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 3rd target.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Strikedown (diagonal)</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Adm vs Carapace armour from 0.25 to 0.3.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a new Heavy Strikedown profile for vertical and uppercut attacks, with the same. properties as Heavy Strikedown (diagonal) aside from:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {100,200} to {115,230}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Carapace armour from 0.3 to 0.5.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Special Stab</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {25,50} to {70,140}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed Crit Chance bonus.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Special Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {25,50} to {60,120}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target impact from {8,16} to {10,20}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed Crit Chance bonus.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint template from “default” to “assault”.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Forward acceleration from {0.15, 0.4} to {0.4, 0.8}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Forward deceleration from 1.25 to 2.1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint speed modifier from {-0.5, 0.5} to {-0.25, 0.85}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased action total time for most Heavy attacks.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This will make continuing the combo chain after the attacks more forgiving.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Allowed during sprint to most attacks and attack starts.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked damage windows, hitboxes and ranges for most attacks.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Buffer time for the Special input from 0.2 to 0.4.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk II</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 515 to Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 550 to Special 1 and Special 2 (from default 500).</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk IV</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed damage profile of Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 from Heavy Strikedown (diagonal) to the new Heavy Strikedown (vertical/uppercut).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lowered chain times to Start Attack and Special Attack from Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 from 0.5 to 0.4.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 515 to Heavy 2 (from default 500).</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk VII</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed damage profile of Heavy 2 from Heavy Strikedown (diagonal) to the new Heavy Strikedown (vertical/uppercut).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 550 to Light 1,  Light 2,  Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Shock Mauls</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Shock Mauls, while being dependable in inflicting stagger, were also below average in damage output and overall not very exciting. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We increased the damage against the 1st target on most profiles, with a particularly large bonus to the Heavy Strikedown and Special attacks. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We also enhanced the base Stamina and Dodge templates, and tweaked hitboxes and active windows of some attacks to better align with their animations. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the attacks with an uppercut direction (Light 3 on the <b>Mk Ia</b> / Light 4 on the <b>Mk III</b>) we slightly delayed the start of the attack active window to make it easier to connect with weakspots. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, for the <b>Mk Ia</b>, we added power level multipliers to the Light 3 and Light 4 attacks, to make them a more enticing combo alternative to just returning to Heavy 1. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Shock Mauls</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {100,200} to {115,210}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Vanguard</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave from “light” to “medium”.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">From {3.0,6.0} to {4.0,9.0}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {100,150} to {110,165}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Relentless</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {110,260} to {120,270}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave from “big” to “light”.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">From {8.5,12.5} to {3.0,6.0}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {140,350} to {160,390}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">4th target damage override removed (from 0 to {30,50}).</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Relentless</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Maniac from 0.8 to 0.75.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Carapace armour from 0.75 to 0.4.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {80,150} to {90,165}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Special attack</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sticky damage tick from {10,70} to {30,80}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stun damage tick from {40,50} to {50,65}.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stamina template update:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Base Stamina from 4 to 4.5.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint cost per second from {1.5, 0.5} to {1.25, 0.75}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Inner angle Block cost from {1.5, 0.5} to {1.0, 0.5}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dodge template update:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Effective dodges limit from {3, 4}, to {3, 5}.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">From 4 to 5 maximum effective dodges at high Mobility stat.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dodge distance from {0.85, 1.0} to {0.9, 1.1}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dodge speed from {1.0, 1.2} to 1.0.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk Ia</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light 1 damage profile from Light Relentless to Light Vanguard.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 530 to Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 550 to Light 4 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked hitboxes for Light 3 and Light 4.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked damage windows for Light 4 to make it easier to connect with weak spots.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk III</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked hitboxes and damage windows for Light 1 and Light 2.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked damage windows for Light 3 to make it easier to connect with weakspots.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Tigrus Heavy Eviscerators</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Eviscerator’s thunder was in part stolen by the Relic Blades, which have overall better cleave properties while also being no slouch in the single target department. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">To give these iconic Zealot weapons a deserved bump, we tweaked most of the attack profiles: we removed the damage caps on secondary targets for the sweeping Vanguard/Relentless attacks, but also increased several armour modifier values, significantly improved the damage on the Heavy profiles and normalised most of the Special active profiles. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk III</b>, we changed the chain times to key actions after the Heavy 1 attack to make it more responsive but less spammable with swap cancelling, slightly increased the speed of the Light 2 attack and added a power level multiplier to the Light 3 and Heavy 2 attacks. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Tigrus Heavy Eviscerators</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Maniac from 0.5 to 0.9.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Infested from 0.75 to 1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed adm reduction on 1st target vs Carapace armour; from 0.1 to 0.25.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Vanguard/Relentless</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Upped damage on secondary targets.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed damage cap after 4th target.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Vanguard</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {150,300} to {165,345}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target finesse multiplier from 0.5 to {0.4,1.0}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Upped damage on secondary targets.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Strikedown</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target damage from {150,300} to {175,350}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target adm vs Carapace armour from 0.25 to 0.5.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target finesse multiplier from 0.5 to {0.5, 1.0}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Strikedown (Special active)</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed damage overrides.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed finesse multiplier override.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Vanguard/Heavy Strikedown/Pushfollow (Special active)</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed damage overrides.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 0.4s buffer time to the Unwield input.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"> <b>Mk III</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy 1 chain to Unwield from 0 to 0.45.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy 1 chain to Start attack from 0.6 to 0.45.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy 1 chain to Block from 0.7 to 0.6.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light 2 time scale from 0.85 to 0.9 (sped up).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added power level multiplier 525 to Heavy 2 and Light 3 (from default 500).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated Heavy 2 and Pushfollow attack damage profiles on Special abort.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk XV</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated Pushfollow attack damage profiles on Special active and Special abort.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Lucius Helbore Lasguns</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Helbore Lasguns suffered from a very long Wield action duration, making it hard to quickly swap to priority targets (especially accounting also for the charging shots).</p><p class="bb_paragraph">While this behaviour was intended, it also became increasingly punishing as the enemy numbers grew in higher difficulties. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">In this balancing pass we sped up the Wield action, walking the line of maintaining the cumbersome feeling while also allowing for the weapons to be easier to swap into. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alongside this change, we improved some of the armour and Finesse modifiers for ranged shots, and extended the hitscan radius of the las projectiles<b>*</b>, to make it easier for the weapon to shine as a marksman tool.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>* </b><i>This will make the hitscan detection more generous and allow for shots that would have slightly missed the target to still be considered a hit.</i> </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk V</b>, we slightly increased the camera zoom in ADS mode. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk IV</b>, we increased the camera zoom in ADS mode to be equivalent as the <b>Mk IIIa.</b> </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We also improved the speed and offensive properties of the Special Slash attack, to be more in line with the Special Stab used in the other marks. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Lucius Helbore Lasguns</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Near charged shot </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Unarmoured from 1 to 1.1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Maniac from 1 to 1.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Infested from 1 to 1.1.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Far charged shot</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Unarmoured from 1 to 1.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Infested from 1 to 1.25.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">All shots Finesse Boost</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">vs Carapace armour from 0.1 to 0.2.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">vs Maniac from 0.25 to 0.35.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">vs Unyielding from 0.25 to 0.3.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Special Slash</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Ignore stagger reduction.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1st target finesse multiplier from 0.75 to 1.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All Marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added time scale 1.5 to Wield action (sped up).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added 0.05 radius to hitscan templates.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Buffer time for the Special input from 0.2 to 0.4.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk V</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">ADS Vertical Field of View from 65 to 55.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk IV</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Chain from Special start to Special attack from 0.3 to 0.25.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Chain from Special attack to Special start from 0.7 to 0.645.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked Special attack hitbox and damage window.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">ADS Vertical Field of View from 65 to 45.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Combat Shotguns</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Combat Shotguns have been in a spot where they are mostly used for their Special shells, while the normal shots felt underwhelming in most circumstances. They also suffered from long reload times relative to other weapons.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">With this update we are trying to improve the overall usability without relying solely on the Special mechanic.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Along with increased base damage and reload speed, the Combat Shotgun family gets updated Sprint and Stamina templates, to enable a more mobile, close-range playstyle and not rely only on precision weak-spot shots.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We also significantly increased the ammo reserves for all marks. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, we slightly increased the Cleave and Impact values to allow it to punch through lesser enemies. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk VII</b>, we aligned the Finesse boost curve between hipfire and ADS modes. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the <b>Mk IX</b>, we slightly extended the Near and Far effective ranges. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Combat Shotguns</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>All Marks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint template from “killshot” to “assault”.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint forward acceleration from {0.15, 0.4} to {0.4, 0.8}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint forward deceleration from 1.25 to 2.1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint sideway acceleration/deceleration from 5 to 7.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint speed modifier from {0.5, 0.5} to {0.25, 0.85}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated Stamina template </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stamina modifier from 2 to 4.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sprint cost per second from {2, 1.5} to {1.5, 0.5}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased Reload speed by around 10%</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Affecting both regular and special shells.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Zarona MK VI</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Damage from {250, 500} to {300, 600}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave attack From 0.01 to {2, 4}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave impact from 0.01 to {2, 4}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ammo reserve from {60, 80} to {70, 95}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Agripinaa Mk VII</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Damage from {200, 400} to {250, 480}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave attack From 1.3 to 2.5.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave impact from 1.3 to 2.5.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ammo reserve from {75, 95} to {80, 105}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Finesse boost curve shooting from HipFire increased to match ADS.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">{0.6,1.2} to {1.25,2.5}.</p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Accatran Mk IX</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Damage from {450, 700} to {550, 740}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave attack From 2 to 3.5.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cleave impact from 1 to 3.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ranges</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Close range from {6, 8} to {6, 11}.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Long range from {12, 16}  to {12, 17}.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ammo reserve from {45, 65} to {55, 85}.</p></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Double-barreled Shotgun</div><p class="bb_paragraph">To increase the reliability of the weapon against bigger targets, we increased the armour damage modifier against the Unyielding type at both Near and Far ranges. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, we slightly raised the ammo reserves to allow for more aggressive approaches. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Detailed Changes - Double-barreled Shotgun</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Damage profiles</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">adm vs Unyielding</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Near from 1.0 to 1.1.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Far from 0.5 to 0.65.</p></li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ammo reserve increased from {40, 80} to {50, 90}. </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Bug Fixes &amp; Changes</b></div><div class="bb_h2">Weapons and Blessings</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the description for the 'Run n Gun' blessing was displaying incorrect prefixes.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Classes</div><div class="bb_h3"><b>Psyker</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Disrupt Destiny keystone sometimes failed to show stacks in the HUD.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><div class="bb_h3"><b>Inter-Zone Void Sector Omega-12</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Clandestium Gloriana</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several places in Clandestium Gloriana where players could get out of bounds.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rotated the door after the mid event in Clandestium Gloriana to avoid players getting trapped behind it when it opens. </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">UI/UX and Animation </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where an “additional objectives” string in the Penance menu would not localize correctly.  </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deadzone options now apply to both sticks when playing on controller.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issue on the Zealot “Stygian Kantrael MK IVG Flak Helm” headgear.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issue behind the arms on the Veteran “Stygian MK lll Flak vest” upper body.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed longer hairstyles clipping issue with the Psyker “Stygian MK IV Psykana Collar with Rebreather” headgear.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshoud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear would remove the operative's eyebrows.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with the Veteran “Militarum Field Jacket” upper body clipping with “Militarum Type 47” lower body.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues where the following Veteran headgear cosmetics would clip certain hairstyles  </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ock's Blood Goggles</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tinker Zard's Superior High-vis Goggles</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Chasm Railer Goggles</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed corrupted texture on Veteran “Vostroyan Hat with Tox Guard Face Mask (Mountain Snow)” headgear.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issue on the Veteran “Stygian Mk I Armoured Fatigues” lowerbody. </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– The Darktide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog: Arbites Weaponry</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961123583</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Today we’re showcasing the new tools of justice coming your way just for Arbites. In addition to the arsenal already at your disposal in the game (five melee and nine ranged weapons), four new unique weapons have been crafted to bring swift judgment to lexbreakers. We’ll also take you behind the scenes, sharing how these righteous implements were forged.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Here’s what’s hitting the field with the Arbites DLC:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Exterminator Shotgun: Unleash righteous fury with Special Issue shells.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Subductor Shotpistol and Riot Shield: Darktide’s first hybrid ranged/defense combo.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbites Shock Maul: Crush dissent with every electrified swing…</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shock Maul and Suppression Shield: …And if that’s not enough, bring the bash too.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Design</div><p class="bb_paragraph">For the design direction of these weapons we spoke to Matteo and Erik, Designers on Darktide who helped bring these weapons to life.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How does the Arbites shotgun special shell work?</b><br/>With the Arbites shotgun, we are introducing a new type of limited specials.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New Functionality:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Limited Special Shells</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The number of special shells are limited and visible on the weapon’s top rack.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Special shells are replenished when picking up ammunition.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Both shotgun variants’ special shells retain their (high) regular damage output, plus special properties.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Specific Shell Variants:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mk III: Electric Shells - Stun enemies upon impact and give Electrocution debuff with Damage over time.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mk VIII: Rending Shells - Gives armor-breaking debuff.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Notes:</b> <i>The design intent for this is to give room for them to have a high impact. To be powerful with utility but scarce, so that you should consider saving it for difficult encounter</i>s.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are there synergies planned between the weapons and the rest of the Arbites’ Talent Tree?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Arbites talent tree has several nodes which enhance and/or are triggered by Blocking, which the <b>Shock Maul &amp; Suppression Shield</b> and the <b>Shotpistol &amp; Riot Shield</b> can easily utilize due to their strong block properties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The <b>Arbites Shock Maul</b> can benefit from any source of Electrocution to trigger its powerful Special Stun, while also having the ability to slot in the High Voltage weapon blessing.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How does the special work on the Shock Maul &amp; Suppression Shield?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Upon blocking attacks, the absorbed energy is converted into the Special gauge, indicated diegetically from a display in the inner side of the shield. The Special gauge also slowly refills passively over time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">When the gauge is at least half full, performing the Special input consumes half of the gauge and then triggers a high intensity shockwave in a cone in front of the shield, staggering nearby enemies and inflicting a high amount of Suppression in a large area.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Block properties of the shield are active while performing the Special, meaning it can be used as a safe way to turn the tempo of an engagement from defensive to offensive, but also to disorient ranged enemies before closing in for the kill.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What were the influences for these weapons?</b><br/>The inspiration for the shotgun was actually the Kill Team: Exaction Squad miniatures. A large Will of the Lex dispensing shotgun!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites shotgun Mk III:</b><br/>To elaborate. We imagined a large pump-action shotgun. Mk III comes with a duckbill muzzle (Horizontal spread with dynamic choke).</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The intent for it is to be great at clearing large hordes with hipfire, and competent elite single-target Aim Down Sights. Excelling at close to mid range. This should make for a versatile gun with interesting second-to-second gameplay.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites shotgun Mk VIII:</b><br/>While still being a large pump-action shotgun, the Mk VIII comes with an extended barrel and is a standard spread heavy-hitter variant. Intended for mid range, with armor piercing capabilities - it serves better as a single target focus weapon.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Shotpistol &amp; Riot Shield:</b><br/>Introducing the first ranged weapon with a shield in Darktide.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We wanted to create what you would expect from an Arbites hand-cannon and shield, offering a unique playstyle that blends offense and defense.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Shotpistol unleashes devastating pellets and allows blocking while firing. This is a different weapon compared to existing revolvers. For close encounters and melee combat, use the special to push attack or heavy shield swipe.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Shock Maul + Suppression Shield:</b><br/>The idea for this weapon was to use the shield to promote blocking as a useful tool alongside the other damage-avoiding mechanics, whilst also giving it a Special which can be activated to turn the tide from defense to offense.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We also added some attacks using the shield itself, giving it a dual-wielding feel.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites Shock Maul:</b><br/>The Adeptus Arbites field a large amount of mauls, so we wanted to explore the niche further by playing on their shock/stun repressive properties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This weapon employs a primer mechanic, where the Stun from the Special attacks is triggered only if hitting an already Electrocuted enemy.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since staggering with any attack triggers Electrocution, this creates a two-stage combo structure where players want to be looking at sources of bonus Impact and Electrocution to be able to follow-up immediately with a Special attack.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Do the shield weapons have any unique blocking properties?</b><br/>The <b>Shock Maul &amp; Suppression Shield</b> can block Ranged attacks coming from a frontal angle, while also being able to block normally unblockable attacks (e.g. Crushers’ overhead slams).</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The weapon also has a high base Stamina value and a stronger than usual Push.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites Shotpistol + Riot Shield</b> can be used to block both ranged and melee attacks, while maintaining the ability to shoot when blocking.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Animations</div><p class="bb_paragraph">To round this dev blog out, we’re going to talk about the animations with some of our animators, Jonas and Julia.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What was it like animating these new weapons?</b><br/>A different experience than usual for sure! There was quite a lot of going back and forth, adjusting the size and shape of the weapons to make sure that it fit well with the feeling of the combat loop of Darktide. The general feel that I wanted to go for with the Arbites weapons was heavy, methodical and relentless. I also looked up at some reference material of Arbites figurines and lore to get an idea of their behavior.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This time around I didn’t have any matching props for an assault shield, so I posed around using a cardboard cut-out to test and feel how to animate certain motions and actions. The Shotpistol reload actually came to be through me testing around with holding a prop gun in different unconventional ways. As usual, I probably looked like a reject finding out what guns are for the first time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">At first with the Shock Maul &amp; Suppression Shield, I animated the shield much slower and heavier, but at some point it felt too similar to the Ogryn slabshield and I made it a bit faster and lighter in motion. This decision made it a bit easier to incorporate the shield into the light attack chains.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Instead of making the shield feel slow and sluggish, I tried to mix it up a bit by making the<br/>Shock maul feel a bit more top-heavy instead. In the end I animated the Shock maul together<br/>with the shield to have a bit more anticipation and windups in the animations and having the<br/>impact feel a bit more like a baton. - Jonas</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Were there any challenges in the development of the Arbites’ weapons?</b><br/>In general I think there was a fun challenge in animating weapons with shields. Especially ranged weapons that kinda require you to use both hands when reloading or for a similar action. As an animator on Darktide I really want to highlight reloads or any other unique weapon interactions as much as possible.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">I think Shotpistol and Shield have been the most challenging weapon overall because of how<br/>you can cancel reload to go into a block. That is, since this weapon has a third state that allows<br/>you to block when you run out of ammo in-clip, it creates a lot of unexpected interactions for when going to reload and from reload or to any other disrupting action. - Jonas</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Which is your favourite weapon that you’ve worked on for Arbites?</b><br/>Hard to say to be completely honest. I think I like the Shotpistol and Shield most because of<br/>how different it is in comparison to other weapons. But I also really like how the new Shock Maul feels. - Jonas</p><p class="bb_paragraph">My favorite is the Shotgun, I think the model itself is really cool with its chunkyness and with the special ammo casings visible on top, and the designers did a great job with how it plays. I feel like the law! - Julia</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are there any unique animations associated with them?</b><br/>The Shotgun’s special ammo reload received a bit of a different animation than usual. There is special ammo attached to the top of the Shotgun model, which provided an opportunity to make an animation where you pick the ammo off one by one from the model itself instead of having the ammo arrive from out-of-frame. - Julia</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How long do animations for these take?</b><br/>It depends on the weapon and how it is going to work, but it can definitely take a while! Which was the case for the Arbites weapon family. Since we didn’t have any weapon family in Darktide that has a shield (Except for you Ogryn, you lovely brute), we chose to animate almost everything from scratch. Using Ogryn animations for this wouldn’t have worked because of rig and size differences.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There are about 220~ different animations for each weapon family/pattern that needs to work well together in a lot of different ways due to how fast-paced and high-action Darktide is. Around 50% of my time is spent on putting everything together in the state-machine, making sure that all the animations blend well. - Jonas</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What is your creative process?</b><br/>First I figure out how the weapon I’m going to animate actually functions, and try to find solid references for how they’re used. Then, for first person animations, I’m a big fan of using a GoPro as a sketching tool to showcase my early ideas and choreography. I attach it to my face (Yes, face! It looks ridiculous!) or chest, find a suitable weapon prop and then do some first person recording. It enables shaping and showcasing early ideas without having to spend any time in animation software or the game engine.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">But even without a GoPro, I like to act out the movement for more complex animations, like reloads for example. For me, it enables my first blockout pass to have passable motions and pacing, and having that to begin with makes it easier for me to push and exaggerate the timing within the movements to a speed that I myself am not able to do, but will be smooth and believable in the game context. - Julia</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The process I have is that I usually look up references for different weapons that I start working on, and learn more about the what, why and how on functionalities. Using those references on stances/poses/handlings I go further with the process of testing out motions myself with props and see what feels and looks convincing and good. After brainstorming ideas and testing around I start animating and tweaking so that it works for first-person view. - Jonas</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Any fun bits of trivia?</b><br/>When recording motion capture for the Shock Mine, we used a duct tape roll as our prop! - Julia</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading our dev blog on the making of your new weapons in your new Arbites Class, releasing on <b>June 23, 2025</b> on all platforms. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll do our best to answer them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War 25 years - Wallpaper giveaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/539982509474060349</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/20e2c5ed47308cfa8cb3345b14240fcfa54e9356.png"/><br/><br/>​Greetings, Total War fans!<br/> <br/>Decorate your screens and celebrate 25 years of Total War with a fancy new wallpaper.<br/> <br/>Head to the CA Community rewards section, and get this exclusive Anniversary Wallpaper now!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog: Free Update - Battle For Tertium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961123451</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alongside the release of the Arbites Class on June 23, Warhammer 40,000: Darktide will also receive a free update, dubbed Battle for Tertium.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">New Player Journey</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The core player experience has been reworked to provide a new clearer narrative focus, following the conflict of the Battle for Tertium. Players will now experience a linear campaign with new mission debriefs and embedded cinematics. This new progression path is designed to ease in new players and gradually unlock features that were previously gated by character level. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While previously each new player’s experience was completely random, the Battle for Tertium narrative presents maps, enemies and characters in a specific order, allowing players to discover all aspects of the game at a much better pace.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The story missions play the same as regular missions, except that these missions have a more tight control over which enemies spawn. You might also hear some new VO lines during missions, and some brand new mission debrief cinematics when completing each mission.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Existing players with characters at level 10 or higher can choose to skip the story or play it from the beginning</b>. Players who change their minds about playing the campaign can opt out by using the Personality Scourge at the Chirurgeon. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Mission Board Rework</div><p class="bb_paragraph">A new mission board system will be bringing several changes to how you engage with missions and difficulties. Missions are no longer tied to a specific difficulty, allowing you to select a mission and then choose the difficulty you want. This will effectively increase the amount of mission options available for players of all difficulty levels. While most circumstances remain consistent across difficulty levels, some are disabled on lower difficulties. Notably, Maelstrom missions are exclusive to the Heresy and Auric difficulties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, the difficulty system has also been overhauled. You now unlock new difficulties by completing missions rather than leveling up your characters. You must prove your skills at your current maximum difficulty to unlock access to the next one. We intend to create a motivation for new players to master the game step by step, and for veteran players to feel assured that their teammates have earned the right to be there.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">You will make progress by playing missions at your current maximum difficulty. Completing missions advances your progress. Failure reduces progress but very slightly. Additionally, you will never be demoted to a lower difficulty tier, regardless of how many missions you fail. Higher difficulties will require you to complete more missions to unlock them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>For existing characters, your difficulty progression will be migrated based on their character level and completed missions.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Auric is now a standalone difficulty tier, placed above Damnation. We felt that Auric Heresy fell in an awkward spot compared to Damnation, with the increased mission options per difficulty, we decided it was best to turn Auric into its own difficulty level. Additionally, we have removed Sedition difficulty and made a few minor changes to Uprising to take its place, as we felt there was too much downtime with too few enemies between hordes. These changes aim to keep you in the action more often.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>Mortis Trials</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Secrets of the Shipmistress</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Sefoni’s indiscretions are getting worse! During Mortis Trials, keen-eared Rejects now have the opportunity to sift pieces of Shipmistress Brahms’ past from the psychic chatter. How did she inherit the Mourningstar? What is she hiding? Is she really on the same side as Grendyl, let alone his irksome busybodies? Delve deeper into all these and more across dozens of new memory echoes, unlockable by claiming victory in the Mortis Trials!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note: </b><i>If you've ever wanted to relisten to the memory echoes you've unlocked in the Mortis Trials, you should take a look behind the pillars in the meat grinder.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New difficulty for Mortis Trials</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since the release of Mortis Trials we have noticed people requesting a higher challenge in Mortis Trials! So, we are adding a new difficulty, Auric, as well as some other small changes.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There will now be a shorter time in between waves.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Waves will now have more enemies and enemy types increasing variety.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We are changing the base difficulty to match an Auric difficulty mission.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Weapon Balancing</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This initial set of balance adjustments focuses on improving underperforming weapons so they can better compete with top-tier options. Some of these changes also pave the way for new weapons, such as the powerful signature shotgun coming with the Arbites class. Adjustments to existing shotguns were made to ensure the Arbites weapons feel satisfying without completely overshadowing their existing counterparts.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This first round is not exhaustive but represents a step toward better overall balance. While we are aware of some currently powerful weapons that need addressing, we chose to first elevate the lower-performing options rather than immediately nerfing the top ones.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Key Changes in Update 1.8.0:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">"Devil's Claw" Swords</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tactical Axes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shock Mauls</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Eviscerators</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Helbore Lasguns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Combat Shotguns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Double-barreled Shotgun</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Detailed notes of all changes can be found <b>HERE</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– The Darktide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
