<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4265553497866490903</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/154b4f3e9ad5eb3a98cdd87641b031e1e43741f7.jpg"/><br/><br/>Greeting folks,<br/><br/>Today we're rolling out Hotfix 5.1.1, addressing a number of issues that have come to light since the launch of Patch 5.1, as well as some additional balancing.<br/><br/>Here's what we've got for you today:<br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h3">General:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where vassals did not provide income after reloading a save. Vassals will now correctly provide income as intended.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some unit faction colours were too dark, resulting in their base materials not rendering correctly. Notably affecting empire units.<br/></li><li> Fixed rendering issues with Empire Outriders' guns which would result in either not rendering the gun or textures appearing weirdly.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Eldred's Guard weren't using the correct colours.<br/></li><li> Fixed UI issue where Tower of Zharr district completions effects were missing.<br/></li><li> Fixed lag in matchmade lobbies, and inability to change spell lores after locking in factions.<br/></li><li> Increased the Stegadon armour piercing missile damage from 150 to 350, as originally intended.<br/></li><li> Fixed Legendary Heroes not spawning if your faction capital is besieged, causing you to lose them in a given campaign.<br/></li><li> Fixed required resource bar in Chaos Gifts panel showing incorrect state.<br/></li><li> Fixed various character skills that were hidden from certain characters due to being overlapped by other skills.<br/></li><li> Updated Arkhan the Black's lord select movie to include eye VFX.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Boris Todbringer was missing some skills in his skill tree.<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of effects meant to apply to all Nurgle marked units not applying to Bile Trolls units.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the unique Dwarf Lord Mikael Leadstrong where his unit card would not display correctly.<br/></li><li> Fixed Cursed Yhetee Jawbone item not modifying armour piercing missile damage.<br/></li><li> Fixed the timer tooltip in Conquest battle mode showing the wrong winner/loser when the timer runs out.<br/></li><li> In Realm of Chaos campaign, fixed an issue where armies would teleport if they marched over a Teleport Locus while retreating from a battle in the Tzeentch realm.<br/></li><li> Removed the Mentor skill from the Legendary Heroes that had it. <i>This was misleading in most cases where other Heroes gained experienced (e.g. Saytang the Watcher would give experience to Gate Master Heroes) and in some cases, there would be no characters to give experience to. This now makes it consistent across all Legendary Heroes, as some did not have this skill.</i><br/></li><li> Fixed the counter on Book of Nagash showing the wrong values in multiplayer.<br/></li><li> Fixed slight hang when opening multiplayer campaigns or battles if the player had a lot of multiplayer saves.<br/></li><li> Fixed settlement label showing temporarily in between pre- and post-battle when autoresolving.<br/></li><li> Moved the button to swap between lores to the left hand side of the spell UI to give more space to the overcast toggle button.<br/></li><li> The Empire technology "Protection of the Patriarch" now also applies the ward save bonus to Battle Wizards that are part of garrisons.<br/></li><li> The Wood Elf technology "Hukon, the Sunderer" now also affects the Enigmas of Ghyran (Zoats) Regiment of Renown unit.<br/></li><li> The Altdorf College of Forbidden Magic and Altdorf Conclave of Forbidden Magic buildings for Vampire Counts now provide recruitment of the Mortis Engine and Terrorgheist units.<br/></li><li> Fixed the growth element on horde armies disappearing when selecting a hero inside that army.<br/></li><li> Improved the visuals of the Chaos Warhounds 2D porthole image.<br/></li><li> Fixed path of glory contact effects showing placeholder text instead of the correct contact tooltip.<br/></li><li> Fixed plague immunity icon on settlements not updating its tooltip on turn start.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where selecting Gotrek after Felix would make the empty rune slots disappear on Gotrek.<br/></li><li> Fixed events showing in Mortuary Cult and Forge panels after crafting an item, causing the panel to disappear until the event was dismissed. Events will now only pop after the panel is closed by the player.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in multiplayer campaigns where upon completing the mission to gain Karanak, the dilemma would appear for players rather than just the player completing the mission.<br/></li><li> Character type restrictions on ancillaries and magic items tooltip now always show, instead of only showing when trying to equip on an invalid type. (When valid, the text will show yellow instead of red.)<br/></li><li> Unit upgrades, such as the Wood Elf Aspect Upgrades, are now displayed in a consistent order.<br/></li><li> The enemy Skaven undercities UI panel no longer goes offscreen when there are multiple entries.<br/></li><li> Shadowy Dealings will now no longer discover your own Skaven undercities.<br/></li><li> Cost requirements will now no longer show on horde buildings you have already constructed.<br/></li><li> The "Warpstone Detonation" ability for Doom Flayer characters in Ikits Workshop no longer erroneously blasts targets with the "kill_self" phase from the Warpstone Detonation army ability, causing the user to instantly die.<br/></li><li> Fixed a material error for Malekith on Seraphon that caused invisible wings.<br/></li><li> Fixed a material error on the Knights of the Blazing Sun's shields.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Additional balancing:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Karanak:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Prey Of The Blood God<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage per tick: 67 -&gt; 33<br/></li><li> Max number of uses: infinite -&gt; 3<br/></li><li> Karanak was intended to get roughly the effect of a spirit leech alongside his net. Currently his damage per tick is identical spirit leech but it lasts twice as long, we've normalized this.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li> Deepwood Scouts (Swiftshiver Shards):<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Range 180 -&gt; 155<br/></li><li> Calibration distance 120 -&gt; 100<br/></li><li> At identical range to the regular deepwood scout arrows, swiftshiver shards outcompeted the regular arrows in every way, we're pushing this back a little to the midway point between the old and new value.</li></ul></li><li> Warshrine of Tzeentch:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Giver of Arcane Glory:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reserve winds generated per second at maximum intensity: 0.2 -&gt; 0.15<br/></li><li> Winds regeneration and reserve bonus only applies to the shrine itself. (No longer multiplies the bonuses to winds based on the number of nearby units.)<br/></li><li> Mastery bonus still applies to all nearby allies.<br/></li><li> While the dark gods are fickle, the gameplan we saw of players obliterating their own units with vortexes to kickstart an ultra rapid infinite mana engine wasn't quite intended. The intention is that your shrine itself is a generator that gets powered up by nearby deaths, not that nearby units become generators themselves, multiplying the payoff many times over. <i>Keep your wizards close, and your forces close but not that close.</i></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Modding:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Generated new up to date scripting documentation for modders including model hierarchy documentation. <i>This can be found by heading to the Steam folder on your PC and navigating to 'steamapps\common\Total War WARHAMMER III\assembly_kit\documentation\script\script'.</i></li></ul><hr/><br/>Alongside the above points, we are temporarily removing the ‘Bordeleaux Landing’ map in order to make some improvements. In Patch 5.1.0 we added a number of new maps originating from some of those made by our top community map creators, and after discussion with the original creator of this map, we agreed that it was badly implemented on our part. Our aim is to bring Bordeleaux Landing back in line with the creator’s original vision, and look forward to re-introducing it in a future update. If you’d like to check out the original, you can do so here.<br/><br/>As always, thanks for your feedback and bug reports. Should you experience any issues after updating to 5.1.1 please remember to let us know over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum so we can get them logged and investigated.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Dev Blog and Versus RAT Takeaways</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4231776500647364554</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Greetings Heroes and Pactsworn,</div><br/>My name is <b>Joakim</b>, Design Director on Vermintide 2, here with a game update recap just in time for the summer.<br/><br/>As you all know, we started this year with a <b>Closed </b>and an <b>Open Alpha Test</b> for <b>Versus</b>, we celebrated the <b>6th Anniversary</b> with a <i>Quiet Drink</i> and then wrapped up the Karak Azgaraz storyline with <b><i>A Parting of the Waves</i></b> - where Kruber’s team building excursion led to an encounter with <b>a new type of Chaos Warrior</b>.<br/><br/>A bit over a month ago, for <b>Warhammer Skulls 2024</b>, we released a big <b>Chaos Wastes and Things™ update</b> where we introduced <b>Weekly Expeditions</b> with new boons and rewards. Per popular demand, we added a <b>loadout system</b> to the game as well as the (even more requested) option to equip weapon illusions outside of Weaves. Both game modes saw some quality of life- and bug fixes, which increased their popularity and hopefully set you up for some fun games over the summer.<br/><br/>As for the <b>Skulls event</b> itself we once more had you collecting daemonic skulls and killing enemies - this year we set the aim for <b>1 billion kills</b>, which you reached on the last day of the event. We did notice an issue with kills not counting correctly for losses in Versus or Chaos Wastes and we mitigated that halfway through the event in honor of some of the more devout pilgrims of you (Shoutout to <b><i>Lancerkils</i></b> and his <i>113 Cataclysm attempts</i> in the first Weekly Expedition! Cousin Okri would be very proud indeed!)<br/>Also, being able to purchase last year’s frame and weapon illusions with shillings during the event seems to have gone down well, so we’ll take that into consideration going forward.<br/><br/>Halfway through Skulls, we booted up the <b>Returning Alpha Test</b>, or <b>RAT</b>, where just <b>over 25000 Steam</b> players kill-slayed together in over 16000 games of Versus. Compared to the last test, the GOAT, the test ran for a bit longer and introduced the <b>playable Bile Troll boss, pre-made Hero loadouts, and the PvP version of Against the Grain.</b> Based on previous feedback we addressed the hotjoin hero picker, tweaked and tinkered with balancing for some of the Pactsworn, as well as adjusted some Hero temp HP gain and decay.<br/><br/>The survey made an appearance again, and the responses show that you’re still happy with the way Versus is progressing, giving it an <b>8.38/10 rating</b>, with the score increasing for every test we do. Pactsworn are still perceived as more fun (no surprises there) but the Hero side is lagging behind. Part of this is due to class- and talent-specific balancing and tweaking, but other big requests relate to preventing speed running, onboarding &amp; practicing, as well as clearing up objectives and scoring; some being specific to Against the Grain while others apply to the mode as a whole. <br/><br/>Speaking of <b>Against the Grain</b> - it does play quite differently compared to the previous missions and we were really keen on seeing what you’d do with the open fields and long sightlines. So far the feedback is a bit mixed, but now we can compare your opinions on the <b>Screaming Bell, Righteous Stand, and Against the Grain missions.</b> Aside from being popular Adventure missions, <b>they represent a cross-section of Vermintide’s environments, map lengths, and topologies</b> that will guide future PvP mission work.<br/><br/>The <b>Bile Troll</b> was generally perceived as a good (although squishy) addition to the game mode that made boss-killing Hero careers more relevant; the Bounty Hunter, Outcast Engineer, and Zealot made it into the top 10 list for the first time, with weapon preference staying mostly the same apart from the addition of the Blunderbuss. On the Pactsworn side, the Globadier is still strong and the buffed Warpfire Thrower got a better rating in RAT.<br/><br/>As always - <b>a huge thank you</b> to everyone who participated in the test, to all of you who filled out the survey (we got nearly 750 responses to read through), as well as everyone posting videos, streams, and thoughts on social media, discord, and forums. We can’t do it without your invaluable feedback!<br/>We’ll be looking over all the feedback and bug reports to see what’s feasible for the next iteration - but as a lot of you wanted <b>more mechanics for the Pactsworn side</b> we’re looking into if we can expand their gameplay with some form of ability. We’re also making progress on <b>matchmaking</b> to pair up similarly skilled players for the next test, but we’re saving up on a Versus progression and reward system for release.<br/><br/><b>We are of course working on other things as well outside of Versus.</b> As a fun teaser, here’s an animation reference prop for a potential upcoming weapon. Care to guess what it is and who it is for? You might win a pumpkin, you lucky bleeders.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/28ceb60a63944f215bd899546dd3b877f0687d3b.png"/><br/><br/>Vermintide will take a bit of a break in July, but keep an eye out for updates and be hyped for an exciting autumn. By Sigmar, the Hammer, and the Empire - have a very pleasant summer!<br/><br/><i>Joakim, and the Vermintide team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097482596319</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f127c3bedc657be87151c262bd3b80a8dcf14d05.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey there Devoted Rejects, </div><br/>It’s that time of year again. During the month of July, a lot of people in Sweden take time off to enjoy the peak summer weather before it disappears. A lot of employees at Fatshark take this time, too. <br/><br/>While not everyone is going to be away, there will be less hotfixes during this time. The next hotfix is expected in the first full week of August.<br/><br/>We know communication from us has been a sore point for the community and we’re working on it. This isn’t going to be a period of silence. We are working through pages and pages of feedback from the Introduction to Itemization Rework dev blog. After talking more with the team, we hope to begin dropping at least a couple updates and responses to those questions in the form of additional news posts throughout July, with longer posts coming in August.<br/><br/>We are also working on a couple of dev blogs about creating Darktide and what it looks like from a game development perspective (think cinematics, voice overs and audio, etc.). These will be coming in July, as well.<br/><br/>Thank you again for the feedback recently and the opportunity to change the momentum. We’ll be talking soon. <br/><br/>P.S. In the meantime, have you listened to the newest Darktide OST? <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Devblog 8 - Deffkilla Wartrike 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4241909599807668128</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/66c1dfee82f7451b747f85ebe995c1e2cbb7d07e.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7b9cc95e1497b2ae0b77d83327d347961a4d3aef.png"/><br/><br/>The Deffkilla Wartrike is as heavily armed as it is brazen.  Built for close-quarters combat, this vehicle’s Speedboss will pull himself in quickly to rip hunks of hull off any vehicle unfortunate enough to be targeted.<br/><br/>Weave in and out of fights as you cut your opponent's vehicles to pieces with close range prowess. Hook onto petrified enemies and blast your boomstikks while reeling yourself in for the kill.  Nobody gets away from a Wartrik​e​ unscathed. <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b78437e4a2bfc2c8350c7ea16b34b4fd3c547208.png"/><br/>This vehicle currently has the second fastest base speed in the game, right behind the Shokkjump Dragsta. The Snagga klaw will allow you to latch on to enemies and pull yourself along at extreme speeds, making the Deffkilla Wartrike one of the best racing vehicles.<br/><br/>In Speedfreeks the Deffkilla Wartrike is best used strategically for finding opponents that are unsuspecting, damaged, or both. Take down enemies who find themselves out of position, and punish high value targets to push your team towards victory. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3bdafdd608eac99992595f178672c220ffbf5b26.png"/><br/><b>Twin Boomstikks</b><br/>Fire the stubby Ork shotguns mounted on the front of the bike.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/12e1f9c73a2f525d9bbdfc593d9178527ba1bf84.png"/><br/><b>Snagga-Klaw</b><br/>Krump ‘em with the Snagga-Klaw for big damage!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/94c4c4ae6de319d8d60d827f55059d2ec64f58c7.png"/><br/><b>Hook</b><br/>Shoot the barbed hook attached to the Snagga-Klaw at the targeted enemy and pull yourself towards them to deliver the killing blow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4346af90da9a6945385d1ba4948228ea4512fdb0.png"/><br/><b>Dash</b><br/>The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming determines where the vehicle will go.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/52ce4785d5322f5e740056744a0b27536efcf84d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Pro tip:</b> The Deffkilla Wartrike is very front-loaded with its forward facing Boomstikks and Snagga Klaw melee attack – which deals a lot of burst damage.  One of the best plays is to find a damaged enough enemy to secure a one-shot kill, and escape battle before the others realize what hit their mob.<br/><br/>Be mindful of your own hit points and be sure to have an escape plan if things get hairy.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-Ups</div><br/><b>Looted Wagon</b> – This long-range tank will spend most of its time shooting from afar as fire support. Keep an eye on who they’re shooting at, and race in to help finish enemies off before they can repair.<br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b> – Similar to the Looted Wagon, the dragsta likes to poke at enemies from afar, but also uses its speed to get shots in on harder to reach targets.  A combination of the Wartrike’s grapple and high damage klaw along with the Dragsta’s Shokk Rifle make this combo a scary one to be pursued by.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70bf4d96b1457562b172a3a5ee6bed4bc37dc0c8.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against</div><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b> – A perfect candidate for a quick drive by slashing by the Wartrike’s klaw to help pick apart the opposing team’s support.<br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b> – As the Shokkjump Dragsta cannot shoot backwards, you can use your hook to keep up with their speed, and chase them down. A single mistake can mean you stop them in their tracks.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weak Against</div><b>Grot Mega Tank</b> – Don’t underestimate this vehicle as it has a lot of health and is rarely alone. It can also use its repair ability to get an edge on hit points and pivot quickly to smash you down with its plow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cb40f778b22a24b856424fa455db909b04f6dba5.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Guides Recap</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999249951350</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Incoming Transmission</b><br/><br/><i>Attention, Lord Captains! Gather your crew and prepare for an extensive debriefing. Your exploits in the Koronus Expanse have been nothing short of legendary, and it's time to revisit your victories and prepare for what lies ahead.</i><br/><br/>Previously, we've been your loyal guides through the nebula of space combat, the artistry of character creation, and the tactical depths of ground combat.<br/><br/>Now, we're uniting our arsenal of tutorials for a recap.<br/>Whether you're a battle-hardened veteran or just preparing to start your own adventure, our video series has something for every Lord Captain. <br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Space Combat</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/odQ08XJUsDc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Character Creation</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GvfbRJvfGkQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Ground Combat </div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IA1C_6v4rP0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
