<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097482596319</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f127c3bedc657be87151c262bd3b80a8dcf14d05.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey there Devoted Rejects, </div><br/>It’s that time of year again. During the month of July, a lot of people in Sweden take time off to enjoy the peak summer weather before it disappears. A lot of employees at Fatshark take this time, too. <br/><br/>While not everyone is going to be away, there will be less hotfixes during this time. The next hotfix is expected in the first full week of August.<br/><br/>We know communication from us has been a sore point for the community and we’re working on it. This isn’t going to be a period of silence. We are working through pages and pages of feedback from the Introduction to Itemization Rework dev blog. After talking more with the team, we hope to begin dropping at least a couple updates and responses to those questions in the form of additional news posts throughout July, with longer posts coming in August.<br/><br/>We are also working on a couple of dev blogs about creating Darktide and what it looks like from a game development perspective (think cinematics, voice overs and audio, etc.). These will be coming in July, as well.<br/><br/>Thank you again for the feedback recently and the opportunity to change the momentum. We’ll be talking soon. <br/><br/>P.S. In the meantime, have you listened to the newest Darktide OST? <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Devblog 8 - Deffkilla Wartrike 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4241909599807668128</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/66c1dfee82f7451b747f85ebe995c1e2cbb7d07e.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7b9cc95e1497b2ae0b77d83327d347961a4d3aef.png"/><br/><br/>The Deffkilla Wartrike is as heavily armed as it is brazen.  Built for close-quarters combat, this vehicle’s Speedboss will pull himself in quickly to rip hunks of hull off any vehicle unfortunate enough to be targeted.<br/><br/>Weave in and out of fights as you cut your opponent's vehicles to pieces with close range prowess. Hook onto petrified enemies and blast your boomstikks while reeling yourself in for the kill.  Nobody gets away from a Wartrik​e​ unscathed. <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b78437e4a2bfc2c8350c7ea16b34b4fd3c547208.png"/><br/>This vehicle currently has the second fastest base speed in the game, right behind the Shokkjump Dragsta. The Snagga klaw will allow you to latch on to enemies and pull yourself along at extreme speeds, making the Deffkilla Wartrike one of the best racing vehicles.<br/><br/>In Speedfreeks the Deffkilla Wartrike is best used strategically for finding opponents that are unsuspecting, damaged, or both. Take down enemies who find themselves out of position, and punish high value targets to push your team towards victory. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3bdafdd608eac99992595f178672c220ffbf5b26.png"/><br/><b>Twin Boomstikks</b><br/>Fire the stubby Ork shotguns mounted on the front of the bike.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/12e1f9c73a2f525d9bbdfc593d9178527ba1bf84.png"/><br/><b>Snagga-Klaw</b><br/>Krump ‘em with the Snagga-Klaw for big damage!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/94c4c4ae6de319d8d60d827f55059d2ec64f58c7.png"/><br/><b>Hook</b><br/>Shoot the barbed hook attached to the Snagga-Klaw at the targeted enemy and pull yourself towards them to deliver the killing blow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4346af90da9a6945385d1ba4948228ea4512fdb0.png"/><br/><b>Dash</b><br/>The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming determines where the vehicle will go.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/52ce4785d5322f5e740056744a0b27536efcf84d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Pro tip:</b> The Deffkilla Wartrike is very front-loaded with its forward facing Boomstikks and Snagga Klaw melee attack – which deals a lot of burst damage.  One of the best plays is to find a damaged enough enemy to secure a one-shot kill, and escape battle before the others realize what hit their mob.<br/><br/>Be mindful of your own hit points and be sure to have an escape plan if things get hairy.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-Ups</div><br/><b>Looted Wagon</b> – This long-range tank will spend most of its time shooting from afar as fire support. Keep an eye on who they’re shooting at, and race in to help finish enemies off before they can repair.<br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b> – Similar to the Looted Wagon, the dragsta likes to poke at enemies from afar, but also uses its speed to get shots in on harder to reach targets.  A combination of the Wartrike’s grapple and high damage klaw along with the Dragsta’s Shokk Rifle make this combo a scary one to be pursued by.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70bf4d96b1457562b172a3a5ee6bed4bc37dc0c8.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against</div><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b> – A perfect candidate for a quick drive by slashing by the Wartrike’s klaw to help pick apart the opposing team’s support.<br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b> – As the Shokkjump Dragsta cannot shoot backwards, you can use your hook to keep up with their speed, and chase them down. A single mistake can mean you stop them in their tracks.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weak Against</div><b>Grot Mega Tank</b> – Don’t underestimate this vehicle as it has a lot of health and is rarely alone. It can also use its repair ability to get an edge on hit points and pivot quickly to smash you down with its plow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cb40f778b22a24b856424fa455db909b04f6dba5.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Guides Recap</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999249951350</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Incoming Transmission</b><br/><br/><i>Attention, Lord Captains! Gather your crew and prepare for an extensive debriefing. Your exploits in the Koronus Expanse have been nothing short of legendary, and it's time to revisit your victories and prepare for what lies ahead.</i><br/><br/>Previously, we've been your loyal guides through the nebula of space combat, the artistry of character creation, and the tactical depths of ground combat.<br/><br/>Now, we're uniting our arsenal of tutorials for a recap.<br/>Whether you're a battle-hardened veteran or just preparing to start your own adventure, our video series has something for every Lord Captain. <br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Space Combat</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/odQ08XJUsDc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Character Creation</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GvfbRJvfGkQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Ground Combat </div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IA1C_6v4rP0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #43 (1.4.3) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097478200713</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7325b82f44f883c94461a6b74b9c637492f6277c.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey there Devoted Rejects,</div><br/>Hotfix #43 (aka 1.4.3) is now live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms.<br/><br/>(<b>Note</b>: <i>It takes a little bit of time after the release of the hotfix before the old servers are disconnected and players are migrated over to the new one.</i>) 🙏<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reverted an issue that caused some players to experience crashes when entering the game. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 11:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #42 (1.4.2) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097474985883</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1a637bfb339920cd74ea325ed0192297010bde15.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey there Devoted Rejects,</div>Hotfix #42 (1.4.2) is out now on Steam and it will shortly be out on our other platforms.<br/><br/>(<b>Note</b>: <i>It takes a little bit of time after the release of the hotfix before the old servers are disconnected and players are migrated over to the new one.</i>) :pray:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Combat</div><div class="bb_h3">Shooters</div>Reverting the following Shooter Changes from the 1.4.0 Patch:<br/><i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Scab Shooters now have a tighter shot spread, making them more threatening at range. While they still have ranged damage falloff, they will be more consistent in how they hit players at range.<br/></li><li> Additionally, Scab/Dreg shooters will now stay in cover longer (and remain exposed longer) with a reduced cooldown between sprays, making cover-taking enemies more of a threat but also enhancing the viability of player weapons that apply suppression.</li></ul></i><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are pulling back a few of the Enemy changes from the Previous Patch, as they were a bit too oppressive.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased the range of what would be considered Close Range: 8m to 12.5m.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>In Patch #13 (Class Rework), we changed Close Range from 15m to 8m, and in return increased the power of Blessings triggered only in Close Range e.g. Fire Frenzy and Deathspitter. We did this because we wanted to differentiate the Close Range Gunplay a bit more from the Far Range one. This was considered by many as a bug, though it was an intended change. However, we have re-evaluated that change, and while we after some extensive testing still believe 15m is a little too far, we think 12.5m is a justified increase. This will also increase the power of specific Talents tied to Close Damage such as Veteran’s ‘Close Quarters Killzone’ and Zealot’s ‘Anoint in Blood’ which we will monitor closely.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div><b>Tigrus Mk XV Heavy Eviscerator</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bumped the speed for windup timings of Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attacks:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Heavy 1 chained from base start or Light 4: 0.4 (unchanged)<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.76 to 0.65<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 chained from Light 1 / Heavy 1 from 0.85 to 0.65<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 chained from Light 3 / push follow-up from 0.6 to 0.4.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i> The windup timing for Heavy attacks varied significantly depending on which attack they were chained from. The windup timings should now be more aligned with each other, and in general shorter to reward players accessing attacks further down the chain instead of resetting the combo.</i><br/><br/><b>Artemia Mk III Purgation Flamer</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bumped power distribution for primary and secondary direct fire:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primary burst attack from (10,20) to (15,30)<br/></li><li> Secondary continuous attack from (30,50) to (60,100)</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Damage scales with distance and time inside the cloud. Burn damage and max stacks are unaffected by the change.</i><br/><b>Ogryn Pickaxes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Normalised the attack ranges for all marks.<br/></li><li> Slightly tuned the damage window timing for specific attacks to be more accurate with the attack animation.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes*</div><br/><b>*Dev Note:</b> <i>You can view the exact number value changes at the bottom of these patch notes.</i><br/><br/><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Slightly reduced reach for the Light 1 attack.<br/></li><li> Improved reach for the Light 2, Light 3, Heavy 1 attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Push follow-up attack.</li></ul><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved reach of the Light 1, Light 2, Light 3 attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Heavy 1, Heavy 2 attacks.</li></ul><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved reach of the Light 1, Light 2, Light 3, Light 4, Light special follow-up, Heavy special follow-up attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Heavy 1, Heavy 2 attacks</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The reach of the attacks for Ogryn Pickaxes differed significantly between marks or even different attacks in the same mark, and in several cases it was shorter than the attack range of other Ogryn weapons.<br/><br/>We performed a pass on all attacks, normalising the ranges and in general bumping up the values to make sure that these two-handed weapons always have the reach appropriate to their size.<br/><br/>We also fine-tuned the time windows where some specific attacks are active, to be more aligned to their attack animations.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><b>Clandestium Gloriana</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with the valkyrie in the outro cutscene.<br/></li><li> Did some various optimisations to assets.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players were unable to interact with pickups under a pile of snow.<br/></li><li> Fixed some visual bugs during the horizontal shuttle ride.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where deploying a med kit or ammo box would have it go through the floor of the horizontal shuttle.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>However, there is still a known issue where it lands a bit further back than where you deployed it, so for now be careful to not deploy it too far back in the transport.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with a small corner before the middle event where players would get instantly killed when standing there.<br/></li><li> Side missions like grimoires and tomes should now count correctly.<br/></li><li> Fixed a location where bots would often fall off the side of the map.<br/></li><li> Fixed so enemies can now reach you inside the elevator.</li></ul><b>Excise Vault Spireside-13</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed wall unit lacking collision allowing players to leave gameplay space.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are aware that in bulk-lifter-32 some pick-ups cannot be collected, and one is floating. We will be addressing these in the next hotfix.</i><br/><br/><b>Enclavum Baross</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some VO lines at the end of Enclavum Baross did not trigger at all.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Additional Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue related to memory that caused stalls and crashes or disconnects for players (especially those playing with mods).<br/></li><li> Fixed issue which caused penances tracking mission types not to progress.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Any missions that were completed during this time will not be added after this fix. We apologise for not catching this sooner.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Torment blessing did not work on the Branx Pickaxe special poke attack.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where “Crosshair Type” user settings didn’t revert when using the “Reset to Default Settings” button.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Force Staves incorrectly had their crosshairs overridden when using anything but the “Weapon Specific” option of “Crosshair Type”.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with candle flame blocking line of sight with the Magistratum Bolt Pistol (Blessed) skin. Candle flame effect disabled until we move the candle slightly, it will be reenabled in a later patch.<br/></li><li> Fixed crash when trying to equip a trinket with the Magistratum Bolt Pistol (Blessed) skin equipped.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue which caused some players to need to reassign keybinds, or being unable to assign some keybinds at all.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where heavy melee attacks would be cancelled to light attacks if an Ability was used during the windup of the attack.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This fix does reintroduce an issue where players cannot activate the Zealots ‘Chorus of Spiritual Fortitude’ or the Psykers Telekine Field/Dome’ Abilities while charging a heavy attack. We decided this was better than leaving this issue unaddressed. We will investigate potential solutions that address these issues without affecting other abilities.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the text for Psyker’s “Malefic Momentum” where it wasn’t localised.<br/></li><li> Fixed missing pipes on Zealot’s headgear, Magistratum Scrivener’s helmet.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where part of the mannequin was missing when viewing Magistratum Mk II Patrol Uniform.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the pipes on Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress were deformed for female characters.<br/></li><li> Fixed additional clipping issues on the pipes for the Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress.<br/></li><li> Fixed some visual issues with the Magistratum Mk II Patrol Uniform knee pad stretching when emoting.<br/></li><li> Removed the glass material in the slit of the Magistratum Riot Shield skin.</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>This is to fix an issue where several visual effects were not correctly rendered through the shield slit due to conflicting transparency with the glass material.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed clipping issues with the glove on Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress.<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping issues for the Baross Patrol Armour (XXXXL).<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping issues for the Enforcer Patrol Helmet (XXXXL).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Tome Xenos accessory did not properly align with the Magistratum Mk V Patrol Armour cosmetic.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes for Pickaxes (Numbers)</div><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.2<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window start from 12/30 to 10/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.55<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.35<br/></li><li> Light 3 damage window end from 22/30 to 24/30<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.5 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Push follow-up range mod from 2 to 2.5.</li></ul><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window start from 9/30 to 12/30<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window end from 15/30 to 16/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.5<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.4.</li></ul><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window end from 15/30 to 16/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.4<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.38<br/></li><li> Light 4 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.67<br/></li><li> Light special follow-up range mod from 1.25 to 1.35<br/></li><li> Heavy special follow-up range mod from 1.3 to 1.5.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
