<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Commissar Report I &amp; II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157956347822483</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<i><div class="bb_h3">[1]<br/>MILITARUM WARZONE MISSIVE ALPHA-ONE<br/>TO: Astra Militarum (Moebian) Command Staff<br/>FROM: Dukane, D. Commissar<br/>++via astro-node x-sym-226-aleph++</div></i><br/><br/>My honoured lords militant. I am now in rapid transit to the capital world Atoma Prime, lacking as I am updated orders from you. I intend to build upon the instructions you have already blessed me with, which is to say to inject fire and disciplined determination into our beleaguered forces in the face of this wretched traitor uprising.<br/>	There is no time to regroup for direct consultation. In the last few months (relative) the Traitorous 6th have committed sundry crimes of violence and treachery across the Domain. This would be unacceptable from any adversary, but when this horror is perpetrated by soldiers of the Astra Militarum, it is a crime and an outrage against our highest honour. I do not have the words to express my disgust. These were our own people. <br/>	The 53rd Steelheads are proud soldiers, impeccable in their loyalty. Moreover, as I need not remind you, they are Branx-born. Like their birth world, they are young and aspirational. Atoma Prime has ruled the Domain for too long. It has grown fat and lazy, and slumped into privileged corruption. How else can one explain the gross deviation of their infamous 6th? Atoma, and the Lord Margrave, has allowed this treason to breed. Yes, Atoma must be freed and delivered. Yes, the traitors must be expunged without delay. But beyond that, I believe that the ancient hive must be soundly purged. The uprising must be put down and the enemy eradicated, but the soil from which this infamy sprang must also be cleansed with fire. <br/>	It must be the Astra Militarum that achieves this. I trust, my lords, that you will concur with my intent. The direct military deployment of the Steelheads, their honour bruised and their pride mauled, is the most expedient solution, and it is the most just. Let us clean our own house. Let the Guard restore its own dignity. <br/>	I am told, by coded transmission, that an Inquisitorial warband leads the reclamation effort on Atoma. On the one hand, I am reassured by this. On the other, I am dismayed by the lack of material strength. A warband is merely paramilitary. This outrage requires a response of the full force of the Astra Militarum on a formal war footing. Rest assured that, under my direction, the 53rd will execute the matter with the strictest and most steadfast discipline, a credit to the Throne and the Aquila banner.<br/>	I invite your response and instruction, but until any such is received, I will press on with my intent as stated above and bring legitimate war and restored honour to the hive of Atoma.  The Emperor protects, and the Guard prevails. <br/><br/>[affirmed by my sigil] - Dukane.    <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><i><div class="bb_h3">[2]<br/>MILITARUM WARZONE MISSIVE ALPHA-TWO<br/>TO: Astra Militarum (Moebian) Command Staff<br/>FROM: Dukane, D. Commissar<br/>++via astro-node z-ki-787-talos++</div></i><br/><br/>My honoured lords militant. Upon Atoma, in the great and ancient hive of Tertium, things are worse than we feared. The Traitor forces, all soldiers of the once vaunted Moebian 6th, now deplorably transformed by heresy and corruption, have wrought great damage and hardship and, further, have claimed significant areas of territory. <br/>I have conferred with the Inquisitorial undertaking, in the person of one Rannick (though not directly with their Inquisitor himself, an individual known as Grendyl). I fear this Grendyl may be trying to keep me and the Steelheads at arm’s length, out of concern that we might fall as the 6th fell. The Ordos clearly have little faith in the Astra Militarum. Rannick, for his part, insists to me that the corruption of the very Warp itself has lodged within the hearts of the traitors, and that we face a foe empowered by forces beyond mortal limit. I remain unconvinced. I believe we face an enemy driven by disdain, by privation, and by idolatry, and an enemy that has been allowed to breed thanks to the venal weakness of a hive and a ruling society that has fallen prey to its own luxuriating entitlement. I have declared to Rannick that the Steelheads are born of greater mettle, and thus can be fully trusted, for they are not prey to such infantile whimsy.<br/>	Of the Inquisitorial warband itself, I have little to remark. They are, for the most part, thugs and rejects, who seem little better or more disciplined than the very traitors we combat. They are ill-tempered, and regulation-shy. They are not soldiers, and they certainly lack the numerical strength to achieve any lasting compliance. Further, their loyalty to the Throne appears shabby and forced, not bright and willing as is the case with the Astra Militarum Steelheads. I will, in fairness and balance, record that this “warband” has fought hard and at great cost thus far, achieving some gains against the enemy. But it is not enough, and they are not enough, and I fear that their morale will soon snap as thoroughly as the loyalty of the Traitorous 6th. I will take field command of their endeavours, and have my trusted sergeants train their rabble squads to something approaching military composure.<br/>	This is a perilous situation. For all its wrongs and its canker, Atoma cannot be allowed to fall and give this enemy a foothold in the Domain. The Emperor protects, and in his name, the Steelheads will prevail. <br/><br/>[affirmed by my sigil] - Dukane.  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Interested in learning more about Commissar Dukane? Check out our latest Vox Intercept</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fZqECA5-Rx8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><b>Don't forget to <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="The URL that was linked here has been removed by our filters.  Usually this is done to prevent phishing and malware attacks.">{LINK REMOVED}</span>join our newsletter to stay up to date with all things Darktide!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 19:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLC Survey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557172354851012984</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>To all Rogue Traders of the Koronus Expanse! Word has reached us of the illustrious ways in which you've dealt with the new trials. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Share with us your insights on the mysterious Death Cults and your most recent adventures!</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c037f3353cb7c2836a9156cbac6f402b47e77314.jpg"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Blog - Progression Rework</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4540283856248373497</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hi, my name is <b>Joakim Setterberg</b> and I’m the Design Director on Vermintide 2. The season of Geheimnisnacht, pumpkins, and general spookiness is upon us, and on behalf of the team, I’d like to share some upcoming changes coming to Vermintide 2.<br/><br/>Over the last year, we’ve touched on nearly all areas of Vermintide 2 to improve the core experience of the game with a wide range of features, updates, and improvements. I’m sure Saltzpyre would agree that like an old Reikland wine, we are not aging, we are delicately <i>maturing.</i> One thing we haven’t done though is to address some of the frustrations and issues we’re seeing for players that are new to the game. With the upcoming Versus mode being an opportunity for new players to jump in and experience the End Times, we want to make some improvements to our onboarding and progression to help those new recruits to stick around.<br/><br/>Let’s start out with the issues we’re seeing:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> If you’re starting as a new player, the restrictions on Hero and Power levels make it hard for you to play together with experienced players until you have leveled up. This is particularly tough if you’ve been recommended to play Vermintide 2 by a high-level friend.<br/></li><li> The time investment to level up a Hero or career is quite significant, making it a slow grind to unlock a fun playstyle and/or promote a behavior where players feel the need to play (Screaming Bell) repeatedly on lower difficulties.<br/></li><li> The Spoils of War chest rewards are varied enough, but the gear journey can be unsatisfying due to random factors, and promotes Commendation Chest hoarding until you’ve reached higher Item Power levers.<br/></li><li> The drop rates for the Spoils of War are not visible to players, which results in community guesswork and a lack of motivation to play certain difficulties.</li></ul>So going forward, what are we changing to improve the Ubersreik 5 experience?<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Unlocking Difficulty</div><br/>First off, we’re removing any Hero Power restrictions for Private games. This should make it easier for a mixed group of friends to find a difficulty they can tackle together (and if said friends think your first experience should be Legend then… well, friendship carries a long way). It is also a chance for new players to check out the higher difficulties and practice for those Legend runs.<br/><br/>We’ve also removed the Hero Power restriction for the Veteran difficulty for Public games. We believe that Veteran can be a suitable entry point for players familiar with similar games, like Darktide, and are looking for a more challenging experience. However, we are keeping the Public restrictions for Champion and Legend as a necessary skill-check (although we have lowered those requirements just a tad) - the same goes for Cataclysm.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Introducing Experience Multipliers</div><br/>To tweak the time investment for leveling we are (re-)introducing Difficulty Multipliers to the experience gains when playing a mission. When completing a mission you will now get the regular XP gain multiplied by an additional 0.25 for each difficulty level:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 1x for Recruit (same as current)<br/></li><li> 1.25x for Veteran<br/></li><li> 1.5x for Champion<br/></li><li> 1.75x for Legend and Cataclysm</li></ul>We hope that this better motivates and rewards players leveling - especially when progressing their other careers that have unlocked and gotten access to better equipment like necklaces, charms, and trinkets.<br/><br/>For our PC players, Versus will have its own game mode-specific progression, but doing things like completing matches will also feed into the main progression.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Reworking Spoils of War</div><br/>To make the journey to get better gear both faster and more interesting, we are making some significant changes to the way Spoils of War rewards work. <br/><br/>All gear has an Item Power value attached to it that indicates how good it is. Without going into detail, the way Item Power rewards are currently calculated is based on an average obtained Item Power level with a random modifier attached to it, which leads to players getting generally slightly better loot than they previously have obtained. We are now changing this to be a range based on Hero Level, Difficulty played, and Chest Tier.<br/><br/>So when completing a mission you will get a Spoils of War chest, like normal. The rewards it contains will be within a range defined by your Hero Level, with a floor and ceiling cap based on the Difficulty. Recruit is capped out at an Item Power level of 100, Veteran at 200, and Champion and beyond at 300. Chest Tiers, upgraded by Ranald’s Blessings, Tomes, Loot Die, and Grimoires, will raise the floor of the range to push the rewards to higher Item Power levels. As you level up your Hero, the range first expands and subsequently narrows toward the higher end of the range.<br/><br/>With Spoils of War rewards being dependent on the Hero level when obtaining the chest, a chest obtained in level 1 will now yield level 1 Item Power rewards, regardless of when opening it. Thus, we are removing an incentive to hoard chests when leveling up, and instead aim for players to continuously open chests for more satisfying “jumps” in Item Levels (over the current flattened grind).<br/><br/>Related to this we are also changing the Rarity rates for rewards to not factor in Hero Levels. Again, we are simplifying the way the system works to make rare loot drops possible in every game. You will now almost always have a chance to get Common, Rare, Exotic, and even Veteran items from a game, but by playing on higher Difficulties and upgrading your Chest Tiers you will simply increase your chances for the rarer items. This means that you don’t have to have that perfect book run to get a cool reward and that you might get lucky finding a rare weapon even when starting out playing the game.<br/>Veteran items will always be maxed out within your current Item Power level range.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a15fb370715dd5f6358683667a0bb2792e6993e2.jpg"/><br/>In addition, we're also changing how we decide what weapon skin you get when opening a Veteran weapon in a chest. You will now, if possible, get a non-unlocked veteran skin before defaulting back to a random skin. We're also making it possible to obtain DLC weapons from chests (as long as you've unlocked all requirements for said weapons)<br/><br/>We hope that these changes will incentivize players to open Spoils of War more regularly as they progress, especially Commendation chests, rather than hoarding them - but we will of course be open to your feedback for any adjustments to all of the systems previously mentioned.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Crafting Changes</div><br/><i>“Hold on, drengbarazi, surely you aren’t reworking crafting as well?”</i><br/>Well, we are making some changes to it to align it with the rewards rework. So first off the items you craft will be based on your Hero level, similar to chests, with Veteran rarities set to the max of your possible range. However, upgrading to Veteran will only be available for Hero level 30 or above to ensure that players don’t spend their crafting materials at a point where they will come to regret it later. <br/><br/>The crafting economy will see some tweaks where we’re generally lowering upgrade costs by decreasing the amount of Scraps needed, but also requiring a small amount of Dust. To balance this we will be giving players more Dust when converting higher rarity Dust into lower rarities.<br/><br/>Oh, and we are also making sure that item properties and traits remain after an upgrade, so you will now be able to more reliably tinker with your favorite gear.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Showing the Numbers</div><br/>As you can see, these are significant changes we are doing to the item and rewards system. Our intention is simplification, but we can’t do that without making it all understandable in-game. With this update, we are providing additional information in the Difficulty Select menu screen, as well as for individual Spoils of War chests, where the Item Power range and rarity percentages are clearly visible. Again, we hope that this clears up any confusion and motivates players to push for harder Difficulties and increased Chest Tiers, as the Ubersreik 5 can more clearly see what to expect in terms of potential rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/81dbb91928097d8fd159e51821fb4b47fd58cf38.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Introducing the Handbook</div><br/>On the note of showing things, there is a lot of information a new player needs to understand about how the game works. Everyone gets to play the Prologue in the beginning, but after that we are pretty much throwing the players into the fight against Skaven, Chaos, and Beastmen without further onboarding. So far it’s been working OK, but there are a lot of nuances and mechanics to the game that you as a community have (very helpfully) had to relay through forums and social posts. We want to provide that same information in-game without adding more tutorials you need to play through, so we are happy to announce the in-game Handbook, available both as a Menu, with an interaction point in the Keep, and as helpful pop-ups when reaching key moments in the progression.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/f02b1d2159a39a8d924db9685351f95134772568.jpg"/><br/>The Handbook is a collection of images and short videos explaining the mechanics and systems of Vermintide 2. Initially, we’ve focused on the basics, but there is room to expand this feature in the future to dig deeper into specific game knowledge for our various game modes. Make sure to feedback and comment for features that you would really have liked to see when starting out (or even have missed as a veteran player)!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">So when do you get to see this?</div><br/>We’re aiming to have this out for the release of Versus later this fall. Due to certification and submission processes on consoles being slower than on PC, we’re hoping to get those platforms on an even footing shortly after.<br/><br/>We will also get around to some additional career balancing around the same time - more details at a later date - but for Geheimnisnacht we’ve snuck in an initial fix addressing the Outcast Engineer bomb cooldown bug. <br/><br/>Also we haven’t forgotten about Adventure - here’s a little <b>teaser image</b> for something that will come out in just a bit.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/d27a272793b8ca02cd212b9868cffaf925a9be42.png"/><br/>On behalf of the Vermintide production team and Fatshark, <i>thank you</i> for all the support and memes throughout the year - and stay hyped for a packed finale of 2024!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 15:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Random Vehicle - Timed Mode  💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4676515207786597647</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Random Vehicles</b> is a limited time mode that challenges players to succeed without selecting their preferred vehicle. Often a fun way to warm up, and who knows, random mode might introduce you to different styles of gameplay that you might not have considered before. <br/><br/>For this weekend, until Monday, vehicle select screen does not exist. Players are given a random vehicle each time they spawn.<br/><br/>This mode applies to all 8vs.8 Deff Rally maps<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c053a6ed3708e01119672334b0cdf738f6c5f604.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 4.1 and Game Director commentary</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4530150757095178287</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Hi, Space Marines!</div><br/><i>As we discussed late last week, we’ve been monitoring your feedback since last Thursday’s Patch 4.0 and have decided to address your most pressing concerns with a new balancing update, coming <b>this Thursday</b>.<br/><br/>Before we get to the details of the new patch, we want to thank you all for being so involved with the game and making your opinions heard. While we noticed criticism with regards to difficulty adjustments—and rightly so—we’d also like to thank you for your very positive feedback on the new “Termination” map. No matter the feedback, we’re grateful that you feel so passionate about <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>. The key takeaway for me, personally, is that I forgot that once the game comes out, it's no longer a dev's game. It's yours first and foremost.<br/><br/>This is why, moving forward, we’d like to harness this energy by establishing Public Test Servers. They would let you try out major balancing updates and make your voices heard before they are pushed onto public branches. We’re hoping to make these available around early 2025, so stay tuned to our channels for more info</i>.<br/><br/>‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎  -  Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a98158606c540cd7d874f94c1c764dfce8617dbc.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Gameplay and Balancing Tweaks - Operations mode </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">AI director and enemy spawns</div><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>Here was our reasoning before Patch 4.0: When the game came out in September, the Ruthless difficulty win rate hovered around 60%. Weeks later, and with the changes introduced by Patch 3.0, we saw that the same win rate had jumped to over 80%, and we received a lot of feedback stating that the game had become too easy—even at its maximum difficulty (at the time).</i><br/><br/><i>With Patch 4.0, our aim was to tweak enemy spawns to increase the overall number of enemies rather than reverting to buffing their Health. Unfortunately, this had an impact on the easier difficulty levels as well.<br/><br/>For example, the win rate on the easiest difficulty dropped slightly after Patch 4.0, from 95% to 93%. This may not look like a lot, but numbers aren’t everything. Your feedback made it clear that the game had become more intense and stressful on lower difficulties, and this was never our intention. As I’ve personally emphasised in interviews, Space Marine 2 is all about the power fantasy, and Patch 4.0 negatively impacted it for many of you.<br/><br/>This is why we’re rolling back these changes. Extremis enemies’ spawn rates in Minimal, Average, and Substantial difficulties will revert back to their pre-Patch 4.0 levels and will be significantly reduced in Ruthless difficulty to hopefully strike a balance between how hard the game was at launch and how “easy” it became with Patch 3.0.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u>Minimal, Average, and Substantial Difficulties</u>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced spawn rate of Extremis enemies to match pre-Patch 4.0 levels</li></ul><u>Ruthless Difficulty</u>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Significantly reduced spawn rate of Extremis enemies</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ea8e4d47f0ca45ce397a78fe792d6c22b51cb365.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Weapons (only in Operations mode)</div><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>We've been wanting to address the Bolter family for a while, as they've been underperforming across all difficulty levels. This has been a frequent piece of feedback from many of you, and the data confirmed improvements were needed across the board. The percent Damage increase is based on which classes have access to which kind of weapon and how the Bolters compete with the other options available.</i> <br/>‎  <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Auto Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 20%<br/></li><li> Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Heavy Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Stalker Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Marksman Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Instigator Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Bolt Sniper Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 12.5%<br/></li><li> Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Occulus Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Heavy Bolter -&gt; Damage increased by 5%</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/48cbeba86ee7252b6da6a6c181eb6b66f4bd42e5.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Difficulty</div><br/><u><b>⚙️ Ruthless: Player’s Armour is increased by 10%</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>We are partially rolling back the change from the previous patch on Ruthless difficulty following your feedback. With Patch 4.1, we’re hoping to find the right compromise between how easy Ruthless difficulty felt after Patch 3.0 and how it felt after last week’s Patch 4.0.<br/> <br/>The reason why it was reduced last week was that we noticed a very substantial bump in win rates on Ruthless after Patch 3.0, as Minoris enemies would no longer remove the entire Armour bar with their attacks, ranged AI Damage was nerfed across the board, and the ability to regenerate Armour by parrying normal Minoris attacks was added.<br/><br/>Additional note: Despite the last patch notes listing a decrease in Armour in Substantial difficulty, this change was mistakenly left out of our last update, hence why you won’t see it being reverted as part of this week’s patch.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u><b>⚙️ Lethal: “Tight Formation” system is removed</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>Before anything else, let us clarify our reasoning for the introduction of this mechanic. As we worked on adding a new difficulty tier, we needed to make sure this new challenge was meaningful and interesting. With “Tight Formation”, our objective was to add a new layer of challenge for our most skilled players by adding horizontal progression rather than just vertical progression (i.e., dealing more damage to ever stronger enemies). This game is about the power fantasy, and enemies that take dozens of melee hits break it. Thus the challenge needed to come from other sources.<br/> <br/>This system was also designed as a first step towards the introduction of gameplay modifiers down the line, both negative and positive—something World War Z players will be familiar with—but your feedback showed that the proximity requirements felt too restrictive. Classes like Assault and Vanguard felt especially penalised as playing them effectively requires a certain freedom of movement.<br/><br/>As a result, we’re removing the system entirely and will continue to work on modifiers until they’re ready. We will continue to monitor your feedback after the deployment of Patch 4.1 to make sure Lethal difficulty feels as challenging and rewarding as it should.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u><b>⚙️ AI</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>A recurrent piece of feedback we’ve seen is that the AI allies can feel useless at times. We already improved allies’ behaviour in Patch 3.0, and we hope this additional buff will help solo players complete their Operations.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bots deal 30% more damage to bosses.</li></ul><i>DG</i>: Fighting Zoanthropes is often reported as a source of frustration. Alongside the changes to the AI Director, we’re taking away some of their shields’ effectiveness to alleviate some of that frustration.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Zoanthrope: Shield swap cooldown with another paired Zoanthrope is increased by 10%.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f60c85e6b08d5337a57570cc7deb6bbd6c203400.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes &amp; Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a bug that caused roll distance to be shorter than before.</li></ul><i>DG</i>: <i>This was probably the most impactful and annoying consequence of Patch 4.0. While i-frames were the same, the distance difference made it much less effective versus ranged attacks. With this bug fixed, you should feel a great improvement in your fights against ranged enemies and bosses.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed bug with unlocking Lethal difficulty rewards decals.<br/></li><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.</li></ul>Our teams are constantly working on improvements to the game’s stability. This patch is no exception, so you should encounter fewer crashes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0987068ebeefc14bd9004c2edbde7945e0fcb9a9.png"/><br/><br/>That’s it for Patch 4.1! Your feedback is absolutely invaluable to us, and we’re looking forward to hearing your thoughts on this new update. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Emperor protects.</div><br/><i>The Space Marine 2 team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
