<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 8.0 - Siege Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500576552635859479</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">​Hi Space Marines!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The 8.0 “Siege update” is now live on every platform! Here’s a quick summary of its content:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ecbb29f9efaa85dbb69f458e2fd5c0a1cb1c9551.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2">New Features</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New PvE Mode — Siege</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e7a5450c1d6579a0b3b5eb7d5822bcb9ad53785f.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Siege Mode expands on our PVE operations, emphasizing endless enemy waves that challenge even the strongest teams. When overwhelmed, players may call reinforcements for assistance. Engage in intense battles across three distinctive sectors, each requiring strategic adaptation. Side objectives emerge during combat, providing essential resources used to summon elite Space Marines or a formidable Dreadnought, drastically shifting battlefield dynamics.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>The Battlefield</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The battle unfolds within a fortified Imperial stronghold on Kadaku, relentlessly attacked by endless waves of Tyranid and Thousand Sons enemies. The fortress has three rotating sectors: Defensive Positions, the Arsenal, and the Control Room. In each sector, you will face five waves of enemies before your squad advances to the next sector, ultimately cycling back to reinforce earlier positions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Survival Against Waves</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Face increasingly challenging enemy waves, with direct assaults from Tyranids and cunning sabotage by Chaos forces. Brief (1 minute) intermissions between waves offer strategic opportunities, clearly indicated through UI notifications.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Side Objectives</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Dynamic tasks such as capturing strategic points or retrieving Data-slates from fallen allies deepen tactical gameplay and supply critical resources essential for continued survival.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Shop and Reinforcements</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Earn Siege Mode resources through successful combat and Side Objective completion. You can spend these resources at the fortress Shop. You can:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ol><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Buy ammunition, medicae stimms, equipment, armour boosts, guardian relic (these items have the same exact behaviour as in Operations Mode).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Summon specialized Space Marines providing targeted support and bonuses. Each player can have only one summoned Space Marine.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deploy Cadian Troopers to provide additional firepower. </p></li></ol><p class="bb_paragraph"><u><i>Note about reinforcements changes from the PTS</i></u>: guardsmen are now cheaper.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">      4. Collectively pool your resources to unleash the devastating power of a Dreadnought.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfviEfHvwlz6aYq4r2sr-HTPRk9J5hQmhb8nTnIV7TbrtKKWNlf9WdONqHsTF6IGKtvcWw0CV7NLt77aOj7FljNuI0ZRgY3aA8r3Hk6c7QnteRqgQJzXTdEKoeFjlYK0QwBb6ro?key=gnyzwl0aHXvpELg_kEjf1g"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Boss Encounters</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Every fifth wave introduces formidable boss battles, occasionally facing multiple elite foes simultaneously. Triumph in these encounters to progress to new fortress sectors.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Infinite Waves</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">If your resolve endures through fifteen brutal waves, prepare for endless combat of increasing difficulty, reduced resources, and shorter preparation times. Even the Primarch of the Ultramarines understands that ultimate victory here is unlikely — but your bravery will echo through the halls of eternity.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><u><i>Note about timer changes from PTS:</i></u></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The biggest criticism regarding Siege mode from the community was the wave timer limit. It exists only for technical reasons. In this build we've made some optimizations so the Siege mode can last longer. </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Timer got reworked, instead of having a limited timer per wave that can get to a very short time on higher waves, there is a timer for the entire session and each time you beat a wave the timer increases. </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We've also adjusted the difficulty curve of infinite waves so enemies will get stronger faster after the 15th wave. These changes will make players die in fair combat rather than due to the timer. Also, with some optimizations coming down later we think we can get rid of the timer entirely.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added an option to disable bots spawn in Private Mode</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Perfect if you’re looking for a challenge.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">RTAO experimental feature added — enables in in-game video settings</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">DLSS 4  — better upscale, multiframe generation in NVIDIA settings for 50xx series cards.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXenLPQDlFcQgBWG82J2E0FVxKbS3YGnb-X8L64V4QbpFJp4Sst7CrY8Yug3GSO5etQJ0Si4qExbqhYYQjs75_Za_ZcPsmT2_pFsBcVOR-1oMQ5UNl96RXtLXDvOzxdf3JTgMq2UPg?key=gnyzwl0aHXvpELg_kEjf1g"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>New Season Pass Content</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added White Scars Chapter Champion. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added White Scars Chapter Weapon Skin Pack. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added White Scars Chapter Customisation Pack. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Blood Angels Customisation Pack.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b066256ea388e1db5bd6cd8e09d0c10107cd25eb.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f0a261a65d0e9e65f99d2e59ec33868f81f85c4.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0254e5bfaa406e0d3d52e12db225d7cd3bd87237.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c0fc4a0e132d08919324e6e27654fe15b3958f0a.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b73fa5f9b8a36fa2e713d59c294a66e6f6151489.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b4c834898fa174b67debd3bf94cb8ed02cab7f98.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6db692fa5ef96c40a3454b8eafdfcf58f7d9b219.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e9b00e197758eebd0757f8b7881c56347bd9766e.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2fb39e0f5017cf83ce924c48783bd696c67ac436.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/46d0d37e4263b8b2ba15f7bd6d5127e61871dc7b.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6b8123edd3debacc0b18ab3e0d9d99dd7d4347a5.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">GAMEPLAY AND BALANCING TWEAKS</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Extended Weapon arsenal in PvE</b> </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Thunder Hammer for Bulwark. Picking this weapon won’t allow you to use the Storm Shield.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We are adding this option only because we think it will be very cool and it's a shame that only 1 class can use the Thunder Hammer. We are not done with Bulwark, more interesting gameplay things are to come.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>New Finishers for Bulwark</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Adding new finishers for Bulwark with shield — 1 for Hormagaunt and 1 for Tzaangor.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Terminus Update for Absolute Difficulty</b> </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">A second Terminus can now appear during a mission.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Carnifex, Neurothrope and Helbrute HP increased by 33% on Absolute difficulty.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Level specific Terminus enemies (with the exception of the Hierophant Bio-Titan) HP increased by 66% on Absolute difficulty.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Additional enemy packs will appear upon Terminus enemies spawn and again when their HP is reduced to 50%</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">These additional packs are now slightly more challenging featuring more Extremis enemies</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mission with final bosses can now also spawn Terminus enemies (previously, missions like “Decapitation” didn't allow any Terminus spawns)".</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This change is made according to the community poll that we made a while ago. We think that Absolute difficulty wasn't that hard to begin with and now with a slight power creep of constant weapons buffs, perk buffs and prestige perks the situation is much worse.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>After doing multiple test we have scrapped the idea of having 2 Terminus enemies in Operations mode at the same time (except in Siege mode), because this meant that you would have to encounter them all of the time, otherwise one run with dual terminus spawns would be much harder than a run with 2 Terminus enemies spawning one by one. We are increasing the health of the Terminus enemies on Absolute difficulty because they often can die before even dealing any damage. While this may seem like it goes against poll results, keep in mind that if we had 2 Terminus enemies, that would effectively be +100%  hp buff. Also we are nerfing Neurothrope base hp across all difficulty levels so its hp pool won’t become a problem for melee classes.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Instead we've tried to make Terminus spawns harder and more intense. We are going to continue to monitor how Absolute Difficulty is, and make necessary tweaks.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Prestige Perks Class Update</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bulwark Prestige Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>“Rally Point”: The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Emboldened Stand”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “Chapter Banner additionally removes negative Status Effects while active.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: “When the Chapter Banner is active, all Squad Members do not lose control upon taking Heavy Hits and cannot be knocked back within its zone.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Assault Prestige Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Boosted Recharge": The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Unyielding Oath”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “Collecting an Armour Boost restores Ability Charge by 100%.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "When charging a Ground Pound, you become Invulnerable for 3 seconds."</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Sniper Prestige Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Boosted Recharge": The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Materiel Upgrade”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “Collecting an Armour Boost restores Ability Charge by 100%.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "Equipment Damage radius increases by 15%."</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Heavy Prestige Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>“Restorative Capacity”: The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Honed Precision”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: ” Activating Iron Halo removes negative Status Effects.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "Equipped Weapon's Maximum Spread decreases by 25% when firing without aiming."</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Tactical Prestige Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Skilled Supplier":</b>  Fixed a bug preventing the player from getting the maximum ammo.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Class Perks Updates</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bulwark Perks Update</b> </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Perks have been updated to reflect the addition of the Thunder Hammer to the Bulwark’s arsenal.</i> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Forward Momentum": The perk has been updated.</b> </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “After a Shield Bash, Melee Damage increases by 30% for 10 seconds.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "After a Shield Bash or Thunder Hammer Pommel Smash, Melee Damage increases by 30% for 10 seconds".</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Concussive Force": The perk has been updated.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “Shield Bash deals 200% more Damage.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "Shield Bash deals 200% more Damage. Thunder Hammer Pommel Smash deals 100% more Damage and deals area-of-effect Damage within a 7-metre radius. Cooldown is 5 seconds."</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Merciless Resolve": The perk has been updated.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “After a Shield Bash, Melee Damage increases by 15%, you do not lose control upon taking Heavy Hits and you cannot be knocked back for 10 seconds”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: "After a Shield Bash or Thunder Hammer Pommel Smash, Melee Damage increases by 15%, you do not lose control upon taking Heavy Hits, and you cannot be knocked back for 10 seconds".</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Focused Restoration": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Every 40 seconds, all Squad Members automatically restore 1 Armour Segment “ -&gt;  Cooldown decreased from 40 to 30 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Tactical Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Final Shot": The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Emperor’s Judgement”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “After a Finisher, the equipped Ranged Weapon reloads automatically.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New:"After a Finisher, the equipped Ranged Weapon reloads automatically, and your Primary Weapon deals 20% more Damage for 10 seconds".</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Communion of Fire": The perk has been reworked. The new perk is “Secure Stockpile”.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “Recoil is reduced by 25% and Ranged damage against Extremis-level enemies is increased by 10% for all Squad Members.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: “Equipment Charge is restored by 1 for all Squad Members. Cooldown is 60 seconds.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Steady Aim": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Weapon Spread and Recoil is reduced by 20% and Ranged Damage against Terminus-level enemies is increased by 10%” -&gt; Ranged Damage bonus increased from 10% to 15%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Assault Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Winged Fury": The perk has been buffed</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Damage from Melee Attacks executed while sprinting or dashing increases by 40%.” -&gt; Damage increased from 40% to 100%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Hammer of Wrath": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“After a Ground Pound, you take 15% less Ranged Damage, do not lose control upon taking Heavy Hits and you cannot be knocked back for 10 seconds” -&gt; Damage reduction increased from 15% to 20%. Knock back immunity duration increased from 10 to 15 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Vanguard Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Moving Target": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Each Melee Attack you land reduces the Ranged Damage you take by 2% (up to 20%). If you do not land a Melee Attack for 5 seconds, the effect ends.” -&gt;  Consecutive hit multiplier increased from 2% to 5%. Max bonus increased from 20% to 30%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Retribution": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“After you are grabbed or knocked back, you deal 25% more Melee Damage for 15 seconds.” -&gt; Bonus damage increased from 25% to 30%. Duration increased from 15 to 20 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Sniper Perks Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Precision Targeting": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Weapon Spread is reduced by 25% and Ranged Damage against Extremis-level enemies is increased by 10% for all Squad Members.” -&gt; Ranged Damage against Extremis-level enemies increased from 10 to 15%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Dexterous Hands": Instigator Bolt Carbine is now also affected.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“Bolt Carbines reload 20% faster, and their Weapon Spread and Recoil are reduced by 15%.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Weapon Perks Update</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Inferno Pistol Perk Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Know no fear": The perk has been reworked.</b> </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Old: “When your Health is below 10%, Reload Speed increases by 30%”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">New: “If your Armour is fully depleted, Reload Speed increases by 20%.”</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Neo-Volkite Pistol Perk Update</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>"Combustive momentum": The perk has been buffed.</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">“After a Gun Strike, heating speed increases by 30% for 6 seconds.” -&gt; Duration increased from 2 to 6 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Combat QoL</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">If a Sniper type enemy aims at you, using Assault’s Jump Pack ability will allow you to dodge the shot. The sniper will shoot instantly, but the shot will miss.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Neurothropes' Warp Storm afterblasts could stun-lock the player with heavy hits. Now, afterblasts will damage the player but not control them. Additionally, Neurothropes' shots now have a slightly longer delay between them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a lot of minor issues improving overall combat responsiveness </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Firearms (PvE Only)</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>There are not many weapon balance tweaks in this patch because our statistics show that usage and win rate for all weapons is in a good spot right now. With the next big update we are going to focus on weapon versions balance inside each archetype, because this is where we see a big room for improvements.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bolt Pistol</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Hip-Fire spread decreased by 50%. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Velocity of spread increasing in minizoom state is decreased by 15%.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Inferno Pistol</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Gun Strike Damage increased by 20%.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">PvP</div><p class="bb_paragraph">With the next patch we are going to take a closer look at PvP weapon balance.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Large amount of small fixes in level geometry collision.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of minor fixes for private lobbies gameplay modifiers.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">AI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Spore Mines</u>: Explosion damage is reduced by 55%.</p></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Neurothrope</u>:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health reduced by 15%</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Temporary invulnerability is replaced with high damage resistance when it flies up from the ground.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of minor animation fixes for various enemies.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Customisation</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We are preparing a very big update for customisation, players will be able to reuse chapter champion armour parts on other classes (with lore accuracy, clipping and technical restrictions). While it's not going to be in this patch, we wanted to mention this in this patch notes to assure you that we are going to continue expanding our customization system.</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Red, White and Blue weapon skins as Siege mode rewards</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Prestige reward shoulder pad on left shoulder as well.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added left pauldron decal "Ultramarine Sergeant".</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of other minor fixes for customizations of armour parts and emblems.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Levels</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Large amounts of small fixes in level geometry collision and Terminus enemies getting stuck in some areas.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where spore mines could spawn on top of the player.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several cases where contested health may decrease while performing a finisher.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed: Combining Sniper's prestige perk Emperor's Grace with Lingering Concealment perk drains the ability charge while linger is active</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed: Weapon perk "Reloaded Restauration" was not activated by the Sniper's perk "Efficient Readiness".</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Bulwark perk’s “Intimidating Aura” was not triggering with a Perfect Block.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Tactical’s perk’s “Battle Focus” was not triggering with a Perfect Block.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Intimidating Aura and Battle Focus are probably the most overpowered perks right now, but we think that it should still work independently from selected weapon</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug with the “Final Shot” perk not increasing damage in some cases.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug affecting Heavy's “Bonds of brotherhood” perk not granting full health when the player is revived by a bot.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue provoking a game freeze on a black screen at the end of a PvE level on Xbox Series S.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some pick ups were inaccessible as a consequence of the interaction button failing to appear. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed rare camera bugs after finisher.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of minor animation fixes for the player.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor UI, sound and VFX fixes and improvements</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Crash fixes and general stability improvements.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Matchmaking and network stability fixes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor memory optimization. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improvements to game modding capabilities.</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitch Drops Campaign to celebrate the Siege Update!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500577186633220365</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Dear Space Marines,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To celebrate the release of Patch 8.0, Twitch Drops return! This time, get the Mark VIII Errant Helmet (yes, it back), Mark XI Hell’s Teeth Pattern Chainsword and the Porphyr Shield Bolt Pistol! ✨</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The rules go as follows: from June 25 11PM CEST to July 14 11PM CEST:</b> </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">30min watch time of <b>any streamer playing SM2</b> → Mark VIII Errant Helmet</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">60min watch time → Mark XI Hell’s Teeth Pattern (Chainsword)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">120min watch time → Porphyr Shield (Bolt Pistol)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b75f7e10e2bd88322ea2da488c6e2ea1c7c20120.jpg"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.190 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732839</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We don't want to keep you waiting, so another hotfix for some of the most commonly reported issues is up!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Beware of possible spoilers below:<br/><br/>Patch notes:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In some circumstances, the Lord Captain would never get their original form back after the Feudal World of Thassera, resulting in a narrative inconsistency and a loss of access to inventory and levelling - fixed;<br/></li><li> The third combat on Commorragh arena sometimes never ended after all the enemies were defeated - fixed;</li></ul><br/>Note that because we wanted to deploy these fixes as early as possible, these two changes <b>will not be retroactive</b>, which means you will need to reload an earlier save if you want to continue playing right now. <b>Existing saves with this problem will be repaired a bit later, with one of the following updates.</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.188</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732802</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The first hotfix for the new expansion is live, dealing with some of the reported issues over the last night.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Beware of possible spoilers below:<br/><br/><b>Patch notes:</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Abelard could become missing in Commorragh if the Lex Imperialis expansion was activated in Act III. Fixed, let's not have the dear senechal suffer even more!<br/></li><li> If the first Abelard's quest was failed or skipped, it was impossible to start the expansion content from a save in Act 4 due to the lack of the quest NPC - fixed;<br/></li><li> For the first arena of Commorragh, it was possible to get 3 companions if Solomorne, Abelard and Argenta were in the party - fixed, Abelard will come after the first arena in this case;</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Imperialis Twitch Drops!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523094550774809104</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
To supplement the launch of the Lex Imperialis, we're launching a new Twitch Drops campaign! <br/><br/>Starting right now and up until July 15, watch your favourite streamers play the new expansion and have a lot of fun discussing your impressions while you earn exclusive in-game items!<br/><br/>https://roguetrader.owlcat.games/drops<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/5600c899165155b4c24ede0780323323dd16aeef.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
