<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Fixes, Vehicle Balance &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515216422280888364</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We've got a quick one for ya about the latest patch. This one focuses on balance changes mostly, but this is pretty significant, plus there's many other things done to help improve the game. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Check it out ːsteamthumbsupː </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>(we really need green hand emojis)</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>VEHICLES ⚙️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>GENERAL</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Speed required to drift is reduced, partially to make entering a drift more consistent</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health for most vehicles increased. See notes below:</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>With hit registration improvements, Time-To-Kill has been reduced because players deal damage more consistently. We've universally increased health values to bring the TTK closer to where it was before the hit reg improvements. </i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Range for most weapons increased. Minimum damage dealt (at new max range listed) is now 33%. Initial falloff distance for all weapons was not changed.</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The intent of the range change is to improve the feel of the game (less disappearing bullets) without actually disrupting balance too much</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You can no longer target invisible vehicles with lock-on weapons</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Vehicles should no longer miss-fire sometimes when trying to use an ability right when the cooldown ends.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>TANKS</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tanks can now drift - cause why not?</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>DEFFKILLA WARTRIKE</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 120 (from 100, +20%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Twin Boomsticks vertical spread increased to 2 (from 0.5), horizontal increased to 4 (from 1.5)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The range required to eliminate the disappearing bullets syndrome would have been like 200m, so instead the Boomsticks got some more spread to make the current range look more natural.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>BOOMDAKKA SNAZZWAGON</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 140 (from 120, +16%) </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mek Speshul max range increased to 120m (from 100m)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mek Speshul Burst max range increased to 150m (from 125m)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>GROT MEGA TANK</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 260 (from 230, +13%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Drifting added</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Plow no longer requires targets to be grounded</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This was a long-standing bug and removing it makes the plow much more consistent.</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Grotzooka max range increased to 125m (from 100m)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dakka max range increased to 150m (from 100m)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>KUSTOM BOOSTA-BLASTA</b></p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The KBB did not receive a health increase. It now has the same amount of health as the Wartrike due to their similarly powerful mobility.</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Can now control jump height by holding down the button (this was broken due to a bug)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rivet Kannon spread increased to 1 (from 0.5), max distance increased to 170 (from 150)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>A mix of spread and range bump for the Rivet Kannon to make the far end of the range look more natural.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>LOOTED WAGON</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 180 (from 160, +12%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Can now launch the Grot Bomm in midair</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Can now press E while flying the Grot Bomm to return to the Looted Wagon. The GB will continue to fly on its last path</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">GB damage reduced to 30 (from 40). GB knockback increased by 50%</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>To compensate for the buff above, we're trying out a version of the Grot Bomm that is more about disruption (and setting up the pop up &gt; Kannon shot combo) than straight up damage.</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You can now steer the Grot Bomm with WASD (or remapped driving inputs), and the analog control is much more sensitive</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kannon knockback reduced by 90%</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dakka max distance increased to 200m (from 150m)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>MEGATRAKK SCRAPJET</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 140 (from 120 + 16%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Recoil Rokkit does more recoil on grounded targets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Drill no longer slows you down in midair</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>RUKKATRUKK SQUIGBUGGY</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 150 (from 130, +15%)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>SHOKKJUMP DRAGSTA</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 140 (from 120, +16%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shokk Rifle max distance increased to 250m (from 200m),</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Unstable Shokk Rifle now shoots a 4 second burst, with a downtime equivalent to the duration of 1 shot. So it shoots for 4, rests for 1, and repeats. Damage increased to 9 (from 8)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Unstable Shokk Rifle DPS has been reduced to 21.6 from 24, and holding the mouse button will deal suboptimal DPS compared to timing your volleys, so there is a bit more skill expression and a nerf to simply holding m1.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>TRUKK</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health increased to 180 (from 150, +20%)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ladders no longer require targets to be grounded</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Can now control jump height by holding the button (this was broken due to a bug)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>A tap will not cause a jump, so you can choose to continue steering if you are in combat.</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stronger forward jump strength when holding the ladder button</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Main gun max distance increased to 150m (from 125m)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>FREE ROAM </b>🕊 Race Creator</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You can now select, move, and delete waypoints. Editing races is much more robust</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Waypoints are now numbered for the person creating the race</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with non-English race names </p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Please fill out this survey and help shape the future of Free Roam mode</i>.</p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>KILL KONVOY / DEFF RALLY </b>💥🏁 </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In Kill Konvoy, bombs now pass to teammates first. Dropped bombs (when killed) now passed to enemies first</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Health now regenerates slower when holding the bomb</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the "random force applied to bomb when a player is killed" bug</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added the missing voice lines for "TAKE DA BOMB FROM ME", "GIVE ME DA BOMB", and "FANKS A LOT"</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In Deff Rally, your racing podium position is shown at underneath the medal when a race is finished</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MAPS </b>🗺️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Jump pads adjusted on Da Gorge to reduce flying into walls</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added jump pads to Da Dust Up so you can climb back up the mountain in Free Roam</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added alternate weather variations for Kill Konvoy maps: Ded 'Ard Desert (sandstorm), Da Gorge (rain), Frozen Dakka (snowstorm) and Big Erupta (spooky lightning)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/194eab0ace03d0b935a12c5bbdd0af2edc8f7fd2.png"/></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MISC </b>🎲</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added potential fix for invalid "host disconnected" issue</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a potential fix for achievements not popping as they should for players. Hopefully this is the last time we'll have to talk about this one...</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Gamepad aim assist added</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This is the first step for controller compatibility, next will be alternate driving control schemes.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">As for <b>Soundtrakk</b> newz, it will be coming in early August, so start prepping your speakers for a loud one⚡</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We understand that we've talked about it a few times, but we've had some issues with Steam approval, plus we're trying picking the right spot to release it in.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">What to look forward to in future updates:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The return of game mode <b>Mutators</b> that can be selected when created a match.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The new <b>Vehicle</b> (to be disclosed soon™)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New <b>Maps</b> for Kill Konvoy and Deff Rally</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">A new <b>WAAAGH Path</b> with more free items to unlock</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Steam <b>Workshop</b> support for <b>custom races</b>, plus a <b>Kustom Rally</b> game mode that allows players to choose any races they want and host a lobby that plays through them all</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Moar stuffs</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks for playing and sticking with us while we keep working on the game!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live Now: Rotten Armor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520845543638828949</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">New in-game event: Rotten Armor</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Blight has mutated, twisting the very armor our enemies wear. Watch out for these decaying, disgusting threats. <b>Crushers, Maulers and Scab Ragers</b> in missions with the Event active will bear an infested armor, which makes them <b>slower</b> but <b>much tougher</b>! And <b>beware their vile secretions</b>, the blood they shed might not be so harmless...</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e744570ab002de8b053806400167010c3188fa18.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Rotten Armour condition. This goes for any combination of Rotten Armour and other modifiers that are available, such as Rotten Armour and Hunting Grounds, Rotten Armour and Pox Gas and more.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event <b>starts on Thursday, July 24</b>, and will run <b>until August 11!</b> Progress in the event will reward <b>Ordo Dockets, Plasteel, Diamantine</b>, and a <b>brand new portrait frame </b>at the last tier!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3b0cde78869e8906f7130c487a154ef3bcdf725e.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3c1b2382f472d118ba893dc549e9495242ef470b.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proving Grounds: Siege Beta NOW LIVE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497202023769309216</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/4f569267de38d1ab94576ad967141a65bd1016b2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Proving Grounds Siege Beta is now available to download on Steam! This is your chance to get hands-on with the changes, share your feedback with us and help shape the future of siege warfare.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This Beta phase will be available until <b>Thursday 7th August </b>and is open to all owners of Total War: WARHAMMER III. In case you missed the blog earlier in the week where Battle Team Lead Milcho Vasilev talked us through what his team have been cooking up for it, you can get yourself up to speed right here.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've also started streaming again on Twitch and YouTube! If you missed our first stream last week, check out the VOD below for a closer look at some of the changes Milcho and his team have made before you take the dive yourself. <i>(Skip through to 42:10)</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" t5brzvzn8nk?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For additional information on how the Beta works and how we will gather and use your feedback, check out our handy FAQ. Otherwise, you can follow the steps below to get yourself opted-in and downloading the Beta right now!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We look forward to hearing your thoughts, and thank you for your participation!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the (siege) battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The <i>Total War</i> Team</p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h2">How to download the Beta branch</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ol><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Open your Steam client and go to your Library.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Right-click on <i>Total War: WARHAMMER III</i> and select 'Properties'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Navigate to the 'Betas' tab.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In the drop-down menu, select '<b>proving_grounds - Siege Beta</b>'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Steam will then download the necessary files and begin the patching process to install the Beta.</p></li></ol><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The download is relatively small, but Steam will need to patch around 330 MB of game data in order to install the Hotfix. This can take some time depending on your hard drive speeds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">⚠️🛠️Please note that the use of mods with this Beta can and will lead to unexpected results.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Enjoy!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.1.217 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523097721627738134</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Hotfix 1.4.1.217 is live, dealing with a variety of bugs, crashes and softlocks.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>As usual, consoles will receive the same update within 24-48 hours.<br/><br/><u>Beware of possible plot spoilers below!</u><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed massive lag related to cases where companions with familiars were not in the party, yet were actually present on the location for technical needs, hidden from the player;<br/></li><li> The game could crash during the battle at Corrupted Cogitator at Kiava Gamma - fixed;<br/></li><li> Solomorne could sometimes never return to the party after Vheabos-VI - fixed;<br/></li><li> Solomorne could sometimes lose all his gear after taking a bath with the Lord Captain - fixed;<br/></li><li> Solomorne will now be located with the rest of the crew during the final dialogue before Epitaph;<br/></li><li> Rogue Trader will no longer sometimes get stuck in space after entering the voidship's bridge;<br/></li><li> Argenta sometimes refused to die in Commorragh when killed, softlocking the game - fixed;<br/></li><li> The Heretical dialogue option when executing Bluff did not have a text description - fixed;<br/></li><li> It was possible to get Solomorne's recruitment quest for players without the DLC in some circumstances - fixed, it will disappear from the journal for them;<br/></li><li> Solomorne has received his own loading screen;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases where one of the characters in the party would ride an invisible bycicle, which meant a cutscene with them was played incorrectly;<br/></li><li> Fixed cases with the loading bar sometimes being stuck at 100% after Leethus space combat;<br/></li><li> Fixed Respec not always functioning correctly if a character had the talent to equip shields into a single slot and had 2 shields equipped;<br/></li><li> Solomorne will no longer display as Error Speaker in the dialogue before first arrival to Footfall;<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare softlock with Jae's personal quest, where a certain selection of answers could break the dialogue and make it impossible to leave the location;</li></ul><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submit your KRUMP KLIPS for weekly videos + Soundtrakk news</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515213885413789704</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3"><b>KRUMP KLIPS</b></div><div class="bb_h3">We'z been keepin' our'z peeperz on all da racin' n' fightin', n' we'z like wot we'z see 👀</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We're seeing some great clips from the community pop up in the Discord and other platforms, and want to showcase all the snazzy gameplay you gits have captured while having fun. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">This can be be awesome krumps, trickshots, big stunts, fast racing, hilarious interactions - whatever is worth a watch.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">So feel free to drop links or files for your favourite clips in the submission form below, as we're compiling <b>Krump Klips Ov Da Week</b> videos to show off the best submissions chosen by Wired and Caged Element.  Ideally you don't have music playing in the background of your clips, but feel free to have voice chat if it's funny.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Note that we are choosing clips from any point in time to post, so klips ov da week just means ones we thought were cool to post that week </i>ːsteamthumbsupː</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2ff7e688a3471c2acedb21f8abfba80eed95681e.png"/> GIVE US DA CLIPS Form <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2ff7e688a3471c2acedb21f8abfba80eed95681e.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" cpbbt6llcbg?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If we put your clip in a <b>Krump Klips </b>video, we'll be sharing it on social media with credit, plus giving you the<b> Caged Squig</b> accessory unlock to attach to <i>any </i>vehicle (previously only available in early access)  </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cc554d408a3a168b1d090c133f8e88dedd1e6a5c.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"> </div><div class="bb_h3"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/></div><div class="bb_h3"><b>The </b><i>bangers</i> <b>are coming</b> <b>💥</b>🎵</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The <b>Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks official soundtrack</b> is getting close to release, and we'll be sharing when that is, along with a new patch next week. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The <i>soundtrakk</i> includes some truly <i>ded 'ard metal muzik</i>. This roster has the same pumping tunes you've heard in the various trailers, but also includes unreleased music as part of one long, continuous jam by <b>Cave Bat </b>that is the highlight of the OST.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Not only that, but if you didn't know, there are two Speed Freeks songs created by the legendary <b>Frank Klepacki</b> - the same Frank Klepacki who smashed out the official <b>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</b> theme back when it released.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We find this soundtrack very special, and very Orky - and we hope you gits do too.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">And don't worry, we haven't forgotten the <b>Soundtrakk giveaway</b> for guessing the next incoming vehicle correctly.  We'll be announcing the winners (<i>and the vehicle!</i>) in the near future.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>BE FAST, BRUTAL, </b><i>AND</i> <b>KUNNIN'</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Quick reminder that we have a couple of bundles. Wired and <b>Slitherine (Gladius)</b> have teamed up for a Warhammer 40k bundle that scratches your itch for both kunnin' strategy and brutal action. If one of the gits you know doesn't have either game, this is the time to jump on it!</p><div class="bb_h3">https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/55421/Warhammer_40000_Speed_and_Strategy_Bundle/</div><p class="bb_paragraph">You might have seen this one already, but Speed Freeks is bundled with developer Caged Element's previous game GRIP, too. The ultimate combat racing bundle 💪</p><div class="bb_h3">https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/54112/Combat_Racing_Bundle/</div><div class="bb_h3"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Get involved in the community and mob up with other Orks</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Our community may be kunnin' n' brutal', but they're also super nice gits. Jump into one of these places to go full Ork:</p><div class="bb_h3">Discord</div><div class="bb_h3">r/SpeedFreeks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4632f08ea6bbd65d79448452c0b0d37c241b0742.png"/> </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
