<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Void Shadows DLC Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4705787971877987782</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>We have been granted permission by Seneschal Werserian to report to you directly on our current situation.<br/><br/>We are pleased to report that the <b>Void Shadows DLC has arrived in stores and is now officially released</b>! Check out the links below and start playing right now!<br/><br/>We are receiving numerous reports about disturbing incidents taking place on your voidship. We have reason to believe that a vile Genestealer Cult may be involved in these atrocities. We request that you come immediately and take control of the situation personally.<br/><br/>To see the full details of our report, we suggest you take a look at the Void Shadows DLC release trailer!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hsgKGORxxXc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>Get the DLC as part of a Season Pass (with access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC):<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Or buy it separately:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2951990/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Void_Shadows/<br/><br/>The Emperor protects, but your crew is in great need of you right now, Lord Captain.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.2.1.7 is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4705787971878526385</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Update 1.2.1.7, supplementing the launch of Void Shadows DLC, is here! <br/><br/>In it, you’ll find various bugfixes, improvements and a number of brand new features!<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below and <b>MAKE SURE TO UPDATE YOUR MODS!</b><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">New features:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Grim Darkness mode has been added to the game! Play in “ironman” mode with a single save and achieve a feat of strength by finishing the game without dying! Read more. <br/></li><li> Many formulae in the game were updated to show the final expected numbers instead of complicated mathematical operations;<br/></li><li> The game has received a brand new in-game mod and DLC manager;<br/></li><li> A new system of dynamic icons for passive abilities and talents, which updates the old “letters for icons” system, has been added:</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/82a2d8c21ca94c95d25d7cdd477ad4f1c2e3926e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">System and stability</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of performance issues with the Encyclopedia;<br/></li><li> Optimized creating saves to use less memory and be a bit quicker;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> One of Jae's quest endings in Act IV did not work correctly - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Defective Servitors quest would not complete if the player asked Factotum to get rid of the servitors;<br/></li><li> In Cassia's The Price of Power quest, players who romanced her sometimes managed to convince her in the dialogue to <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>renounce her house and title</span></span> but didn't have all the necessary conditions to do that. This choice had no consequences but was very misleading - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug which could cause the Blood Ties quest to pop up on Dargonus and become stuck if Abelard was dropped from the party after picking up the quest (who in their sane mind would drop Abelard out anyway?!);<br/></li><li> The Mercatum Tabula Officiale quest could incorrectly fail at the beginning of Act III - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mechanics</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Assassin's Haemorrhage ability wasn't counted as damage over time ability;<br/></li><li> Fixed the case when the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Lord of Change</span></span> could have an infinite attack (not that it was THAT thematically wrong, but it certainly wasn’t intended);<br/></li><li> A bug has been fixed due to which it was impossible to jump over a blockage at Eurac V if the athletics skill was reduced due to injuries;<br/></li><li> The Bounty Hunter can no longer use offensive Heroic acts during the Savour the Kill bonus turn;<br/></li><li> The Commissar's For the Emperor! talent now correctly grants Momentum when an ally kills a marked enemy;<br/></li><li> The Commissar's Show Them Contempt! talent now correctly disappears when the Commissar is no longer adjacent to any enemies;<br/></li><li> The effect of Ready to Serve talent is now correctly applied on allies when it's used by the character with the talent;<br/></li><li> The Navy Officer's Scatter! ability now correctly halves the damage;<br/></li><li> Danse Macabre could only be used once on additional turns given by a Leader - fixed;<br/></li><li> Supporting Zone talent now correctly works with Rapid Reload Stratagem granted by Arch-Strategist's Visor item;<br/></li><li> Arch-Militant’s Close-Quarters Training talent used to incorrectly give a penalty to hit chance instead of Ballistic Skill - fixed;<br/></li><li> Armour penetration bonus from Bounty Hunter's Guidance incorrectly calculated the target's difficulty tier twice - fixed;<br/></li><li> Easy Target Warrior talent did not work under a number of circumstances - fixed;<br/></li><li> Exemplar's Revenge bonus damage didn't fall off after character melee attack - fixed;<br/></li><li> Know No Heresy talent now correctly applies half of its effects to the allies;<br/></li><li> Pasqal's Machine Spirit Communion ability duration was shorter than intended - fixed;<br/></li><li> Soldier's Enough Bullets for Everyone talent didn't work with extra turns - fixed;<br/></li><li> Dogmatic's Absolution feature now correctly works with damage over time abilities;<br/></li><li> The Master Tactician's Nerves of Steel talent worked even when the Master Tactician was dead or even when the Master Tactician was not in the party at the moment - fixed;<br/></li><li> The Master Tactician's Nerves of Steel talent could sometimes turn momentum losses into momentum gains (when the losses were small and/or when you had more than one Master Tactician in the party) - fixed, now losses can only be reduced to 0;<br/></li><li> The Master Tactician's Comfort in Conformity talent could sometimes save characters from death - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of cases where characters could gain negative temporary wounds, which could break the damage system in unexpected ways. One such example is Above the Thundering Guns (gained from Iconoclast - Follower) that granted temporary wounds equal to the character's Resolve (and Resolve could become negative from traumas and injuries);<br/></li><li> The Navy Officer's Do Not Falter! ability now correctly applies its effect until the end of the combat;<br/></li><li> Warrior talent Easy Target now works on the creatures whose weapons are natural - like teeth and claws. They are no longer considered "armed with melee weapon" for this talent;<br/></li><li> The description of the Shield Pulse ability has been edited to make the effect more clear;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Armour of the Undaunted no longer increases the cost of some attacking abilities (i.e. "Charge") by more than intended;<br/></li><li> Black Signet of the Inquisition now grants less armour and deflection upon use;<br/></li><li> Blast Pistol and its derivatives now use the correct damage cones when shooting. Their shots are now correctly identified as an AoE ranged attack and no longer provoke attacks of opportunity when used in melee (same as other pistols);<br/></li><li> Burnt Aquila Pendant now provides correct Fire Damage bonus (was 1 less than intended);<br/></li><li> Opticon-22 now has a [Retobi-Pattern] Bolter for sale;<br/></li><li> Scarlet Signet of the Inquisition now grants slightly less armour upon use;<br/></li><li> Self-Calibrating Goggles: successful single melee attacks didn't trigger a Willpower check - fixed;<br/></li><li> Self-Calibrating Helmet: successful burst or area attacks triggered a Willpower check - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Locations</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In one of the encounters in the Upperway, added new abilities to the enemies - Let the Blind see the Truth and Behold the Final Dawn;<br/></li><li> Traps in Commorragh now have the correct trigger trajectory;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Visual</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a falling animation in the scene where Kunrad stuns the Lord Captain;<br/></li><li> Added new animations for the Electro-Priests;<br/></li><li> Added physics to some weapon decoration elements;<br/></li><li> During a fight on Salis Prime, one of the Unholy Lenses could stay transparent - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed non-functioning cogitators on the bridge;<br/></li><li> Fixed the issue with the clothes textures interfering with the character model;<br/></li><li> When the Crowd density setting was set to minimal, some people could look the wrong way;<br/></li><li> Bladewings ability now has a correct attack animation;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">User Interface</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It is now possible to inspect the bonuses and rewards offered to you in dialogues, space exploration events and colonisation by hovering over them;<br/></li><li> "Show in Encyclopedia" button in Exploration window didn't work correctly - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the issue where the information about modified resources in colonisation window was not updated after completing orders;<br/></li><li> "Upgrade" button in the end of a space combat did nothing - fixed;<br/></li><li> Added a menu setting to either have the main menu visuals and music change with the new expansion releases, or always keep the original visuals and music;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of visual issues with the selector frame in the Journal;<br/></li><li> Fixed a problem where the ESC menu could stop working after scanning a planet;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the hidden health status was incorrectly displayed after reloading the game - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where sometimes it wasn't displayed who was performing a skill test;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the "Hide completed quests" checkbox in the journal did not work in some cases;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the cursor visuals did not match some interactive objects;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the listener's portrait could sometimes be incorrectly displayed in dialogues;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where, upon reloading the Main Menu with certain settings, sounds from the main menu would play when the settings window was open - Fixed<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with inverted navigation arrows when using Heroic Acts and Desperate Measures when playing with a controller or on console;<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple cases of text not fitting into the selection frame in the game menus;<br/></li><li> Fixed navigation and transition through notifications in the quest journal (it will now always open the correct quest instead of going to the beginning of the list). The journal will also now remember the quest it was focused upon when it was opened for the last time - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the issue of simultaneous double notifications for receiving and completing a quest;<br/></li><li> Fixed the quest notification not always opening the correct page in the journal upon clicking;<br/></li><li> Fixed the visual display of the "required DLC" text in the save slot selection in the cooperative lobby;<br/></li><li> Fixed visual mouse control errors related to systems on the global map;<br/></li><li> Pressing and holding the right stick in the inventory now again expands the text when playing with a controller or on console as it was always supposed to;<br/></li><li> Psychic Assault talent is now correctly displayed when the "warp features" filter is active;<br/></li><li> When playing with a controller or on console, some companions were not automatically assigned to the party when transitioning between locations - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed display of multiple damage numbers near the character's health bar;<br/></li><li> Fixed infinite character gender change bug in the character creation;<br/></li><li> Improved the display of some ability descriptions;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Audio</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added additional combat shouts to the Lord Inquisitor;<br/></li><li> Added additional sounds to Combat Servitors;<br/></li><li> Added additional sounds to Daemonettes;<br/></li><li> Added additional sounds to Horrors of Tzeentch;<br/></li><li> Added additional sounds to Plaguebearers;<br/></li><li> Added sound effects for the planet hologram on the bridge;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to the Electro-Priests' animations;<br/></li><li> The Corrupted Tech-Priests sounded like Chaos Cultists - fixed;<br/></li><li> Added a sound effect to the loot gathering window pop up;<br/></li><li> Added interaction sounds to all icons in the game;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases across the game, where music would not always start playing correctly when facing a major enemy;<br/></li><li> Fixed issues with music during the fight with <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Uralon and the Lord Of Change</span></span>;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Space, Colonisation and Exploration</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tutorial on healing was popping up for no apparent reason in space combat - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where The Haemonculus's Prism rumour would not complete;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the One-Way Road rumour would not complete;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Suspicious Ships rumour would not complete after meeting Drukhari ships;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Unknown Mechanism rumour would not complete in some cases;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Xenos Skirmish rumour would not complete;<br/></li><li> Unknown Mechanism rumour quest marker is no longer shown in Atrium on Footfall;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Co-op</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of desync cases;<br/></li><li> Players can no longer cancel other players' moves;<br/></li><li> Added a visual UI element to indicate that an ability was pinged (highlighted) by another player on a different page of the action bar;<br/></li><li> Fixed the case of duplicating selection bar in the dialogue UI in co-op;<br/></li><li> Pings for abilities, dialogue votes and book events in co-op now work simply by pressing the Confirm button on the controller or by clicking the mouse button on the PC, not with a combination of buttons as before;<br/></li><li> When playing in co-op, one of the payers could become stuck on Rykad Minoris after a cutscene - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added reputation levels for vendors in Act IV. Also, the requirements for increasing reputation level in Act IV were changed;<br/></li><li> The issue with Perfect Timing achievement was fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where after disembarking from the ship to a planet, some party members could end up not being under player control;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mods</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with deserialization exception while applying blueprint patch on the components;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 02 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4678766374101256775</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speedfreeks!,</b><br/>We've been under da hood and changed 'sum 'dings.<br/><br/>Your feedback has been invaluable as ever and led to the following fixes.<br/>We are now live with:<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b391dceab12c8150b09629e8508f65a1ef90842f.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3fd4729dc7c865b082f439204bf520361ac6ae2a.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added heatwave version of Kill Konvoy: Ded 'Ard Desert (the desert map with a big pipline down the middle). There is a 50% chance the server will load this version<br/></li><li> Added some obstacles/cover to Ded 'Ard Desert to improve balance between Stompa routes<br/></li><li> Improved collision in some areas<br/></li><li> Added rainstorm version of Deff Rally: Burna Valley (the volcanic map). There is a 50% chance the server will load this version<br/></li><li> Added snowstorm version of Deff Rally: Mob Mountain (the snowy mountain map). There is a 50% chance the server will load this version<br/></li><li> Added spooky nighttime version of Deff Rally: Krump Canyon (the red sand canyon map). There is a 50% chance the server will load this version<br/></li><li> Improved collision for some parts of Kill Konvoy: Frozen Dakka (glacial map)</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d56220b8eac8e40445b82a86887dcd63b79599a8.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue whereby in some conditions the aiming on the client and the server weren't syncing up properly<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue whereby the Deffkilla Wartrike dealt no damage with boomstikks in certain conditions </li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/525bbc93b070fee41947e8acffa76c958e8235a8.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/83f63332c078a348ca57c98c809814237f790ecf.png"/><li> Added Leaderboards to the game, with various categories/metrics to choose from. Leaderboards are based on a players 10 best matches throughout their lifetime.  This is the first version of the leaderboards, so some things might be janky.  Feedback welcome as always!<br/></li><li> Added Player Account Level next to players' nameplate. This account level is based on the amount of total scrap a player has acquired.<br/></li><li> Fixed Daily Challenges no longer resetting and not granting scrap<br/></li><li> Increased scrap progression speed by around 20%, including increasing daily challenge scrap from 2000 to 3000</li></ul> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/169603a49c541c0a44db1a354c77e07091697a34.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a contextual ping system to the game (default input is Middle Mouse Button)</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/24852a660b47cb1afe7a59773fb3145ba6a76e95.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added the ability for top players to switch from the winning team to the losing team under certain conditions<br/></li><li> Team shuffling/balancing after a match now takes player skill into consideration<br/></li><li> When a player joins a match they are always put on the losing team if teams have an even player count<br/></li><li> Match warm-up time increased to 1 minute to allow for more players to join before the game starts<br/></li><li> Matches are automatically closed if 4 or less players are in them (unless the server has never had more than that many players, meaning it is a region with less players actively online). Players in the closed match are taken to the menu to match-make again<br/></li><li> The Deff Rally capture point kill bonus (1.2x score) is now only for the losing team. The winning team should attempt to hold the capture point to prevent the other team from gaining bonus points</li></ul> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1c24705979de19541dbd846b18d4a72e7b2a8484.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Looted Wagon Grot Bomm FOV increased from 80 to 110<br/></li><li> Looted Wagon and Grot Mega Tank are slowed less when climbing hills<br/></li><li> Vehicles with more armour/hit points no longer receive more healing per shot than smaller vehicles</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2f128ebf1f9b33d8af2cdd7973b11c9fa4e6bb88.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added Bomb Rush and Dakka Frenzy limited time modes to be occurring on weekends<br/></li><li> Improved AZERTY keyboard support<br/></li><li> Fixed some issues whereby the UI showed incorrect damage or healing values<br/></li><li> Player tags now show during the beginning of the match warm-up phase<br/></li><li> Removed Konvoy bomb damage upon detonation since it only damaged the defending team.<br/></li><li> Improved AI bot vehicle and obstacle avoidance<br/></li><li> Fix for a bug where the settings screen remained visible on the HUD when switching to the next match.<br/></li><li> Centered the bomb icon back on the physical bomb (and therefore more on the vehicle when carried)<br/></li><li> Switched Deff Rally and Kill Konvoy mode selection in the menu, updated images, and added animated frames we completely forgot we had made months ago<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with the UI not properly showing Scrap Boost duration <br/></li><li> Fix made for input keys not refreshing automatically inside the game HUD after remapping them.<br/></li><li> A couple crash bug fixes, including one on the server</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Top priorities still being worked on:</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hit Registration and client/server sync<br/></li><li> Matchmaking improvements<br/></li><li> Issues with parties<br/></li><li> General bug fixing<br/></li><li> More maps, vehicles, weapons and game modes<br/></li><li> Seekret stuff</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e5145502eb1255df1b0cfc9dd4759ea76c5e4b2e.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/>  <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4658500175787534900</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/82667f5cf76ba8d38b59f173a5ca577271355db8.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>Today we're rolling out Hotfix 5.2.5, bringing with it a variety of bug fixes and tweaks to improve the gameplay experience.<br/><br/>Read on for the full details...<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">SKILLS</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Blue Scribes' skill ‘Tzeentch's Quaestors’ now correctly modifies the Assassinate action, rather than Wound (which they did not have!).</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SETTLEMENTS</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Special settlements (e.g., Altdorf, Karaz-a-Karak, etc.) will now correctly use the Wood Elf settlement battle map when occupied by Wood Elves.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ENVIRONMENT</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the edges of The Great Canal, south of Cathay, appeared jagged; the canal's edges should now display smoothly.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in The Lost Valley where building assets for a landmark near the settlement of Oyxl were visible despite being covered by the Fog of War.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TEXT/LOCALISATION</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Korean translation of ‘Livery’ was incorrectly displayed as ‘Symbol’; it has now been corrected to ‘Horse House.’<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a Lord's name in the Visions of the Old Ones mission panels was not localized.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">AI</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The AI has been improved in chokepoint battles to prioritise moving swiftly through chokepoints when under fire, rather than reforming or trying to cross while in formation. This enhancement increases the overall challenge and reduces the dominance of artillery and ranged units in these scenarios.<br/></li><li> Fixed the disabled AI skirmish mode for isolated units; it will now be disabled only when it is clear that the unit will lose, preventing unnecessary prolongation of the battle.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where AI-controlled units were moving chaotically in some quest battles while incorrectly waiting for reinforcements.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ENVIRONMENT</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We've asked the flying trees in Dwarf Mountains to calm down, thereby resolving an issue with them floating above the ground during battles.<br/></li><li> Nan-Gau is no longer affected by random fires, and specific assets have been grounded properly, fixing the issue where they were floating above the battlefield.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue on ‘The Shifting Monolith’ map where the camera could move under a lavafall, revealing unintended areas of the map.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed black spots on the Chaos Sorcerer, caused by transparency maps being turned off at different levels of detail (LODs).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where parts of the Marauders of Khorne's armour would disappear due to LOD errors.<br/></li><li> Fixed a visual issue with the inner wall of the cabins on the Thunderbarge and The Spirit of Grungni.</li></ul><br/><br/>As always, thank you all for your feedback and bug reports. If you experience any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.2.5 please be sure to report them over in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 09:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grim Darkness comes to the Koronus Expanse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4705787971875022163</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<i>…In the darkness between the stars<br/>The weak and the faithless find no deliverance…</i><br/><br/>Lord Captains!<br/><br/>With the Void Shadows expansion just around the corner, we are proud to announce a major new feature that is coming to Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader for all owners of the base game alongside the expansion:<br/><br/><b>The Grim Darkness mode.</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/ba2198ee14835b83952888d6ec044d43de8b17d6.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is the Grim Darkness Mode?</div><br/>Often referred to as “Ironman” in other titles, the Grim Darkness mode is the ultimate trial for the boldest of Lord Captains - a challenge for the most experienced, most prepared (or perhaps, most reckless!) players, who wish to truly immerse themselves in the dark and dangerous universe of Warhammer 40,000.<br/><br/>In this mode, you only have a single save, which is updated automatically every time you exit the game. No second chances - you will have to live with the consequences of all your actions and decisions. If your party or voidship are defeated, your Grim Darkness journey will end.<br/><br/>But if you manage to successfully overcome all the obstacles and make it all the way to the end, your feat of strength will be rewarded with the brand new “There Is Only War…” achievement, which will also unlock a special item for all your future playthroughs (surely feels fitting for Abelard, don't you think?):<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/baeba85fa082aa00d13856a425e0513b57400a0b.png"/><br/><br/><b>Amulet of the Indomitable Spirit</b><br/><br/><i>Such a trophy can only be worn by one who has fully comprehended an ancient truth — that in the universe there exists only war.</i><br/><br/>Once per battle, whenever the wearer's wounds drop to 0, they regain 20% of their maximum wounds.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How to Activate the Grim Darkness Mode</div><br/>When you start a new game, you’ll find a new “Grim Darkness” option under the difficulty settings marked by a distinctive skull icon. When turned on, it will prompt you with a warning about its dangers and if accepted, will enable Grim Darkness rules for the new game. All Grim Darkness mode saves will be marked in the Load Game menu with the same skull icon. <br/><br/>Such a trophy can only be worn by one who has fully comprehended an ancient truth — that in the universe there exists only war.<br/><br/>At launch, the Grim Darkness mode is <b>only available for PC and only for single player</b>, but we plan to expand it to the other platforms and co-op mode later. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/43d27cd61a8ab63a4d25f5267db4dd1e43f7118a.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Designing the Grim Darkness Mode</div><br/>In both our previous games, Pathfinder: Kingmaker and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous, there was a similar mode called The Last Azlanti. The mode earned a lot of acclaim in our community, providing a trial of gaming skill and wits, while also adding a whole new level of emotional investment due to the high risk and reward. We’ve seen many players discussing builds for this mode, competing between each other in beating the games in exotic ways, and sharing their stories of glorious victory (or no less glorious demise!). <br/><br/>We even went as far as hosting a large challenge event for streamers, known as the Last Azlanti Challenge. <br/><br/>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader originally shipped without an “Ironman” mode. But players kept asking us about it, and we also felt it was missing compared to our previous titles, so we always wanted to eventually revisit it.<br/><br/>It took us some time, but we’re finally there! And this time we’ve brought some innovations to the familiar approach. Among them:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Unlike in the previous games, the Grim Darkness mode is not affected by difficulty - you may now freely switch it or customize it at any time during your playthrough, the same as in the normal game mode. Some would say that this allows the player to abuse the system - but we believe that the players playing this mode are, first and foremost, looking for an honourable challenge. We felt that we rather let you, the players, decide for yourself how you want it played, and adjust your settings to your preferences;<br/><br/></li><li> The conditions of defeat are no longer attached to the main character falling in battle - you only lose when the whole party or the voidship is defeated;<br/><br/></li><li> You can now convert the Grim Darkness save into a normal save at any time if you no longer wish to continue playing that mode. Note however, that the opposite is not true and, once made, the conversion cannot be reversed. Converting your game into normal mode will make you ineligible for the “There Is Only War…” achievement or its reward;<br/><br/></li><li> The moment you meet your demise, you no longer instantly lose the save as it happened in the previous games - instead, you will be offered a choice to either accept your fate and delete the save, or to continue your playthrough, converting your save into a normal, non-Grim Darkness game as described above. This will allow you to finish the story if the death caught you close to the end of the game, but you will no longer qualify for the achievement or reward.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/f5e3ea7fd22cf5b5022a7b4e69600f22542b3d80.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s on the horizon?</div><br/>We are preparing a large exciting event related to this feature. Stay tuned for the announcement!<br/><br/>On a more general note, this feature is a good example of how we intend to approach the game in future updates. Besides the DLCs, we plan to gradually improve and expand the base game, not only with bug fixes, but also with alterations based on your feedback (which we are really grateful for, by the way!) and by adding brand new content in major updates.<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
