<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.1.208 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/497201025048904236</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Lord Captains!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 1.4.1.208 is live, fixing the issue with cyber-mastiff claws that persisted after the last hotfix. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now mastiff got his claws back and in case you equipped him with another weapon, you should find it in your inventory. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Note that </p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.1.207 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/501704535970938969</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Hotfix 1.4.1.207 is live, dealing with the issue where Glaito's claws may go missing after the recent big update. Worry not - we gave the cyber-mastiff his intimidating weapons back!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive post-release update 1.4.1 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762737337</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! We are back with a massive post-release update 1.4.1 for the Lex Imperialis expansion!<br/><br/>In it, we’ve addressed many of your common concerns - we allow you to recruit Solomorne earlier, add a lot of narrative adjustments, bring you new reactivity, new visuals, new items, fixing many technical issues and much more!<br/><br/>Note that consoles will take a bit more time to receive this update - it may be deployed there within 24 to 48 hours.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9f1ebc19233017338a5777658687d3c87eb07651.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Highlights:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> By your numerous requests, Solomorne’s recruitment mission now begins much earlier, at the very beginning of Act II. He will also now properly address the Lord Captain before leaving for Footfall!<br/></li><li> Also by your numerous requests, helmeted portraits for the Arbitrator origin!<br/></li><li> Additional reactivity and NPC banter across the Lex Imperialis locations;<br/></li><li> Narrative adjustments and improvements for Lex Imperialis locations and characters;<br/></li><li> Many new beautiful visuals;<br/></li><li> New protocols for familiars and interaction of protocols with Convictions;<br/></li><li> Many new items;<br/></li><li> Fixes and clarifications for items and abilities;<br/></li><li> Fixes for crashes, softlocks, lags, desyncs and other reported issues;<br/></li><li> Localization fixes;<br/></li><li> And MUCH more!</li></ul><br/><u>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</u><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/dad3b6cd1951f2a7e9844c62e1b3b17e074c96c6.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">System and Stability</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Crashes and Softlocks</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Quickly skipping a cutscene with Solomorne on Dargonus no longer breaks the dialogue with him;<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash related to units leaving a Servo-skull Swarm ability area;<br/></li><li> Saving immediately after respeccing an Overseer no longer causes the game to crash or the UI to go haywire, including the main menu;<br/></li><li> A battle with Chtonos in Act III no longer sometimes freezes on the enemy turn;<br/></li><li> Skipping the cutscene at the Bloodspun Web temple no longer causes the game to freeze;<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare case where Glaito would become impossible to interact with in Act III, making it impossible to rescue Solomorne;<br/></li><li> Fixed a softlock caused under rare circumstances by the Veil of Blades ability, which could prevent the player from ending the turn;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Lag and freezing</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Optimized memory usage by the audio, and fixed one of the sound-related stutter cases;<br/></li><li> Fixed frame drops caused by presence of familiars on certain locations;<br/></li><li> Fixed an frame drop caused by Reactivate ability of the Overseer;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case of lag in one of Pasqal’s dialogues during a Warp event, that was caused by a certain internal loop. Let the Cycle be discontinued!<br/></li><li> Fixed a lagspike caused by the use of Heel! ability;<br/></li><li> Hovering over Ruinous Flows talent no longer causes temporary performance degradation;<br/></li><li> Visiting Mortus Acies system from the Lex Imperialis expansion on the global map no longer causes temporary performance degradation;<br/></li><li> Inspecting a unit under the effects of Destroy the Weak no longer causes frame drops;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><b></b><li> By your numerous requests, Solomorne’s recruitment mission now begins much earlier, at your first visit to Footfall! For players who are past this point but haven’t yet recruited Solomorne, the errand will pop up after a couple of warp jumps;<br/></li><li> By your feedback, in the recent update we’ve allowed the Heartless to join the Rogue Trader’s fleet earlier, in Act II. In this update, we’re also supporting it with additional narrative adjustments to account for that change;<br/></li><li> At the beginning of Act II, Solomorne will now converse with the Rogue Trader about his disembarkation from the ship and his further plans;<br/></li><li> Solomorne will now have new things to say on colony decisions, with appropriate rewards;<br/></li><li> Added narrative adjustments, improvements and new answer options in multiple dialogues related to the characters and locations from the Lex Imperialis expansion;<br/></li><li> A brand new dialogue related to Warp entities at the finale of Thassera;<br/></li><li> New reactivity to the player's background on Leethus, Thassera and aboard the Heartless;<br/></li><li> You can now learn a bit more about the former wielders of the skulls in the servo-skull swarm;<br/></li><li> A new dialogue option regarding an Arbites visit was added at Footfall in the conversation with Vladaym Tocara;<br/></li><li> Many new flavour items and interactable icons with lore descriptions were added to the Palace of Justice, Administratum and Thassera;<br/></li><li> New minor cutscenes and character animations for dialogue options at Thassera;<br/></li><li> New NPC banter was added on Thassera;<br/></li><li> Added a new event where you can encounter the Heartless around your colonies if you choose the option to patrol the trade routes;<br/></li><li> New reactivity for the servo-skull swarm at the distress signal planet;<br/></li><li> Some additional reactivity for familiars has been added across book events;<br/></li><li> Added additional narrative description for the sculptures and the cyberlacerax area at Thassera;<br/></li><li> New epilogue was added for Maive. In Grim Darkness of the far future, all sorcery comes at a price…<br/></li><li> Vigdis’ reaction to the consequences of attempting to pet Glaito is now less emotional, more in line with her usual character;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the player received an invitation to talk to Solomorne in Act IV, but no new dialogue options appeared;</li></ul>[/b]<br/><li> The new portrait for Master of Seals wasn’t added to the older content at first - we’ve fixed this inconsistency;<br/></li><li> One of the choices in the dialogue with Solomorne at the scene with the organ incorrectly led to the same reaction from Solomorne as another choice - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of cases where the narrative description was contradicting the cutscene or NPC visuals on Thassera;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug making it impossible to report to Prefect Inscribia Vultur if the player decided to abort the landing and return later;<br/></li><li> Some of companion banter related to Lex Imperialis expansion lacked the necessary conditions, causing it to pop up in irrelevant situations or mention companions that are not in the party - fixed;<br/></li><li> During Solomorne’s bath scene in the Lord-captain’s quarters, the dialogue now correctly refers to a servant, not an enforcer;<br/></li><li> A dialogue option for Solomorne to shoot the mutant on Thassera will no longer appear if he has no ranged weapon;<br/></li><li> After the scene with Jae, Marazhai or Ulfar at the bath ended, sometimes control would not return to the player for 30-60 seconds after the end of the cutscene - fixed;<br/></li><li> Arbitrators at the Palace of Justice will now converse with each other;<br/></li><li> Arbitrators at the Administratum will now converse with each other;<br/></li><li> The governor on Thassera no longer looks to the side while greeting the Lord Captain. How dare he!<br/></li><li> Solomorne’s body is no longer replaced by Kibellah in the vision of the voidship bridge in Act III;<br/></li><li> Description of the psyber-raven devouring a demonic essence at Eufrates II no longer has Uralon as a speaker;<br/></li><li> Argenta will no longer chat with Solomorne in Commorragh if he’s not in the party;<br/></li><li> In rare circumstances, it was impossible to check the cogitator for Nomos’ quest - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some Solomorne-related events could occur for players without the Lex Imperialis DLC - fixed;<br/></li><li> Choosing a dogmatic option to have the brothers on Thassera flogged no longer displays that they were executed on the character history screen;<br/></li><li> Heinrix no longer inserts himself into dialogues with Solomorne if he’s not in the party;<br/></li><li> The message from Vigdis about meeting with Solomorne in Act II now has a correct speaker;<br/></li><li> Maive no longer says that she would wait for the Lord Captain when we know she’ll continue to follow him anyway;<br/></li><li> Fixed a repeatable introduction line in the dialogue with Glaito;<br/></li><li> Companions will no longer provide their stats for the checks during the bath scene with Solomorne. We cheer for you, Lord Captain!;<br/></li><li> Companions will no longer provide their stats for the checks during the feast at Thassera;<br/></li><li> The dialogue option that required a skillcheck in the dialogue with the servo-skull swarm was only available once - subsequent dialogues with the swarm didn’t show that option anymore - fixed;<br/></li><li> A dialogue option regarding Abelard appearing in one of the dialogues on Thassera will no longer show if Abelard is not in the party;<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple Error Speaker cases across the game related to Lex Imperialis content;</li>[/list]<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mechanics</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enemies on the Heartless could sometimes skip their turns or buff instead of attacking - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed movement issues for Consolidation, Blood for the Blood God, Notch of Purpose and "That's an Order! abilities. Movement should be more predictable now and still work even in cases when the preferred position of the movement is too far away from the affected unit;<br/></li><li> Reinforcements at the Palace of Justice received new abilities and talents, becoming a bigger threat;<br/></li><li> Flanking Manoeuvre no longer references the cyber-mastiff in the description when used by a cyber-eagle;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull Swarm and Psyber-raven’s Relocate ability sometimes triggered attacks of opportunity in contrary to its description - fixed;<br/></li><li> Binding Purpose now correctly removes debuffs when restoring wounds;<br/></li><li> Attacks blocked with a shield no longer consume Exploit stacks;<br/></li><li> Fixed the description of Overseer’s Heroic Act and Desperate Measures upgrade, which implied to only increase ability damage, while in fact all damage done was increased;<br/></li><li> Clarified that the buff from Dependable Ally talent lasts for 1 round;<br/></li><li> Resistance is Futile Overseer talent now displays the malus correctly when multiple Overseers in the party have it;<br/></li><li> Servitude now additionally states that the familiar is not affected by Momentum;<br/></li><li> Run! ability no longer mentions Attacks of Opportunity because the familiar is already immune to them;<br/></li><li> Cyber-mastiff’s Battle Mode: Terror now stacks up to 100 times;<br/></li><li> Cyber-mastiff’s Auto-regeneration now also works on soul and warp burning;<br/></li><li> Cyber-eagle’s Strafe description no longer incorrectly indicates that the familiar will begin soaring after using the ability;<br/></li><li> Bounty Hunter’s prey mechanics now correctly interact with familiars killing the target;<br/></li><li> Cyber-laceraxes on Thassera will now bite before death more often;<br/></li><li> Description for Servo-skull Swarm now correctly states that INT and FEL are the primary stats, not AGI and PER;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull Swarm’s Emergency Stimulation can no longer work more than once per combat if the familiar was reduced to zero wounds and then reactivated;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull Swarm’s Vitality Signal no longer has a random “cannot be over 90” unrelated text in the middle of the description;<br/></li><li> Fixed familiar ability interactions with Anchor points at Leethus;<br/></li><li> In a dialogue with Solomorne during the feast, only Rogue Trader’s own stats are now used for checks;<br/></li><li> Obstruct Vision now allows the Cyber-Eagle to attack the target even if they have Stunned, Prone, or Can't Attack status effects;<br/></li><li> Some shotguns didn’t allow burst attacks in melee range - fixed;<br/></li><li> Spectrovisor enemy ability now always correctly ignores smoke;<br/></li><li> Familiars will no longer teleport to their hideouts after loading a game in combat on the voidship bridge or at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> While Soaring, the cyber-eagle no longer provides a Momentum bonus from the Brothers-in-Arms talent to its allies;<br/></li><li> While Soaring, the cyber-eagle is no longer a valid familiar for the Side by Side Overseer's talent;<br/></li><li> The effect of Overcharge now correctly affects the next three Overseer abilities' AP cost if the psyber-raven is the chosen familiar;<br/></li><li> Dependable Ally now correctly grants +5 Agility if the Overseer's familiar is a psyber-raven;<br/></li><li> The psyber-raven now correctly lowers enemy Agility via the Overseer's Suppression Factor talent;<br/></li><li> While Soaring, the cyber-eagle no longer provides a characteristics penalty from the Suppressive Factor talent to the enemies;<br/></li><li> Scourge of the Feeble now correctly works with Warp Burn and Immolate the Soul;<br/></li><li> Priority Signal now correctly gets bonus Armour and Dodge from Enhanced Radio Signal;<br/></li><li> Step into the Abyss caused enemies to move towards the psyker instead of the psyber-raven - fixed;<br/></li><li> Heel! ability from "Heel!" Protocol item now correctly counts as an Overseer ability for the purposes of mechanical interactions;<br/></li><li> Blinding Strike — Soaring now correctly triggers a harder to pass Agility resistance test;<br/></li><li> Steel Talons debuff wasn't stacking for parry - fixed;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull swarm Self-Learning Algorithms talent no longer works from the other Officers targeting the familiar with their abilities;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull swarm Safe Shelter talent no longer stacks from several servo-skull swarms;<br/></li><li> Servoskull swarm's Energy Multiplier talent can now only be chosen by an Officer Overseer;<br/></li><li> The following Officer talents no longer grant bonuses to the servo-skull swarm when using Officer's abilities through the servo-skull swarm, instead granting them to the targets of Extrapolation: Focus!, Inspire Courage, Personal Oversight, Be Vigilant!, Inspiring Speech, Iron Discipline, Seize the Initiative, Undaunted;<br/></li><li> If more than one psyber-raven with the Bound by Warp talent is present, the Willpower penalty will be applied only once;<br/></li><li> The psyber-raven's Ruinous Flows talent now deals the correct amount of Warp damage;<br/></li><li> Demons summoned under the effect of Thassertium Mask were still prioritizing the player - fixed;<br/></li><li> Stalwart Defence now only works on marked enemies;<br/></li><li> The servo-skull swarm underwent a number of sacred rituals in the name of the Omnissiah and now correctly interacts with some of the Origin abilities of Noble, Arbitrator Castigator and of course, Pasqal;<br/></li><li> Fixed some cases of problematic interaction between familiars and elevators;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with psyber-raven missing its base features in some cases of playing on custom difficulty settings;<br/></li><li> Clarified interaction between basic shield attack discount and Shield Swing;<br/></li><li> You can now use Shield Swing as any other AoE - targeting a tile instead of a creature;<br/></li><li> Fixed Shield Swing cost and infinite attack bug when using it in conjecture with Daring Breach;<br/></li><li> Overseer's Overcharge (both Heroic and Desperate) now removes different hard-control negative effects if the familiar is not unconscious;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><b></b><li> Added additional effects to 8 protocols in Act II that interact with the Overseer's Conviction;<br/></li><li> Added 4 new protocols with Conviction interaction between Footfall and Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Moved protocols on Footfall to more convenient and easy-to-spot places;<br/></li><li> Added a new arbites-themed helmet to a new loot box on Footfall, which can be found near the Arbites squad and will let you obtain the iconic Arbitrator look for your Lord Captain quicker:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/76ecbfb6e31e49b72b3fb6aaab8b7bda6c42c5ad.png"/><br/></li><li> Added a new color variation of laspistols;<br/></li><li> Added a new Heavy Stabber version with purity seals on it;<br/></li><li> Added a new default protocol for Glaito to boost his initial damage. If you've already recruited Solomorne, it will be added to your inventory;<br/></li><li> Vindictor Flamer is now available as a reward for the Heartless being used as trade transport, not from a vendor:</li></ul>[/b]<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2ddb4518d91638eca88a23b90d4874a76c197b0e.png"/><br/><li> Vindictor Flamer melee attacks no longer spend ammo and have correct animations;<br/></li><li> Vindictor Flamer melee AoE attack pattern size was increased. BURN THE HERETIC!<br/></li><li> Burning Faith Insignia no longer only causes your faith to burn (the memes were deserved), but also makes the first Melta weapon attack per combat not count for the limit of attacks per turn, and allows one free Melta weapon reload every round:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/d5e5e5e984046bbb220062fad029ef6e71554e35.png"/><br/></li><li> Solid Shield Enarmes had an incorrect formula in the description - fixed;<br/></li><li> Impulse Boots had an incorrect formula in the description - fixed;<br/></li><li> Advanced Sensors had an incorrect formula in the description - fixed;<br/></li><li> FI-DR-Alpha module protocol description was updated to reflect that it gives +15 to the relevant stats, not +10;<br/></li><li> Description for Heavy Maul has been corrected to include that it causes a shield bash if a shield is equipped;<br/></li><li> Optical Linking protocol calculated the values incorrectly - fixed;<br/></li><li> Vindictor Flamer didn’t have an animation for its chainsaw part, and was held incorrectly - fixed;<br/></li><li> Last Ditch Armour now always correctly awards momentum;<br/></li><li> Intimidating Growl was missing its flavor text - fixed;<br/></li><li> Claustrophobia now correctly adds bonus dodge against melee attacks;<br/></li><li> Feudal Plate armor can no longer be worn by xenos and Astartes;<br/></li><li> Merciless Onslaught now correctly scales as 5 x Overseer's PER Bonus instead of 3 x Overseer's PER Bonus;<br/></li><li> Black Omen Mk II protocol was giving incorrect stat bonus - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the value in the description of Falconry protocol always displaying as 0;<br/></li><li> Retobi-pattern Shotgun now correctly costs 1 AP to shoot like the other shotguns;<br/></li><li> Armour of the Final Threshold was available for purchase without Lex Imperialis - fixed. If you've already got the item - it won't be removed. Finders keepers;<br/></li><li> Impulse Boots now correctly only trigger once when attacking with Chain Saws;<br/></li><li> Composite Gloves were not giving stacking block bonus - fixed;<br/></li><li> Wrathful Mask now correctly decreases damage taken;<br/></li><li> Bonus stats from Dog Tag were applying for 1 round instead of until the end of the round as stated in its description - fixed;<br/></li><li> Reactivator Pack was not working - fixed;<br/></li><li> Singed Cape was providing armor instead of damage reduction - fixed;<br/></li><li> Bonus from Meragon Boots were not being lost when losing Ruthless Suppression effect - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed Elastic Gloves working inconsistently;<br/></li><li> Iron Grip gloves were not working - fixed. This fix will only apply on the next combat with these gloves;<br/></li><li> Spiked Gloves were providing the target with armor instead of providing armor penetration for the attacker, and were not applying Bleeding - fixed. While the drukhari are known for their unconventional battle tactics, making their enemies tougher is too much even for them;<br/></li><li> Removed duplicate rewards from the Tithe-related contracts;<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect reputation requirement for Power Shield Amplifier which prevented the player from buying it;<br/></li><li> Updated the behaviour and description of Ultrasonic Whistle;<br/></li><li> Intimidating Growl shield was non-equippable for companions - fixed;<br/></li><li> Sturdy Shield Straps were completely redesigned;<br/></li><li> Portable Motive Force Storage now correctly works with familiars other than the cyber-mastiff. This change will become active starting with the next battle;<br/></li><li> Meragon Ring was giving autohits to 2 attacks instead of 1, and sometimes gave an additional attack - fixed. Also, moved its flavour text from description into flavor text proper.<br/></li><li> Updated the visuals for Assault Armour, Steel Triad, Insulator Shield and Armour of Iron Will to match the icons;<br/></li><li> Updated the visuals for Self-Calibrating Helmet, Retinal Analyser, Meragon Helmet, Tactical Vox-Transmitter;<br/></li><li> Updated visuals for the Kinesiostatic Shield, Hardened Shield, Radiant Shield and Heavy Shield:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2d560fdc093412398876ab80df90e906cf516404.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a7275df6f5fee7e5911af0da5fa88dacf3e2018e.png"/><br/><br/></li><li> Updated the visuals for Feudal world maces;<br/></li><li> Tactical Genius now supports block as well;<br/></li><li> Updated the model geometry for shotpistols - the hole at the end of the barrel was so big that this size of the barrel would not fit in the actual pistol, clipping through the targeting optics. Thanks to one of our community members, it has been noticed and fixed;</li>[/list]<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Locations</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Loading a save at the Epitaph no longer causes Solomorne and Glaito to run back towards the shuttle;<br/></li><li> Camera can no longer get stuck at Dargonus when you watch from the balcony;<br/></li><li> Improved the placement of NPCs and objects on Thassera and added some new commoners;<br/></li><li> Minor improvements of cutscenes on Thassera<br/></li><li> Deployable ladders at the Necron worlds no longer sometimes return to a folded form while pathing remains the same;<br/></li><li> Moved a box in the battle with the Ambull that let the player position their characters in such a way that the only person on the open ground was unreachable by the Ambull. Previously, that led to her skipping turns doing nothing, but she'll get you this time, Lord Captain;<br/></li><li> Curiosity Merchant no longer randomly appears on the voidship bridge clipping through the star map;<br/></li><li> Improved some lighting and visual effects during the boarding of the Heartless;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with disappearing lootable corpse at Rykad Minoris Star Port;<br/></li><li> Fixed some pathing and clipping issues on Thassera;<br/></li><li> Under some circumstances it was possible to obtain 3 companions early in Commorragh: Abelard, Solomorne and Argenta, for the first arena battle at Commorragh. Fixed, Abelard will be coming a bit later in this setup;<br/></li><li> A number of doors in the game could sometimes become impassable after saving in an opened state - fixed;<br/></li><li> Elevator on Thassera was missing during Maive’s adventure;</li></ul><br/><b>Visual</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>On the feudal world of Thassera, a gargantuan aquila made out of farm fields is now visible in the distance:<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/7bfd2b1e8adc6fa61e8aea1447f5eeb2ade0604d.png"/><br/></b></li><li> Added a stunning destroyed planet background for one of the new space battles from the Lex Imperialis expansion:<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/b20c0d1b81d8bba4ae8099492ac4d9e8037fadd2.gif"/><br/></li><li> By a popular community request, we’ve added additional helmeted versions of portraits for the Arbitrator origin for you to radiate Lex Imperialis in all its glory: </li></ul>[/b]<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9f1ebc19233017338a5777658687d3c87eb07651.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/48e9796b3939c7f8a6b808bf158181c5ece5dc50.png"/><br/><li> Lady Cassia’s animation for holding a shield was incorrect and was fixed. That was to be expected though - where would a noble lady learn to wield a shield? And no sane Lord Captain would ever send their only precious Navigator into melee anyway, right..? Right?<br/></li><li> Rogue Trader shuttle sometimes could lose heraldry and colors on Footfall - fixed;<br/></li><li> Leader of the knights on Thassera has received distinct armor visuals;<br/></li><li> Increased the size of some shields;<br/></li><li> Familiar colors will no longer sometimes reset on loading the game;<br/></li><li> Colors for servo-skull swarm have been updated;<br/></li><li> Familiar models will no longer sometimes disappear in the inventory screen;<br/></li><li> A selected option to show the headpiece for the base outfit no longer causes the headpiece to stay during romance and bath cutscenes;<br/></li><li> When dragging items, familiars would sometimes teleport around or move oddly - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a visual issue where scanning the systems around the ship would reveal them before the scanning visual effect actually reaches them;<br/></li><li> Fixed minor visual issues with psyber-raven petting animation;<br/></li><li> Elements of the Arbites or Astra Militarum origin armour sometimes could randomly start protruding through Solomorne’s outfit - fixed;<br/></li><li> After reloading the game in the captain’s quarters, the cyber-eagle will no longer appear on the psyber-raven’s nest for a few seconds and then fly off;<br/></li><li> Familiars will no longer ruin the final cutscene at the Epitaph by appearing randomly across the screen;<br/></li><li> Improved the cutscene with the Adeptus Arbites Marshal in Act IV;<br/></li><li> Some Thassera citizens are no longer invisible;<br/></li><li> Ordering Argenta to execute Yrliet in Act IV no longer sometimes causes all character models in the party to become horribly twisted;<br/></li><li> Shadow from the Rogue Trader’s statue on Thassera remained after combat - fixed;<br/></li><li> Visors of all Arbites helmets are now always red;<br/></li><li> Lord Captain’s model could sometimes disappear during the trial at Commorragh - fixed;<br/></li><li> Foehammer model is no longer invisible:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e25ef2419050bc9c7973b2a33e94e1ff968c28ad.png"/><br/></li><li> Mutants on Thassera will now have proper animations for ranged attacks;<br/></li><li> Armoured glass at the Arbites palace will no longer always dissolve at most camera angles, becoming invisible;<br/></li><li> Fixed NPC clipping during the mutant attack on Thassera;<br/></li><li> Texture improvements for the cyber-eagle;<br/></li><li> Texture improvements for the psyber-raven;<br/></li><li> Removed visual glitches remaining after the combat at the ritual ground on Thassera;<br/></li><li> Improved the visuals of some Adeptus Arbites armors and helmets, fixed minor clipping issues;<br/></li><li> Explosions of large ships in space combat are now larger;<br/></li><li> The color of sand in the fight with the Ambull is now in line with the rest of the sand on the planet;<br/></li><li> Quickly skipping turns in the encounter at the Palace of Justice no longer causes some visual effects and animations to get stuck;<br/></li><li> Default appearances for the new Arbitrator portraits have been adjusted to better match the portraits;<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping issues with Feudal Plate armor;<br/></li><li> Fixed mismatch in visuals between Spiked Gloves model and its icon;<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect idle animation for the Leman Russ tank;<br/></li><li> Fixed a visual glitch where a cyber-mastiff would ride forward in a sitting position. Stop that, Glaito!<br/></li><li> The horse on Thassera no longer runs through the door before it opens in the cutscene;<br/></li><li> Color correction for many Arbites-themed weapons and armor;<br/></li><li> Visual adjustments for nobles at Thassera to reflect their medieval style;</li>[/list]<br/><br/><b>UI</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added tutorials for familiars;<br/></li><li> Abilities that are only available for Retransmission during Heroic Acts or Desperate Measures, will now only display the appropriate tag in the description during Heroic Acts or Desperate Measures;<br/></li><li> You can now select the placement of your familiar when playing on console or with a controller during the preparation round;<br/></li><li> Some familiar abilities would display incorrect icons and descriptions if the familiar was dead - fixed;<br/></li><li> When on console or playing with a controller, the UI timer for the battle at the Heartless no longer covers the Start battle button;<br/></li><li> It’s no longer possible to equip Claws on non-familiar party members when playing on console or with a controller;<br/></li><li> Some shield icons related to shields with purity seals now have purity seals on them too;<br/></li><li> The pirate captain’s speech bubbles at the Heartless no longer hang in mid-air;<br/></li><li> Purchasing less than maximum amount of stimulants from Opticon-22 no longer breaks the trade UI;<br/></li><li> Pack Hunting no longer gives a buff with a missing icon;<br/></li><li> Replaced an icon for the Hope Is Weakness ability;<br/></li><li> Changed the icon for Forceful Paw Strike;<br/></li><li> Solomorne will no longer sometimes disguise himself as a cyber-mastiff on the character panel on the voidship bridge;<br/></li><li> Fixed a problem where descriptions of Overseer abilities could disappear for Idira;<br/></li><li> Restored missing descriptions on accusations in Vigils Castle and names on some Arbites weapons;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Localization</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ebonite Sword no longer refers to a maul in its description;<br/></li><li> Multiple Arbites weapons didn’t have any names except for their weapon class - they all received proper names;<br/></li><li> The maul in the rewards for the Palace of Justice had no name - fixed;<br/></li><li> Description for Koronus Expanse Marshal’s helmet was updated for clarity;<br/></li><li> Description for Blood Feast cyber-eagle protocol was updated for clarity;<br/></li><li> Description for Cyber eagle’s Wind Currents was updated for clarity;<br/></li><li> Improved the English localization for some of Solomorne’s phrases;<br/></li><li> A few cyber-eagle buff descriptions lacked a Russian translation;<br/></li><li> Fixed some ability names in Chinese localization;<br/></li><li> Some abilities that were updated to interact with the new Block mechanics, missed the updated description in Russian - fixed;<br/></li><li> Numerous typo fixes in all languages;</li></ul><br/><b>Audio</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Sad music will now play during the death of Solomorne and Glaito in one of the outcomes of the Lex Imperialis story;<br/></li><li> The Heartless now has proper sound effects in space combat;<br/></li><li> Added additional sound effects to multiple Lex Imperialis cutscenes and NPCs;<br/></li><li> Selecting a female Arbitrator portrait no longer resets your current selection of voice to male;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to final dialogue on Palace of Justice;<br/></li><li> </li></ul><br/><b>Space</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Systems from the Lex Imperialis expansion couldn’t be previewed on the Koronus Expanse map - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Co-op</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You can no longer select another player’s familiar in co-op;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case of desync during the dialogue with Argenta on her second quest;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case of desync when loading the game in the middle of combat;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Release the Hound! achievement was incorrectly awarded for 6 bites a turn instead of 7 - fixed;<br/></li><li> Release the Hound! achievement wasn’t awarded on Xbox and MSStore - fixed;<br/></li><li> No Stone Unturned achievement is now always awarded correctly;</li></ul><br/>This is all for now, and we hope you’re enjoying the work we’re doing! <br/><br/>Thanks for all your feeback, and keep it coming!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 18:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of torment - Release Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497199486905357074</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/185de1e5f7f5045e0a2392cc897c15091ca86b28.png"/><br/><br/>We are moving the release date of Total War: WARHAMMER III - Tides of Torment to later this year.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 Read the full Release Update here 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #72 (1.8.4)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520843384949052047</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #72 (1.8.4) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed server crash occurring while playing Refinery Delta-17.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rolled back to FSR version 3.1.2. This change is made to ensure the best overall experience for players, while maintaining support for key features like FSR 4 and others. We're actively working on updating to a newer version in the future and will reintroduce newer improvements when ready.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue where the Arbites Talent 'Razor-Jaw Augment' was being affected by Cyber-Mastiff damage increasing buffs.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note</b>: <i>Regarding the last issue on the list, this resulted in damage being increased by up to 450% at times.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Havoc Campaign - Mission Pool and Mutator Rotation</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Every third week during a Havoc Campaign, we are rotating the mission pool and mutator pool. One or two missions and mutators will swap out during this time. This rotation will happen next week.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mission Pool</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Incoming</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Hab Dreyko</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Mercantile HL-70-04-510</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Outgoing</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Consignment Yard HL17-36</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Chasm Logistratum</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mutators</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Incoming</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>None</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Outgoing</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Pus-Hardened Skin</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Inferno Special Event</i></p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 12:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
