<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #51 (1.5.4) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157321628805552</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cc881a4ff16e80234fb139208c6f4a1a5703f925.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div><br/>Hotfix #51 (aka 1.5.4) is out now and you can find the patch notes for it below! It is out now on Steam and it will shortly follow on our other platforms. <br/><div class="bb_h2">Render Settings Reset</div>With 1.5.0 and the introduction of FSR 3.1 Frame Generation we accidentally defaulted the Frame Gen setting to be on. This was unintentional and we apologize for the inconvenience. With this hotfix, the launcher will be doing a proper re-detection of your render settings and reset the frame generation setting to off. This applies even if you have explicitly turned on Frame Generation. You will have to turn it on again, and you might want to tweak other render settings to your liking after the first time you launch the game.<br/><div class="bb_h2">Deprecating Fullscreen Exclusive (FSE) Display Mode</div><div class="bb_h3">What?</div>With 1.5.4 we will be deprecating our Fullscreen Exclusive (currently named "Fullscreen") display mode and adding the ability to set custom resolution for the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode. You will not see any performance degradation from this change.<br/><div class="bb_h3">Why?</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We have now added the ability to set custom resolution for the "Borderless Fullscreen" which was the last remaining blocker for making the "Borderless Fullscreen" fully usable.<br/></li><li> The Fullscreen Exclusive display mode no longer serves a purpose when it comes to improving the performance of Win10/DX12 exclusive titles after Microsoft's improvements to borderless window modes*. <br/></li><li> For quite some time we have seen a lot of issues connected to the Fullscreen Exclusive display mode.<br/></li><li> With the latest release we also added FSR3.1 FG which added even more crashes with a similar connection to the Fullscreen Exclusive display mode and it is clear that the focus on testing for Fullscreen Exclusive display modes from our partners is dropping.<br/></li><li> The borderless window approach to fullscreen shows significantly more stable and user friendly behavior for players that frequently alt-tab in and out of the game.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">How?</div>Going forward we are renaming "Borderless Fullscreen" to only "Fullscreen" and will have only two display mode options "Window" or "Fullscreen". We are also decoupling the resolution from the window size, meaning that you will now be allowed to set any resolution for the game when using the new Fullscreen (previously "Borderless Fullscreen") mode. Previously you were always locked to using the desktop resolution if you used the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode. This caused players that had a 4k desktop resolution but hardware that wasn't able to push the game to sufficient frame rates at 4k, to be unable to use the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode.<br/><br/>* https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/demystifying-full-screen-optimizations/<br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">"The DWM manages the composition/organization of the desktop display content from various applications, meaning it controls what is rendered and presented to the front of your display and what is held in the background. However, this control has historically resulted in a slight performance overhead vs FSE, where the game has full control.<br/><br/>To get back this performance overhead, we enhanced the DWM to recognize when a game is running in a borderless full screen window with no other applications on the screen. In this circumstance, the DWM gives control of the display and almost all the CPU/GPU power to the game. Which in turn allows equivalent performance to running a game in FSE.”</blockquote><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes and Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some of the weapons with a Special activate action failed to correctly refresh their activation if the Special action was performed again while in the active duration of a previous Special activation.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where shots from the M35 Magnacore Mk II Plasma Gun failed to penetrate Bulwark shields.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Valkyrie briefings would sometimes not finish before loading into a mission. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you would occasionally see a <text> subtitle when getting close to a character in the Mourningstar.  <br/></text></li><li> Fixed an issue where subtitle text from Morrow would sometimes remain displayed after the VO ended.  <br/></li><li> Fixed some issues with Darinda Dukane’s animations.  <br/></li><li> Updated the description of the Ceaseless Barrage blessing to correctly match the gameplay mechanics.<br/></li><li> Updated software that should address the issue of players being unable to see or type in chat.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash related to enemy spawning that could occur during certain mission events.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that could cause a crash when navigating the Mastery menu using a gamepad without any Blessings present.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some gaps would appear while wearing the Zealot “Pious Banneret's Garb” upper body cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the rivets on the Veteran “Lucius KM VIIIB Death’s Head” and “Lucius MK IIIA Death’s Head” headgear cosmetics wouldn’t always line up correctly, creating incorrect shadows.  <br/></li><li> Made slight changes to the collar of the Veteran “Krieg Greatcoat MkI” upper body cosmetic to avoid clipping with the “Lucius KM VIIIB Death’s Head” and “Lucius MK IIIA Death’s Head” headgear cosmetics.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the shoulder pad on the Psyker “Kobaloi Topcoat” upperbody cosmetic would appear to be offset from the arm.  <br/></li><li> Fixed some clipping issues while wearing the Psyker “ "Timeworn" Psyker Jerkin (Taros Tan)” upper body cosmetic together with the “ “Timeworn” Psyker Regalia” lower body cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed the insignia on the Zealot “MK IX Pot Helm and Rebreather” headgear cosmetic being depressed into the helmet.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where certain faces would lightly clip into the visor of the Zealot “Votarist’s Pot Helm with Rebreather” headgear cosmetic.  </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><b>Fsr 3.1 Frame Generation Does Not Do Anything During Excessive Fullscreen Effects </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FSR 3.1 Frame Generation excludes the entire screen from generation when there are a lot of fullscreen effects playing that impact all pixels on screen. This will cause frame gen to just copy the previous rendered result which results in the framerate looking like framegen is disabled while frame counters saying that it is running correctly. <br/></li><li> <b>CURRENT WORKAROUND:</b> If players disable Lens Quality, it addresses this issue for the time being.</li></ul><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.<br/></li><li> <b>UPDATED:</b> A fix for this will be shipped with the next hotfix.</li></ul><b>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).<br/></li><li> <b>UPDATED: </b>A fix for this will be shipped with the next hotfix.</li></ul><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Render Settings Reset Ahead of Hotfix 1.5.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157321628469454</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0863570d8496f418ed7318b81d3e816e471b8c51.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heya Everyone, </div><br/>We are putting out a hotfix this week which might require players to tweak their render settings again when first launching the game on PC. <br/><br/>When Unlocked &amp; Unloaded came out last month, we added FSR 3.1 Frame Generation. As many noticed, this was defaulted to “on” and it caused issues for some players.<br/><br/>Honestly, this was unintentional, as it was not meant to be defaulted to on. <br/><br/>For this next Hotfix #51, we will update the settings version which will force the launcher to re-detect players’ render settings, this will reset the FSR3.1 frame generation to off. This is partially to revert the defaulted frame generation setting and partially to clean up resolutions and render settings to prepare for another change coming with the hotfix. 	<br/><br/>When launching the game for the first time, the launcher will show a pop up to notify the user that settings have been reset based on hardware detection. Some players might want to go and tweak settings based on their own preferences. <br/><br/>This note will be included in the patch notes this week for Hotfix #51, but we wanted to make sure this isn’t missed by players and it is clearly communicated ahead of time!<br/><br/>Thank you,<br/><br/>The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitch Drops - Exclusive items</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720136550730</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>As the Grim Darkness Challenge arrives in the Koronus Expanse, so too does the exclusive Twitch Drops campaign!<br/><br/>To activate Drops and receive items, you will need to link your PC account to Twitch. Simply enter the game and locate the special chest inside the Lord Captain’s quarters. Click on it to interact and then follow the instructions on our website to link your account. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/61f7e5ef9349ae20e4a0bce2db66d1ed4da84b7a.png"/><br/>Once your account is successfully linked, all you need to do is watch any of the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader streams on Twitch with Drops enabled for at least an hour, and the rewards will be yours to enjoy!<br/><br/>There are <b>three unique in-game items</b> up for grabs: a pack of mind-twitching grenades, a helmet of tactical superiority, and a special servo skull (rumour has it, the skull has a few words for those who decide to click on it). The items will be dropped right into the special chest inside the Lord Captain’s quarters - no need to do anything! Also, these items are not limited to one playthrough and will replenish if you choose to start a new game.<br/><br/>The campaign starts with the Grim Darkness Challenge on <b>October 22nd</b> and will end on <b>November 4th</b>.<br/><br/>Find more detailed information on our website:<br/>https://roguetrader.owlcat.games/drops<br/><br/><br/>May luck follow our Grim Darkness Challenge contestants, and may the Emperor protect them on their perilous adventures!<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grim Darkness Challenge is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720136624929</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The Grim Darkness challenge is here!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1wCja-jxGv4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is The Grim Darkness Challenge?</div><br/>It is an intense competitive event for streamers, where, over the course of two weeks, participants will compete live in beating (or making it as far as they can in!) Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader on Daring difficulty in Grim Darkness mode - a newly introduced brutal gameplay mode where only a single save is allowed and is rewritten every time a player exits the game. All decisions and consequences in this mode are final, reloading is impossible, and if the party is defeated—the game is over!<br/><br/>The challenge will begin in just a few hours, on 00:00 GMT October 22, and last for 2 weeks until 23:59 GMT November 4, or until all players have successfully completed their playthroughs or were eliminated. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Participants:</div><br/><ol><li> Amm0ni	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Arkcard	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> ArmiaStars	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> BearlyTactical	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> BringItDon	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> coredumped	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Daily Dose of Warhammer	(Twitch)(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Flynnflytaggart	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Game kNight Plays	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> GruntarTV	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Kaerenai	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Kommissar Azura	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> kormakrtv	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Mirianatir	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Mortismal Gaming	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Nightharrow	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Otrod1e	(Twitch)	<br/></li><li> Remortis Gaming (Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Revan	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Slandered Gaming	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> TangerineBlade	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> TheCriticallyClueless	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Unknownhost	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> The Station	(Twitch)	(Youtube)</li></ol><br/>Watch your favourite streamer best the hardest trial or fail on the road to the grand prize!<br/><br/>Full rules of the challenge can be found here!<br/><br/>May luck follow our Grim Darkness Challenge contestants!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.2.1.19 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720122109386</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>We're deploying a new routine update where we've fixed a number of mechanical and narrative issues, improved visuals for the Freight Line and adjusted a certain Act IV fight in the Void Shadows DLC to be a bit less frustrating. <br/><br/>The same update will be coming to consoles within ~24 hours.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Watch out for possible spoilers below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">System and stability</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It's no longer possible to Quick Load in Grim Darkness mode;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After defeating the Aurora, instead of the usual cutscene on the voidship, the player could sometimes receive the bathing dialogue instead, causing the game to break in wild ways - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a broken trigger in a dialogue with Nemesite which could lock the quest progress. Players who have already experienced this, will have the quest automatically switch to the next stage;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that caused one of the dialogues with Marazhai on the arena in Act III to break. Those who already had this happen will need to restart the event;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where after defeating the main enemy of the Void Shadows DLC, the Rogue Trader could be teleported outside the Voidship bridge, unable to come back;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where failing A Card Inverted quest could make it impossible to talk to Kibellah in Act IV;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you could incorrectly add Marazhai to your party right after he accepted your offer to join your retinue. That caused a number of odd story issues and could make you lose some of the other companions. He will now wait in the Pit as intended;<br/></li><li> In the Ablution in Blood quest, Jocasta's investigation report could suddenly stop, locking the quest progress - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some uncompleted quests from Act III didn't fail after proceeding to Act IV and cluttered the journal - fixed, they will now fail correctly;<br/></li><li> Removed an empty Ulfar’s comment in Act IV;<br/></li><li> say something You could receive the Three Phalanges quest even if you denied the aid of the Death Cult - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mechanics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dogmatic — Adherent "Absolution" ability now correctly counts the attacker as the character who applied Burning, instead of the player character;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few more cases with enemies becoming invincible with 1 wound remaining if the player had a certain set of values for Custom difficulty selected.<br/></li><li> The difficulty of the prone check in the fight with the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Forceful Genestealer</span></span> in Act 4 has been reduced by 25 to reduce the necessity of building specifically for this encounter;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a combination of talents (such as Heavy Gunner) that reduced AP costs didn’t interact correctly with Soldier’s Heroic Acts. Fixed, the costs will now calculate correctly;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Well-Maintained Chainsaw could disappear from the player's inventory. Don't worry, Lord Captain, your belongings are back and Jocasta Sauerback is already working with those responsible for this outrageous theft;<br/></li><li> Kibellah's mask will no longer disappear from her inventory under mysterious circumstances;<br/></li><li> Noble Sword damage bonus no longer applies for hits with other weapons and abilities;<br/></li><li> Temporary Wounds from Camaraderie Badge are now capped correctly at described values;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">UI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Expose Weakness ability description was inconsistent with its effect - fixed, the description has been updated to reflect the ability behaviour correctly;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you could close the party setup selection window without selecting the party members mandatory for the specific quest, which could cause some companion quests to lock;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Localisation</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of typos across the game;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with missing Japanese and Chinese localization for some strings in the DLC/mod manager window;<br/></li><li> Some text was missing in the character generation window for Japanese localization - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Visual</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added some rats to the Freight Line to make it even more atmospheric;<br/></li><li> We have added the representatives of the Adeptus Mechanicus to the train cutscene when exploring the Freight Line. No sacred mechanisms should remain without the watchful eye of the Omnissiah!<br/></li><li> Kibellah's model now reflects the described scars;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Audio</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed inconsistencies of Pasqal's voice lines with the dialogue text while talking with him on the Voidship Bridge.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
