<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius | 1.17.2 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/493840816042672275</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.17.1</i> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Balance</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Increased Kommando melee attacks from 1 to 2 (affects Stikkbomb).</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed game potentially not starting due to incorrect IGD initialization handling (this is likely to have happened in offline mode).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed Dialogus' Verse of Holy Piety not reducing The Emperor's Deliverance cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed missing Plague Spewer sounds.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed Armiger Helverin barks not showing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Armiger Autocannon now benefits from Scriptorum Ordinatus research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Blight Grenade now benefits from Daemonbone Casings research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Tank Commander research now unlocks the Additional Heavy Bolters research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Updated missing mentions of units in researches descriptions.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/489630/" width="850"></iframe>
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.0.3 Now Live for All Players</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/563646078927241788</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">​<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0be0bd2770edbec3191d6c5054934a9e515bbabe.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 7.0.3 is now out of Beta and has rolled out to all players. Thanks to everyone who checked out the Beta and shared their feedback and bug reports over the holidays and in these first weeks of January.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve added a number of additional fixes to the full release which are listed below, as well as in their respective categories in the full release notes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue introduced in the 7.0.3 Beta where the option to Subjugate a faction would sometimes not appear after defeating them.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with Elspeth’s Gunnery School missions and progression issues.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Norscan Marauding actions would incorrectly have a 5 turn cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Pleasurable Acts for N'kari and The Masque would incorrectly having a 10 turn cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed broken Encampment stance for Dragonship horde armies (Aislinn unaffected).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue so that the Nemesis Crown dilemma should no longer display a placeholder image.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where you could only select 1 spell after resetting skill points for Kairos Fateweaver.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Kairos couldn’t change spells in Fragments of Sorcery once confederated.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Multiplayer would crash if any player was playing as Kairos.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed performance issues when using Chinese Text language on high UI Scale (160% to 200%) on 4K Resolution.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">👉 Read the full Hotfix 7.0.3 Release Notes here 👈</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, should you run into any new issues after updating to Hotfix 7.0.3, be sure to raise them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve, Pingu &amp; Freeman // TW Community Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Survey! Help us Improve the Future DLCs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/496089445472143444</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain, your counsel is required.<br/><br/>We launch a new survey to learn what you think about certain aspects of the DLCs. Take a few minutes to tell us what you love, what matters most, and what you'd like to see in future DLCs.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Take the survey</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/8b76fe6ce3a106c026b9ed8107a285f9f1ae7ce2.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis expansions were added to the Digital OST</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/496089445472143288</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Praise the Emperor! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">The epic tracks from the Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis expansions were added to the Digital OST available in the Deluxe Pack! <br/><br/>If you already own the Deluxe Pack or any edition that includes it, your collection of music from the grim darkness of the far future will update automatically — no additional action required!<br/><br/>If you still don't have it, you may check it out here: https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/ </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plenty O' Fixes &amp; Improvements</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/657092583901627781</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">As we wind down 2025, we as a team have got to say that we're pretty proud of what we've done with <b>Speed Freeks</b> this year.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The game launched into 1.0, we added a wild new vehicle, a level editor with workshop, and a new mode for playing custom maps - along with a ton of bug fixes and improvements overall that brought the game up to to a higher level of quality. We're really happy with the current state of the game itself, and hope you gits are too. Just need more players now! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Thanks to all the gits who stuck with us and continue to do so, we've used your positive feedback, crazy gameplay videos and awesome custom maps as fuel to keep us going. You da best Orks around 💪</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4bbf5c7b41218bfeadb372e928347b716aa19df2.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3">DA UPDATE</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As for our final update of the year, it's got plenty of changes, so have a look below 👀 </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>VEHICLES ➤</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon</b>Burst Speshul weapon damage reduced by 15%, removed weapon rotation clamp</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deffkopta</b>Knockback from enemy weapons increased<br/>Brief timeout on accel/reverse inputs added when hit by a weapon with knockback</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Looted Wagon</b>Fixed issue with Grot Bomm yeeting players randomly</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with <b>Deffkilla Wartrike </b>and <b>Grot Mega Tank</b> not taking damage from the front. Whoops</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>TEAM BALANCE ⚖️</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added team balancing pass right before the 3,2,1 countdown, to account for any payers that have left during warm-up</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Made changes to player skill rating calculation to be more accurate. This should result in more balanced matches</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Maximum difference in player count between teams due to balancing reduced to 2</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>CREATION MODE </b>🛠️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Free Cam can now clip through geometry for easier movement</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mouse wheel now increases free cam flying speed</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added death volume assets for placing in maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added spotlight assets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Set rotation to snap to 5 degrees</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fix for AZERTY keyboard issues</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with host not showing up as a player in Game Browser player count</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stopped Creation Mode from sending host back to main menu if a network error occurs</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved thumbnails for some interactive assets</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MEK WORKSHOP </b>⚙️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added functionality for easily playing a map from anywhere in the Workshop. Now players can click on a map then go to Play ːsteamthumbsupː</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a search bar to easier find maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added sorting by author</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Name of the base level used now shown for custom maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with maps getting duplicated as well as other submission issues</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Workshop map reporting issue</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved handling of map IDs to avoid issues with overwriting or deleting maps</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>KUSTOM RALLY 🏁 </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added "GO TO NEXT MAP" vote in ESC menu</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">An automatic vote prompt will pop up every 5 minutes in case players are stuck</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">End of race timer increased to 60 seconds from 30</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with players not being able to respawn during end of race timer</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">End of match timer is now cancelled when the last player finishes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed start and end timers in solo matches</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MISC </b>🎲</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bots now have <b>a lot</b> more fun while waiting for the match to start</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reduced the amount of Stompa defense bots to 1, so most of them enter the fight</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Teammate bots now don't block players as much, having better avoidance code</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enabled Dakka Frenzy in Kill Konvoy mode</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MENU / UI 📜 </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There's now a warning on the HUD for all players when the host's PC or network performance is poor</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This will make it more clear as to why there are sync issues in the match, if the host PC is struggling</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Switch teams prompt now showing on the HUD again</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with painting vehicle accessories</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with painting Ork Lootas</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed "Distance Travelled" calculation for popup medal</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed eligibility text on Leaderboard screen to be more accurate</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Refactored player report/vote kick into a single screen in ESC menu called PLAYER LIST</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Optimized colour swatches UI in KUSTOMIZE screen, so now all colours have proper image associated</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you celebrate anything this time of year, we hope you have a great time with whoever's in yer mob (if it's a solo mob, too - dey still be krumpin' 'ard)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll be jumpin' in fer sum krumpin' over da holidays, so we'z see you'z on da battlefield n' racetracks. YA GITS!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bff6e97958bf7cec3025c8f54db27b7e22dbc4ee.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
