<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - The Feast of Grimnir</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060648</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>An absent-minded man of mysteries, Franz Lohner relies on his bulging journal to keep track of occurrences, intrigues and arguments around Taal's Horn Keep. Sometimes his notes are even useful, believe it or not. The Franz Lohner Chronicles are extracts from that journal.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - The Feast of Grimnir</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Well, it took them long enough but the Ubersreik Five are back in residence, after chasing after… something. They don’t always tell me what they’re up to these days, but I suppose that’s to be expected. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">I can’t say that they were all entirely thrilled to find Cousin Okri and his grumble of longbeards camped outside the keep. “Just what we needed: more dwarfs,” is how Kerillian put it, but I suppose she has her reasons, good and bad. Kruber and Sienna just joined in with the quaffing as if nothing was out of place, and while Saltzpyre clearly wasn’t happy to have Okri hanging about and giving him competition for his otherwise uncontested mantle of “disapproving presence”, it was actually Bardin of all people who seemed least at ease. At least to start with.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The air cleared a little when Okri laid out his intentions, in a voice as close to walking on gravel as makes no difference. No, the Ubersreik Five hadn’t yet earned the title of drengbarazi but he, Cousin Okri, was prepared to give them a fine opportunity to do so.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The dwarf hold of Karak Dal isn’t what you’d call a particularly thriving settlement, so when a particularly belligerent troll chieftain stomped his way into its upper levels, they quickly found out that they didn’t have enough steady dwarfen warriors to chop the brute into strips of easily-cured meat. Though the elders quickly petitioned aide from other holds, times are tough, and with the ratmen running hither and yon across this part of the world, no help has readily been forthcoming.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Enter the Ubersreik Five! Or, at least, that’s the plan. Okri’s claiming that tomorrow marks the first day of the Feast of Grimnir, and that such times are best marked by finding the biggest and nastiest troll you can and letting your axe do the talking. I don’t know how much of that’s actually true. Both Bardin and Hedda were giving Okri funny looks. Could be that he’s just spinning a tale  - you never can tell with dwarfs.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">However, Feast of Grimnir or not, some facts aren’t for questioning. The Ubersreik Five have to prove themselves to Okri’s discerning eye, and the dwarfs of Karak Dal need a bit of good old-fashioned derring-do and elbow grease to put an end to their troll troubles. Okri’s even wrangled Olesya’s crystal ball away from her so he and his grumble can keep an eye on what my bold heroes get up to down in the depths.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Win, lose or draw, it’s definitely going to be a fight to remember. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">And then, if I know my dwarfs, the drinking’s going to begin all over again.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gameplay Overview for Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/547870056202109075</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">The Omnissiah has blessed us with a glimpse of what to expect from Warhammer 40,000 Mechanicus II. Get a first glimpse of what’s to come in the sequel:</p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xd_nkrcwz0w?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Whether you’re a faithful servant of the Omnissiah or aligned with the ancient dynasties, wishlist today and prepare for the battles to come.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New In-Game Event: Light the fuse!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/668340807104725674</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Light the fuse!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Things are getting explosive on the streets of Tertium. Wyrmwood agents report an unusually high presence of explosive ordnance in the drop zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0188db98ed9b99cc84a6492b4a4410104c4abaf2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Explosive Uprising condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will <b>start on Thursday, August 21.</b> The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.</b> Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6b52012cfdbee0700f9e9978dc94faea8180c82c.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0f18727b59622f0cfa9f1f0949f4e0c355c2d20a.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060644</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>An absent-minded man of mysteries, Franz Lohner relies on his bulging journal to keep track of occurrences, intrigues and arguments around Taal's Horn Keep. Sometimes his notes are even useful, believe it or not. The Franz Lohner Chronicles are extracts from that journal.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">I can’t tell you what a relief it is to have this chronicle back in my hands. It’s been missing so long, I couldn’t even tell you when I’d lost it. Turned the keep up and down, I have, and took every scoundrel in the place to task into the bargain. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Sienna insisted Saltzpyre had nobbled it to ascertain as to whether or not I’d been scribbling down heretical musings. Heretical! Me! And this from the man who set us all looking for the Citadel of Eternity! Anyhow, when I’d had a good rummage through Saltzpyre’s chamber without success - some of the things I found there are better left uncommitted to the written page, I can tell you - Kerillian blamed Bardin, Bardin blamed Kruber, and Kruber just gave me that long, patient look I’ve been seeing a lot lately, and ushered me back downstairs with a stiff drink and a pat on the back. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Where, naturally, I found this wretched book in a pile of unsorted stock for the Emporium of Wonders. Where’d I left it in the first place, most likely. Still, I don’t feel entirely unvindicated. There’s been a lot of little notes left in the margins in at least three different styles of handwriting. It’s a damned liberty is what it is, but I suppose under the circumstances I’d be better off not making more of a fuss. They’re all halfway to thinking that I’m just a foolish old man already,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Anyway, I’ve more troubling things to think on.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve got guests. And not more of those “we took a wrong turn on the mountainside, and are powerfully averse to getting gored by beastmen” sort of guests. Dwarfs, in point of fact, and not any old dwarfs at that. This is no less a personage than one Cousin Okri, and a good grumble of longbeards. I’m pretty sure that a “grumble” is the collective noun for longbeards. If it isn’t, it should be, because so far as I can tell that’s all they do apart from fight endless bouts of practice combat and drink honest men out of their meagre stocks of ale.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">What brings Cousin Okri – who I have to say is shorter than I expected, which is a strange thing to say about a dwarf – to my door? It’s a matter of honour, because of course it is. Turns out, that the title of “drengbarazi” is a weightier one than I’d realised, and Okri’s not best pleased to hear that Bardin’s chosen to bestow it on the other four-fifths of the Ubersreik Five. He’s insisting that their right to bear it be proven in suitable fashion, and forthwith – which I don’t mind saying is awful hasty for a dwarf. In the meantime, Okri and his grumble have set up camp part way down the mountainside, and the nights have been full of drunken singing and the clash of gromril axes ever since. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">I tell you, I can’t wait for the Five to return so we can get this matter sorted out. I’m not getting any younger and I need my beauty sleep.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">And besides, I’m sure whatever Okri has in mind won’t trouble my merry band too much.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Almost </i>sure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.3 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/825966793744974705</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/144e2169665d770754abf1fca495ff21314d0a86.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re expecting to publish the full release notes for Patch 6.3 this Friday, followed by the Update itself next week, but if you can’t wait that long join us tomorrow on Rally Point where we’ll be playing and discussing Patch 6.3 live on stream. In Patch 6.3, look forward to updates and improvements to the Tomb Kings and Lizardmen races, audio updates including the death and rebirth of Alberic le Generic, new unusual locations, new free units, some streamlining on how to claim FLC for WH3 as well as a little extra blood splatter for everyone that likes to stick their noses right into the thick of it during battle.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This week, we have Senior QA Live Technician Liam Newman covering the changes and improvements coming to the Tomb Kings and Lizardmen, Principal Designer Mitch with the sports and weather on Unusual Locations and more, Sam, John and Chris for an update from the audio department and Game Director Todor Nikolov with a quick breakdown of WH3 FLC and how we’ve simplified how to get it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With that, I strongly urge you to click the link below to read the full blog. Enjoy!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">PATCH 6.3 DEV BLOG</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Pixel Daddy™   </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
