<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>​Hotfix 6.3.4 - Preview</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535305226</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/1f7217bf15ae6e0f0798c834c252d094aafe0c26.png"/><br/><br/>Hey Folks -<br/><br/>Following the fix for last week’s FLC issue, we promised to keep you updated on our direction of travel towards the next game update. This week we’ve continued our work on building out fixes and improvements that will form the foundation of what we’re internally calling 6.3.4. We start our testing on 6.3.4 later this evening, continuing through the weekend, and right across all of next week.<br/><br/>We’re not currently locked in on the release date for 6.3.4, but we have softly targeted its release on November 6th. We hope that you’ll understand that our testing phases for significant changes is often extensive and can cause us to make changes to release dates, or make further revisions to what we include in the update itself over the course of testing.<br/><br/>I’m happy to shed as much light as possible today on what our top focuses and expected fixes are based on where we stand today, but please expect some changes to the below between now and 6.3.4’s release. What I’m sharing today is pretty raw information, hot from the ovens, but all things that we’re happy to chat about.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What key issues are we looking to address in 6.3.4?</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Idle Armies on the Campaign Map <br/></li><li> Chaos Dwarf Recruitment Issues (Higher Tier Units) <br/></li><li> Golgfag Idle AI Campaign Behaviour </li></ul><br/>Before I get into breaking down our progress on these three key issues, it’s important that I highlight that we are in the earliest stages of testing. As you’ll read below, we have different levels of confidence on these three key issues, which may see us change up what’s included in 6.3.4. If we make changes, you’ll hear that from me as soon as we make that decision. If we do remove one of these key issues from 6.3.4, please know that it won’t mean that we’ve stopped working to solve the problem, only that we’ll continue to work on the problem and instead look to make it a part of a future update.<br/><br/>As things stand today, <b>Idle Armies</b> is something that we have a positive outlook on. The issue itself is presently believed to be a complication of several different issues, all conflicting with one another, and causing the behaviour that many of you have highlighted across our communities, where you see multiple armies standing around settlements and not taking any direct actions in your campaigns.<br/><br/>We’ve looked to address problems we’ve discovered over the ways in which Campaign AI is prioritizing Defensive Tasks too aggressively (a lovely bit of Friday irony for you there), a specific issue with Vampire Counts that often saw them get tied up in odd recruitment logic (similar to what we’ve recently tackled with Lizardmen and Tomb Kings), and instances of factions who sit idle whilst surrounded by allies (despite having valid enemy targets in more distant provinces). We’re also starting to investigate complaints of cowardly diplomacy AI, where if an AI faction isn’t presently at war with anyone, it languishes around settlements instead of engaging with all the tools in the toolbox. There’s no guarantee we’ll have a solution for this last one in time for 6.3.4, but we are looking at it and will keep you updated on our progress.<br/><br/>In spite of the complicated web of problems that contribute toward some of these remaining Campaign AI Issues, we presently believe that fixing the issues detailed above will significantly reduce (though likely not entirely remove) instances of Idle Armies from occurring in your campaigns. Testing over this weekend and through next week will start to paint us a better picture of how effective our changes are proving. Initial tests are showing a positive sign, but we are in a very early stage of that testing, and we’re not out of those woods just yet.<br/><br/><b>Chaos Dwarf recruitment</b> is showing a similar early sign of improvement. We’ve observed that they hadn’t been recruiting higher tier units on a consistent basis, and some of the changes that we’ve developed are giving us an early indicator that we’re starting to see some success in changing that. As with other Idle AI issues, there’s lots of testing to do here to give us a better idea of how successful we’ve been in this space, as well as a need for us to be diligent about checking that we haven’t introduced any new unintended behaviors, but from our initial limited testing, we’re progressing in a positive direction here.<br/><br/>Finally, <b>Golgfag</b> has had their Campaign AI reviewed, and has now started to show consistent interaction with campaigns. Of all of the 3 key issues listed here, this is one that we are most confident that we’re currently making a good improvement on, but still something that will require a lot more testing and plenty of careful study on Golgfags impact in a campaign.<br/><br/>As of today, he’s properly attacking and expanding his territory, though we’ve had a few early tests that raise concerns that he’s prone to enter a state of megabonk, and can often be found to act as quite a menace to anyone within reach. Making a change to Golgfag to get him active is a good first step, but we’re going to be doing some further balancing as part of this process to ensure he doesn’t get out of hand.<br/><br/>Before I move onto chat about other fixes and improvements that we’re also looking to make in 6.3.4, I’ll call out that right now our testing is largely focused around new campaigns, and a lot of the confidence we have today is borne from testing in this condition. We do have access to plenty of saves where these types of issues are occurring, but we currently find that the AI struggles to resolve itself away from its bad behaviors on existing campaigns where these types of problems are already present. Building out fixes that would allow for existing saves to convert into healthier states is likely something of a distant stretch goal for us, and we’re currently forecasting that to make the most of the improvements that we’re looking to make in 6.3.4, a new campaign start is likely to provide the best possible experience.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What else are we looking at for 6.3.4?</div><br/>There are a host of additional changes and fixes that we’ve been tracking in recent weeks, and whilst Campaign AI and related issues are a high priority for us, there are other things that will also enter testing next week and possibly arrive as part of this update.<br/><br/>Here’s just a handful of those fixes, but more are in testing and whilst minor in nature, these are changes we’re keen to make alongside 6.3.4’s Campaign AI focuses. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ironman mode now autosaves when a mission is issued which will protect progress in multistage missions and you may see more autosaving as a result. <br/></li><li> The 2nd level of the Word of Pain skill for lords now gives an increased cooldown, as does the 3rd level for the hero version. <br/></li><li> Occupying the Oak of Ages as Warriors of Chaos now provides the correct building. If you currently own the settlement as Warriors of Chaos, it will not automatically be updated so you will need to re occupy after losing it to an enemy. <br/></li><li> Sequence of the Hardened Scales now correctly applies unit mass to Kroxigors. <br/></li><li> Blades of the Blood Queen (Har Ganeth Executioners) now have the correct Melee Attack. <br/></li><li> Hideous Visage trait provides fear as well as terror. <br/></li><li> Oxyotl's "Inner Sanctum" buildings now give the correct benefits. <br/></li><li> The Big Name Gnoblarkicker correctly unlocks with Gnoblar Flingers in your army. <br/></li><li> Cave Painter follower can now be equipped by Golgfag Maneater, Camp Tyrants and Paymasters.</li></ul><br/>There’ll be further updates and amendments that we’ll be looking to make as we progress through our testing, so do expect further comments from myself and the Community Team as we regroup from the weekend, as well as a return to our usual schedule livestreaming next week over on our Twitch, and Total War Live YouTube next week.  <br/><br/>Thanks for reading – see you on the battlefields <br/><br/>Freeman // Head of Community <br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.5.0.295 is out!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/533239065676351918</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
In this hotfix, we're dealing with a few annoyances that popped up after the massive 1.5 update. <br/><br/>These are the changes:<br/><br/>- Malice portrait didn't display correctly for some players - fixed;<br/>- Fixed an issue where the game would sometimes crash to the main menu when switching locations;<br/>- Commissar's At All Costs! now works with all Inferno pistols;<br/>- Fixed missing chain textures on Thassera;<br/>- Fixed missing textures on some Servoskulls;]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 years of Tide!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/529861365954775433</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" yeazmdtfprs?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Acolytes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">On this very day ten years ago, we released Warhammer: End Times - Vermintide, the very first Tide game! Throughout these years we’ve seen both the games and the community grow, driven by endless passion from both our developers and especially you, our fans! For all the enemies slain, the times shared and the good times, we want to say thank you, and celebrate!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">To mark a full decade since the launch of our beloved Tide series, we're unveiling a special anniversary roadmap detailing the content that's waiting right around the corner for both Vermintide 2 and Darktide, <b>including the reveal date for Darktide’s next class.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/fa91eec45cd862077f23f578bcae00afccf67a4a.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>October 21: Darktide - “Stolen Rations” Special Event (Oct 21 - Nov 10, 2025)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Already live and causing mayhem, the Stolen Rations event introduces Darktide’s first community-versus-community challenge. Players will have to find stolen rations in missions and choose to destroy them or recover them to feed Tertium’s population. Community choices directly shape the event, with the leading decision setting new gameplay conditions each day!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>‍October 23: Vermintide - Geheimnisnacht (Oct 23 - Nov 2, 2025)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Geheimnisnacht is upon us, and the Skull of Blosphoros haunts these lands once more! From October 23 until November 2, you can find foul Chaos worshippers performing vile rituals to awaken this dark master, and it is up to you to stop them! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>November 11: Darktide - New Class Reveal</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We will reveal the next playable class for Darktide. More details and developer insights will follow in the days after the reveal.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>November 20: Vermintide - New map: Return to the Reik</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A brand new free level, Return to the Reik is a re-imagining of one of Vermintide 1’s most popular missions, River Reik! Our Heroes will return to these treacherous waters in search of a family heirloom, but things have only gotten worse in the seven years since then, and this search will take them on a voyage full of adventure, fending off ships of both Ratmen and Chaos alike! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>December 2: Darktide - Free Update &amp; Special Event (details to follow!)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A major free update arrives December 2, 2025, with a new Operation mission set in the trenches of Atoma and a new time-limited special event. More features related to this update and the special event will be revealed in the coming weeks!  </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>December 9: Vermintide - Gifts of the Wolf Father</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, as with every year, the Gifts of the Wolf Father event will go live in December through January for Vermintide! Log in each day to claim a new gift, ranging from cosmetics, to brand new illusions, currency and more! End the year with a jolly celebration alongside us!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/e9df856fad5721ba547b0da8ef69758cf81f049e.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once again, a massive thank you to all of our players! We couldn’t have gotten this far without your passion and support, and we hope you’re looking forwards to everything that’s in store for you, and for our Tide games!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you in the Mourningstar, in Taal’s Horn Keep, or both!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– Fatshark</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 years of Tide with New Content and a New Class</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/547875764461111699</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" yeazmdtfprs?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Acolytes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">On this very day ten years ago, we released Warhammer: End Times - Vermintide, the very first Tide game! Throughout these years we’ve seen both the games and the community grow, driven by endless passion from both our developers and especially you, our fans! For all the enemies slain, the times shared and the good times, we want to say thank you, and celebrate!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To mark a full decade since the launch of our beloved Tide series, we're unveiling a special anniversary roadmap detailing the content that's waiting right around the corner for both Vermintide 2 and Darktide, <b>including the reveal date for Darktide’s next class.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fa91eec45cd862077f23f578bcae00afccf67a4a.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>October 21: Darktide - “Stolen Rations” Special Event (Oct 21 - Nov 10, 2025)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Already live and causing mayhem, the Stolen Rations event introduces Darktide’s first community-versus-community challenge. Players will have to find stolen rations in missions and choose to destroy them or recover them to feed Tertium’s population. Community choices directly shape the event, with the leading decision setting new gameplay conditions each day!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>‍October 23: Vermintide - Geheimnisnacht (Oct 23 - Nov 2, 2025)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Geheimnisnacht is upon us, and the Skull of Blosphoros haunts these lands once more! From October 23 until November 2, you can find foul Chaos worshippers performing vile rituals to awaken this dark master, and it is up to you to stop them!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>November 11: Darktide - New Class Reveal</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We will reveal the next playable class for Darktide. More details and developer insights will follow in the days after the reveal.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>November 20: Vermintide - New map: Return to the Reik</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A brand new free level, Return to the Reik is a re-imagining of one of Vermintide 1’s most popular missions, River Reik! Our Heroes will return to these treacherous waters in search of a family heirloom, but things have only gotten worse in the seven years since then, and this search will take them on a voyage full of adventure, fending off ships of both Ratmen and Chaos alike!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>December 2: Darktide - Free Update &amp; Special Event (details to follow!)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A major free update arrives December 2, 2025, with a new Operation mission set in the trenches of Atoma and a new time-limited special event. More features related to this update and the special event will be revealed in the coming weeks! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>December 9: Vermintide - Gifts of the Wolf Father</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, as with every year, the Gifts of the Wolf Father event will go live in December through January for Vermintide! Log in each day to claim a new gift, ranging from cosmetics, to brand new illusions, currency and more! End the year with a jolly celebration alongside us!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once again, a massive thank you to all of our players! We couldn’t have gotten this far without your passion and support, and we hope you’re looking forwards to everything that’s in store for you, and for our Tide games!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you in the Mourningstar, in Taal’s Horn Keep, or both!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– Fatshark</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFFKOPTA Takes To Da Skies!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/655961606822299882</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">FLYBOYZ! YOU'Z REDDY?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The wait is over... time to fly 🚁</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://youtu.be/csOxDI0YpZ0 <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/> </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Grab the latest <b>Speed Freeks</b> update and play to unlock the new <b>Deffkopta</b> vehicle.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">You'll need to travel 70 km in any vehicle to do so (don't worry, it doesn't take long - you can track progress in the <i>Challenges</i> menu)</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3720867577dc70f8d92cdb3f88e031c027cddfed.gif"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once you start flying around with the Deffkopta you'll notice that it controls a lot differently to any of the game's wheeled vehicles.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">"No zoggin' guff, ya scrap fer brainz"</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Well, the huge difference is that you can strafe from side to side, and you glide off of jumps/cliffs. You'll be rethinking the way you traverse the game's maps because of how different this vehicle is - in a great way.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This agile little fella also has a variety of weapons / abilities:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Kopta Rokkits</b> which are consistently fired out of the front of the vehicle</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Spinnin' Blades </b>which is a smashin' n' slicin' melee attack, but also a movement ability</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deff From Above</b> which is a single large bomb dropped from the bottom of the Kopta, causing decent damage and lifting enemies off the ground in a large radius</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Kopta Control </b>which lets you fly the Kopta closer to the ground for better chance at melee attacks, but also maneuvering under low objects like arches/tunnels</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/49f3bf37ac8ca75364def60737e741933ce9b711.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h2">DA MAPS 🗺️</div><p class="bb_paragraph">You'll be flyin' the Deffkopta through <b>two new Maps</b> for each of the main modes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Kill Konvoy - Scrap in Da Yard</b> is a giant scrapyard full of verticality that leads into a deep trench.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c314b0a341603bb4c175d39b285bf698ce625ad2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deff Rally - Deff Gorge </b>is a snowy version of the Kill Konvoy map Da Gorge, which has players racing through checkpoints - including a forest race full of corner drifting. If you like tight racing, this is the map for you.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1189f34d99948a7c654f3ec1a4322845ac0a8ab2.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0fa0dd919b90b8558aad90bfb0c15745b68527ef.png"/> </p><hr/><div class="bb_h2">WOT ELSE? 📝</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Balancing changes, bug fixes and more. Point yer peepers below...</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>VEHICLES ⚙️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>GENERAL</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Wartrike Boomsticks, Scrapjet wing missiles, and Trukk main turret all can aim up to 80 degrees so they can interact with Deffkopta more easily</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>BOOMDAKKA SNAZZWAGON</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mek Speshul <i>Burst</i> fire rate reduced to 0.9 (from 1), damage decreased to 2 (from 2.2)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The much requested nerf to the Snazzwagon's alt weapon has arrived!</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>DEFFKILLA WARTRIKE</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Speed reduced to 94.5 (from 99), now the same as the Shokkjump Dragsta</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The Wartrike's ludicrous bomb delivering ability has been toned down a bit.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>MEGATRAKK SCRAPJET</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Fixed Scrapjet missiles</b> frequently getting out of sync and dealing no damage</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Missile proximity fuse increased to 3 (from 2), impact radius increased to 13 (from 10)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Recoil Rokkit cooldown reduced to 6 (from 8)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rokkit Kannon damage increased to 30 (from 25)</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The Scrapjet's two secondary weapons have been made more effective, either dealing more damage or getting shorter cooldowns, and the missiles hit much more consistently now. We'll keep an eye on the changes for balancing purposes.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>SHOKKJUMP DRAGSTA</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Fixed Dragsta missiles</b> not firing in certain conditions</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MISCELLANEOUS </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We added some killer new 🎵 <b>MENU MUSIC </b>🎵 </p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph">Produced by our resident sound guys / musicians, <i>Cave Bat 💪</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">(We'll be adding this song to the Soundtrakk DLC as well)</p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a fix for preserving windowed screen mode</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Trukk now has Ork VO comments play sometimes when using abilities (as they do for other vehicles)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kustom Rally now supports up to 16 players instead of 8</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Many small optimizations to ingame assets</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Match Balancing ⚖️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You can now switch to the losing team at any time, as long as an empty slot is open</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This is an experiment to see how it not only affects balance, but also gives friends a chance to put themselves on the same team (a workaround for the lack of a <b>party system</b> right now)</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Player skill rating (used for balancing) now only considers the last 20 matches played</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This keeps the skill rating relatively recent and more relevant.</i></p></blockquote><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In order to update skill rating, a player must be part of a match with 6+ human players for at least 75% of the duration</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Skill rating now increases logarithmically, and there is a hard cap to make sure players don't falsely become god-tier rating and cause lopsided matches</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Teams are now less likely to be balanced with a different amount of players on each team</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug where opting out of leaderboard tracking also froze your skill rating</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">User Interface</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added modifiers to the game browser legend for clarity</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added "GAME ENDING" text to game browser entry when the progress bar is red and the match is not joinable</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a medal for finishing a capture point race in Deff Rally</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed Quick Match option in PLAY GAME, as Game Browser is the optimal way of joining matches</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">General UI texture optimization, improvement and clean up pass</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Maps</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some art tweaks to <i>Da Gorge</i> which are also present in the new <i>Deff Rally - Deff Gorge</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved performance on <i>Da Dust Up</i> and <i>Da Gorge</i> for lower end settings</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">🚨 STEAM DECK 🚨</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Currently there is a severe issue with Steam Deck performance that we couldn't figure out before this patch was going live, so we're still looking into it and think we have a lead on when the issue started, which helps us narrow down the cause</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Apologies for the Steam Deck issues, we're on it though and will hopefully have some good news soon 👍</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">LEVEL EDITOR 🛠️ (coming soon)</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Don't forget that <b>next month's update</b> will bring the much anticipated <b>Level Editor</b> and cloud <b>Workshop support</b> to share / download community creations.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You can see the buttons for these features are greyed out in the latest build, but they are already fully functional - just we're adding more functionality and polish before we release it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">So excited for this massive feature. Some <i>madlad</i> testers have already created a plethora of amazing maps and races, the latest more insane than the last.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d19e99c4275f99c91c1ec52d5384dd9356915e88.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">New <b>WAAAGH! PATH</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Also coming with the Level Editor update will be another <b>WAAAGH! Path</b>, complete with a plethora of new items to unlock including clan kits and valuable pit bosses.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Plus there's a new menu scene theme with Deffkoptas flying around. It's awesome.</p><hr/><div class="bb_h3">If you can guess who the next Pit Boss crew will be, we'll give you a <u>free Speed Freeks Soundtrakk DLC</u> 🎵🔥</div><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hint:</b> it's from an official Warhammer miniature pack.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>ALT WEAPONS </b>🔫</div><p class="bb_paragraph">And we'll be releasing more alternative versions of weapons for a bunch of vehicles, so you'll have even more ways to play.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, we hope you enjoy playing with the <b>Deffkopta </b>as much as we've been having fun making it!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We look forward to seeing you gits buzzin' around ingame.</p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">We've got an active and dedicated community already on the official <b>SF Discord</b>, so smash your way onto it if you fancy chatting and playing with other gits</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>JOIN DA DISCORD</b></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
