<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Developer’s Blog: Feast of Grimnir</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546744156294218077</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>A brand new limited time mission! The Ubersreik 5 must venture into a Dwarfen hold that’s been overrun with Bile Trolls and exterminate them.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve interviewed the main level designer for the new and upcoming Vermintide 2 event mission: <i>The Feast of Grimnir!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Mikael Sundvall, I’ve been at Fatshark since 2016. I joined production of Vermintide 2 when they had just started as a Level Designer. \[...] I’ve been a Level Designer and a Level Artist, right now I am both. I’ve been involved in all the levels except for Bögenhafen.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">What was the initial idea behind the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">From the beginning we knew we wanted to have a new recurring event sometime during the end of Summer to complement the rest of the yearly events. Mikael was asked to come up with ideas for a map that was unique and experimental enough to fit the celebratory nature of the event!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Mikael came up with about five different pitches, each more extravagant than the last. While this time we picked Feast of Grimnir, there’s always a chance to revisit those other ideas for later maps!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“That was kinda the pitch: adding ‘Dwarf’ and ‘Nurgle’ as a setting, and then focusing on Trolls as a gameplay theme.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The dwarf setting also gave Mikael the opportunity to use some assets he had already prototyped before, such as the giant statue setpieces used in the beginning of the level.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">What was the design process for the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, after the pitch was selected, a <b>Level Design Document</b> was crafted that outlined a rough map of the level, showing each area with reference images and concept art to give an idea of what each area is meant to look like. From there, a basic blockout version of the level was made. Since we already had a lot of dwarfen assets, those were used instead of the typical gray boxes we usually use for blockout maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once this foundation was established, Mikael, along with our other designers and artists, began to work on fleshing out and polishing the level through various iterations and tests, bringing it to life.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Beyond the troll theme, <b>one of the more unique aspects of this map is its non-linear nature!</b> It was also one of the biggest challenges. Unlike most maps, which start you from point A to B (with some maps also having different paths you can take to reach point B!), this level has a portion in the middle where there are multiple paths the players must take, each its own section of the map. <b>Players can choose the order in which they tackle each path, but eventually they must go through all of them to complete the level!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The idea for the whole setup is that \[...] there should be differences in each area depending on the order. So, for instance, if you take the cog first you gotta turn off all the lights, which will make the other areas dark. If you turn on the water, you’re going to raise the water level in the other areas \[…] I hope that players at least try to go through it in different order and realize that there are differences and find their own preferred path.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While that might not sound overly complicated, it actually proved quite challenging because of how the game’s Enemy Director functions, since it was designed with linear paths in mind. Near the end of Vermintide 2’s original production, Mikael had attempted and prototyped making entire levels out of this concept – an entire map split into different chunks that players could tackle in any order – but it had proven too incompatible with the Enemy Director’s linear nature. This map provided an opportunity to tackle it at a smaller scale; a section of the map being non-linear rather than the entire thing.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“This kind of level is kind of a test for it. If this is really cool we’ll see if maybe we want to try this in something bigger but… Anyhow, this was years ago that we were talking about this and now I finally got the chance to do this, to try it in a simpler setup.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In case you’re curious, the way we went about this is to make the AI director consider the entire multiple paths section (along with its central ‘hub’) to be one unified area. It’s only once you exit it through the elevator that the Director finally acknowledges the players moving to a different area!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“\[Originally] that was really the main thing, the end event. So it would be a section of traversal leading up to that area and that would be the main event in the level. But then \[...] we knew we wanted to have this ending where players could choose to <b>not</b> kill the trolls. \[...] It felt like that’s kind of anti-climactic for an ending, so that’s why we kind of said ‘we need <b>something more</b> at the end there’.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While escaping from a pack of trolls by the skin of your teeth is exciting enough, a troll <i>hunt</i> would not be complete without a proper slaying of trolls at the end, ey? But you’ll have to find out what that ‘something more’ at the end is yourselves. We’re really proud of how it turned out! There’s even some additional secrets to be found by those with a keen eye and a drive for exploration!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Bonus question: What’s your favorite part of the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I really like the statues. \[...] I mean the big, big statues. Even though it might be kind of simple from a gameplay perspective, it’s still like a cool moment I think.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>That’s all we have for today! We hope you have a blast playing Feast of Grimnir!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>~The Vermintide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - The Feast of Grimnir</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060648</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>An absent-minded man of mysteries, Franz Lohner relies on his bulging journal to keep track of occurrences, intrigues and arguments around Taal's Horn Keep. Sometimes his notes are even useful, believe it or not. The Franz Lohner Chronicles are extracts from that journal.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - The Feast of Grimnir</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Well, it took them long enough but the Ubersreik Five are back in residence, after chasing after… something. They don’t always tell me what they’re up to these days, but I suppose that’s to be expected. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">I can’t say that they were all entirely thrilled to find Cousin Okri and his grumble of longbeards camped outside the keep. “Just what we needed: more dwarfs,” is how Kerillian put it, but I suppose she has her reasons, good and bad. Kruber and Sienna just joined in with the quaffing as if nothing was out of place, and while Saltzpyre clearly wasn’t happy to have Okri hanging about and giving him competition for his otherwise uncontested mantle of “disapproving presence”, it was actually Bardin of all people who seemed least at ease. At least to start with.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The air cleared a little when Okri laid out his intentions, in a voice as close to walking on gravel as makes no difference. No, the Ubersreik Five hadn’t yet earned the title of drengbarazi but he, Cousin Okri, was prepared to give them a fine opportunity to do so.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The dwarf hold of Karak Dal isn’t what you’d call a particularly thriving settlement, so when a particularly belligerent troll chieftain stomped his way into its upper levels, they quickly found out that they didn’t have enough steady dwarfen warriors to chop the brute into strips of easily-cured meat. Though the elders quickly petitioned aide from other holds, times are tough, and with the ratmen running hither and yon across this part of the world, no help has readily been forthcoming.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Enter the Ubersreik Five! Or, at least, that’s the plan. Okri’s claiming that tomorrow marks the first day of the Feast of Grimnir, and that such times are best marked by finding the biggest and nastiest troll you can and letting your axe do the talking. I don’t know how much of that’s actually true. Both Bardin and Hedda were giving Okri funny looks. Could be that he’s just spinning a tale  - you never can tell with dwarfs.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">However, Feast of Grimnir or not, some facts aren’t for questioning. The Ubersreik Five have to prove themselves to Okri’s discerning eye, and the dwarfs of Karak Dal need a bit of good old-fashioned derring-do and elbow grease to put an end to their troll troubles. Okri’s even wrangled Olesya’s crystal ball away from her so he and his grumble can keep an eye on what my bold heroes get up to down in the depths.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Win, lose or draw, it’s definitely going to be a fight to remember. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">And then, if I know my dwarfs, the drinking’s going to begin all over again.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gameplay Overview for Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/547870056202109075</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">The Omnissiah has blessed us with a glimpse of what to expect from Warhammer 40,000 Mechanicus II. Get a first glimpse of what’s to come in the sequel:</p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xd_nkrcwz0w?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Whether you’re a faithful servant of the Omnissiah or aligned with the ancient dynasties, wishlist today and prepare for the battles to come.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New In-Game Event: Light the fuse!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/668340807104725674</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Light the fuse! </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Things are getting explosive on the streets of Tertium. Wyrmwood agents report an unusually high presence of explosive ordnance in the drop zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" espcw5-rezg?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0188db98ed9b99cc84a6492b4a4410104c4abaf2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Explosive Uprising condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will <b>start on Thursday, August 21.</b> The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.</b> Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6b52012cfdbee0700f9e9978dc94faea8180c82c.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0f18727b59622f0cfa9f1f0949f4e0c355c2d20a.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060644</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>An absent-minded man of mysteries, Franz Lohner relies on his bulging journal to keep track of occurrences, intrigues and arguments around Taal's Horn Keep. Sometimes his notes are even useful, believe it or not. The Franz Lohner Chronicles are extracts from that journal.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">I can’t tell you what a relief it is to have this chronicle back in my hands. It’s been missing so long, I couldn’t even tell you when I’d lost it. Turned the keep up and down, I have, and took every scoundrel in the place to task into the bargain. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Sienna insisted Saltzpyre had nobbled it to ascertain as to whether or not I’d been scribbling down heretical musings. Heretical! Me! And this from the man who set us all looking for the Citadel of Eternity! Anyhow, when I’d had a good rummage through Saltzpyre’s chamber without success - some of the things I found there are better left uncommitted to the written page, I can tell you - Kerillian blamed Bardin, Bardin blamed Kruber, and Kruber just gave me that long, patient look I’ve been seeing a lot lately, and ushered me back downstairs with a stiff drink and a pat on the back. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Where, naturally, I found this wretched book in a pile of unsorted stock for the Emporium of Wonders. Where’d I left it in the first place, most likely. Still, I don’t feel entirely unvindicated. There’s been a lot of little notes left in the margins in at least three different styles of handwriting. It’s a damned liberty is what it is, but I suppose under the circumstances I’d be better off not making more of a fuss. They’re all halfway to thinking that I’m just a foolish old man already,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Anyway, I’ve more troubling things to think on.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve got guests. And not more of those “we took a wrong turn on the mountainside, and are powerfully averse to getting gored by beastmen” sort of guests. Dwarfs, in point of fact, and not any old dwarfs at that. This is no less a personage than one Cousin Okri, and a good grumble of longbeards. I’m pretty sure that a “grumble” is the collective noun for longbeards. If it isn’t, it should be, because so far as I can tell that’s all they do apart from fight endless bouts of practice combat and drink honest men out of their meagre stocks of ale.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">What brings Cousin Okri – who I have to say is shorter than I expected, which is a strange thing to say about a dwarf – to my door? It’s a matter of honour, because of course it is. Turns out, that the title of “drengbarazi” is a weightier one than I’d realised, and Okri’s not best pleased to hear that Bardin’s chosen to bestow it on the other four-fifths of the Ubersreik Five. He’s insisting that their right to bear it be proven in suitable fashion, and forthwith – which I don’t mind saying is awful hasty for a dwarf. In the meantime, Okri and his grumble have set up camp part way down the mountainside, and the nights have been full of drunken singing and the clash of gromril axes ever since. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">I tell you, I can’t wait for the Five to return so we can get this matter sorted out. I’m not getting any younger and I need my beauty sleep.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">And besides, I’m sure whatever Okri has in mind won’t trouble my merry band too much.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Almost </i>sure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
