<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #75 (1.8.7)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520849092932272631</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #75 (1.8.7) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash which could happen during loadings, and particularly the transition between missions and the Mourningstar.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The related crash error message is: \[Script Error]: scripts/foundation/managers/package/package_manager.lua: 436 Trying to unload resource.</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a number of Access Violation crashes which could occur in different situations.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The related crash error message is: Access violation \[...]</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.3 now available as an opt-in Beta</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497205194887528873</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Patch 6.3 is now available as an opt-in Beta! As detailed yesterday, due to some unforeseen compatibility issues with some AMD hardware that can cause crashes, we've delayed the full release of the Patch until next week to get these resolved.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We wanted to still give you the chance to get your hands on the update today via this Beta, but please be aware that if you have an AMD GPU and choose to opt-in, that you may experience infrequent crashes, but rest assured that our teams are already on the case.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You can find full instructions on how to opt-in to the Beta further down this post.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the full details on what's included in Patch 6.3, check out our Dev Blog and Release Notes at the links below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">6.3 DEV BLOG</p><p class="bb_paragraph">RELEASE NOTES</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Apologies for the last minute shift in plans and the confusion around this release - we'll be back next week with further info on the full Patch launch.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks all!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The <i>Total War</i> Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">How to download the Beta branch</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ol><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Open your Steam client and go to your Library.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Right-click on <i>Total War: WARHAMMER III</i> and select 'Properties'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Navigate to the 'Betas' tab.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In the drop-down menu, select '<b>proving_grounds - Siege Beta</b>'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Steam will then download the necessary files and begin the patching process to install the Beta.</p></li></ol><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Steam will need to download around 2.1 GB of game data in order to install. Please be aware that the patching process can take some time depending on your hard drive speeds.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feast of Grimnir - Double XP &amp; Limited Time Event Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546744156294218079</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" gn3bvihpdh8?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes,</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Feast of Grimnir is upon us! Our brave Heroes must venture into the troll-infested hold of Karak Dal to prove themselves worthy of the title of ‘Drengbarazi’ by slaying every troll in sight!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/650ebf0ac99aa7590df5b142a707329dd8569538.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">The Feast of Grimnir</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Feast of Grimnir is a brand new, limited time, <b>annually recurring event</b>. This year’s event <b>begins today</b> and will last <b>until</b> <b>September 14</b>. For the duration of the event, the new event level, <i>‘The Feast of Grimnir’</i>, will be <b>accessible via the Weekly Event Game Mode</b>. Play the level to complete <b>event specific Okri’s quests </b>and unlock rewards!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/1bcad24f78e4df627eded2f7e731cf59a3509479.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">On top of that, <b>Lohner’s Emporium of Wonders</b>’s event section is open again, where you’ll be able to purchase a <b>brand new cosmetic frame</b>, alongside old event rewards from other recurring events!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/e29fc5d1b3ccea6ac9b5d373a0bde56236e90bdc.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, there will be <b>double XP</b> for all actions for the duration of the event!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you’d like to know more about The Feast of Grimnir, check out the most recent entries in Lohner’s Chronicles (Part 1 and Part 2), as well as this dev blog about the level!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Without further ado…</i></p><div class="bb_h1">Patch 6.7.0 patch notes</div><div class="bb_h3">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enabled the new <b>Feast of Grimnir event</b>.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Complete event-specific Okri’s Quests during the event to receive exclusive rewards.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Taal’s Horn Keep has received a <b>summery makeover</b> that some of you might be familiar with!</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heroes will gain <b>Double XP</b> for the duration of the event.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a new event level <i>‘The Feast of Grimnir’</i>, available for the duration of the Feast of Grimnir event.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bots now avoid damage circles in Enchanter’s Lair.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bots are now able to detect attacks from multiple enemies at once that don't directly target them.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bots are now less prone to dodge into enemies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Boss health bars no longer disappear until bosses are dead. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Teammates attacking bosses will now make the health bar appear for oneself as well (similar to pinging). </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Additional health bars will now appear if more than one boss is active at once.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Players joining mid-match can now spawn while other players are riding an elevator</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the Chaos Spawn contemplating existence if a grabbed player disconnects.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with an illusion for Kerillian’s Dual Swords where it had the wrong name (Now correctly named ‘Eternos-Ichor Dual Swords’)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue in Fort Bringing Bacon where the intro dialogue would not play if either Bardin or Saltzpyre were missing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed playback limits for Blightstormers and Lifeleeches where audio issues could occur if a huge amount of them were spawned at the same time.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with the barrel pit in the finale for Tower of Treachery. Throwing barrels into it should be far more consistent now.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug where the whole party immediately returns to the keep when the host presses "Return to The Keep" after losing a level, instead of the 45 second timer appearing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash when a source damaging a player is destroyed while dealing damage when the Baleful Empathy curse is active</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug where enemies hit while Aqshy's Incineration is active in a Bright Delving weave don't visually catch on fire while they are affected by the damage over time effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a typo in the Louen Leoncoeur skin for Grail knight.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Patch 6.7.1 Patch Notes</div><div class="bb_h3">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Feast of Grimnir - Slightly moved pickups before boss drop (to hopefully make bots pick them up)</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed various boons playing sound cues for the host when bots proc them during weekly chaos wastes runs.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash entering the chain end event in Garden of Morr.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash related to bot navigation.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Feast of Grimnir fixes:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Filled in small hole in ground just before boss drop</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added extra collision in space under stairs (and platform)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash when the Troll Chief stands back up from the knocked down state if Troll Chief is in a very tight spot where no barrel socket manages to fit.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fix for trolls not seeing players in the elevator.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a spot where players could get stuck in the Waterwheel section.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the music so that it’s properly synchronized between Host and Clients.</p></li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #74 (1.8.6)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520848458437886668</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #74 (1.8.6) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash caused by the new Buff HUD changes.</p></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that can occur when opening the Mission Terminal while network connection is lost.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that can occur when trying to dodge while carrying a luggable.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a sync issue that could end up blocking some players from joining the Mourningstar.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reduced memory usage in the Mourningstar which should lead to reduced crashes on PlayStation.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reworked how particle destruction works to avoid a set of fairly common crashes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reduced maximum packet size to improve network stability under poor network conditions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Solved a case in which the game could lose access to data services during a gameplay session.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic and Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Hangledge Rescue animation was playing too quickly.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Havoc Campaign - Mission Pool and Mutator Rotation</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Every third week during a Havoc Campaign, we are rotating the mission pool and mutator pool. One or two missions and mutators will swap out during this time. This rotation happened at the beginning of this week, August 25.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mission Pool</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Incoming</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Enclavum Baross</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Comms-Plex 154/2f</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Outgoing</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Archivum Sycorax</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Hab Dreyko</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mutators</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Incoming</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Cranial Corruption</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Outgoing</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The Blight Spreads</i></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Arbites Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff was teleported in the elevator with incorrect rotation.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff would sometimes move upward after colliding with walls instead of falling naturally due to gravity.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic and Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the Suppression Shield &amp; Shock Maul to block the view during the outro cutscene for assassination missions.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer’s Blog: Feast of Grimnir</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546744156294218077</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>A brand new limited time mission! The Ubersreik 5 must venture into a Dwarfen hold that’s been overrun with Bile Trolls and exterminate them.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve interviewed the main level designer for the new and upcoming Vermintide 2 event mission: <i>The Feast of Grimnir!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Mikael Sundvall, I’ve been at Fatshark since 2016. I joined production of Vermintide 2 when they had just started as a Level Designer. \[...] I’ve been a Level Designer and a Level Artist, right now I am both. I’ve been involved in all the levels except for Bögenhafen.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">What was the initial idea behind the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">From the beginning we knew we wanted to have a new recurring event sometime during the end of Summer to complement the rest of the yearly events. Mikael was asked to come up with ideas for a map that was unique and experimental enough to fit the celebratory nature of the event!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Mikael came up with about five different pitches, each more extravagant than the last. While this time we picked Feast of Grimnir, there’s always a chance to revisit those other ideas for later maps!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“That was kinda the pitch: adding ‘Dwarf’ and ‘Nurgle’ as a setting, and then focusing on Trolls as a gameplay theme.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The dwarf setting also gave Mikael the opportunity to use some assets he had already prototyped before, such as the giant statue setpieces used in the beginning of the level.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">What was the design process for the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, after the pitch was selected, a <b>Level Design Document</b> was crafted that outlined a rough map of the level, showing each area with reference images and concept art to give an idea of what each area is meant to look like. From there, a basic blockout version of the level was made. Since we already had a lot of dwarfen assets, those were used instead of the typical gray boxes we usually use for blockout maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once this foundation was established, Mikael, along with our other designers and artists, began to work on fleshing out and polishing the level through various iterations and tests, bringing it to life.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Beyond the troll theme, <b>one of the more unique aspects of this map is its non-linear nature!</b> It was also one of the biggest challenges. Unlike most maps, which start you from point A to B (with some maps also having different paths you can take to reach point B!), this level has a portion in the middle where there are multiple paths the players must take, each its own section of the map. <b>Players can choose the order in which they tackle each path, but eventually they must go through all of them to complete the level!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The idea for the whole setup is that \[...] there should be differences in each area depending on the order. So, for instance, if you take the cog first you gotta turn off all the lights, which will make the other areas dark. If you turn on the water, you’re going to raise the water level in the other areas \[…] I hope that players at least try to go through it in different order and realize that there are differences and find their own preferred path.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While that might not sound overly complicated, it actually proved quite challenging because of how the game’s Enemy Director functions, since it was designed with linear paths in mind. Near the end of Vermintide 2’s original production, Mikael had attempted and prototyped making entire levels out of this concept – an entire map split into different chunks that players could tackle in any order – but it had proven too incompatible with the Enemy Director’s linear nature. This map provided an opportunity to tackle it at a smaller scale; a section of the map being non-linear rather than the entire thing.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“This kind of level is kind of a test for it. If this is really cool we’ll see if maybe we want to try this in something bigger but… Anyhow, this was years ago that we were talking about this and now I finally got the chance to do this, to try it in a simpler setup.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In case you’re curious, the way we went about this is to make the AI director consider the entire multiple paths section (along with its central ‘hub’) to be one unified area. It’s only once you exit it through the elevator that the Director finally acknowledges the players moving to a different area!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“\[Originally] that was really the main thing, the end event. So it would be a section of traversal leading up to that area and that would be the main event in the level. But then \[...] we knew we wanted to have this ending where players could choose to <b>not</b> kill the trolls. \[...] It felt like that’s kind of anti-climactic for an ending, so that’s why we kind of said ‘we need <b>something more</b> at the end there’.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While escaping from a pack of trolls by the skin of your teeth is exciting enough, a troll <i>hunt</i> would not be complete without a proper slaying of trolls at the end, ey? But you’ll have to find out what that ‘something more’ at the end is yourselves. We’re really proud of how it turned out! There’s even some additional secrets to be found by those with a keen eye and a drive for exploration!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Bonus question: What’s your favorite part of the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I really like the statues. \[...] I mean the big, big statues. Even though it might be kind of simple from a gameplay perspective, it’s still like a cool moment I think.” ~ Mikael</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>That’s all we have for today! We hope you have a blast playing Feast of Grimnir!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>~The Vermintide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
