<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Ultima Founding DLC: join us for Slitherine Next</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/521951078763201278</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Get ready to be the first to discover the new DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Gladius, Ultima Founding. <br/><br/>Join us for Slitherine Next event <b>December 10th at 6:00 PM CET</b>.<br/><br/>Make sure to save the date:<br/>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bNMPY51noiw?si=FTa3mq0ivM2Uso6K<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction - Meet Gorbad Ironclaw</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4476109467940814900</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/92d39fdf82c96b48b8db81f6cf959c1b5884b2ca.png"/><br/><br/>​Greetings, Total War community!<br/><br/>This week da boyz are back in town as we discuss warrin’, Warbosses and WAAAGHS! - please welcome Omens of Destruction’s final Legendary Lord, Gorbad Ironclaw. Packing a terrifying mix of strength and intelligence (for an orc), he’s an Emperor slaying Warboss who burned Solland to the ground and is back to show the rest of the WARHAMMER world how to get ‘invasions done propa’.<br/><br/>As always, if you happen to have missed our previous blogs about Skulltaker, Golgfag or Arbaal, then just click on their respective names to check them out now!<br/><br/>We'll be back tomorrow with Gorbad's gameplay showcase which premieres at 3PM GMT, so remember to check back then to feast yer eyez on 'iz video!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HMrBhXDjamE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Until then, let's dive in to Gorbad's introduction...<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 GORBAD IRONCLAW 👈</div><br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forsaken Temple is out now! Patch 6.1.0</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546720876705350491</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GSRosPZqHhU?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><br/>Today we bring you a brand new mission: The Forsaken Temple! This FREE mission is the first of three maps in the brand new ‘Verminous Dreams’ campaign.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3283440/Warhammer_Vermintide_2__Verminous_Dreams/<br/><br/>Tipped off by an otherworldly visit, Lohner’s investigations have led to the discovery of Skaven around the ruins of an ancient elven temple, possibly one that was rumored to not even exist. What could the Pactsworn be looking for in these mythical ruins?<br/><br/>Better stop them regardless, Heroes! Can’t be anything good.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Gifts of the Wolf Father</div>And of course, this December will also mark the return of the Gifts of the Wolf Father! He’s got an exciting bag of goodies to share with you all this year!<br/><br/>How it works: <b>Starting today</b> and <b>until January 3rd,</b> every day you jump on Vermintide 2, you can access Lohner’s Emporium to claim that day’s Gift*. There’ll be cosmetics, illusions, coins, frames, and all sorts of goodies!<br/><br/>There might even be a very, very special hat that makes its long-awaited, fishy return!<br/><br/>Today’s gift, you might ask?<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/8fd537bc296a295054fda902804c238cef7471bc.png"/><br/><i>*: You may also claim the gifts from two days prior, as a small buffer to make things a bit more flexible.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Upcoming playable monster: Rat Ogre - December 17</div>We also wanted to give you guys a taste of what’s coming next for Versus! <br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/2dc0740c-942f-4cda-bbc0-b6b44aa8e773/Rat_Ogre_169.png?format=1000w"/><br/><b>Coming December 17th,</b> the Pactsworn are going to get another fun toy to torment the Hero team: The Rat Ogre will be a playable monster before the end of the year!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Premium Cosmetics: The Mythic Masquerade</div>Can’t just let you guys go on a brand new Adventure without some brand new swagger to show off, ey?<br/><br/>This bundle of Premium Cosmetics, purchasable directly from Lohner’s Emporium, has a fantastic set of new cosmetics inspired by iconic characters from Warhammer Fantasy!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Gotrek Gurnisson</div>Our dear Bardin gets to look even more fierce than usual with this intimidating outfit fashioned after the most deadly of all slayers: <b>Gotrek Gurnisson</b>. Available only to Bardin’s <b>Slayer career.</b><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/83511b6b-b8a2-43b7-92c1-b8aebf9fe476/Gotrek+Gurnisson.png?format=2500w"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Felix Jaeger</div>Of course, we can’t have Gotrek without Felix! Kruber gets to accompany his best buddy in with this dashing outfit inspired by Gotrek’s faithful companion, <b>Felix Jaeger</b>! Available only to Markus’ <b>Mercenary career.</b><br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/0befe44e-522b-4452-8d4d-159dbee2f253/Felix+Jaeger.png?format=2500w"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Count Boris Todbringer</div>Proving that he ALSO can sport a magnificent beard, the imposing <b>Count Boris Todbringer</b>-inspired hero skin and hat are equipable by Saltzpyre’s <b>Bounty Hunter career.</b><br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/6b1e65d6-b88f-4e6b-9c75-d7158a9f353e/Count+Boris+Todbringer.png?format=2500w"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Naieth the Prophetess</div>Delving into mysticism, Kerillian has access to an outfit inspired by <b>Naieth the Prophetess</b>, equipable on <b>all of Kerillian’s careers.</b><br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/cebdaf07-9621-4c80-aee2-a6d8293ec87b/Naieth+the+Prophetess.png?format=1000w"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Isabella Von Carstein</div>With a sudden propensity for walking around with a cup of wine (at least, we think it’s wine!), Sienna gets a new regal look with this armour inspired by <b>Isabella Von Carstein</b>. This hero skin and hat are equipable on her Pyrom<b>ancer and Necromancer careers.</b><br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/202758a3-02cb-43ba-b386-b6632db36230/Isabella+von+Carstein.png?format=1000w"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Developer stream: December 9th, 17:00 CET!</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/ea5c35021def20ff6650f4c930b80b2d8a4cebb1.png"/><br/><br/>Don’t forget to tune into our <b>twitch stream</b> today, at 17:00 CET!  Developers Anton, Theodor and Tom are going to go over the new DLC, play the new map, and talk a little bit about what’s next for Vermintide, including both Versus and PvE.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Versus Spotlight: Week 4 extension</div>Perhaps we overshot a bit when adjusting the kill counter target! We were so impressed with your performance in the first weeks that we got a bit overambitious for the new one.<br/><br/>In the spirit of giving during this Gifts of the Wolf father, we’re extending the period to reach the kill counter from Sunday to Wednesday. Make sure to reach the target of 250.000 Heroes killed in Versus before the next spotlight starts, or you really might miss out on the rewards!<br/><br/><i>Without further ado…</i><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch 6.1.0 patch notes</div> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks		</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Added the new free map: The Forsaken Temple.</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	This map is the first mission in the new Verminous Dreams campaign. More maps coming later!							<br/> </li><li>	Added Okri's Challenges &amp; rewards related to The Forsaken Temple</li></ul></li><li>	Added a new set of Premium Cosmetics: the Mythical Masquerade.								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	The <b>Gotrek Gurnisson</b> hero skin and hat, equippable by Bardin's Slayer career.							<br/> </li><li>	The <b>Naieth the Prophetess</b> hero skin and hat, equippable by all of Kerillian's careers.							<br/> </li><li>	The <b>Felix Jaeger</b> hero skin and hat, equippable by Kruber's Mercenary career.							<br/> </li><li>	The <b>Isabella Von Carstein</b> hero skin and hat, equippable by Sienna's Pyromancer and Necromancer careers.							<br/> </li><li>	The <b>Count Boris Todbringer</b> hero skin and hat, equippable by Saltzpyre's Bounty Hunter career.</li></ul></li><li>	Minimum and maximum power level for items in chests and crafting increase by one for every level above 30 (added across all characters), before limiting it to its original max value.								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Increasing the minimum means that at a certain level, all items are guaranteed to be max power.							<br/> </li><li>	Increasing the maximum and then reducing it to the cap means that you are more likely to roll a maximum power item as you increase levels, even before your minimum power gets high enough to be equal to the cap.</li></ul></li><li>	Enabled the Gifts of the Wolf Father advent calendar! Log in every day and check the calendar to unlock gifts!							<br/> </li><li>	Purchasing a DLC while in the keep now requires a game restart.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes		</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed an UI issue where Shillings and Helmgart Sellsword Marks would overlap with the store interface when looking for a match.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue causing Saltzpyre's animation to not take a cool step forward when shooting the rapier's pistol. Now he does his fancy move again!								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Bardin could sometimes respond with a Kerillian voice line when Victor gets knocked down too many times</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birthday report from Abelard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/509566179781640769</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>Today is a special day for us. Exactly one year ago, we embarked on the perilous journey across the Koronus Expanse. On this occasion, allow your faithful Seneschal to recall the heroic deeds you have accomplished this year!<br/><br/>Happy Birthday, Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader! <br/><br/>Let us know in the comments how many of our memes you spotted in the video!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/L9Qm6RBj6G0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Protocols - Dark Communion Mission - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/512943879502168737</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e9954f52ba71e57c1623ed6e9233403b36f05c9e.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>For Grim Protocols, we are releasing a new mission known as Dark Communion. To celebrate its release, we interviewed some of the devs and Fatshark team members who helped bring it to life. <br/><br/>We’re going to talk a bit about the narrative that inspired it, the level design process, the art and the visual effects. As always, we want to give you an overview of the process of creating the mission, but we still want to leave some things unsaid for players to discover for themselves when they boot up the map for the first time. <br/><br/>Let’s dive back into the carnival.<br/><br/>P.S. We waited to share this dev blog until a few days after release so everyone could have a chance to try it out without any spoilers.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Level Design</div><br/>With Dark Communion we wanted to forward the narrative of the Moebian 6th activities in The Carnival, as well as their relationship with the Cult of Admonition. This level sends players deeper into the heart of the Carnival district, following reports of sinister, ritual activity and a growing presence of heretic cultists. You’re being sent in to investigate these reports, but as always, things can and will escalate, so keep your eyes peeled and your weapons ready.<br/><br/>While building the previously seen missions set in the Carnival district, we had already planned to revisit it when the time was right. As such, players are likely to have already noticed, for example, the Cathedrum of Messelina Vengeant, seen in the background near the beginning of Warren 6-19 - now you will get to see it up close, and purge the heretics on its steps.<br/><br/>The other parts of the mission follow our usual modus operandi of interconnectivity. We wanted to revisit certain parts with a new coat of paint, and introduce new combat spaces that are different, while staying true to the DNA of the already established architecture.<br/><br/>As always, Jesper Kyd also created a masterpiece of a track for this mission. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bringing it Back to the Carnival</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Is this a continuation of the Carnival maps?</div><br/>Absolutely, but not only that. This level sees the culmination of the threads that began in the Carnival and continued through last year’s Orthus Offensive. We now know that Wolfer and the Traitorous 6th have made the Carnival a base of operations for their foul, tainted stimm production. While the warband continues to stymie their progress, their shipments are still getting through, as evidenced by that unfortunate business with the Moebian 21st, poor souls. Killing Rodin Karnak was a blow to their plans, but we already know that Rinda is still at large. Somehow, they brought her back from the brink of death. She’s calling herself the Herald of Admonition now. This mission promises to shed more light on what is driving the Traitorous 6th and their tainted stimms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Will future missions continue the story that’s being played out in Dark Communion?</div>Without giving away the mission ending, there are definitely new leads to follow after the conclusion of Dark Communion. Though, what those are, you’ll have to find out alongside the warband. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Who are the Cultists?</div>Originally assumed to be rabble-rousers and disorganised, disenfranchised gangs of hive citizens, we discover in Dark Communion that this is not the case and something much more sinister lies behind these yellow-clothed maniacs.<br/><br/>Since the mission is to ruin the ritual, does that “close” Rodin’s story? What would have happened if the ritual had worked?<br/><br/>When dealing with the fell powers of Chaos, it is unwise to write off any victory as final. The warband seems to have dealt with the threat for now, but who knows what effect those foul energies could have on Tertium.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Does this mission herald the start of a new narrative arc? Gloriana felt self-contained narratively, but Dark Communion raises a lot of questions.</div>To us, Dark Communion is a continuation of several of the previous story arcs in the game, it harkens back to the story we started to tell with the release of the Traitors Curse update but also starts to show us that there is more to the cult of Admonition than the warband has previously understood. We’ve got loads of plans for future storylines.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Art Design</div>For Art Design, we reined in Environment Artist Jonatan W. to give his thoughts on working on Dark Communion. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6e760b62f500cf31f1a3a735f643237e14aae017.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What was it like designing the art for this mission? </div>Most of my work was on the setpieces for the end event, but designing that was really fun. There was already a rough blockout for the event in the level that had Stimm tanks from one of our older levels with cables running up to a chaos star that was hanging over the altar. That gave me a good idea of what to make. <br/><br/>After clarifying with the level designers what the objectives were and how you would interact with the event, the actual work on designing and creating the units began.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What kind of feeling were you trying to capture with the end event?</div>Since the event is set inside of a cathedral, I thought it might be cool to make something that resembled church organs in its silhouette. I thought it would frame the altar and Rodin in a nice way when you enter. <br/><br/>I came up with the design of the two large vat tanks that would pump out fluids to Rodin from a central dispenser and started blocking it out. For some reason, I got the image of a horror monster being brought to life and retro-tesla coils stuck in my mind and thought that designing something like that would be neat, and fit into the whole vibe of trying to resurrect Rodin.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Were there any challenges?</div>Yes there were some technical and performance limitations to consider. Making destructible units always has some inherent challenges, not only from a technical standpoint but also from an art perspective! Like making nice transitions in destroyed states and getting VFX and sound in to sell it properly.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Visual Effects</div>Hi everyone, I’m Felicia and I work with visual effects (VFX) for Darktide. When I got the task to work on the new mission - Dark Communion, I knew that this was right up my alley. Scary and spooky Warhammer 40k with cultists and a ritual and a lot of new effects? Sign me up! <br/><br/>After the level designers had done the blockout for the level I knew that it was gonna be a cathedral that you could see from the start of the mission and the direction I got was that you were supposed to see that something scary and big was happening over there. I usually try to look at real life videos for visual effects (like snow, explosions, steam, rain etc.) but how does it work when it comes to more illusion-like effects and references that I can’t find in the real world? Then you have to imagine what it will look like and mash things together. Like what indicates a spooky atmosphere above a cathedral? I knew it had to be big. I thought of some kind of thunderstorm that was just above the cathedral and experimenting with different behaviors and it ended up with a spiral of clouds to make it more unique than just a thunderstorm. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7bf3e084f43947d939e34bf2123c180a4c6170eb.jpg"/><br/><br/>After the clouds above the cathedral, then most of my work came in the end event inside the cathedral where the ritual was going on. <br/><br/>The second thing I started to work on was the shields that are a big part of the end event and the gameplay. For these I got concept art so that I knew kind of how it would look. So I knew that it would be green and look a little bit like northern lights in its behavior. It’s a mesh with a material on it so it’s not any particles except when the shield goes down when smoke is pushing the player back as the shield goes down.  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fe5ec1bd24a5c7fc5b197cd1570b574e08bbb6b4.jpg"/><br/><br/>We also have the cultists that are keeping the shields up to protect the ritual. When it comes to these effects I just knew that I wanted it to be kind of rough but still have subtle things that you wouldn’t notice at first but it does a lot for the feeling. Like adding a distortion when the cultists effects are hitting a shield so it kind of wobbles on the shield as an impact from the cultists.   <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3914c263d6b1d0048d919a0eaafb923168f3f70f.jpg"/><br/><br/>When you have destroyed all the shields you get to the altar where you will destroy tanks, resulting in a big energy explosion. It was gonna be a build up over some time, so I did 4 different stages and I was thinking of some kind of implode explosion with a lot of energy.  So at first it would start off with a small indication that the energy is getting bigger and bigger in the energy source (the corpse) until it finally reaches maximum and then explodes. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0cd72d700a28fdcc8e8da0da46ab711169ac532d.jpg"/><br/><br/>And the last thing that happens is Rodin’s soul leaves his body and flies out of the cathedral windows. How does a soul look/feel like leaving the body? That was the question I asked myself and I thought of some smoke that is spawning from the body and flies in different directions so you can’t mistake it as smoke from an explosion, to make them stand out so you as a player understand that it’s something more than just smoke. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/befa042a77132029ca45e7223c6122e02999c4bb.jpg"/><br/><br/>Hope you liked to step into my visual effects mind and ideas that became the effects for Dark Communion, this was a really fun mission to work on and I hope you’ll enjoy it as much as I do! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><br/>That’s our sneak peek for Dark Communion! We hope everyone enjoys jumping into the Carnival again, and we look forward to seeing what everyone thinks. We’ll be reading the comments. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
