<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.1.11 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503940938959159390</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>We are deploying an update to resolve some of the frequently reported desync cases in co-op. <br/><br/>While this update should improve the situation, it does not yet cover all known cases. We are still in the process of investigating and fixing more of them, and will deploy another update as soon as possible.<br/><br/>It will help if you report any desyncs you encounter via the bug report tool! Can be done by pressing ALT+B or pushing both sticks on a controller at once.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Desperate Measures;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Cassia’s Lidless Stare;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Grand Strategist’s stratagems;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by hovering the cursor over Apexalium Stimulant in combat;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by opening the inventory in combat;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by quickly clicking through the items in the inventory;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by certain sequences of attacks and abilities;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abelard, announce that over 1 million Warrants of Trade have been claimed!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/764023459821912840</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Abelard, announce that over 1 million Lord Captains have claimed their Warrant of Trade and ventured boldly into the Koronus Expanse! <br/><br/>To be the paragon of Humanity, unbroken by adversity, to walk bravely first into darkness, to unite and reclaim what was lost, to triumph over nightmares untold, to hold boldly the reins of fate, to walk steadily the road of thorns, through pain to greatness.<br/><br/>This was no easy task, but you have succeeded, Lord Captains.<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/60db023bbb78af0550692d663b79668c31b9164e.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devious Delvings: FREE New Map coming January 23rd</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/738127762059952828</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>We hope you enjoyed the Holidays and are itching for more Vermintide! In early December last year, we released a brand new map <i>‘The Forsaken Temple’</i>, and it’s already time for another.<br/><br/><i>‘Devious Delvings’</i> is the second installment of the Verminous Dreams campaign and picks up where the last mission left off. Our Heroes have successfully infiltrated the ruined Elven temple that Skaven has taken over; it’s now time to investigate what they’re up to.<br/><br/><b>This new map will arrive on January 23rd, FREE for all owners of Vermintide 2!</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live NOW - The Waking Giants!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/631167087315779613</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey there,</div> We hope everyone on Tertium is having a good year so far. <br/><br/>We’re back for the year, and starting off with a new event: The Waking Giants. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e64c2be48d23d12e7e0d936a5e69c32f029491b5.png"/><br/><br/><b>How would we describe this event?</b><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><i>The Traitorous 6th seem to have conscripted Ogryns in vast numbers, literally swelling their ranks to enormous proportions. Defeat this bulwark of corrupt flesh and take back the streets of Tertium.</i></blockquote><b>To make progress in the event, complete any missions with the Brute Conscripts condition.</b><br/><br/>This event will start today, Thursday, January 16, 2025. Right now, actually! <b>This event is exclusive to Auric.</b><br/><br/>The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the final tier of the event will receive a new Frame: the Killiest Frame. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1c3dd599a47a63d79b1df5cd9d676b0f723146bf.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ae70dad1d3820f6c14f3113807951e57c9f1c08e.jpg"/><br/><br/>We are working on the next Hotfix which will be released at the end of January. Next up in January, we’ll be sharing the dev blog with Jesper Kyd. We interviewed him all about his process of creating music for Darktide. <br/><br/>Let’s have a year filled with eviscerating heretics For The Emperor.<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/538842566974505652</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/4467df634c9fb3482140b6d254f0bb5925a2a84f.png"/><br/><br/>Hey everyone,<br/><br/>We hope you all had a fantastic festive break and New Year celebration!<br/><br/>At the end of 2024 we rolled out Hotfix 6.0.3 as an opt-in Beta for you to try over the holiday period. We're pleased to announce that we've now rolled this hotfix out to all players, including one additional fix:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved a script error that prevented events from triggering after completing missions as Gorbad Ironclaw.</li></ul>Our original plan was to release this in late January but we wanted to get these changes out to you all as quickly as possible so you could all enjoy them. We're now working on Hotfix 6.0.4 which is currently aiming for the end of January, but if this changes we'll be sure to let you know!<br/><br/>For those who didn't opt-in to the Beta, here's a full list of changes in 6.0.3:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.0.3 Release Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">SKULLTAKER UPDATES AND FIXES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Adjusted Blood Hosts and Disciple forces so they no longer benefit from the Daemonic Reforging chance.<br/></li><li> Adjusted the effects of the Cloak of Skulls so that they now only apply when Skulltaker himself defeats a Lord.<br/></li><li> When playing as Skulltaker, the Legendary Lord 2x bonus for Champion’s Essence will now only be applied once. After defeating a Champion in battle, the bonus will no longer stack.<br/></li><li> Blood Hosts now increase the cost of the ‘Blood for the Blood God’ occupation option while they are on the map. This means that the more active Blood Hosts there are, the more costly it becomes to create new Blood Hosts. This change addresses the over-reliance of Khorne factions on excessive Blood Host forces.<br/></li><li> Reduced the XP gain bonus from the Cloak of Skulls on the ‘Dubois the Prescient’ skull, from 25/50 to 20/40.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Bloodspeakers lacked mounts when playing as Valkia.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Heralds of Khorne and Bloodreapers on Blood Throne mounts were missing Siege Attacker.<br/></li><li> Fixed the 2D porthole for The Slaughtergard (Chosen of Khorne - Halberds) using the wrong image.<br/></li><li> Fixed a text inconsistency in the description of the Daemons Reforged effect for the Skulltakers faction.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved a rare crash that could occur during VFX rendering.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when loading saved Savage Orc Great Shaman lords.<br/></li><li> Fixed a potential crash when loading a battle in certain cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when loading the Black Orc Big Boss character.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when teleporting to the Great Drill of Hashut quest battle.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Erd Mentality Rebalance:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Melee Defence: 40 &gt; 20<br/></li><li> Ward Save: 40 &gt; 20<br/></li><li> Number of Squig Herds in range for maximum value: 10 &gt; 5</li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue where Da Acid Burpa (Colossal Squig RoR) was not counting towards the unit requirements for the ‘Splode Da Big One Tactik’ in Da Plan.<br/></li><li> Ogre Camps now take only 3 turns to be redeployed, instead of 5.<br/></li><li> Removed Destroy ‘Kraka Drak’ from Throgg and Astragoth’s victory conditions and replaced it with Malakai’s faction<br/></li><li> Nasty Skulkers, Rogue Idol, River Trolls, and Snotling Pump Wagon (base unit) have been added to Gorbad - Omens of Destruction DLC for use in his Da Plan feature.<br/></li><li> Resolved a script error that prevented events from triggering after completing missions as Gorbad Ironclaw.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TECHNOLOGY TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Hammer of Gork’s Blinded contact effect is no longer replaced by Dazed from the Orcs &amp; Goblins’ Avalanche Smash technology.<br/></li><li> Eshin Maneater’s Weeping Blade effect is no longer replaced by Armour Sundering from the Ogres’ Betta Plunda technology.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SKILL TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Snagla's ‘Beneath the Gloomy Canopy’ skill would lose its Stalk effect when upgraded.<br/></li><li> Removed the ‘Immune to Contact Effects’ from the Slaughtermaster's Poisonmaster skill, as they possess that attribute innately.<br/></li><li> Removed the Thundertusk and Stonehorn from the Hunter skill effects that provided Vanguard, Frenzy, and Stalk Hunter skills.<br/></li><li> Fixed the missing Idol of Gork Scrap upgrade for Savage Orc units.<br/></li><li> Fixed the Divinatory Authority skill incorrectly reducing cooldowns for Cold-Blooded instead of Focus Instincts.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Markus Wulfhart’s Imperial Regiments of Greatswords had a different tier to regular Greatswords.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a UI issue with the Ogre’s army ability ‘Meat Feast’, which incorrectly stated it affected multiple units when it only affects a single unit.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Colossal Squigs were missing Siege Attacker.<br/></li><li> Added missing MP unit caps to the following: Colossal Squig, Da Acif Burpa, Snagla Deff Throwa, Piggyback Knights, Slaughterbrute, Eshin Maneater, Skullcannon, Hellforged Bellowers, and Arachnarok Flinger.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Khorngors were still available for Warriors of Chaos when unit caps were active.<br/></li><li> Fixed the abilities ‘Bathed in Blood’ and ‘Blinding Radiance’ being incorrectly labelled as active abilities.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/>​Thanks to everyone who’s shared their feedback with us since the launch of Omens of Destruction and Update 6.0. If you run into any new issues after updating to 6.0.3, please let us know over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
