<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 05 – Da Beta Results! 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/5997186379225962903</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0bcb5eed2bda77f53be9d0ebbb0822705ea9fb36.png"/><br/>You mobbed up with us and krumped your way through the High-Octane Mayhem that was the Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks Open Beta.  <br/><br/>To celebrate this achievement, we’ve collected some of our favorite facts and statistics in the infographic shared below. We hope you all enjoy looking through them as much as we did, and it won’t be long till we see you all back in the game for release this summer! <br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we'z shoutin' a big WAAAGH! with da mob! Thanks for joinin' da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/681cc030335c6a1f840a08a65bb52c4265cf5c16.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What a WAAAGH!</div> You krumped <b>1,624,734</b> gitz with <b>1,098,898</b> assistz. That’s 32% krumped solo and 68% falling to the mob!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/47a6ccd520067e28b9c95ff81147adaa86b2f7e3.png"/><br/><br/><b>75,542</b> of these krumpz were airborne. Knocking Orkz out the sky like a Fly Swatta!<br/><br/>Altogether, you Freeks played <b>18,737</b> matches! <b>9,386</b> games on Ded ‘ard Desert and <b>9,351</b> on Frozen Dakka <br/><br/>On Average you scored <b>1,495</b> points per match and dealt <b>1,068</b> damage. <i>No slacking Orkz in our mobz!</i><br/><br/>To prove it, <b>43,222</b> players achieved a kill frenzy! That’s killin’ loads of gitz without dying. Waaagh!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aa96d2d93f6339ddc1b6f32bc4dd9e5bd7e9c3eb.png"/><br/>The average kill/death ratio was <b>1.1</b>, meaning each of you krumped your own worth. Besides we can find plenty more Orkz where they come from. <br/><br/>However, one of you, and we bet you know who you are, is da biggest, ‘ardest and greenest killing machine with a kill streak of <b>41</b>!<br/><br/>Partz went flying and you greedy gitz scrounged a total <b>395,942,135</b> of Scrap, that’s <b>1,576</b> on average!<br/><br/>Slap dashing and scrapping it together, while under fire, you fixed <b>14,804,734</b> health. <br/><br/>Altogether, this tells us we got nothing to worry about, you gitz love a good stomping!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Wishlist da WAAAGH!</div>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/>Wishlist and follow to give Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks the nitro it needs to cross that starters line later this summer.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">JOIN DA WAAAGH!</div><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>With the conclusion of Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks Beta, we will take your feedback, polish up and launch full speed onto Steam <b>this summer</b>! <br/><br/>Your relentless energy has been top tier. It’s with that dedication and support that we look forward to sharing more info with you in the coming weeks so stay tuned and join us as we officially start the Speedwaaagh! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e4720e8b9dd905f56b4a553dcad45caf487cfc58.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.0.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/6018578477453058528</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/d5b6046ef6cbcf87b20c9161390983aed17d96d1.jpg"/><br/><br/>Hey everyone,<br/><br/>We've got a couple of quick fixes for you today in Hotfix 5.0.5, focused on Black Arks.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where executing the Sacrifice to Mathlann would unintentionally spawn multiple Black Arks, leading to spam. The fix ensures that characters are only added to the recruitment pool without spawning, preventing the spam.<br/></li><li> Minor adjustments to AI-controlled Black Ark behaviour, improving end-turn performance.</li></ul><br/>We'll also be looking at adding further improvements to Black Arks in future updates to help them move more meaningfully within the AI framework.<br/><br/>Thanks for your ongoing feedback and bug reports. If you experience a bug or issue while playing, remember to report it over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 09:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Alpha Test extended to June 17th! Hotfix 5.5.6 + 5.5.7</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4160842903734551758</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div><br/>Surprise! We've actually decided to extend the Versus Alpha for another week! Today's <b>hotfix, 5.5.6</b>, includes a few <b>fixes to both Adventure mode and Versus</b>, and has some <b>balance adjustments made to the playable Pactsworn for Versus</b>.<br/><br/>The RAT will now end on <b>June 17th!</b> Starting from yesterday and until the end of the test, the Versus servers will <b>automatically swap between the three active Versus maps:</b> <i>Against the Grain, Righteous Stand and Screaming Bell.</i> You get to play all of them this week and have more fun with our playable Bile Troll!<br/><br/>In case you haven't already, we have a <b><span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="The URL that was linked here has been removed by our filters.  Usually this is done to prevent phishing and malware attacks.">{LINK REMOVED}</span>Versus Feedback Survey</b> that we'd really appreciate if you all filled it out and gave us all your feedback from playing this Alpha!<br/><i>You can also find the survey link on the launcher.</i><br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 5.5.7 - 13th of June		</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes	</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed challenge "Sheltering Thicket" not tracking blocked ratling gunner shots properly.<br/></li><li>Fixed crash when hosting a game with a Waystalker Bot whose loadout contains a javelin, while the hosts own Waystalker loadout has a bow.<br/></li><li>Fixed an issue where you could select career by using the arrow keys.</li></ul></blockquote><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 5.5.6 - 12th of June		</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes	</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Chaos Wastes) Fixed rare crash when boon drones fly towards something very far away.	<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash that would occur if you upgrade an item currently equipped on any other loadout.	<br/> </li><li>	Fix crash when trying to update character data while having 5-6 loadouts on all careers</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Versus Tweaks	</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Enabled automatic map rotation between Righteous Stand, Screaming Bell and Against the Grain.<br/> </li><li>	Monsters now block warpfire thrower fire.		<br/> </li><li>	Increased Bile Troll health from 600 to 750.		<br/> </li><li>	Increased the size of Bile Troll's vomit hit boxes, to make it slightly easier to use.		<br/> </li><li>	Increased damage taken while standing in Bile Troll vomit by 40%.		<br/> </li><li>	Decreased spawn chance for Poison Wind Globadier slightly.		<br/> </li><li>	Increased Packmaster damage by 50% (per tick).		<br/> </li><li>	Increased Packmaster health from 30 to 50.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Versus Fixes	</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed pinging a potion with the ping wheel in versus causing a server crash			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed crash when showing pact sworn choices while playing with a controller			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed rare end of game dedicated server crash related to warrior priest ability being active.			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed certain spots in Against the Grain where Packmasters could pull hooked players out of the playable area and leave them stuck.			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a climb spot in Against the Grain where Pactsworn players could get stuck while climbing.			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed NPC enemies getting stuck on destructible stuff in Against the Grain.			<br/> </li><li>	Fixed NPC enemies sometimes getting really obsessed with attacking a spot on the ground in Against the Grain.<br/></li><li>	Fixed players being stuck in matchmaking if a hero picker appears and times out<br/></li><li>	Fixed crash caused by friend joining into a versus keep after playing as pact sworn.</li></ul></blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 08:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tune in for the Gameplay Overview Trailer on June 20!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4193493367544577084</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Space Marines, attention.</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Join us live on June 20th, at 6PM CEST | 12PM EDT | 9AM PDT to <b>take a deep dive into <i>Space Marine 2</i>’s gameplay mechanics and learn more about the campaign, co-op and PvP modes</b>. <br/><br/>Stay tuned by clicking the alert button, and see you on Focus Entertainment YouTube Channel!</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">We're excited to be part of this year's Summer Game Fest with this new gameplay sneak peek ahead of the Overview Trailer on June 20! </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch our Summer Game Fest Trailer now:</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f_HpG_9fiyY?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Pre-order four editions today - in digital or retail</b></div><br/> In addition to the Collector’s Edition exclusive to the Focus Store, three Editions are now available for preorder: Standard, Gold, and Ultra Edition.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/67eca0e2fd64688d7ff3f005d9c2e21102254a7e.jpg"/><br/><br/>Heed the call of battle when <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> launches September 9, 2024, on PC. Pre-order the Standard, Gold, Ultra, and Collector’s Edition now! <br/><br/>Sign up as a Focus member to get exclusive news and upcoming special offers for Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 and the whole Focus catalog.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.0.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4184486168273831319</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/1d9460e67a6c79baf7651974cef972c4d067845e.png"/><br/><br/><i><b>UPDATE 04/06/24 @ 14:35 BST:</b><br/>We're aware that the fix to Anvil of Doom melee attacks seems to have slipped through during the hotfix deployment, and are investigating. Thanks for your reports and patience while we look into it, and sorry for any confusion caused!</i><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>We've just rolled out Hotfix 5.0.4.<br/><br/>Here's what we've got today:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Confederating minor factions will no longer increase the cost of confederating Legendary Lords in the Great Book of Grudges<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Nurgle Plagues button could sometimes become permanently disabled in multiplayer campaigns<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue preventing Anvil of Doom characters from performing melee attacks under certain circumstances<br/></li><li> Added some missing VFX and audio to Thorek's Anvil of Doom melee attacks, including a fresh new effect where his anvil runes glow brighter when making a strike!<br/></li><li> Made Malakai's gun a tiny bit less eager - it now fires its bullets in sequence instead of firing every bullet immediately on the first shot<br/></li><li> Added audio to Malakai's third shot in his firing sequence<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where several different Legendary Heroes (I've got my eye on you, Ghoritch!) could spawn at a random character that did not belong to the player<br/></li><li> Fixed health bar not filling correctly on unit information panel in campaign<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Hero character names and icon outline did not match the player's colour<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in multiplayer campaigns where the Tomb Kings Mortuary Cult HUD button was locked if another player was Dwarfs<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Chaos Lords of Nurgle and Chaos Sorcerer of Nurgle variants were missing their Nurgle Authority skills<br/></li><li> Fixed the bandits caravan event not triggering<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some generic combat skills in the Daemon Slayer's skill tree used the hero variants (three levels instead of two that lords usually require)<br/></li><li> Fixed crash when loading a saved character in the army setup<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where horde factions could infinitely recruit capped units by creating and loading a save immediately after recruiting them</li></ul><br/>As always, thanks for your ongoing feedback and bug reports. We'll be back in the coming weeks with Patch 5.1. Until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
