<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog - No Man’s Land Level Design</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/660470283024466011</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xz0g-lybujo?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello, everyone!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As you saw, December 2 was not just the release date of the Hive Scum DLC class, but also of the No Man’s Land Free Update!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In addition to our Hive Scum focused dev blogs (check out the last one here), we’ve prepared this dev blog to break down the level design of No Man’s Land, a brand new Operation-type mission that is coming as part of the Free Update.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For this dev blog we've interviewed <b>Karl Thornblom</b>, the <b>level designer</b> behind the <b>No Man’s Land Operation.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I’m Karl Thornblom, Level Designer \[...] I’ve been working on Darktide since like two years before launch \[...] and I’ve pretty much worked on every level to a certain degree.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Free Update: The Road to No Man’s Land</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Road to No Man’s Land is a new story mini-campaign, similar to <i>‘Battle For Tertium’</i>, where you play through three missions in a connected storyline, unlocking new chapters as you go. The first chapter features the Rolling Steel operation, followed by Excise Vault Spireside-13 as the second chapter. The third and final chapter of this mini-campaign is the new Operation: No Man’s Land.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b530a913b6ecc2d467b2b8680ba96cf50594ea12.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">No Man’s Land Operation</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“What we wanted to do was kind of like a very intense, movie-like war mission.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">No Man’s Land is an Operation-type mission that lets you dive into an active warzone and blitz through the trenches, making your way past enemy lines to accompany a Leman Russ tank on its way to disable enemy artillery!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“You start in the trenches, in one of the few places where a Valkyrie can land and that the Imperial Guard still hold, and then you push into the sections of the trenches where \[the Heretics] have taken over.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/106cb2363be1776608ecd472ba65cac83a757cae.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While the trenches provide some much needed cover from all the gunfire and artillery being unleashed above, you will only be able to rely on them for so long. As you keep pushing through, you will go into more open spaces, devastated ruins and shelled battlefields while you make your way to the occupied bastion.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ecd5990b0156aede7bb001e9870bb7ca4c79a9ee.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“\[...] which creates a very different environment and also a very different type of gameplay. Trenches are kinda, like, corridor-y and a bit claustrophobic at times… And then it opens up into this ruined plaza, pretty much. \[...] And then you get into the real “No Man’s Land” section, and that’s where it <b>really</b> opens up.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/132785bd4352efd3776d08a6bef6ee411e5a78b7.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Operatives have a task not just to wade through hordes of enemies and make it to the stronghold, but to also ensure that the Leman Russ they’re accompanying makes it to its target. Both the team and the Leman Russ are key to this mission, helping each other by clearing the path and removing obstacles in ways that the other cannot. Success would not be possible without one or the other!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The tank helps you, but you also help the tank sometimes.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d5dd5e2d1953de2f69366cac9c28f7c9ee6fc282.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Why an Operation?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Operations fill a niche in our game of being tighter experiences that allow us to explore different concepts. Compared to normal missions, they’re shorter and more linear, but also allow us to hand-craft each encounter and keep the whole mission tight, action-packed and spectacular.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The shorter nature of them is also part of the goal, as we want Darktide to offer options for those players who, every now and then, just want a quick 15-minute session or so. As Rolling Steel is our only Operation at the moment, we wanted to add another one to fill that niche a bit more, which was the starting point for No Man’s Land.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s not to say that they play exactly alike! No Man’s Land does not feature a hard time limit, for instance, and we actually expect it to last a few more minutes than Rolling Steel on average. However, while Rolling Steel involves a lot of advancing and stopping to complete some objective, No Man’s Land is a non-stop push towards the finish line! It is only at the very end event that you’ll be halted by an objective that requires some time to complete.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Visuals and Inspiration</div><p class="bb_paragraph">No Man’s Land was a great opportunity to explore some environments previously unseen in Darktide, the Operation doesn’t take place inside the Hive but actually on the outskirts of it. Poking out of the trenches you can see that there’s actual landscapes, that the buildings don’t reach up endlessly into an artificial roof, and that you can actually see the sky.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“In some ways it was freeing, but it was also a new thing.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cfcf04fa36c825c760212aec490f0be7a2db5b72.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">No Man’s Land shows a more gruesome and grim aspect of the war against the Heretics. There’s a lot of inspiration taken from historical warfare that was used to build this level; trudging through the trenches while all hell is breaking loose on the surface, the devastated buildings wrecked by artillery, the vast sea of rubble that’s all that’s left of a once bustling part of the Hive.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“We even have rockets and mortar fires landing in gameplay space \[...] And you actually get knocked back from it and stuff, so it’s really cool!” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This also gave us the opportunity to depict some of the most iconic pieces of scenery used in the Warhammer: 40,000 tabletop game! You might recognize some particular sections of ruined buildings and half-destroyed environments that are very characteristic of what’s most commonly used to play on the tabletop, which is something we’ve been wanting to do for a while.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6459491ab9c55c64a336d71e73837c89f47cd258.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“And also, we’ve had the Leman Russ in multiple missions, but it’s always been a static one. \[...] So we were like, it’d be so cool to actually see the Leman Russ in action.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Design Process and Challenges</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6970644380923607489d6aedcfa6303b30021c26.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The idea of a warzone mission like this has been something we have wanted to tackle for a long time, and that concept has floated around in various iterations until finally landing in the short and action-packed version we have for the Operation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As with most levels, the design of the layout begins with a rough blockout where the level and its gameplay are built up using placeholder assets.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fa1cb71cc5847c3ccdb6e69a4ef90501ce712dec.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“For quite a while I worked alone on this and I made an entire, fully playable blockout (with a very janky tank driving by!)” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is also where most of the experimentation with the pacing and gameplay happens, as it’s the easiest to adjust. There’s an intentional design of having the gameplay space of the map constantly change between tight, oppressive corridors and more open spaces, then back again. This constant shift in how you play through the map can give it a lot of variety in the moment to moment, but also hopefully makes the Operation feel truly unique compared to normal missions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9aafe4004dad246b716c4e76d9040e3ee1979883.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">One of the more challenging aspects of this map was the Leman Russ itself. We wanted to showcase it as much as possible and have it be a vital part of the mission, and a lot of thought and planning had to go into making that a reality within the technical limits of the game. After all, we didn’t have a working tank before!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I had to spend quite a lot of time figuring out the tank’s path. Where it goes in relation to the player, and the timing and the moments you can see it and all of that. In some aspects I had to arrange the tank’s path after the players’, but sometimes it was the players’ path that depended on how I could make the tank go, and make it pop and be visible.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Bonus: What did you enjoy the most about No Man’s Land?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I think it’s really fun to create something that is a bit smaller and more contained, but also very intense. And I think the coolest thing for me is (since this was an idea that I had for a long time and I worked on it alone for quite a bit) to see all of the cool things that the team added to make it all pop, and make it feel cinematic and epic. \[...] It’s been really, really cool to see it all come together.” ~ Karl</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for today, but keep an eye out for our next and final Dev Blog of the year, coming soon!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Purchase the Hive Scum here:</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.17.1 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/596293989202657298</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Changes since 1.17.0</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed crash when a unit with a Storm Bolter is produced.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/489630/" width="850"></iframe>
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.0.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/493837011861373244</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/4410d3de16c093379a0cff9e2ceb836e693f85db.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just rolled out Hotfix 7.0.2 for Total War: WARHAMMER III, implementing a number of additional fixes in the wake of Update 7.0 and Hotfix 7.0.1.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've also listed some known issues at the bottom of this page which are currently on our radar. Our teams are deep in preparation for 7.0.3, which will include a number of additional fixes. With the holidays fast approaching our plan is to release this into a Beta branch later in December, with a view to releasing in full at the start of the new year if all is well.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, if you run into any new issues after updating, please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting area.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>PERFORMANCE </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur when opening the Patrons of Ulthuan panel during a High Elves multiplayer campaign. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash-to-desktop issue that occurred when users who only own the Champions of Chaos DLC attempted to play Vilitch the Curseling’s ‘The Altar of Battle’ quest battle. </p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>CAMPAIGN </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where players were incorrectly able to interact a second time with Monstrous Arcanum markers after completing their associated missions. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor Cult Pleasure Palaces will no longer grant immortality to settlement garrison leaders. </p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>BATTLE </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Monstrous Arcanum quest battles occasionally having incorrect deployment zones when teleporting to them. </p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>LOCALISATION </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several untranslated strings and updated various existing translations in Brazilian Portuguese, Simplified Chinese, German, French, Italian, Spanish, Polish, Russian, Turkish, Traditional Chinese, Korean, and Czech. </p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>ASSEMBLY KIT</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Addressed and resolved an issue in Assembly Kit BOB where campaign processing was disrupted due to incompatibility with the latest Gaming Services update on the Microsoft Store platform.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>​STILL COOKING</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Note: This list is just a spotlight on some of the things that you are talking to us about most — there are lots of other things that we are investigating in the background!</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Unlocking Heralds of Civilization on turn 1 allows Aislinn to gain up to 30k gold on turn 2 from joining wars against minor factions. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enemies in second-stage Monster Arcanum hunt markers may retreat after the player interacts with the marker. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Two High Elf factions can complete the Caradryan hero quest, enabling one to confederate the other and acquire two Caradryans. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sea Patrol Outpost chain fails to provide its Control effect. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ashtari mount disappears when switching mounts with Caradryan. </p></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Merwyrm, Dread Maw, Dechala, and other units are missing audio on the latest Steam release (Patch 7.0.1). This issue was reproduced on 7.0.2 (Steam) but has not been observed in local testing.  </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER - Tides Of Torment And 25th Anniversary Wallpapers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510724876254840611</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/568a5e1f35a0a7c797baf162fb3daf39f12b405f.png"/><br/><br/>​Hey folks!<br/><br/>While decorating for the holidays, you may want to spruce up your desktops and phone screens for Total War: WARHAMMER as well!<br/><br/>Tides of Torment and 25th Anniversary wallpapers are now available in the rewards section of the CA Community!<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 CA REWARDS 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Rampage Pack out now</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/525361575047988913</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Rampage Pack </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Deploy 8 brand-new units with the Rampage Pack on the battlefields of Gladius Prime. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">The new units will bring a new offensive layer and will unlock new strategic options for commanders.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">These new units are available now: </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Seraphim - Adepta Sororitas: </b>jump infantry equipped with potent hand flamers</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Kommandos - Orks: </b>melee unit specialized in infiltration and elimination of priority targets</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Armiger Helverin - Adeptus Mechanicus: </b>long-range heavy walker</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Genestealers - Tyranids: </b>elite infiltration melee unit</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Krootox Rampagers - T’au: </b>disruptive melee infantry</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hexmark Destroyer - Necrons: </b>short range specialist able to teleport</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deathstrike - Astra Militarum: </b>long-range artillery vehicle carrying a single, destructive missile</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Plague Marines - Chaos Space Marines: </b>short-range heavy infantry unit carrying poisoned weapons</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Update - Version 1.17.0</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Special thanks to MaidrosTwin and the rest of the Gladius community for helping to identify and fix bugs for this patch.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>"We will rise and claim the engines of labour that have bound us in servitude. This world will burn. It will be cleansed, purified, made ready, and the Heavens will deliver our reward!"</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>— Unknown Genestealer Cult Magus</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">New Units (Rampage Pack DLC)</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Seraphim (Adepta Sororitas) \[Tier 4] - Jump infantry equipped with potent hand flamers to burn down hostile mobs.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Armiger Helverin (Adeptus Mechanicus) \[Tier 8] - Long range heavy walker.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deathstrike (Astra Militarum) \[Tier 7] - Long-range artillery vehicle carrying a single, destructive missile.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Plague Marines (Chaos Space Marines) \[Tier 4] - Short range heavy infantry unit carrying poisoned weapons.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Hexmark Destroyer (Necrons) \[Tier 3] - Short range specialist able to teleport.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kommandos (Orks) \[Tier 3] - Melee unit specialized in infiltration and elimination of protected targets.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Krootox Rampagers (T'au) \[Tier 2] - Sneaky melee cavalry.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Genestealers (Tyranids) \[Tier 2] - Elite infiltration melee unit.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked research screen top and bottom bar sizes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved multiplayer connectivity.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed buildings constructed in post-game stats counting when a building begins construction instead of when it is completed.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed targetting not being cancelled when an item is removed, potentially causing crashes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Ruins of Vaul tip triggering for Sororitas Holy Site.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Succubus being able to target Fortifications with No Escape.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Spirit Seer's Destructor not applying Soul Blazed.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Cronos' Spirit Probe correctly mentioning that it can affect monstrous creatures.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Cronos' Reservoir of Pain not being able to affect fortifications and vehicles.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed R'Varna damaging itself with Nova Electromagnetic Shockwave.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Twin-Linked Storm Bolter having Rapid Fire (to be consistent with Storm Bolter).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Interceptor Drones damage against Flyers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Talos and Cronos having Relentless because it has no effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Sicarian Ruststalkers research not unlocking the Voices in the Code research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Attilan Rough Riders research not unlocking Hammer of Wrath research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Vypers research not unlocking Crystal Targeting Matrix, Ghostwalk Matrix, Holo-Fields, Spirit Stones, Star Engines and Vectored Engines researches.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Canoptek Reanimator research not unlocking Immortal Form and Hammer of Wrath researches.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Squighog Boyz research not unlocking Hammer of Wrath research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Primaris Inceptors research not unlocking Hammer of Wrath research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Norn Emissary research not unlocking Hammer of Wrath research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Vypers enabled weapon by default not matching its first Cycle Weapon slot.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Chaos Terminators' Power Sword not using the Chaos Power Weapon glow effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Saint Celestine Miraculous Intervention not removing its trait if the action was disabled due to low morale.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Saint Celestine Miraculous Intervention not reapplying its trait if the cooldown was reset by a Dialogus.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Laud Hailer not granting Zephyrims the ability to use their Act of Faith while Shaken.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Zephyrims not losing Angelic Visage when Broken.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Angelic Visage not being affected by Vow of the Militant Order research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Stikka (Ranged), Psychic Tendril (Neurolance) and Psychic Tendril (Neuroblast) damage that were higher than intended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Stikka (Melee) damage that was lower than intended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Hunting Lance (Melta Tip) damage that was lower than intended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Clawed Limbs damage that was lower than intended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Adeptus Mechanicus Voices in the Code not mentioning Sicarian Ruststalkers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Astra Militarum Frag grenades not mentioning Attilan Rough Riders (Bullgryns were also missing in French).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Astra Militarum Hammer of Wrath not mentioning Attilan Rough Riders.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Chaos Space Marines Gift of Mutation and Melta Bomb not mentioning Rubric Marines.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Eldar Crystal Targeting Matrix, Ghostwalk Matrix, Holo Fields, Spirit Stones, Star Engines and Vectored Engines not mentioning Vypers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Necrons Hammer of Wrath not mentioning Canoptek Reanimators.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Orks Hammer of Wrath not mentioning Squighog Boyz.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Space Marines Frag &amp; Krak grenades not mentioning Primaris Hellblasters and Primaris Intercessors.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Space Marines Hammer of Wrath not mentioning Primaris Inceptors and Primaris Redemptor Dreadnought.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Tyranids Hammer of Wrath not mentioning Norn Emissaries.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4084640/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Rampage_Pack/</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><br/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
