<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Crash Fixes! + Deffkopta Changes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/686362177252098883</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">OI YOU'Z GITS!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This isn't the spookiest of Halloween updates, but it's certainly an Orky one - Or is it? We're fixing things, not breaking them...</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><div class="bb_h3">Alright, some big <b>stability</b> updates first:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with <b>vehicle explosions</b> causing crazy forces and lagging the entire server</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved overall stability and fixed <b>crashing</b> associated with some maps. Hopefully this helps disband the <i>fatal error gang</i> for good ːsteamthumbsupː</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash for systems using an <b>Intel Arc GPU</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some performance improvements to various maps</p></li></ul><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some extra things in this update:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a <b>fade</b> function to vehicles so when the camera gets close to it, they don't block the entire view. This is mostly a change to help players aim at <b>Deffkoptas</b> flying around/above them</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added updated main menu buttons in preparation for the HUGE upcoming <b>level editor</b> update</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with Stompa desyncing in <i>Scrap In Da Yard</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deffkopta kits now show in the UI even if not unlocked yet</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Hid some unused Ork animations in Kustomize</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some audio optimizations</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Steam Deck</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">We're still figuring out what went wrong here that's causing extreme performance issues, but we think we have a lead on what's happening and can pinpoint the game update that started the issues. Hoping to have a fix soon, apologies for the wait.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>DEFFKOPTA 🚁</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Most people have been loving piloting this little guy and wreaking havoc from the skies - but some of you gits haven't enjoyed being on the receiving end of the Deffkopta's aerial wrath. Thank you everyone for all the feedback and meta discussion, it's been very fun to read!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've made some changes that we hope will be received well, with the Deffkopta still being a formidable opponent, but less frustrating to fight against:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Deffkopta now has two primary weapon options: <b>Kopta Rokkits</b> and <b>Kopta Drop Rokkits</b>. The Drop Rokkits are the ability you've already experienced.</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>To sum up the difference, the Kopta Rokkits are a shorter range, easier to hit weapon that has a bit of bonus damage when used at the limit of its range. The Drop Rokkits can be fired much further, but are more difficult to hit and don't have access to the bonus damage.</i></p></blockquote></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Drop Rokkit damage reduced to 11 (from 14)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkits (the new default weapon) deal 9 damage in close range, and 14 damage when hitting targets over 50m away. Missile and trail VFX change to show rokkit instability (meaning higher damage) after flying 50 meters.</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>14 damage is the original missile damage value, which you now only have access to at a distance. We found that Deffkoptas hovering directly over your head was not that fun to fight, so we've added an incentive to adopt more of a hit and run playstyle: use your bomb and melee coooldowns, and then retreat to a short distance away to get max damage from your rokkits.</i></p></blockquote></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkit explodes after 100m (compared to Drop Rokkit 200m)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkit impact radius is 8 (compared to Drop Rokkit 6), and proximity fuse radius is 6 compared to Drop Rokkit 4)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Projectile spread/inaccuracy removed from all Deffkopta Rokkits.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased hit box size slightly, extended it downwards to help with vehicle-on-vehicle body blocking (ie. bomb defense)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Spinning Blades ability now has less ability to change momentum when turning</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Spinning Blades cooldown increased to 7 seconds (from 5)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shows the correct health value in the help screen (100, not 110)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta weight reduced to 4k (from 5k)</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This makes the Deffkopta take more knockback from weapons, and jump higher from its own bomb knockback.</i></p></blockquote></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>OTHER VEHICLES</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Scrapjet Combat Rokkit damage reverted to 25 (from 30)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">So yeah, this is the first round of DK changes after reading everyone's initial feedback. Our goal is to keep what makes the Deffkopta fun while also improving the experience of fighting against it, and also to simplify things overall but add a bit of complexity for those who want it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since you've played the Deffkopta a certain way already, it will feel a bit different at first. Please give these changes a bit of time to sink in, and we look forward to reading everyone's thoughts and opinions on the update.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3720867577dc70f8d92cdb3f88e031c027cddfed.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>WOT'Z COMIN'</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">A reminder that the next big update includes the <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> (with online workshop support) and a ton of wacky custom maps ready to play.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">It will be the biggest, most game-changing update the game has ever seen and we are very excited to watch the community adopt the tools and have a ton of fun making their own maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">WORKSHOP</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The <b>WORKSHOP</b> will have a rating system and we'll highlight player creations in the main menu of the game, too.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some players will be able to access the level editor ahead of launch to put their creations on the workshop in advance - more details on this in a future post.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Really pumped for this, it's a huge feature for the game and we don't think our players truly understand yet how much it elevates the game :)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/> </p><div class="bb_h3">Thanks for playin' our Orky game</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, we appreciate our players and their dedication to Speed Freeks. We're actively trying to get new players in as it's more fun with other gits. Hope to see you ingame!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.5.0.300 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/659340578353315865</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hotfix 1.5.0.300 is live, dealing with a number of issues reported over the last few days.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Patch notes:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Multiple Overseer abilities didn't work properly when used while stepping out from full cover - fixed;<br/></li><li> Female Commissar's hat did not get removed by setting "Show Base Outfit Headgear" to off - fixed;<br/></li><li> Base outfit hats were sometimes missing from the character generation screen and character inventory screen - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some details could disappear from the base outfit when "Show Armour" was set to off - fixed;<br/></li><li> Commissar's At All Costs! ability was dealing 100% more damage than it should have - fixed;<br/></li><li> There were issues with selecting the 4th ability during level up for Soldier and Operative on console and when playing with a controller - fixed;<br/></li><li> Emergency Injector has got its description back;<br/></li><li> Some of the new Commissar talents had incorrect descriptions - fixed;<br/></li><li> When playing on consoles or with a controller, it was impossible to change the appearance of mercenaries or change the Lord-captain's appearance using the mirror in the quarters - fixed;<br/></li><li> When inviting Pasqal into the party for the first time, the character that was removed to give him a party slot, stayed in the party bar on the top of the screen - fixed;<br/></li><li> The game could sometimes fail to load during transition between parts of a large location - fixed;<br/></li><li> The Fractal Blade gave incorrect bonus to parry - fixed;<br/></li><li> AI turns would sometimes fail to end properly after counter-attack with a burst-fire weapon - fixed;<br/></li><li> Removed the {0} symbols that popped up in some colony project descriptions;<br/></li><li> Returned the letters to some talent icons that lost them after 1.5;<br/></li><li> Bringer of Terror was usable without Bolter Proficiency despite being a Heavy Bolter - fixed;<br/></li><li> A cutscene in Anatomical Opera would sometimes fail to run, causing the location to become empty - fixed;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 09:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/506217467911081454</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Space Marines!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With Halloween creeping closer and Update 11.0 just weeks away, it’s the perfect time to mix the two: so here are a few treats from the game to sink your teeth into. 😉</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>SOMETHING TERRIFYING IS COMING 🦇</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the latest Community Update, we gave you a sneak peek of the upcoming new PvE Map and told you it would have a “new boss fight “. Today, we wanted to announce that this new boss is a Tyranid Prime! Except there’s a twist. There’s <i>two</i> of them. You’re welcome. 😁</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It is a formidable enemy: a winged Tyranid leader beast, the apex of the Tyranid Warrior strain. Its heavy bladed limbs can slice through the toughest targets, so make sure you’re ready.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">You will meet this foe on "Reclamation", the new Operation map coming with Patch 11.0, which is off-planet. Your mission? Infiltrate the captured ship and destroy it. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Along with the new map and Boss fight, new Battlefield Conditions will be implemented to the Stratagems mode, with new weapon variants and armor pieces.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">​<b>Patch 11.0 - Reclamation Update</b> is planned for the <b>end of November</b>, stay tuned for the precise release date.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>UPCOMING DLCs</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Reclamation Update comes with two cosmetic DLCs: The <b>Blood Angel Champion Pack</b> and the <b>Salamanders Cosmetic Pack</b>. The Blood Angels Champion is quite special this time as it is directly inspired by the Blood Angels Captain miniature. This skin also comes with an optional jump pack variant for Assault, for you Sanguinary Guard fans. We hope you like it! ❤️</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>BLOOD ANGELS CHAMPION PACK</b></div>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fdffc1b59b7d81c46e8c6a99b7200fbe8a39f82a.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4cd718a4409a34e7d514e364d73c3ebbe6827141.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/046d7c4fbc88486ce3eaede582fb16567ece2d44.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/13eb26b1a81f799220f66e5f9ab137baf5870f79.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1d567dc2c66ea8f063ab093e4109ec0d51fbfb55.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a6723e6f235781f34ff53d08fd01d879ceb51f7.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Along with that, the Salamanders return with a Cosmetic Pack this time including 5 Armour Pieces, 4 Successor Chapters and various decals. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Have a closer look at it:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>SALAMANDERS COSMETIC PACK</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>[carousel autoadvance="true"]<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1114adce4a5e673e55464740399ebbe2843eaa35.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ca364d7114aab9493e03ac7a081632abe73c1e51.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>SALAMANDERS SUCCESSOR CHAPTERS</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dark Krakens</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Dragonspears</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Black Vipers</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Covenant of Fire</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/49619f581fef6e80bee9debee64371f49b14bef2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>RESULTS OF THE EVENT</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This month you were missionned to collectively annihilate 400,000 Mutalith Vortex Beasts. And you made it!! ✅</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">More than <b>400,000 Vortex Beasts were taken down in the span of two weeks</b>. You’ve truly outdone yourself this time Space Marines. You make the Emperor proud.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The reward for completing this task with such diligence is the Infiltrator Helmet for the Vanguard and Sniper classes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>We hope you’ll make good use of it! 💥</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/21012ab15122595510533db2c9cb21a75321e563.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>THE PUBLIC TEST SERVER IS STILL UP!</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you want to experience Patch 11 before everyone else and you're playing on Steam, we’ve got good news for you! <b>Until November 4</b>, try out the <b>new PvE Map</b>, <b>new Heroic Weapons</b>, <b>new equipment “Sanctified Wrath”</b>, <b>Chaos armour pieces swap in PvP</b>, and more via the Public Test Server!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a11ca3b61fed8da3ae812ff123cf327b988d0428.png"/><i>You can now mix Chaos armours and equip them to different classes</i> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>👉 Here’s an <u>easy tutorial on how to access it!</u></b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>👉 And here are the <u>Patch Notes</u></b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that the cosmetic DLCs can't be equipped if you don't own the Season Pass, and Reclamation's Boss Fight is not available either. Also, the PTS runs as a completely separate game version. It does not carry over your previous progress in the game; instead, it provides all players with a default maxed-out level and weapons.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">💬 Don’t hesitate to give us feedback, either on <u>Focus Together </u>or on our <u>Discord server</u>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Since it’s been a few days already, we’ve received some feedback and wanted to address it quickly here. We wanted to reassure you on the following:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blood Angels’s Champion parts will be colourable.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Salamanders’ shoulder will have an emblem.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Jump pack dash attacks aren’t final.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Please keep in mind that PTS is not a final version of the upcoming update, and thus many things are still Work In Progress.</b> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ac435e9d20cfa260bb3cc9b9fd123ff7095b8a5f.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>RESULTS OF THE COMMUNITY VOTE</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We were eager to know which PvE Operation was your favourite. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With 265 votes, Decapitation is your favourite Operation so far! Doing this kind of vote really helps us to know what you prefer, thanks again for your participation! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ca1307049c0e0a0abe195667e71948e2324dd211.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>ULTIMA EDITION GIVEAWAY </b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To celebrate Halloween together, we’re offering 2 Ultima Limited Editions! This gorgeous bundle contains the Base Game, an exclusive SteelBook®, Season Pass 1 and Season Pass 2 and the Macragge’s Chosen DLC.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To participate you need to:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Follow @Focus_Entmt on Instagram, X, Facebook, Threads or Bluesky</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Comment #SpaceMarine2 under the post, either on Instagram, X, Facebook, Threads or Bluesky and tell us which platform you want your base game to be on!</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Facebook</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Instagram</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">X (formerly Twitter)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bluesky</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Threads</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">The two lucky ones to get picked will be contacted on November 10 via their DMs, so don’t forget to open them! Make sure to read the <u>rules</u> of this contest.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Good luck, Space Marines! 🍀</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9a7529d2034dce5432bd76011d337c1d396c53d9.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Q&amp;A - ADDRESSING A SELECTION OF IDEAS FROM FOCUS TOGETHER</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">On Focus Together, you have been submitting ideas for the game since launch. Today, we wanted to address some of the latest and most discussed ideas and bring an answer to them with insights from Game Director Dmitry Grigorenko! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For each question, you may find the title of the idea with a hyperlink (<b>➡️</b>), a subtitle summarizing it (🟰), and then, our answer (💬). There are more questions we did answer, so don’t hesitate to check <u>Focus Together</u> for a complete overview!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>➡️ “<u>Remove Stratagem Currency</u>”</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">🟰 <b>Remove Accolades</b> <b>or make Accolades tradable with Requisition points so they can be farmed.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>💬 </b><i>Currently, removing Accolades or making them possible to trade with Requisition points is not planned. However, as we stated in the September Community Update, we will implement different ways to earn Accolades in the future.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>➡️ “Allow all classes to use the Space Wolf Champion's fur shoulder pads”</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>🟰 Have less Class restrictions for which Class can use the Space Wolf Champion’s shoulder pads.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">💬 <i>The reason behind locking the Space Wolves' shoulder pads is because Phobos armor parts cannot be used on Tacticus or Gravis armours (Lore reasons. Plus, it simply doesn't fit 🥲). What you are asking actually implies creating a new shoulder pad for Tacticus and Gravis armour sets. We are going to do that for the most popular Champion parts and Space Wolves Shoulder Pad is one of those!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>➡️ <u>Power Axe for tactical and Space wolves cosmetic for tactical.</u> </b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">💬 <i>We are thinking of something cooler and more complex than that. 👀</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>➡️ “<u>Add MK VII without laurels</u></b>”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">💬 <i>Yes, we’re planning to add the “laurel-less” version of the Helmet in an upcoming update.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>➡️ “Training sim/arena”</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>🟰 Add some kind of training simulator / shooting range to the Battle Barge.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">💬 <i>Yes! We’re planning to expand the Battle Barge in this way.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Each month, we try our best to address the trendiest and most upvoted ideas on Focus Together. But as you may have seen yourselves, there are now more than 10K ideas. Therefore, we need time to consider all suggestions, discuss them and eventually bring an answer. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your patience, and mostly for your devotion and interest in the game.</p><div class="bb_h1"><b>THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH!</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you want to keep yourself updated on the latest news on Space Marine 2, join our <u>Discord Server right here</u>, and become a member of <u>Focus Together</u>. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">You can also follow Focus Entertainment and our <u>socials</u>! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your unwavering support. 🖤</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>-Focus and Saber</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.5 - A Deep Dive Article</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/576022713144969256</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Our major update for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, Update 1.5, has been released, and it’s about time we dive deeper into the changes!<br/><br/>Before we start, we would like to extend our special thanks to our community and our Owlmates partnership program members for their massive help with pinpointing issues and offering ideas for improvements.<br/><br/>We’ve got a lot to show, so get comfortable, and let’s get started!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2495b04cbd33f28c5caa7ee7cc3ad86da3992d48.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Portraits</div><br/>Let’s begin with the beautiful new art! Based on popular community requests, we’ve added portraits for four well-known and beloved NPCs:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Commissar:</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/7423e503d573bf36289af31ffed97f56d4d17bfc.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Malice:</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/db23502a9a93b17300c20f11d1879d0e30a6485e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Clementia Werserian:</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/8d84ca6989845d8b8f54623d847112198a4e276f.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Abel:</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9646b899ae336df7bbe71f2586aea35bdac8179f.png"/><br/><br/>By the way, in case we decide to do more of these, which characters would you most like to see next?<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Xeno and Space Marine Itemisation</div><br/>Since release, we’ve received a lot of feedback saying that Xeno and Space Marine items in the game lack variety and diversity. We want you to know that we heard you. That’s why, in this update, we’re adding over 15 new Space Marine items and over 30 Aeldari and Drukhari items of all types, providing you a massive increase in build variety for your Xeno and Space Marine companions!<br/><br/>Take a look at this gorgeous new suit of armour for Ulfar, for example:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/53afa53afbc3b394cd3e9ba35435f22a49bb3c58.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e95ac228d6b473b6d8ce7b2a23cd57c101d3e3ef.gif"/><br/><br/>Or this new aeldari armour, that looks just perfect on Yrliet:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/58e094f786761fc4fd7ab7a84ad4c4aa6d0235f6.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e419234a9f57e397d1e5c14a702f8939e3c2f39f.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Visuals</div><br/>In addition, we’ve added a range of new armour and weapon model skins and recolors, which will be used for the new items described above, as well as many old items that previously shared the same model. Here are a few examples:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2234300e1c43c5d83206e277e0461faa65e1e685.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/fb730c97e03dd2b0bf2b5461ea3aeeedebd91345.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9a0997b0814948b79f645b13639715b24c764aab.png"/><br/><br/>While we were at it, we decided to also review and improve a number of visual effects such as weapon projectiles or candle glow:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/fb591f9cbc122bd0a323d18ba3570d064fcfe51e.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/303f03366746f9066b4e22fdd53544e8e44a8045.gif"/><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Origins Rework</div><br/>While we’ve never sought to create a perfect power balance between different playstyles, it became apparent over time that certain choices had become way too underpowered when all the new patches and expansions were applied.<br/><br/>Older and weaker origins simply no longer felt as fun or engaging to play, so we decided to give them each a well-deserved update!<br/><br/>Behold:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Astra Militarum Commander Rework</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/cb70730d46dd06c7e32726f0467a9844ca3d6ce4.jpg"/><br/><br/>Many of the old Astra Militarum Commander bonuses were either very situational or else very hard to set up, and the playstyle didn’t really support the image of an experienced leader who once commanded massive armies.<br/><br/>In this rework, we wanted to keep the focus on shooting and cover, but add a bit more emphasis on the tactical/commanding aspect of the Astra Militarum legacy while simultaneously encouraging heavy use of the iconic Astra Militarum weapon — the Lasgun.<br/><br/>Here’s what’s changed:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>PER bonus</b> was replaced with <b>FEL bonus</b> and <b>Medicae</b> with <b>Coercion</b> for better synergy with Officers. <b>FEL </b>is now always available for level up instead of <b>PER</b>.<br/></li><li> <b>Regimental tactics</b> ability no longer requires being adjacent to the Commander or their allies, but instead works on enemies that were already attacked this turn by Commander or their allies.<br/></li><li> <b>Suppression Fire!</b> now applies not just to the Commander, but also to their allies, and will now work on enemies that were already attacked this turn by Commander or their allies, no longer requiring adjacency.<br/></li><li> <b>Timely Rescue</b> is gone and was replaced with the brand new <b>Fix Bayonets!</b> talent, which allows all two-handed lasguns to make a Bayonet Strike melee single target attack for 1 AP once per round, which deals weapon damage and does not count towards the attack limit per turn.<br/></li><li> <b>Shoulder to Shoulder</b> is gone and replaced with the <b>Trench Warfare</b> talent, which gives the Commander +20% rate of fire with las weapons in partial cover, and +40% rate of fire in full cover.</li></ul>Vengeance for Cadia!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Ministorum Priest Rework</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a3017a421cb65cb1252cb32b3d14f3ea250cb2d8.png"/><br/><br/>The previous version of the Ministorum Priest was arguably the least useful of all the old origins, with most of its bonuses being either very situational or just outright weak. In this update, the Ministrorum Priest has undergone a massive redesign. Our idea was to make it more fun and interactive, and offer a new Willpower gameplay option not related to that of Psykers.<br/><br/>We started with granting the Priests a brand new passive ability: <b>Unshakable Faith</b>. <br/><br/>It gives the Ministorum Priest <b>(StrB+TghB+AgiB+PerB)*2</b> additional <b>WP</b> in combat, and introduces a new resource: <b>Zeal</b>. At the start of combat, the Priest receives a number of Zeal points equal to their WP bonus. For each new enemy attacked with a bolter, melta, flamer, chain, or power weapon, they receive 1 Zeal point. If a xenos or daemon is killed as a result of the attack, they receive 2 additional points.<br/><br/>The stats, talents and abilities for this origin have also changed in the following ways:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The starting bonuses were replaced with +10 WP and +10 Lore (Imperium). <br/></li><li> <b>War Hymn</b> now grants momentum equal to <b>2*Zeal Points</b> and after the effect, the Priest gains a number of <b>Zeal Points</b> equal to WPB. <br/></li><li> <b>Litany of Purification</b> now deals direct damage equal to <b>5*Zeal Points</b> and applies Perplexed to daemon and xenos enemies within 5 cells.<br/></li><li> <b>Litany of Hatred</b> now causes the weapons of the priest and their allies within 5 cell radius to deal additional damage equal to Zeal Points/2 during the round when War Hymn or Furious Recital were used. Against xenos, psyker and daemon enemies, the bonus is doubled.<br/></li><li> <b>Shield of Faith</b> is gone and was replaced with <b>Tenets of Retribution</b> which adds additional WPB/3 damage and WPB% critical damage to bolter weapons, and increases base damage and burn level from flamers and meltas by WPB%. Against xenos, psyker and daemon enemies, the bonus is doubled.<br/></li><li> <b>Flensing Faith</b> now increases Armour Penetration for Chain and Power weapons by WPB%, and their critical hits additionally inflict burning WPB/2 damage. Against xenos, psyker and daemon enemies, the bonus is doubled.<br/></li><li> <b>The Emperor's Blessing</b> is gone and was replaced with <b>The Emperor Protects</b>, which gives the character additional wounds equal to WPB.</li></ul><br/>Since Argenta’s origin is a modified Ministorum Priest, she also inherits all these changes.<br/><br/>For the Emperor!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Commissar Rework</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/31d181b82382a4e19e81cb704969afe1865704a2.jpg"/><br/><br/>For Commissar, we wanted this origin to have much more impact on the battlefield thanks to their motivating presence, and make their iconic weapon type — pistols — way more attractive than they were previously.<br/><br/>For our redesign, we started by adding a brand new passive ability — <b>Iconic Sidearm</b>:<br/><br/>The Commissar's pistol in their primary hand has +15% crit chance, (2 * FelB)% bonus dodge reduction, and deals (BSB * 2)% additional damage.<br/><br/>Here’s what will change:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Weapon Skill</b> will be replaced with <b>Ballistic Skill</b> as a starting bonus.<br/></li><li> <b>At All Costs!</b> was completely redesigned to work as follows: <br/><br/>The Commissar chooses an ally (not a familiar) in their pistol range and shoots them with their primary hand pistol, dealing (100 + Coercion)% damage. This shot ignores armour, deflection, always hits and can't be dodged or blocked. If the ally survives, they deal (Commissar's FELB * BSB)% more damage, have (Commissar's FELB * BSB)% bonus to Dodge and Parry, and also (Commissar's Coercion / 10) bonus to all stats for 1 round. If the ally is incapacitated, all other allies in the Commissar's retinue (except the Commissar) receive this bonus instead and the cooldown of this ability is reset at the start of the Commissar’s next turn. This damage is always critical against Xenos allies.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Duty and Honour!</b> is gone and was replaced by One for the Enemies, Two for the Traitors, which allows the bonuses from the Iconic Sidearm to work on pistols in the left hand.<br/></li><li> <b>Show Them Contempt!</b> gives 1 more baseline resolve and has a new additional effect - If there are no creatures in the 2-cell radius around the Commissar, the Commissar receives +(1 + FELB / 2) resolve.<br/></li><li> <b>Motivation</b> now makes the Commissar receive additional MP when they attack with a pistol, and also gives this bonus to allies in a 2-cell radius. <br/></li><li> <b>Summary Execution</b> was completely redesigned and now doubles both the damage dealt and the bonuses received if the shot is taken into the back of the ally.<br/></li><li> <b>For the Emperor!</b> was also redesigned, and now allows an ally who survived a shot from <b>At All Costs!</b> to restore 30% of their wounds as temporary wounds.</li></ul><br/>Is your faith in the God-Emperor strong enough?!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Navy Officer Rework</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/232fb433d3f56b0b02c027e049ee14cb821fb5df.jpg"/><br/><br/>The last (but certainly not the least!) of the origin reworks is the Navy Officer. Above all, we wanted to improve this origin’s synergy with both Operative and Warrior, while simultaneously boosting or redesigning its weakest aspects. In contrast to the Astra Militarum Commander, which favors ranged gameplay, the Navy Officer is expected to play more into melee, tank, and support roles.<br/><br/>Here’s what we came up with:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> AGI and FEL starting bonuses were replaced with TGH and PER, while Demolition was traded for Carouse, and Commerce for Awareness. This should allow for better synergy with Warriors and Operatives.<br/></li><li> <b>Brace for Impact!</b> now works within a 5-cell radius (was 3-cell) no longer requires allies to remain in that radius for the effect to work. It can now also be used multiple times per combat - it starts with 1 charge, but more charges are awarded the first time the Navy Officer falls below 50% wounds, and the first time an ally falls unconscious.<br/></li><li><b>Do not Falter!</b> is gone and was replaced by <b>Stentorian Voice</b> that causes the enemies in the area of effect from Brace for Impact! to have (-10 WS/BS * for each Archetype taken by the Navy Officer).<br/></li><li><b>Scatter!</b> is gone and was replaced by <b>Evasive Manoeuvres</b>, which causes all allies affected by the Navy Officer’s non-attack abilities or <b>Brace for Impact!</b> gain +%dodge (10 + PERB * 2) for 1 round. Does not stack. In addition, all allies affected by <b>Brace for Impact!</b> don't provoke attacks of opportunity.<br/></li><li> <b>Perfect Timing</b> is gone and was replaced by <b>Fleet Combat Training</b> which causes the Navy Officer to automatically perform a cheapest attack with the secondary weapon after a successful parry or crit with the primary weapon.<br/></li><li> <b>Get off me!</b> was redesigned and now works as follows: During the effect of <b>Brace for Impact!</b>, the Navy Officer's melee attacks knock enemies prone if they fail an AGI test (-10). The Navy Officer also gains access to a new Get off me! ability for 0AP, which pushes enemies within a 2-cell radius back by 2 cells.<br/></li><li> <b>Get Into Cover!</b> will now boost cover efficiency by 30%, and the provided MP will scale with Navy Officer’s TGHB.</li></ul><br/>Abelard approves!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Improving Rare Weapon Gameplay</div><br/>In this update, we wanted to make the use of rare and exotic weapons, such as Webbers, Arc Rifles, Aeldari/Drukhari weapons, and Plasma weapons, more interesting and attractive. <br/><br/><b>To that end, each of these weapon types has received 5 new talents</b> that further boost their effectiveness or utility. Here are some examples:<br/><br/><b>Promethium Treatment </b>– Burning damage taken by enemies immobilised or slowed by a webber is increased by 35% as long as the effect persists.<br/><br/><b>Overclocking Module</b> – increase the arc jump radius by +INTB/5 (min 1) for arc rifles.<br/><br/><b>Path of the Outcast (Yrliet only)</b> – First kill per turn with a single shot from Aeldari Weapon provides an additional attack that turn. <br/><br/><b>Enhanced Splash Area </b>– Plasma Overcharge (area attack) pattern is increased.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/8e1f64a9a81668f8f016f0ee943536b8314faa2b.gif"/><br/><br/>In addition to these new talents, we’ve also rebalanced or updated many existing weapons of these types, added a baseline difficulty scaling for Webber immobilisation saves, and reworked the overheating system for Plasma weapons to be more interactive and fun to build around.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Convictions for Familiars</div><br/>You thought we were done improving the Lex Imperialis content? You were wrong! <br/><br/>Starting with Update 1.5, the Lord Captain’s familiar will now visually change based on the player’s chosen Conviction. Just look at this:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/f5df09e63efa2821138f4b5f3ba9a70e42af9e6e.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/842e449405d88e01ab162a28c8cc227cab4393c6.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/d2ad820ded9adaa4ce15c9338277a88d62ce7061.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/86b87f1b90c0fc18bb5afe17c0667135a02689e9.png"/><br/><br/>They also gained new abilities. <br/><br/>For example, all allies adjacent to an Iconoclast Cyber-Mastiff will now automatically have their wounds healed for an amount equal to the Overseer's Iconoclast Rank at the start of each of their turns, as well as receive a percent damage reduction from all sources equal to the Overseer's Iconoclast Rank + the Familiar's TGH Bonus. Additionally, any Heroic Act used in combat now fully heals the Iconoclast Cyber-Mastiff's wounds.<br/><br/>Your choices now matter more than ever, Lord Captain!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Hiding Equipment</div><br/>Before this update, the only pieces of equipment you could hide were your helmet and backpack/cloak. Following your numerous requests, starting with 1.5, you will be able to separately show or hide other items, as well:<br/><br/>Now, your party will look exactly like you want them to!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/ecffe1a36a37e3d23390f230e3151eca07c9937c.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug fixes</div><br/>In this update, we’ve squashed <b>hundreds</b> of bugs. You can check the patch notes for more details, but here are a few fixes that may be of particular interest to you:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We heard your feedback regarding the numerous problems related to Yrliet, so she has a whole section in the upcoming patch notes devoted to her, with fixes to various issues, including the infamous teleport to Quetza Temer during romance scenes.<br/></li><li> We’ve done an in-depth consistency pass over all the epilogues, fixing narrative contradictions and rare combinations of decisions that caused some slides to appear incorrectly or never appear at all.<br/></li><li> Players will no longer get stuck in the Crematorium at Footfall.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Game Balance</div><br/>And of course, we couldn’t forget about game balance. Brace yourselves!<br/><br/>With the abundance of new tools that became available over the years through DLCs and updates, we’ve received a lot of feedback that progression in the game felt increasingly off, with overlevelling, weird difficulty spikes, build options becoming obsolete, and a general lack of challenge being the biggest complaints.<br/><br/>Tuning the balance in a single player game is always tricky — it’s good for long term health of the game, but can be frustrating in the short term for players whose playstyles are hit when changes are implemented. Because of this, we’ve been a bit hesitant about introducing balance tweaks. But with so many players voicing their concerns, we felt that action needed to be taken.<br/><br/>In order to make this as seamless as possible, <b>we’ve kept the previous patch 1.4 available through the beta branch system.</b><br/><br/>Players who have mods running on the previous version or who simply want to finish their playthroughs without figuring out the new meta <b>can switch to the beta branch to keep the old version:</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/1906c52a5884ba68c2e5756bb7d2073eb4a75975.png"/><br/><br/>Please note that we do not guarantee compatibility of this legacy branch with future content and mods, will not be able to help with any issues or bugs you may encounter while playing it, and will not process any bug reports sent from this branch.<br/><br/>Now, onwards to the changes!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Experience Squish</div><br/>One of the biggest offenders in making combat less fun and challenging is accumulated power creep.<br/><br/>A mix of experience inflation, new combinations found by inventive players, and the numerous new tools added via patches and DLCs can often cause the party to consistently outgrow the difficulty curve of encounters.<br/><br/>To compensate for this growth (which we actually just boosted even further with this update), we’ve slowed down progression by universally <b>increasing the amount of experience required for each level up.</b><br/><br/>This increase is non-linear and will have a bigger impact on higher levels. Typically, this will mean that you arrive at the final battle being ~3-6 levels lower than you were before, which should help to mitigate down the power overgrowth.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/db107b9f4cbd9a9a35a9b10d152d6c65314a06da.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Overtuned Abilities</div><br/>While we know you guys love the havoc that Bladedancers and Executioners from Void Shadows cause on the battlefield, most of you will probably agree that some of their capabilities were a bit… over the top.<br/><br/>A mindblowing 5,000,000 damage per turn from a single character (yes, we’ve really seen this number) is where it gets outright silly, and that’s the point where we stop, admit that this is clearly a design flaw, and do something about it.<br/><br/>To bring the potential of these two archetypes down to more reasonable levels, we’ve implemented the following changes:<br/><br/><b>Bladedancer - Death From Above and Death Waltz</b><br/><br/>After every jump from Death From Above or Death Waltz, the Bladedancer receives a stacking debuff of -20 dodge, -10% STR and -10% PER for each stack, down to -50% until the beginning of their next turn.<br/><br/><b>Executioner - Forced Repentance</b><br/><br/>The target now takes a resistance check (AGI vs Burning and Warp Burn, TGH vs Toxin, Bleeding and Haemorrhage and WP vs Soul Burn and Biophysical Distortion) for every DoT type it has on itself when the ability procs. On a successful resistance check, the effect fails for that DoT type and is not applied. Typically, you’ll see about ~15-30% procs resisted, depending on target type and level.<br/><br/><b>Executioner - Scourging Strikes</b><br/><br/>The formula was changed from (2*StrB) to (StrB + PerB) to reduce scaling and allow for more diverse build options.<br/><br/><b>Executioner - Where it Hurts</b><br/><br/>The effect of this ability is subject to the same resistance checks for every DoT type as described in Forced Repentance, failing to consume that DoT type on successful resistance. The target can also no longer gain new stacks of the DoT effect that was already removed with this ability, until the end of the turn.<br/><br/><b>Executioner - Carnival of Misery</b><br/><br/>This ability was completely redesigned, becoming a single-target melee attack that causes damage equal to 4x the damage from DoTs on the target. DoTs are not consumed by this attack.<br/><br/>The upgrades are as follows:<br/><br/><b>Upgrade 1:</b> Any target affected by Executioner’s DoTs can’t use armour against DoTs. Works on the target of the Carnival of Misery.<br/><b>Upgrade 2:</b> Carnival of Misery effect also procs for other enemies within 6 cells.<br/><b>Upgrade 3:</b> Executioner’s DoTs deal 100% more damage until the end of combat.<br/><b>Upgrade 4:</b> Any DoTs on Executioner himself no longer deal damage, but heal him instead. <br/><br/>Let us know what you think of these changes and whether you feel they’re enough and make the game more fun for you!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9454df828c54bcd78cd585e7dacc2800e4558008.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Colonisation Rebalance</div><br/>Colony events and projects have gone through a major polishing and consistency pass, with many rewards now improved and updated, experience gains adjusted, and a few narrative tweaks introduced. The system will also offer more Conviction and Navigator’s Insight rewards, which may prove very helpful in your journeys across the Koronus Expanse.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Item, Vendor, and Loot Table Rebalance</div><br/>Many items have received adjustments to their stats, abilities, and descriptions for balance and consistency reasons. A lot of them have also been redistributed across the game in the name of smoother progression, as well. Vendor tables have also been significantly updated, offering new purchase options, swapping or replacing some items, and changing their reputation requirements.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Companion Starting Builds</div><br/>Since the launch of the game, we’ve received a lot of feedback about starting builds for companions, especially the late-game ones, with players pointing out a number of choices as being sub-optimal or incompatible with the expected playstyle of a given companion.<br/><br/>We agreed with many of these opinions, and in this update, we have taken the time to review and replace the talents that were found to provide little to no benefit.<br/><br/>Here are a few examples:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Uralon is no longer be an Expert in Chain Weapons he can’t even use;<br/></li><li> Heinrix traded Defensive Manoeuvres for Rigorous Training;<br/></li><li> Ulfar has seen a total of 6 talents replaced, including getting rid of Heavy Armour Proficiency that he has no use for;<br/></li><li> Marazhai had Elusive Shadow, Seize the Advantage, Bringer of Doom, and Lore (Xenos) replaced with Death Whisper, Lethality Heightens, Deadly Calculation, and Carouse, respectively.</li></ul><br/>This should broaden the capabilities of your companions and give even more build options for your party.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s Next?</div><br/>We are done with the highlights, but there are a lot of changes, great and small, that are available in the patch notes. Check them out here.<br/><br/>We have plans for many more exciting new things and QoL improvements in future updates. It will take some time though — first, we want to let the dust settle a bit and see your reaction to the changes we’ve already made, especially those related to game balance.<br/><br/>As always, we look forward to your feedback!<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/edfc58f657815b6f2904399d4a26ad5d8e2a5a43.gif"/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #80 - 1.9.5 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/547875764461112346</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/aea9c2df49a837b602f654f3cf0e3ecc7e86d5e1.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hotfix #80 (1.9.5)</b> is currently rolling out across our platforms. This hotfix contains the following fix:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where changes to the cosmetic skin on the Cyber-Mastiff failed to apply when exiting the Inventory menu.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This will most likely be our last hotfix until the next major update.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
