<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Custom Sale 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4284698870322092511</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The <b>Isometric Custom Sale 2024</b> on Steam has begun. Let’s take a look at the good deals it offers the players!<br/><br/>Please, note that the sale will take place <b>till August 30</b>, so don’t miss the discount!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Get the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game at a <b>35% discount</b> and dive into adventures of the Koronus Expanse. Claim your Warrant of Trade and become a legendary Rogue Trader!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Boost your gaming experience by getting unique in-game items and models, as well as digital add-ons available in Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>35% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/>Get the Season Pass at a <b>35% discount</b> and unlock access to the first Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader DLC – Void Shadows alongside the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><div class="bb_h2">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>Dive into the adventures in the lands of the World Wound and lead the great Crusade! Get the Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous game at a <b>70% discount</b>. Hurry, Drezen City needs its hero.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Your journey doesn't end here. Three DLCs are waiting for you in the Season Pass 1, which you can get with <b>70% off</b>.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>And that’s not all either. Another three wonderful plot DLCs can be obtained as a part of the Season Pass 2! A ton of fun and content awaits you at a pleasant <b>50% discount</b>! <br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about the customisation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4238536974129469039</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Greetings, Space Marines!</div><br/>Today, we’re going to examine customisation in <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> more closely. We’ve received many questions about this topic, and we hope to answer most of them here!<br/><br/>Customisation <b>starts in the Armouring Hall</b>, where you can select your class, your equipment, perks, and, today’s main topic, customise your Space Marine’s armour.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1257ec2f0e113c1f4ff55c25d5d5ced5dff82a73.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/798202ee80c44d5c8f17b16a4958f7159019bb7e.jpg"/><br/>Each class comes with a selection of pre-made armour sets that you’ll have to unlock in PvE or PvP game modes. You can also decide to <b>create your own custom armour set</b>. This is where your creativity shines! Various designs of helm, pauldrons, breastplate, wargear, gauntlets and greaves <b>can be unlocked by playing in multiplayer modes</b>. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/16eefc0a5c7e68f5cd292cc26d344ffaca2dbc5a.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e5692144b24dd5b8cbdef99cf27800bbeec94509.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/40344855832f07abc6aea8018e1c89f04243d8e6.jpg"/><br/>Customisation gets especially interesting when checking out the second tab of the customisation menu, <b>“Astartes Chapters”</b>. Here, <b>you can access presets </b>representing many <b>legendary Space Marine Chapters. </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e56be28792ee543448d97d9f775c28c9232b573c.jpg"/><br/>Once again, you’ll be able to customise your armour set, <b>personalising each part with different paints, emblems, and colour patterns. </b>You’ll unlock these elements in the Heraldry menu to faithfully recreate the colour scheme of your favourite Chapter, or create your own custom design.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/988e7534ef1715482fee6197d0eaaa1e64228530.jpg"/><i>Before…</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/db3ed76c63323aafb2189e548198b285e5c8d901.jpg"/><i>And after! (don’t even say he’s ugly)</i><br/><br/><b>Heretic Astartes</b> characters can also be customised for your PvP matches! Each class corresponds to a <b>specific Traitor Legion </b>(for example, Assault will always be represented by a Night Lords Raptor), but you can change the colours and apply different emblems.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/80832908b59bf5d89b5a43f66414e062a44879cb.jpg"/><br/>Finally, there’s the <b>Astartes Heraldry menu</b>, where <b>you’ll acquire each Chapter’s unique customisation elements. </b>Emblems, colours and armour parts from Adeptus Astartes, Heretic Astartes, Unknown Foundings, First Founding, Second Founding and Successor Chapters! <br/><br/>On launch, <b>over 30 different Chapters have their colours and heraldry available to unlock. </b>Whilst some of them are exclusive to the Season Pass, the majority of them are available to unlock through game progression.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ad19c4af6cf6be107625b23638690b288db8e4ea.jpg"/><br/>And that’s it for the customisation! Don’t hesitate to let us know if you still have questions regarding this feature. We know how important customisation is for any Warhammer fan! We hope you’ll like it and spend hours in these menus to create YOUR very own Space Marine.<br/><br/>See you very soon on the battlefield!<br/><br/><b>The Emperor protects.</b><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4277943470869998987</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/95fe233fbf4fc3cc9de908b4b9928408bf0040c1.jpg"/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Hotfix 5.2.1</div><br/>Hi folks,<br/><br/>We’ve just rolled out hotfix 5.2.1 which addresses the following:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when hovering over specific settlement resource icons.</li></ul>We're also working on a number of additional fixes that we aim to release next week in hotfix 5.2.2.<br/><br/>In the meantime, please continue to report your bugs and issues in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch 5.2 Additional Notes</div><br/>We'd also like to highlight several additional fixes that were implemented in version 5.2, but were previously not communicated within the original patch notes. Some of you may have already encountered these improvements, so hopefully this will help clear up any confusion. We apologise for the oversight and appreciate your understanding.<br/><br/><b>PERFORMANCE</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a softlock that occurred when declaring war while another player was watching a cinematic or flyby in multiplayer.<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare crash when reloading character models in the campaign.</li></ul><b>CAMPAIGN</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the Black Tower was not providing secondary effects when Elspeth was present in the region.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where bankruptcy attrition was not displayed on the army or unit cards affected by it.<br/></li><li> Fort Jakova is now facing the correct direction on the campaign map.<br/></li><li> Fixed the death animation for the Chaos Lord of Tzeentch on a Disc mount.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug in the text for Cylostra's Emerging Terror ability, which incorrectly referred to the Mourngul Haunter hero instead of the Mourngul unit.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with the Red Duke's textures on the campaign map.<br/></li><li> The Bray-Shaman's Familiar follower can now be equipped by both Great Bray-Shamans and regular Bray-Shamans.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Malagor appeared too zoomed out in the character details panel<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where attacking a garrison that had only an army and no characters would prevent the battle panel from appearing.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Durthu's spell skills were using the wrong colours.</li></ul><b>CAMPAIGN AI</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Changed the unit group of the RoR Doomseekers so the CAI correctly classifies them as melee units.</li></ul><b>BATTLE</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a couple of instances where players could not interact with the pre-battle menu.<br/></li><li> Based on community feedback, Dwarf Warriors, Longbeards, and Giant Slayers no longer have their axes tinted by faction colour.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the positioning of some body part assets for the Minotaurs of Khorne; they no longer have gaps in their necks.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the unit cards of some units with shrapnel projectiles displayed the shrapnel range instead of their actual range.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with the Beastmen faction colours.<br/></li><li> War Wagons now use the correct textures for both regular and RoR versions.<br/></li><li> The Silver Bullets and Sigmar's Sons now have the correct coloured clothing.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Sarthorael the Everwatcher model was missing in battle.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Empire Knights had black colouring on their head and leg armor pieces, in contrast to the rest of their silver armor.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the wrong battle map would load when fighting near mountains in Ulthuan.</li></ul><b>BATTLE AI</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where AI-controlled armies would not attack each other when the player was reinforcing one of them in battle.<br/></li><li> Improved the AI's use of high ground.<br/></li><li> Adjusted AI decision making when defending during an ambush battle to increase priority of fleeing the field.<br/></li><li> Increased the priority of vulnerable artillery pieces when the AI selects targets in battle.</li></ul><b>BATTLE ANIMATION</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the root of the Orc Labourer's defense animation was misaligned.<br/></li><li> The Grace of Quai Yin (Celestial Dragon Crossbows) now display their crossbows while moving.<br/></li><li> Greenskin Trolls now hold their weapons correctly in walking and attack animations.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Hochland Long Rifles sword did not disappear when sheathed.</li></ul><b>AUDIO</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added crackle audio for the Chaos Lord of Tzeentch when mounted on a warhorse or chariot.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/>Until next time, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">—The <i>Total War</i> Team</div><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 12:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 13 - Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4248669523820900459</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/36adaedce51f2a145616fe873621e5943b98d41c.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3fc4b95081ad902ec15a85ea75636faf38b2b8dc.png"/><br/><br/>The Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy is an Orkish marvel, powered by the wild energy of squigs. Armed to the teeth, it tears through enemies with relentless, unpredictable fury. <br/><br/>This is a defensive vehicle with healing capabilities. Stand behind your allies and aid them. If you like seeing your team shine, this is the vehicle for you. <br/><br/>In Speed Freeks the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy is best used behind your team near the front lines. Keeping your allies alive. Be careful, with your healing capabilities you become one of the most important pieces on your team. Expect the enemies to come for you, so stay near your team to keep alive. <br/><br/>The speed of the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy is slightly below average, which it makes up for with an above average health value. As such, positioning is extremely important, as it's harder to escape from dangerous situations. Save your dash ability for when you need it or keep up a high enough average speed with good boost management so that you are hard to pin down. Or you could just always hide behind your allied Grot Mega Tank! <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7d957f866a631bf68a3e02f08a44f3cffbad59de.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c1b24cbb0d9318993ee0b23e4b716f3025423e0a.png"/><br/><b>Squig Launchas</b> <br/>Boom Squigs burst forth from the Ork-wielded Squig Launcha <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d56ccd56cf47dec5a984be3d69ca544608ca1223.png"/><br/><b>Grub Squig</b> <br/>The Squig Launcha fires a bunch of Grub Squigs that heal allies <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d58a954880fe0a908aca74f7ce16748d14a0e6f7.png"/><br/><b>Squig Mine</b> <br/>Drop three Squig Mines that stick to anything they touch and explode when enemies get too close<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/10f81d44f5ff8313ee330da0d2389ace04f7e7fa.png"/><br/><b>Dash</b> <br/>The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming at will determine where the vehicle will go. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/79d5ca72d85b8f02c2df7e75a9d2f01a7d1e30eb.png"/><br/><br/>Staying alive as the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy is your highest priority. Hide behind your team, stay near someone who will protect you, and make sure you know where you’re going if someone comes for you. This allows you to keep everyone else alive. If you are there, it’s harder to take down your team. <br/><br/>Keep an eye on your team’s health and which enemies could become a threat to you. Keep track of their Deffkilla Wartrike players, and Looted Wagon to stay out of harm. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0e9d54fcbed52d517a0c4f46df5587f18a5e4f6f.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-ups</div><b>Grot Mega Tank –</b> This beefy boy will keep you safe. Keep him alive and it’ll be dangerous for the enemies to come close, as they will have to avoid its plough. You can also use the Grot Mega Tank as a wall from enemies. <br/><br/><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon –</b> Keeping a Snazzwagon alive can be your ticket to winning the game. Snazzwagon deals heavy damage to anyone who gets close to you, and a good Snazzwagon will realize when there’s an enemy coming for you and use their Billowing Fumes to protect you. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against </div><b>Booomdakka Snazzwagon –</b> With it being one of the slower vehicles, the Boomdakka Snazzwagon will struggle to catch and take you down. While you can keep your mob alive and negate the damage output from its firepower. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weak Against </div><b>Deffkilla Wartrike –</b> This vehicle will be trying to go for you in every situation they’re allowed to. It’ll sneak into your Mob, take you out, and get back out again. Make sure you’re always near full health and if you aren’t, stay back and keep an eye on it so that you don’t get jumped. <br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon –</b> This tank will try to shoot you from afar. If you’re not careful you will always be driving around with half health because of your foes Looted Wagon at the back. Make sure to use the terrain and your larger vehicles to make it impossible for the Looted Wagon to get a clear line of sight on you. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b04aceaa0796094da124ac638049eb6d8ef6b28b.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Versus Beta August Test is LIVE NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4250921238101303141</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QvtxrK0c8As?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div><br/>Starting now, the <b>Versus Beta August Test (or BAT!) is live!</b> If you haven't already, make sure to sign up by heading to Vermintide 2's Steam Store page and hitting 'Request Access' on the Playtest!<br/><br/><a class="bb_link" href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/552500/Warhammer_Vermintide_2/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/f50095364f3c45bf9921e5f3d1973d1eec4e7a44.png"/></a><br/><br/>As mentioned before, <b>this Beta is open to ANYONE</b>, even non-owners of Vermintide 2! Make sure to spread the word to anyone who might be interested! Tell your friends, tell your family, tell your pets, tell strangers!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/731d03f5dcbe0aa23cc7185eb7e64bcc9d99e73e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What is Versus?</div>Versus is an <b>upcoming <u>free</u> new Game mode</b> for Warhammer: Vermintide 2! It’s an asymmetrical PvP+E experience pitting up to 4 Heroes against our AI enemies and up to 4 special players, what we call Pactsworn. A match will take place over several rounds, with each team swapping places between playing the Heroes and the Pactsworn each round. To simplify, each round consists of the Hero team playing a regular game akin to Adventure mode, while the Pactsworn players have to stop them.<br/><br/><i>Learn more about playing as the <b>Heroes</b></i><br/><i>Learn more about playing as the <b>Pactsworn</b> (yes-yes!)</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What's new for this Beta?</div>Plenty! We have two big features to highlight: <b>Matchmaking changes</b> and <b>The Horde</b> ability. Alongside that we've also done various <b>balance adjustments</b> and <b>quality of life changes</b> based on previous tests' feedback!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Horde Ability</div>One of the bigger features in the Beta is the Pactsworns’ new Horde Ability, available to each of the Pactsworn players on their own individual cooldown. When fully charged and ready, <b>Pactsworn players are able to rally a small horde, spawning a group of AI enemies fighting for them onto the battlefield.</b> This means that Packmasters can summon cover-kin to blend in for sneaky charges, Ratling Gunners can distract Heroes with melee fodder before laying down fire, <i>or the team can sync up and trigger all Hordes at the same time and overwhelm the opposition.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Cooldown Reduction:</b> While the ability re-charges slowly over time, it is possible to quicken the progress by damaging the enemy team. Play well, and you’ll be able to send barrage after barrage.<br/></li><li> <b>Carry over:</b> Ability bar progress is carried over between deaths.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Matchmaking</div>In the Alphas there were no guardrails preventing (for instance) solo queuing new players to meet an experienced four-stack, meaning that the experience could vary wildly from session to session. This, along with other reported issues, led to us reworking our matchmaking systems. <br/><br/>The new system should, on average, result in <b>lower queue times</b>, finding servers closer to you (resulting in <b>lower latency</b>), and <b>more even games</b> (for example, by trying to pair together premade groups). It will also allow us to more easily monitor the matchmaking in real-time and act quicker if we notice that something isn't working as intended.<br/><br/>It won’t stop variously skilled players from meeting up occasionally, but at least the system should be able to favour other match setups. We hope that this will lead to more balanced and fun games, as well as lay a better foundation for future feedback.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Features and Gameplay Changes</div><div class="bb_h3">Gamepad Support</div>Controllers/Gamepads are now properly supported for Versus! Now that we are rounding up the core set of features we can finalize button assignments and focus on input tweaking to bring the controller experience up to par. For gamepad gamers out there, please let us know any feedback you have about the new implementation in this Beta!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pactsworn HUD and UI</div>We have re-done a lot of the Pactsworns’ heads-up-display in terms of art, gameplay and general quality of life.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> New <b>Horde Ability progress bar.</b><br/></li><li> <b>Updated Health bars.</b><br/></li><li> <b>Ability Bar:</b> Each Pactsworn has all of their available moves and abilities listed in the HUD, with cooldowns and input clearly shown in an effort to make the characters easier to pick  play.<br/></li><li> <b>Updated enemy health bars:</b> Wounds, Streak Damage, Regular– and Temporary HP are now displayed directly above the Heroes’ heads.<br/></li><li> <b>Ally information:</b> Your fellow Pactsworns’ respawn timers are now displayed above their heads along with their names, hopefully making teamwork easier to pull off.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Ping adjustments</div>The ping/tagging system has been adjusted to be more responsive, particularly noticeable for the Hero side. As in Adventure mode, <b>pings should now be instantaneous and prioritize marking enemies better.</b> This should make the system more responsive, intuitive and fluid, <b>while still retaining the ability to place world markers and use the Social Wheel for more detailed callouts.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Health Draughts and Medical Supplies</div>We are reconsidering how we should view health pick-ups in Versus. We want healing to have intent and consequences, and to be something that Pactsworn are able to make use of as well.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Level placement:</b> <b>We have moved all healing supplies to be more prominent on each level’s main path.</b> By becoming easy to see “hot spots”, we should be able to create even more interesting and intense scenarios, inviting the Pactsworn to use them for ambushes.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Other Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Updated the visual effects on the Warpfire Thrower and the Poison Wind Globadier.</b> On top of looking better, these new VFX should better reflect the effective Area of Effect of their abilities when active.<br/></li><li> <b>Adjusted objectives in Against the Grain</b> to deter speedrunning and running ahead of the team.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Balance Changes</div><div class="bb_h3">Poison Wind Globadier</div>The Globadier has remained an undisputed menace throughout the Alpha period, and we still want to keep him that way, but things will be a little different for the Beta. <b>We've lowered the base damage of a globe's gas, but also added a ramping damage curve to Poison Wind tick damage</b>, meaning damage increases exponentially over time.<br/>Mindlessly throwing globes won’t be as effective anymore, but catching unfortunate Heroes in a bad spot will create just as much chaos as before.<br/><div class="bb_h3">Ratling Gunner</div>The Ratling Gunner has received a healthy check-up on some basic values that should <b>make him a bit more dexterous and effective at range</b> (where he should be shining best).<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Decreased start up and reload duration.<br/></li><li> Increased effective range and bullet speed.<br/></li><li> Decreased bullet spread.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Packmaster</div>When a Packmaster hooks a Hero and walks off an edge, <b>the Hero will now hang from the ledge instead of falling to their doom.</b> Was fun while it lasted, hehehe.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Bile Troll</div>Introduced in our last test, the Bile Troll is a rare, playable boss that one random player will get to play as each round. He is large, in charge, and full of gross green stuff. For the Beta, we have focused on getting in a bit more polish and making him more fun to use.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Adjusted movement acceleration</b> to give a more sluggish and weighty feel to the character, as well as to limit twitchy movement.<br/></li><li> <b>Reworked the Bile Vomit attack</b> on a few different points:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The ability now has the option to be charged and held, letting players aim more accurately and prepare their attack. Hold the F key to start charging and let go to puke.<br/></li><li> Added an aim indicator to better display where the vomit will land and the rough ground area that gets covered.</li></ul></li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/>As always, we hope you have tons of fun playing Versus! <b>Enjoy the Beta, invite your friends, and give us ALL of your feedback!</b> We rely on you, your experiences and your opinions to perfect this exciting new game mode!<br/><br/><i>If you have any more doubts or questions, check out our FAQ.</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
