<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #42 (1.4.2) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097474985883</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1a637bfb339920cd74ea325ed0192297010bde15.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey there Devoted Rejects,</div>Hotfix #42 (1.4.2) is out now on Steam and it will shortly be out on our other platforms.<br/><br/>(<b>Note</b>: <i>It takes a little bit of time after the release of the hotfix before the old servers are disconnected and players are migrated over to the new one.</i>) :pray:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Combat</div><div class="bb_h3">Shooters</div>Reverting the following Shooter Changes from the 1.4.0 Patch:<br/><i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Scab Shooters now have a tighter shot spread, making them more threatening at range. While they still have ranged damage falloff, they will be more consistent in how they hit players at range.<br/></li><li> Additionally, Scab/Dreg shooters will now stay in cover longer (and remain exposed longer) with a reduced cooldown between sprays, making cover-taking enemies more of a threat but also enhancing the viability of player weapons that apply suppression.</li></ul></i><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are pulling back a few of the Enemy changes from the Previous Patch, as they were a bit too oppressive.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased the range of what would be considered Close Range: 8m to 12.5m.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>In Patch #13 (Class Rework), we changed Close Range from 15m to 8m, and in return increased the power of Blessings triggered only in Close Range e.g. Fire Frenzy and Deathspitter. We did this because we wanted to differentiate the Close Range Gunplay a bit more from the Far Range one. This was considered by many as a bug, though it was an intended change. However, we have re-evaluated that change, and while we after some extensive testing still believe 15m is a little too far, we think 12.5m is a justified increase. This will also increase the power of specific Talents tied to Close Damage such as Veteran’s ‘Close Quarters Killzone’ and Zealot’s ‘Anoint in Blood’ which we will monitor closely.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div><b>Tigrus Mk XV Heavy Eviscerator</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bumped the speed for windup timings of Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attacks:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Heavy 1 chained from base start or Light 4: 0.4 (unchanged)<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.76 to 0.65<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 chained from Light 1 / Heavy 1 from 0.85 to 0.65<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 chained from Light 3 / push follow-up from 0.6 to 0.4.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i> The windup timing for Heavy attacks varied significantly depending on which attack they were chained from. The windup timings should now be more aligned with each other, and in general shorter to reward players accessing attacks further down the chain instead of resetting the combo.</i><br/><br/><b>Artemia Mk III Purgation Flamer</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bumped power distribution for primary and secondary direct fire:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primary burst attack from (10,20) to (15,30)<br/></li><li> Secondary continuous attack from (30,50) to (60,100)</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Damage scales with distance and time inside the cloud. Burn damage and max stacks are unaffected by the change.</i><br/><b>Ogryn Pickaxes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Normalised the attack ranges for all marks.<br/></li><li> Slightly tuned the damage window timing for specific attacks to be more accurate with the attack animation.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes*</div><br/><b>*Dev Note:</b> <i>You can view the exact number value changes at the bottom of these patch notes.</i><br/><br/><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Slightly reduced reach for the Light 1 attack.<br/></li><li> Improved reach for the Light 2, Light 3, Heavy 1 attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Push follow-up attack.</li></ul><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved reach of the Light 1, Light 2, Light 3 attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Heavy 1, Heavy 2 attacks.</li></ul><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved reach of the Light 1, Light 2, Light 3, Light 4, Light special follow-up, Heavy special follow-up attacks.<br/></li><li> Greatly improved reach for the Heavy 1, Heavy 2 attacks</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The reach of the attacks for Ogryn Pickaxes differed significantly between marks or even different attacks in the same mark, and in several cases it was shorter than the attack range of other Ogryn weapons.<br/><br/>We performed a pass on all attacks, normalising the ranges and in general bumping up the values to make sure that these two-handed weapons always have the reach appropriate to their size.<br/><br/>We also fine-tuned the time windows where some specific attacks are active, to be more aligned to their attack animations.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><b>Clandestium Gloriana</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with the valkyrie in the outro cutscene.<br/></li><li> Did some various optimisations to assets.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players were unable to interact with pickups under a pile of snow.<br/></li><li> Fixed some visual bugs during the horizontal shuttle ride.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where deploying a med kit or ammo box would have it go through the floor of the horizontal shuttle.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>However, there is still a known issue where it lands a bit further back than where you deployed it, so for now be careful to not deploy it too far back in the transport.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with a small corner before the middle even where players would get instantly killed when standing there.<br/></li><li> Side missions like grimoires and tomes should now count correctly.<br/></li><li> Fixed a location where bots would often fall off the side of the map.<br/></li><li> Fixed so enemies can now reach you inside the elevator.</li></ul><b>Excise Vault Spireside-13</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed wall unit lacking collision allowing players to leave gameplay space.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are aware that in bulk-lifter-32 some pick-ups cannot be collected, and one is floating. We will be addressing these in the next hotfix.</i><br/><br/><b>Enclavum Baross</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some VO lines at the end of Enclavum Baross did not trigger at all.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Additional Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue related to memory that caused stalls and crashes or disconnects for players (especially those playing with mods).<br/></li><li> Fixed issue which caused penances tracking mission types not to progress.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Any missions that were completed during this time will not be added after this fix. We apologise for not catching this sooner.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Torment blessing did not work on the Branx Pickaxe special poke attack.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where “Crosshair Type” user settings didn’t revert when using the “Reset to Default Settings” button.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Force Staves incorrectly had their crosshairs overridden when using anything but the “Weapon Specific” option of “Crosshair Type”.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with candle flame blocking line of sight with the Magistratum Bolt Pistol (Blessed) skin. Candle flame effect disabled until we move the candle slightly, it will be reenabled in a later patch.<br/></li><li> Fixed crash when trying to equip a trinket with the Magistratum Bolt Pistol (Blessed) skin equipped.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue which caused some players to need to reassign keybinds, or being unable to assign some keybinds at all.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where heavy melee attacks would be cancelled to light attacks if an Ability was used during the windup of the attack.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This fix does reintroduce an issue where players cannot activate the Zealots ‘Chorus of Spiritual Fortitude’ or the Psykers Telekine Field/Dome’ Abilities while charging a heavy attack. We decided this was better than leaving this issue unaddressed. We will investigate potential solutions that address these issues without affecting other abilities.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the text for Psyker’s “Malefic Momentum” where it wasn’t localised.<br/></li><li> Fixed missing pipes on Zealot’s headgear, Magistratum Scrivener’s helmet.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where part of the mannequin was missing when viewing Magistratum Mk II Patrol Uniform.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the pipes on Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress were deformed for female characters.<br/></li><li> Fixed additional clipping issues on the pipes for the Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress.<br/></li><li> Fixed some visual issues with the Magistratum Mk II Patrol Uniform knee pad stretching when emoting.<br/></li><li> Removed the glass material in the slit of the Magistratum Riot Shield skin.</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>This is to fix an issue where several visual effects were not correctly rendered through the shield slit due to conflicting transparency with the glass material.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed clipping issues with the glove on Scrutiniser’s Parade Dress.<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping issues for the Baross Patrol Armour (XXXXL).<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping issues for the Enforcer Patrol Helmet (XXXXL).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Tome Xenos accessory did not properly align with the Magistratum Mk V Patrol Armour cosmetic.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes for Pickaxes (Numbers)</div><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.2<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window start from 12/30 to 10/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.55<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.35<br/></li><li> Light 3 damage window end from 22/30 to 24/30<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.5 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Push follow-up range mod from 2 to 2.5.</li></ul><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window start from 9/30 to 12/30<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window end from 15/30 to 16/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.5<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.4.</li></ul><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Light 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Light 1 damage window end from 15/30 to 16/30<br/></li><li> Light 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.4<br/></li><li> Light 3 range mod from 1.25 to 1.38<br/></li><li> Light 4 range mod from 1.25 to 1.45<br/></li><li> Heavy 1 range mod from 1.25 to 1.6<br/></li><li> Heavy 2 range mod from 1.25 to 1.67<br/></li><li> Light special follow-up range mod from 1.25 to 1.35<br/></li><li> Heavy special follow-up range mod from 1.3 to 1.5.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.2.0.30 is out!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999239245825</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/>A minor hotfix has arrived. Blessed be the Tech-Priests who tirelessly eliminate the vile scrap code!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><b>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</b><br/><br/>If you play with mods, use them at your own risk. Mods can change your save unpredictably and we won't be able to restore it.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The list of changes:</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sometimes the entire party would visit the date night of <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Heinrix</span></span> and Lord Capitan. Due to this violation of privacy, the date wouldn't happen - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Saving and loading the game after trading restored the vendor's assortment - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Locations</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Aebys and Marazhai</span></span> did not approach the edge of the platform in <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>the Anatomical Opera</span></span> which made it impossible to start a dialogue with them - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Animations</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ulfar had troubles with his animations - fixed; <br/></li><li>Enemies preferred to roll into the cover after attack instead of stepping there - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h1">User Interface</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Hide Non-Wearable option worked alternatively - fixed; <br/></li><li>Scrolling failed to work in the trading interface - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Audio</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sound stuttered on Kiava Gamma - fixed; </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Localization</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Russian texts have been updated in accordance with the balance changes. Also, the talents descriptions were updated; </li></ul><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Story: "Need to Know"</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097468296246</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4d48966e598cf862a8284c7971b0ccfbc8a02770.jpg"/><br/><br/>The Rejects didn’t have a motto, but if they did, thought Naibert, it would be “nothing is ever as simple as it looks.” That, or “trust nothing.”<br/><br/>	Naibert wasn’t in the business of trust. The Universe had bitten his arse too many times for him to let his guard down. He was ex-Militarum, infantry, marksman speciality. He’d always had a sharp temper, which is why he’d smacked that officer, and landed in the stockade, and thus wound up in the Rejects.<br/><br/>	When Naibert had pulled the mission that morning, Rannick had taken him to one side. Iven Rannick himself, the toxic old interrogator. Naibert didn’t trust Rannick, but he knew the man had real clout. That Inquisitorial rosette, for start. But more than that, Naibert felt that Rannick was the real power on the Mourningstar. Everyone, high and low, deferred to the great Inquisitor Grendyl; Atoma Prime was Grendyl’s operation. But no one had ever seen Grendyl, not seen seen, not in the flesh. At best, he was a servitor chassis projecting an inconsistent hololith. Naibert didn’t trust Grendyl, or the idea of Grendyl. Maybe there was no Grendyl at all, or maybe the lack of presence was part of the act. The Inquisition never told anybody everything, especially not the dog-soldier Rejects, and if they did tell you something, it was always a small fragment of the truth. They liked to keep people in the dark, uninformed, data-rationed, information starved. “Need to know”, that’s what they said.<br/><br/>	But Rannick… Naibert understood Rannick. He was a flesh and blood man. He was present. He was the man in charge. He was also a bastard, but you couldn’t have everything, Naibert had known worse. He had smacked worse.<br/><br/>	Rannick had seldom spoken to Naibert directly. When he’d finished explaining to Naibert what he required, he’d smiled, that creepy smile, and said, “It’s a matter of trust, you see?”<br/><br/>	“You can trust me,” Naibert had told him. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>The drop was a hard one. A new area - Inter-Zone Void Sector Omega-12 or something. Unknown territory, that’s what mattered, barely mapped. They were going in blind. Plus, it was one of Hadron’s ops. Hadron Omega-Seven. She was in charge, and coming with them. Naibert didn’t like the Mechanicus tech-priest at all. Snide, mean, nit-picking, and arrogantly intelligent. It seemed she always had an agenda of her own, and she wouldn’t share it, because obviously no one in the warband was smart enough to comprehend, but then she’d still get pissy when you didn’t understand what was needed.<br/><br/>	Borovitch was behind the stick of their Valk. That made Naibert uneasy too. Borovitch was all right, but Masozi was the best. Every Reject knew that. However, it seemed Masozi had another drop to attend to. That either meant Masozi knew there was something nasty about the Inter-Zone drop, and had chosen to avoid it, or Rannick knew, and had assigned a more expendable pilot. <br/><br/>	Dropping, the something nasty became obvious. The Inter-Zone was a voidspace between hive levels, a sub-zero voidspace, biting cold and long abandoned. It was a cluster of ancient complexes - maybe research or maintenance - pretty much suspended in a deep, dark circulation gulf between occupied hive zones. A long drop, if you lost your footing, and there was more than enough ice-cake to make that happen. A long drop, and way too much time to review the series of bad choices you called your life before you hit the bottom.<br/><br/>	If there was a bottom at all.<br/><br/>	They exited the Valk’s ramp, the engines screaming above in ‘settle’ mode. Hadron led the way, eager. Naibert took up the rear, lugging his longlas and pulling off the weatherproof sleeve. His job was hazard watch. Spot for trouble, and pick it off with his rifle before it got too close.<br/><br/>	It was treacherous finding a way in. The metal decks gleamed with ice, and there was a gale blowing up the void from below. You could feel the cold in your bones, despite the heated undersuits they’d been issued. Someone, maybe Veedra, speculated that the whole space was a coolant sink designed to bleed excess heat off… whatever the complex was, but Hadron told her to shut up, so that was the end of that. The old need to know.<br/><br/>	Most of the power was off. They had to hand-crank hatches open, or reconnect voltaic trunking, or simply cut with torches. Where there was power, Hadron punched in archaic codes and opened hatchways as easily as if she was back home on the Mourningstar.<br/><br/>	“How come she knows the codes?” Veedra asked him, a whisper.<br/><br/>	“She knows what she needs to know, I guess,” he replied. He didn’t like it either. Hadron had never been here before. He could tell that from the eagerness and fascination with which the tech-priest greeted each new chamber. But it also felt like she knew her way around. Naibert saw some old Adeptus Mechanicus icons las-etched into the bulkhead plating. Maybe that explained it. Hadron’s people had made the place, or at least the template it had been built from. The tech-priest had been here before, just not this here. <br/>	They lost Dronica crossing a walkway bridge. A pane of ice just went out from under him and away he went, limbs flailing as he dropped into the blue gloom below. Naibert could see the tiny light of the lamp clamped to Dronica’s bodyrig still spinning long after his body became invisible. His scream, fading, lingered longer than the speck of light.<br/><br/><br/>They reached what Hadron evidently had decided was the goal, a central part of the complex clinging to the void’s artificial cliff face. She entered first, and powered the place up. It was warm in there. Warmer, anyway. Warm and lit.<br/><br/>	Naibert benefitted from neither. He’d taken up a position outside, on one of the icy service gantries. It afforded him a good, long look back over the walkways and platforms they’d used on their approach. He huddled up, tweaked up the heating of his suit liner, settled his longlas, and adjusted the scope. If anything was following them, anything down here in the dark they didn’t want to meet, he’d see it coming from a distance and put a hotshot through it. Two, if it was persistent.<br/><br/>	He fiddled with the little clamp-on unit he’d fitted to the side of his scope before the drop, and made sure it was running. A little pict unit, to record everything he saw through his high-gain scope. The unit had been a gift. Naibert played his aim across the frost-caked facility below, studying the silence, the cold, the abandoned, dead chambers and silos. The chasm wind stirred flakes of ice, and blew little flurries of powder into the air, making Naibert flinch, mistaking them for movement. <br/><br/>	Nothing. Not a sign of those murdering traitors, nor any sign of the other things, the uglier things, the things that were harder to put a name to. He watched his breath smoke. He listened to the upwind howl, which still seemed to have Dronica’s scream in it.<br/><br/>	Once he was confident it was quiet, he wriggled around and looked back at the complex where Hadron was working. He could see the lit window ports looking out over the gulf. He dragged his longlas round, and took up a fresh position, as though he was lining up a shot on his own team.<br/><br/>	He could see them, once he got the scope settled in. The pict unit was whirring away. He could make out the other Rejects who’d dropped with him, waiting in the outer chambers of the facility, nervous, weapons ready. Veedra was pacing. He panned around, adjusting focus. There was Hadron. He could see her through the windows of the inner chamber. The tech-priest was working alone. She’d left the rest of the team waiting outside so they couldn’t watch her.<br/><br/>	But he could. He could see her quite clearly and close up through his sniper scope. He could see her working at ancient consoles that hadn’t been used in decades, waking up systems that hadn’t been awake in centuries, accessing cold, dormant data and loading it onto her dataslates. <br/><br/>	Naibert had no idea what she was doing, or why. He didn’t understand or recognise the machines the tech-priest was working on. He was a marksman. He didn’t have that kind of technical knowledge. But he knew one thing. No, two things. The first was that, whatever she was doing, it was secret. It was either too sensitive and classified for others to be allowed to observe, or so forbidden that even she shouldn’t be doing it. It was a secret she didn’t want anyone to know about.<br/><br/>	The second thing was he was recording it all.<br/><br/>	Naibert watched her work through the scope. The tech-priest had no idea he could see her. She was such a strange individual, cranky and obsessive, not really human at all in his opinion, her organic life subsumed into the way of the machine. What did that do to a person’s mind? What kind of obsessions and agendas did it breed? He—<br/><br/>	Naibert recoiled. Hadron was looking right at him. She had turned from her work and stared straight out of the window, straight down his scope as though they were eye to eye. She knew. She’d somehow seen him or sensed him or—<br/><br/>	No. Not him. Something else. Naibert turned fast, in time to see the figures on the lower walkways behind him. Six of them, heavy set, armed and armoured, hurrying towards him. Moebian Sixth. Traitor Guard. They hadn’t seen him yet.<br/><br/>	He cued his vox.<br/><br/>	“Incoming,” he whispered.<br/><br/>	Then he lined up his first shot. Lead target, centre mass. He wondered how many of them he could pick off before they returned fire.<br/><br/>	Breathing rate slow, centre mass lined up, nice and easy, on the exhale…<br/><br/>	His first shot cracked.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>“Come in,” said Rannick. “Close the door. An eventful day, I hear?”<br/><br/>	 Naibert nodded.<br/><br/>	“We lost three,” he said. “But we took five of them down, plus another four from the squad that moved in when we were going for extraction. Close call, but Borovitch got us out.”<br/><br/>	Rannick listened, and took a seat behind his desk. His private office was a strange, gloomy sanctum. Naibert had never been in there before. He felt more vulnerable than he’d been on that iced gantry under fire.<br/>	Rannick held out his hand.<br/><br/>	Naibert reached into his coat pocket and took out the pict unit. He’d detached it from his scope during the flight home. He handed it back to its owner.<br/><br/>	“Everything’s there, just like you asked,” he said. “Everything I saw. She was doing something, and she didn’t want anybody seeing it.”<br/><br/>	“That’s good, Naibert,” said Rannick, turning the pict unit over in his hands. “That’s good work. Hadron had no idea she was being recorded?”<br/><br/>	“No,” said Naibert.<br/><br/>	“That’s for the best. I picked the right man for the job then. Someone trained to observe, and trained to be discrete about it.”<br/><br/>	“Do you know what she was up to, Interrogator?” Naibert asked.<br/><br/>	Rannick looked at him, one quizzical eyebrow raised.<br/><br/>	“I might, Naibert,” he replied, “especially after I review this. Do you?”<br/><br/>	“No,” said Naibert.<br/><br/>	“Good,” said Rannick. “You don’t need to.”<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take a Behind the Scenes Tour with the Developers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4225021101192881894</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Marines! 🫡</div><br/>We're happy to bring you a <b>Developer Diary</b> with you today, giving you an inside look at all the hard work that went into creating the hotly-anticipated <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>. And this BTS Dev Diary has some <b>fresh gameplay shots</b>!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Check out our Developer Diary now!</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HWR2vF_i9Xo?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3">A true passion project for everyone at Saber and Focus</div><br/>From Clive Standen playing Lieutenant Titus to the art team, devs, and QA teams, today’s video tells the story of the team’s commitment to delivering a game that lives up to its predecessor, of the fans’ expectations, and true to the immeasurable scale of war in the 41st Millenium. <br/><br/>Be it the brutal efficiency of the Space Marines, the massive game environments, and the unique tech behind the Tyranid swarms… every part of making <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> represents the culmination of what we, at Saber and Focus, have strived for many years.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Don't miss the June community update!</div>As the release of the game approaches, we will gradually share more info with you all through community updates, at the end of each month. Click here to read the June community update! In case you missed it, click here to also read the May community update.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pre-order the game today and become one of the lucky ones to play up to 4 days earlyyyy! 😎</div><br/>Pre-orders are open on Steam and at participating retail stores. Besides the Collector’s Edition (exclusive to the Focus Store), three Editions are also available for pre-order: Standard, Gold, and Ultra Edition. Pre-ordering the Gold or Ultra Edition will let you get <b>exclusive access to the full game on September 5, four days before release</b>!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/67eca0e2fd64688d7ff3f005d9c2e21102254a7e.jpg"/> <br/><br/><b>Heed the call of battle when <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> launches September 9, 2024.</b><br/><br/>Sign up as a Focus member to get exclusive news and upcoming special offers for <i>Space Marine 2</i> and the whole Focus catalog!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - June Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4225021101189985804</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/>Your growing enthusiasm regarding <i>Space Marine 2</i> has us incredibly motivated. Last week, you discovered our <b>detailed Gameplay Overview Trailer</b>: a 6-minute in-depth look into the game modes. It features creative director Oliver Hollis-Leick, who dissects the 3 different game modes: Campaign, Operations and Eternal War!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In <b>Campaign mode</b>, lasting approximately 12 hours, you embody Lieutenant Titus, right after the events of the first opus. Titus fights alongside his Battle-Brothers Chairon and Gadriel against swarms of Tyranids and Chaos. <br/></li><li> In <b>Operations mode</b>, you can either play with 2 mates or solo in endlessly replayable PvE action. Face swarms of Tyranids on 6 different maps to defend the Imperium.<br/></li><li> Last but not least, in <b>Eternal War</b>, fight in heated 6v6 matches in 3 different classic game modes: Annihilation, Seize Ground and Capture &amp; Control).</li></ul> → Annihilation is Team Deathmatch mode: two teams compete against each other. Each take down earns your team 1 point. First team to reach 50 points wins the match. <br/><br/>→ Seize Ground is a domination mode: Two teams compete to keep control of one zone that’s moving throughout the match. Keeping control of the zone grants your team points. The winner is the team that reaches the total amount of points given. <br/><br/>→ Capture &amp; Control is a King of the Hill mode: There are 3 specific zones in the arena and each team fights to control them. Gaining and keeping control of a zone grants your team points. Be the first to obtain a certain amount of points to win the match. <br/><br/><b>Watch it here:</b><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5tqDxvpzsKM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3">To go further</div><br/>This month we delivered a featurette focused on <b>Planet Kadaku</b>, showcasing more detailed elements of the game. These videos aim at giving players a more extensive look into small features of the game. You can expect more content like this coming in the following months so stay tuned and follow our socials to make sure you don’t miss them.<br/><br/>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OFh06AnY6Qk<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h3">Dedicated servers</div><br/>We’re happy to confirm that <b><i>Space Marine 2</i> will feature dedicated servers</b>, enhancing your experience in multiplayer. We have prepared a bunch of servers in North America, Europe, Latin America, Asia, and Oceania.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/568f2b3756d303ccde678a02b3debeaef1e1a178.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">About a Beta</div><br/>Over the past few weeks, we have seen incredible excitement around the game, both online and at the shows during the North American tour. Our teams at Focus and Saber have been truly blown away by your passion, and we’ve loved seeing the fan art, reactions and memes that you have shared so far.<br/><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is almost ready. We are now entirely focused on optimization, polish and fixing remaining issues ahead of launch on September 9. This means we will not run a public online beta, as it would take the development teams away from preparing for the full launch, and our priority is to ensure the best possible experience at release.<br/><br/>We know this is disappointing news for some of you. As a thank you to those interested in participating, players who registered via the online signup before June 28, 2024, midnight Paris Time, will receive the limited Bolt Pistol skin below.<br/><br/>We appreciate your understanding and continued support as we work towards delivering the exceptional game you deserve.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3d5982a4a6adac8650fa5f3f6559c18f1f52bd8a.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">We had a blast at GameCon Canada last weekend!</div><br/>Before you can get your hands on the game on September 9 or on September 5 for the Early Unlock, we’re touring in North America to let future players <b>play the demo</b>! Last weekend, we had an awesome time at Game Con Canada and our next stop will be Denver, Colorado from July 4 to 7!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d310e58c5fd691d89647eac299fe004cf6303ddc.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Join us on the official Space Marine 2 Discord server!</div><br/>This month, we also added brand-new <b><i>Space Marine 2</i> emotes</b> to our Discord server, bringing you more ways to express yourself all while honoring the Emperor! Many thanks to the talented SpyderOwO for creating those.<br/><br/>You can become part of the <i>Space Marine 2</i> community and join us, devs, and your fellow Marines, on the official <i>Space Marine 2</i> Discord server.<br/><br/>We will share news there and spend time discussing the game with you each week. Please keep the feedback and requests coming as they’re the grassroot of our community updates here.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6c8ce59e5c46412f231883ba5fffccb2e05ad666.jpg"/><br/><br/>See you next month for more info.<br/><b>The Emperor protects.</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
