<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Grim Protocols - Free Update Releasing 3 December</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456969803786092611</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<a class="bb_link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oC1HRacColU" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a25fdadf548b5b8376ce415c30d9a118ac81444b.jpg"/></a><br/><br/>(Note: due to a technical issue stemming from formatting, we are reposting the announcement for Grim Protocols - click the cover above to watch our Narrative Trailer🙏)<br/><br/>Hey Everyone, <br/><br/>We’ve been cooking for you. We’re ready to announce our next major update, Grim Protocols. It will be released on 3 December on all platforms. <br/><br/>This update will include: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> New Game Mode - Havoc: Think you’ve mastered the threat over Tertium? Think again. Havoc is a new end-game experience that will test the resolve of the most seasoned operative. Be ready to face daunting challenges and earn new cosmetic rewards. We’ve posted an initial dev blog about this, and we’re working on finishing the Q&amp;A post to follow.<br/></li><li> New Mission - Dark Communion:  Return to the Carnival and explore its darkest corners. Steel yourself as you face hordes of cultists who will stop at nothing to achieve their Dark Communion. We are working on a dev blog for this. <br/></li><li> Three New Weapon Families: Tear through waves of enemies by wielding the destructive might of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords, and the Ogryn Heavy Stubber. We are working on a dev blog for this…but here is a sneak peek: </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Two-Handed Power Sword (2 Marks) - Zealot:</b> A massive, high-damage melee weapon with wide, sweeping attacks.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade<br/></li><li> Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade</li></ul><br/><i>Two-Handed Power Sword - Unique Features</i>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Heat Activation Mechanic</b>: Generates a heat gauge, building over time. Reaching the limit locks activation briefly (overheat mechanic).<br/></li><li> <b>Special Attack</b>: Sprinting Heavy stab attack for unique engagement tactics.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Two-Handed Force Sword (2 Marks) - Psyker</b>: A finesse-oriented weapon combining melee and psychic powers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Covenant Mk VI Blaze Force Greatsword<br/></li><li> Covenant Mk VIII Blaze Force Greatsword</li></ul><br/><i>Two-Handed Force Sword - Unique Features</i>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Force Cleave</b>: Special attack releases a psychic cleave with scaling based on charge power (three stages).<br/></li><li><b> Smooth Flow</b>: Psyker’s psi-assisted techniques make the weapon feel lighter and more agile.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Heavy Stubber (3 Marks) - Ogryn</b>: A heavy, precision-support firearm for Ogryns, blending suppressive fire with marksman capabilities that will keep the darkness at bay. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Krourk Mk IIa Heavy Stubber<br/></li><li> Gorgonum Mk IIIa Heavy Stubber<br/></li><li> Achlys Mk II Heavy Stubber</li></ul><br/><i>Heavy Stubber - Unique Features</i>:<br/>Primary Fire: Heavy, slow automatic fire for suppressive roles.<br/>Alt Fire: A more precise, single-shot mode for longer-range accuracy.<br/>Flashlight: Included to assist in low-light environments.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Anniversary Special Event:</b> To celebrate the second anniversary of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, the game will host an event that will reward players with a unique weapon trinket. <br/></li><li> <b>And more:</b> Including the expansion of the Penance progression track with new challenges and rewards, as well as quality of life improvements such as an extension of the Party Finder feature and idle animations to Stances. </li></ul><br/>Here are some complementary screenshots of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords as well as a glimpse into Dark Communion. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3778d4edc53be9a890ea84b736621f6d1b5798b3.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b73602cb948ac46648af985c199709508f62b36a.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c669d6c29eabca6e8130daec1cef93f4ecaa6ea5.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0c5f8facbf770ac03247b2abc727f475e2c15a17.jpg"/><br/><br/>We look forward to sharing more about this update with players in the coming few weeks. We’re finishing up dev blogs on the new weapons, the new mission Dark Communion, and more. Stay tuned!<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 17:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mod Support - A Message from the Game Director</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6681747476222836957</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello, Space Marines</div><br/>We’ve seen incredible community engagement since launch, and we’ve noticed that some players have started to create and share mods for Space Marine 2. We wanted to make a game that was moddable from the start (this is why our game pack files are not encrypted, for example). It's always a pleasure for me, as a developer, to see what our community can create. Mods are great, and they will no doubt contribute to this game's longevity.<br/><br/>However, we as developers must also ensure game stability and continuously work towards a smoother experience for all players. Our data shows that a non-negligible amount of recent server stability issues are related to mods, and that instability impacts even those users who don’t have mods installed. We have also received user reports that their save files were corrupted after playing alongside players with mods.<br/><br/>This is why, starting with our next big update in December, mods will be prohibited from public online sessions. That means that you will no longer be able to enter a public game if you have mods installed.<br/><br/>However, we know that mods are a source of fun and creativity, and they will still be allowed in private Operations lobbies. We will continue to provide all necessary server infrastructure so you can play online with your friends with mods. Once we add custom Eternal War lobbies, mods will work for them as well.<br/><br/>We will also be providing an easy entry point to our backend for games with mods installed, so modders won’t have to spend time hacking the game executable after each patch. If we somehow break this pipeline for mods by accident in the future, we’ll fix it. In addition to that, we will be releasing some of our tools to modders so they can develop mods with greater ease.<br/><br/>Thank you for your understanding and cooperation.<br/><br/>The Emperor protects.<br/><br/>—Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 15:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vote for us at The Game Awards in the Best Action &amp; Best Multiplayer categories!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6681747476222836977</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">We're so incredibly happy to be nominated for both <b>Best Multiplayer</b> and <b>Best Action Game</b> at The Game Awards!! 🔥<br/><br/>Dear Space Marines, <b>we count on YOU</b> 🫵 to make this happen!</div><br/>You have until December 12 to vote for us at: https://www.thegameawards.com/nominees<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/83d4421a64f053c4cea480f210619dc9debe7844.png"/><br/> <br/>FOR THE EMPEROR ⚔️]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Play Sale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/7168136236401426499</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>A member of your retinue, smuggler Jae Heydari, reports that she has managed to arrange a special deal for your lordship or ladyship. And while her offers usually seem shady to us, we’re ready to vouch for this one.<br/><br/>If you haven't figured out how to spend your weekend yet, don’t miss the <b>We Play Sale</b> and grab Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader with a nice discount! Note that the Sale will be happening only during the weekend till November 17th, so don’t linger!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>You are a pioneer among the grim stars, the Emperor's chosen, the Rogue Trader. Your power is enough to bring many worlds to prosperity or their utter doom. Make your choice in Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, available with a <b>40% discount</b> right now!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Burn out a vile Genestealer Cult nest on your voidship or let the evil reign. Accept the deadly Death Cult assassin Kibellah to your crew and learn about the Cult's secret life on your flagship. Grab the Season Pass with <b>40% off</b> and get the Void Shadows DLC along with the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>The riches of your trading empire give you not only status but also significant benefits. Grab the Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>40% discount</b> and get an artbook, soundtrack, set of wallpapers, unique in-game items, models, accessories, and much more!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Kerillian &amp; Gutter Runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/6374376801654800469</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the first out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, starting today, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun. <br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/1724180032091-C1T2PXCPW7XX88MGNYMQ/GIF-3a%28mid%29.gif?format=2500w"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weekly Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly through the Kill-Counter and personal rewards to unlock through a small ‘win-track’. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Kerillian &amp; Gutter Runner Spotlight rewards will be earnable between November 14 - November 17. All rewards will be granted the following week. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock an exclusive skin for the Gutter Runner.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Spotlight-track</div>Meanwhile, the win-track rewards will be unlocked depending on how much time you spend in Vermintide 2. Don’t worry, it won’t be too difficult, we promise. You can play Adventure, Chaos Wastes, Weaves, or Versus to unlock the rewards*. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Playing for at least half an hour earns you 60 shillings.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least an hour earns you another 60 shillings as well as 30 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least two hours additionally earns you a brand new Portrait frame and 70 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least three hours additionally earns you a Hero Pose for Kerillian!</li></ul><i>This playtime is tracked across all game modes, but is only tracked while in an actual match.</i><br/><br/><i>*You cannot actively check on your track progression. All rewards will be granted the following week</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Kerillian </div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/01e01717e74ae5a1f2e98de0f5d3b27a91a000a3.png"/><br/>Like all wood elves, Kerillian feels the pull of both light and dark. First, as a Waywatcher, and now as a more experienced Waystalker, she has kept those aspects in balance. Indeed, Kerillian’s reason for journeying to Ubersreik was an attempt to help her reclaim her moral poise.  <br/><br/><b>[url=https://www.vermintide.com/news/2018/12/6/dev-blog-kerillian<br/>]Learn more about Kerillian here![/url]</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/5c31138a1d8cd9f53f3ac12945a7734dff4313ee.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Gutter Runner</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/4c71e763ac4d04c15216582ec661f624f5db97a7.jpg"/><br/>A deadly, nimble Assassin of Clan Eshin, capable of pouncing an unsuspecting Hero from anywhere! The Gutter Runner is one of our two Disablers.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Gutter Runner here!</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
