<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Datavault Update is out now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/529837270439562707</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines 🫡</div><br/><b>The 6.0 "Datavault" Update is out! 🎉🎉</b><br/><br/>This update brings more free content and much-requested quality-of-life improvements to all players whilst granting Season Pass owners with evermore cosmetics to customize their Space Marines.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch the trailer now! 👇</div>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EbE29ykkhbs?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h1">New challenges and rewards in the Datavault! 📚</div><br/>Directly accessible through the Armoury, today’s main addition comes in the form of the Datavault, a brand new Battle-Barge chamber where Tech-Priests collect and store intel on the many enemies of the Imperium. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1bcacc5ebb168ffe9f137a78eb8a60dfd37bfebb.jpg"/><br/>By completing Ordeals, you will accumulate Research Data that you will be able to trade for Requisition Points and new cosmetics like pauldron markings, weapon skins (Thunder Hammer, Auto Bolt Rifle) and even new armor pieces (breastplate, gauntlet).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/91ab5714125468ff04fa38f66029339a0bec4891.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New map in Eternal War &amp; Biovore in Operations</div><br/>Eternal War mode gets a brand new Necron-themed PvP map named “Tomb”. 🪦<br/>Operations players on the other hand, will need to keep an eye out for the new Tyranid Biovore, a devastating Majoris enemy able to deal damage both from afar and up close. 🦂<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6d9012f8c0aeb73ce1137893578cb67d3b475b3e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/81adbec012f346c50d1cf5e82667776ccc384592.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/cecf8aeb84657488f907386491e649743daf7735.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/85504f5e9b8ffe58f0ef7f70f537c40e61c43e46.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">Season Pass brings the Raven Guard and Salamanders 🐦‍⬛🦎</div><br/>Season Pass owners today receive the Raven Guard Cosmetic Pack and the Salamanders Champion Pack. <br/>The first comes with the iconic, fan-favourite <b>Mark VI “Corvus” helmet</b> <u><b>(with and without emblem!)</b></u> and over 40 cosmetics to celebrate the Raven Guard Successor Chapters, while the latter brings a new Champion skin for the Sniper class and an exclusive Bolt Sniper Rifle skin.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"> <br/><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a62bc19a1e9e19f11e45fce9f8375b8a7e275d7f.jpg"/></div> <div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1eeda2b0f655b1f3f5c6ffb27c18eeab47c73913.jpg"/></div> </div> </div><div class="bb_table"> <br/><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ec80a47041d92b72324d6dca4171aa8161be0ee9.jpg"/></div> <div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fee5a1a46efb05768ae6ff281563d16ff7324a36.jpg"/></div> </div> </div>The Raven Guard comes with 8 Successor Chapters, take a look:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/64fc7f89cfb534287b8e4a825fff76acf0773e5f.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">“Absolute” Difficulty and big QoL improvements</div><br/>The Datavault update also brings the <b>sixth and final</b> difficulty setting, aptly named “Absolute”, as well as significant quality-of-life features. <br/><br/>These include the addition of:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> an opt-in/opt-out Crossplay feature in PvP matches, <br/></li><li> an FOV slider on PC, <br/></li><li> a number of tweaks to class perks, <br/></li><li> and a “currency exchange” allowing players to trade their Armoury Data for rarer tiers or even Requisition Points! </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">More details can be found in the patch notes.</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/aa98cd0755a64f208304d14999d3f21983f6a4df.jpg"/><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is available now PC.<br/>Create your Focus Together account to receive exclusive rewards, and join the community and development of the game!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Emperor Protects ⭐</div><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.0 Datavault Update - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/529837904419094594</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hi Space Marines! 🫡</div><br/>The 6.0 Datavault Update comes with a whole lot of quality of life improvements and brand new features.  Check out all of the additions, features and updates listed in our patch notes below!<br/><br/>In order, we will detail:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>The new features</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Battle Barge Extension: Datavault<br/></li><li> New PvP Map “Tomb”<br/></li><li> New enemy Biovore<br/></li><li> Emotes System<br/></li><li> Armoury Data Refinement<br/></li><li> New PvE Difficulty: Absolute<br/></li><li> FOV Slider<br/></li><li> Opt in PvP Crossplay option for consoles<br/></li><li> New Finishers<br/></li><li> Additional Mastery for Full Progression<br/></li><li> Quick Match Bonus</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>New Season Pass Content</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Salamander Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Raven Guard Cosmetic Pack</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>Gameplay &amp; Balancing</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Perk Update (in order: tactical, assault, vanguard, sniper, heavy, bulwark)<br/></li><li> Weapon Perks (Melee Weapons Update / Firearms for PvE only, etc)<br/></li><li> Gameplay QoL</li></ul><br/>Let’s deep dive into it! 👇<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/aa98cd0755a64f208304d14999d3f21983f6a4df.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1"> ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀New Features</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Battle Barge Expansion: Datavault</div></u><br/>The Datavault is a new area on the Battle Barge. Players can complete Ordeals in Campaign, Operations and Eternal War modes to challenge their skill and earn Research Data currency. In the Research Center players can unlock <br/><br/>Exploration in the Research Center is rewarded with different rewards: 4 new icons for the right pauldron, 2 new weapon skins and 2 new armour parts.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1bcacc5ebb168ffe9f137a78eb8a60dfd37bfebb.jpg"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">New PvP Map: Tomb</div></u><br/>This PvP map is based around a similar structure to our other maps, but utilizes a different approach to the design of battle zones. Overall, Tomb is the smallest map of all the PvP maps. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0944da711460b17398eae901c8f477de837cb5a8.jpg"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">New Enemy: Biovore</div></u><br/>We have added a new Extremis enemy for the Tyranids, the Biovore. It is a fast, mobile living-artillery creature that can keep the distance, fortify and shoot spore mines in its enemies. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/daecab1a0acf4c1a4d1de9b32da668b5e5e1fddf.jpg"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Emotes System</div></u><br/>We have added an in-game emote system that includes a pound to the chest, a battle cry, and even a stoic handshake. You can use any of the 6 emotes in any game mode via the emote wheel.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9b98b9c43156bec5c0a4230aa5f389ff1c43facd.gif"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Armoury Data Refinement</div></u><br/>We added a new Tech-Priest workshop in the Armoury of the Battle Barge. It is an exchange point where the player can:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Exchange low tier Armoury Data to higher tier variants.<br/></li><li> Sell Armoury Data  in exchange for Requisition points.</li></ul>This will allow players to  obtain relic armoury data without having to beat higher difficulties.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/91ab5714125468ff04fa38f66029339a0bec4891.png"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">New PvE Difficulty: Absolute</div></u><br/>This difficulty is focused on new, more diverse enemy packs that bring extreme challenge. Resources and ammo are aslo limited.<br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">FOV Slider</div></u><br/>Players will now be able to modify the camera's field of view for a more personalised experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/174afc3cb8e4158d9cea24d21f8f4fb30e4b3728.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/deaa843b636e39030b4952731dbb963aa46b739f.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c7a4fad665f054a09c00ca7e868bdb3e5edb7f77.gif"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Opt in PvP Crossplay option for consoles</div></u><br/>We have lifted the restriction on cross-play for PvP across PC and consoles, now  players can choose whether or not they wish to play with the wider community. <b>You must be in the title screen settings to toggle this option.</b><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/36a4c725e87140f17db3ab6c7251e55a1d08e1a0.png"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">New Finishers</div></u><br/>New finisher animations have been added to purge the xenos and traitors with style:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 1 for Zoanthrope;<br/></li><li> 2 for Rubric Marines;<br/></li><li> 1 for Scarab Occult Terminator. </li></ul><u><div class="bb_h3">Additional Mastery for Full Progression</div></u><br/>When a weapon is fully upgraded, the player is now awarded an additional mastery point (works retroactively).<br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Quick Match Bonus</div></u><br/>Players will now receive additional bonus XP if they play in Quick Match, as a compensation for not being able to select the Operation they’re playing.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">  ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀New Season Pass Content</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Added: Salamanders Champion Pack (Sniper class)</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a62bc19a1e9e19f11e45fce9f8375b8a7e275d7f.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Added: Raven Guard Cosmetic Pack</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ec80a47041d92b72324d6dca4171aa8161be0ee9.jpg"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Customisation</div></u><br/><b>Shared slots for Skins Recolour:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a new slots tab in the customiser for Shared Colour Presets. This preset can be used across any class and any game mode</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b46057cd48f9ac17646681cff4dca6a4238ab864.jpg"/><br/><b> Chapter decals are now available for right pauldrons (for the Deathwatch fans!)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All base chapter decals are now available for the right pauldron. (These only need to be unlocked once, allowing you to place them on either pauldron)</li></ul><b>Customisation Bug Fixes</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug with  a Pauldron emblem from the Dark Angels DLC not having a colour option<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where loading into a match while previewing a locked piece of armour could result in this piece being equipped after the match ends or player leaves it<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with Champion's backpack that caused incorrect colouration after switching, in some rare cases</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1"> ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ Gameplay &amp; Balancing</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4c59b83ad387d1233a8dc930fd2a50026caff0a3.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Class Perks Update</div><br/><i>“Balancing wise, the focus of this update was to review perk trees of all classes. There were clear outsiders that didn't get picked. While there are some nerfs in the list, the vast majority of changes are buffs that should benefit different playstyles. With the next patch we will be focusing on weapon perks and weapons class restrictions.”</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c741d6ad228423769275bff7e195c4362308e0d3.png"/><br/><br/><b>Overall: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed damage bonuses from multiple Auspex Scan perks stacking incorrectly.</li></ul><i>Note: We found that several Auspex Scan perks were not stacking correctly when used together. This had to be fixed to ensure functionality. We will be watching for Auspex Scan and will make adjustments in the future if this fix makes the ability not as effective as it originally was</i><br/><br/><br/><b>Heightened Vigour: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Knockback immunity effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds<br/></li><li> Added melee and gun strike bonus damage effect</li></ul><br/><b>Communion of Fire: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Recoil reduction bonus increased from 20% to 25% <br/></li><li> Added a ranged damage bonus effect against Extremis-level enemies</li></ul><br/><b>Close Targeting</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "When Auspex Scan is in cooldown, Melee Damage increases by 15%" from “When Auspex Scan is in cooldown, Melee Damage increases by 50% against Minoris-level enemies.”</li></ul><i>Note: This perk was originally intended to be used to crush hordes of Minoris-level enemies, but we decided to expand its effect to other enemies, lowering the bonus a bit to avoid overpowering it.</i><br/><b>Signal Jammer</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added an effect of automatically killing an enemy who tries to call for reinforcements</li></ul><i>Note: The original perk was not very effective, and we wanted to add some greater utility to it.</i><br/><br/><b>Plasma Boost: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Activation threshold lowered from “50% Overheated” to “30% Overheated” <br/></li><li> Bonus damage increased from 30% to 40%<br/></li><li> Added an effect to reduce the energy cost of charged shots by 1</li></ul><br/><b>Steady Aim</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "Weapon Spread and Recoil is reduced by 20%, and Ranged Damage against Terminus-level enemies is increased by 10%" from “Recoil is reduced by 10%”.</li></ul><br/><b>Aligned Aim</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a typo that stated the perk provides 5% bonus damage instead of the actual 15%.</li></ul><br/><b>Improved Efficiency:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Changed the perk activation condition from “Scanning 20 enemies with one Auspex Scan restores Equipment Charge by 1” to “Scanning 10 any enemies or 3 Majoris-level or higher enemies with one Auspex Scan restores Equipment Charge by 1”.</li></ul><i>Note: This is a great perk, but we found that it performed worse on higher difficulties and against Chaos in particular. The new effect should fix that difference.</i><br/><br/><b>Expert Timing</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage reduced from 100% to 75%<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect perk effect (reducing zone's duration instead of mark's duration)</li></ul><i>Note: This perk has performed much better than we originally planned, especially with the bug that was causing incorrect stacking of damage from multiple perks, so we want to try nerfing its bonus damage a bit while buffing adjacent perks. It should provide more build options to experiment with.</i><br/><br/><b>Radiating Impact:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage from 75 to 100<br/></li><li> Increased perk's radius from 5 to 10 <br/></li><li> Added effect radius in description <br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><i>Note: Damage-dealing perks previously did not scale with difficulty. We planned to keep this to make enemies harder to defeat, but we found that on higher difficulties these perks rarely made a significant contribution. So now several of these perks will have higher damage as difficulty increases.</i><br/><br/><b>Versatility:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 20% to 25%</li></ul><br/><b>Emperor's Vengeance</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed restoring grenades for the Grenade Launcher (now restores one grenade per activation).</li></ul><i>Note: Unfortunately, restoring a full set of grenades every 30 seconds was never intended to be the case and has proven disastrously effective. We understand that this will significantly nerf the perk and will be watching if this makes it less popular. If so, we will make changes in the future.</i><br/><br/><b>Target Lock: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 25% to 75%</li></ul><br/><b>Precise Calibration:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where this perk affected equipment damage.</li></ul><br/><b>Concentrated Fire: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 100% to 120% <br/></li><li> The duration of the Auspex Scan zone is now extended by 40%</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1abf8c6d07944560f7c6535488e606fe81f15ea4.png"/><br/><br/><b>Winged Fury: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 25% to 40%</li></ul><br/><b>Wings of Flame:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now guarantees a perfect dodge on Jump Pack dodge in addition to all other effects</li></ul><br/><b>Overcharge: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 15% to 25%</li></ul><br/><b>Retribution: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 15% to 20%<br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 10 to 20 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Ascension: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added damage scale by difficulty.</li></ul><br/><b>Armour Reinforcement: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed incorrect armour restoration and updated localisation to better reflect the intended effect of the perk (1 armour segment restored per non-lethal Gun Strike).</li></ul><i>Note: Initially the armour restoration effect was equal to the finisher, which allowed this perk to restore all armour on any gun strike to bosses. It allowed almost infinite armour restoration. We will be watching this perk and will make adjustments in the future if this fix makes it  too ineffective.</i><br/><br/><b>Consecutive Execution:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cooldown reduced from 180 to 90 seconds <br/></li><li> The perk no longer goes on cooldown when a player has a full pack of equipment</li></ul><br/><b>Proven Efficiency: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage reduced from 50% to 30%</li></ul><i>Note: This perk has performed much better than we originally planned, so we want to try nerfing its bonus damage a bit while buffing the adjacent Strategic Strikes perk (Squad Cohesion should be pretty great as is). It should provide more build options to experiment with.</i><br/><br/><b>Aerial Grace: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 25% to 30% <br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/49a8b1e1d75b916ba063b4bcda14fc04e773850c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Grapnel Launcher</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Can be now used on Zoanthropes and Neurothropes</li></ul><br/><b>Moving Target: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 1% to 2% by attack <br/></li><li> Maximum bonus  increased from 15% to 20% <br/></li><li> The time for the next attack has been increased from 3 to 5 seconds <br/></li><li> This time no longer counted during finisher animations</li></ul><br/><b>Retribution:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 20% to 25% <br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 10 to 15 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Restless Fortitude: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 10% to 20%</li></ul><br/><b>Zone of Impact:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage from 20 to 50 <br/></li><li> Increased perk's radius from 5 to 10<br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Thrill of the Fight: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 15% to 20% <br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 3 to 5 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Tactical Prowess: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now it also allows the Grapnel Launcher to activate Finisher on enemies, who have less than 25% HP (without this perk, the Grapnel Launcher can do it only with incapacitated enemies).</li></ul><i>Note: Grapnel Launcher has had a hidden mechanic this whole time – when used on an incapacitated enemy, Vanguard would automatically activate a finisher on them. It is not a life-important feature but pretty neat in combat. We would like to highlight it with this perk.</i><br/><br/><b>Close-Combat Focus: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "You take 20% less Ranged Damage” from “You take 20% less Melee Damage but 10% more Ranged Damage”</li></ul><i>Note: This perk was supposed to exchange one type of protection to another, but over time we were unable to make this exchange pleasant for players. So we decided to just give a bonus in this perk.</i><br/><br/><b>Consecutive Execution: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cooldown reduced from 180 to 90 seconds<br/></li><li> The perk no longer goes on cooldown when a player has a full pack of equipment</li></ul><br/><b>Unmatched Zeal: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Health regeneration bonus increased from 5% to 20%<br/></li><li> Perk now works against Terminus-level enemies as well.</li></ul><br/><b>Shock Wave: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added damage scale by difficulty.</li></ul><br/><b>Tenacity: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 25% to 40%<br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 10 to 15 seconds<br/></li><li> The cooldown was removed</li></ul><br/><b>Grim Determination: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased bonus damage from 10% to 15%.</li></ul><br/><b>Emperor's Blessing: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cooldown is reduced from 180 seconds to 120 seconds.</li></ul><i>Note: The Emperor appreciates your hard work in exterminating the enemies of humanity and now grants His Blessing a little more frequently.</i><br/><br/><b>Upper Hand: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds.</li></ul><br/><b>Conviction: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 15% to 25%.</li></ul><br/><b>Inner Fire: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added condition of finishing Majoris-level enemy or higher to activate the perk.</li></ul>Note: This is a good perk both in terms of effect and balance, but finishing off very weak enemies allowed the ability to be restored too effectively, so we added a limitation here.<br/><b>Collateral Damage: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage from 5 to 15<br/></li><li> Added damage value to perk description<br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Adrenaline Rush: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Health restoration is reduced from 10% to 5%.</li></ul><i>Note: This is a great perk, but unfortunately it allows experienced Vanguards to solo all their problems and leave their team to be torn apart by the enemy. Our test shows that even despite significant numerical reduction this is a very, very strong perk, and as always will be watching to see if this perk is nerfed too much.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b008de073c9e7e17f7c5410a6ebec4145b7304ca.png"/><br/><br/><b>Camo Cloak class perk (Starting Perk): </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added bonus damage value to perk description.</li></ul><br/><b>Iron Grip:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "Weapon Spread and Recoil is reduced by 20% and Ranged Damage against Terminus-level enemies is increased by 15% for Bolt Sniper and Stalker Bolt Rifles" from “Recoil from Bolt Sniper Rifles and Stalker Bolt rifles is reduced by 30%"</li></ul><br/><b>Purification: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now also restores all Contested Health when manually activating Camo Cloak.</li></ul><br/><b>Persistence</b>: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added heavy hit protection and knockback reduction effect<br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Melee Mastery</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 10% to 20%</li></ul><br/><b>Vantage Point</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now also works on secondary weapons.</li></ul><br/><b>Dexterous Hands</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reload speed increased from 15 to 20<br/></li><li> Added Bolt Carbine's spread and recoil reduction effect</li></ul><br/><b>Precision Targeting</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Spread reduction bonus increased from 20 to 25 <br/></li><li> Added a ranged damage bonus effect against Extremis-level enemies.</li></ul><br/><b>Efficient Readiness</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now also provides a 20% movement speed boost effect while Camo Cloak is active.</li></ul><i>Note: This was an effect we wanted to try out initially but only managed to do it now. Use it to reposition yourself and strike down enemies but not to abandon your teammates!</i><br/><br/><b>Adaptability</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 15% to 25% <br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Tactical Ambush</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 100% to 150%.</li></ul><br/><b>Ambush</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cooldown reduced from 30 to 25 seconds.</li></ul><br/><b>Pattern of Excellence</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced the number of consecutive headshots required to activate the perk from 4 to 3.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8884de443755dac7bb5665350a070df9cb37914c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Overcharge:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "Melee Damage increases by 30%" from “Damage from Charged Melee Attacks increases by 20%”.</li></ul><i>Note: We like the possibility to cover Heavy's almost only weakness – Melee Combat – with perks, so we decided to significantly improve this perk.</i><br/><br/><b>Encompassing Aegis: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 20% to 25%</li></ul><br/><b>Adamant Will: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Saving Grace: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added full armour restoration effect</li></ul><i>Note: Selflessly saving your allies is a noble act that should be rewarded more than the ability charge used for it.</i><br/><br/><b>Offensive Capability:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage frequency <br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Consecutive Execution:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cooldown reduced from 180 to 90 seconds<br/></li><li> The perk no longer goes on cooldown when a player has a full pack of equipment</li></ul><br/><b>Field Adjustment: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Iron Halo durability reduction changed from 30% to 25%</li></ul><br/><b>Coolant Reserve: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added 15% bonus damage effect</li></ul><br/><b>Auxiliary Ammunition</b>: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed incorrectly working cooldown</li></ul><br/><b>Strategic Stand:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added heavy hit protection and knockback reduction effect</li></ul><br/><b>Power Regulator: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Iron Halo charge drain reduction changed from 15% to 20%</li></ul><br/><b>Wrath of the Imperium: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage from 50 to 100<br/></li><li> Radius increased from 5 to 10 <br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Conversion Field: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a typo that stated the perk worked at 100 meters instead of the actual 10 meters</li></ul><i>Note: Sure, it was too good to be true. But we will be watching this perk in case it needs a buff.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6dc73b997ce968ed4d170cec92bf099029c43431.png"/><br/><br/><b>Overall:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>We’ve moved some perks around the tree so it would be possible to create certain builds. (i.e. it was previously impossible to configure your perk tree to make a banner that buffs your team mates a lot, because some of those per</li></ul><i>Note: We noticed that players were making the same build for Bulwark with some minor differences and swapped two pairs of perks to provide players with more build options, making the perk sets in tiers more versatile.</i><br/><br/><b>Conviction: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Armour of Contempt:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Focused Restoration (renamed from “Reinforced Ceramite”): </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The perk effect has been reworked, the new version is: "Every 40 seconds, all Squad Members automatically restore 1 Armour Segment" from “The delay before Armour begins to passively regenerate is reduced by 5 seconds for all squad members”</li></ul><i>Note: We noticed that this perk hardly works in combat, essentially only reducing the wait for armour to regenerate after combat. So we decided to try a different approach and made armour regenerate periodically.</i><br/><br/><b>Concussive Force: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage from 4 to 8<br/></li><li> Changed perk's description<br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Purity of Purpose: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased perk's damage frequency<br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><br/><b>Intimidating Aura: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added cooldown (5 seconds) <br/></li><li> Added damage scale by difficulty</li></ul><i>Note: This perk has been performing incredibly well on lower difficulties and with the damage scale it should be just as powerful on higher difficulties. We do not want to reduce the damage of this perk, so we decided to add a small cooldown only to prevent spamming it.</i><br/><br/><b>Steel Within: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 25% to 30%.</li></ul><br/><b>Rapid Regeneration: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Chapter Banner duration reduction is changed from 5 seconds to 10 seconds.</li></ul><br/><b>Merciless Resolve:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added 15% bonus melee damage effect </li></ul><br/><b>Glory's Shield: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the typo in description, which did not specify the ranged damage type <br/></li><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 10% to 20% <br/></li><li> Added 20% bonus to banner's duration</li></ul><br/><b>Forward Momentum:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 25% to 30%<br/></li><li> Effect duration increased from 5 to 10 seconds</li></ul><br/><b>Scrambled Targeting:</b> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Damage reducing bonus increased from 20% to 25%</li></ul><br/><b>Armour Reinforcement: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed incorrect armour restoration <br/></li><li> Updated localisation to better reflect the intended effect of the perk (1 armour segment restored per non-lethal gunstrike)</li></ul><br/><b>Effective Formation: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Now works against Extremis-level enemies as well</li></ul><br/><b>Invigorating Icon: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added effect of slowing by 100% the recharge time of the banner. (twice longer)</li></ul><i>Note: We have noticed that this perk often encourages players to hold off on using Banner until the very last resort. We like this change in strategy, but the perk itself makes Banner overpowered. So we want to tone it down so that it requires more thoughtful timing when activating the ability.</i><br/><br/><b>Inspiration: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bonus damage increased from 10% to 20%</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/06c948bffaf81502eb733da542c6c34afb0fa7b4.png"/><br/><b>Contingency Plan Perk (Multi-Melta; Heavy Bolter; Heavy Plasma Incinerator)</b>:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed incorrect numbers in perk's description.</li></ul>Elite Restoration Perk (Multi-Melta):<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed incorrect display of enemy class in perk's description.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/572c8074dba7bf2d598568e7ffa6f465674ddd03.png"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Perfect Block (All melee weapons)</div></u><br/><i>“We think blocking weapons were almost in a good spot. This is a significant buff that should make blocking weapons more viable versus Chaos enemies, because they don't have a lot of melee combos, making it difficult to gain full damage bonus from blocking weapons.”</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Adrenaline Surge stacks needed for maximum effect are decreased to 2 from 3.<br/></li><li> Armour recovery from maximum effect is decreased from 2 to 1.</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Power Fist</div></u><br/><i>“Power Fist is one of the least popular melee weapons (despite being one of the coolest👊). We are making it more practical in combat by extending its AoE damage and making it easier to charge.”</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Maximum charge time reduced from 3.9 seconds to 2.5 seconds for hold attacks.<br/></li><li> Hold attacks can now be partially charged (it used to be 1 charge for full damage bonus, now it's 2 quicker charges for 50% smaller bonuses).<br/></li><li> Forward cone damage distance is increased up to 10 meters, making it more viable in mid range.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/69bf0cdada2f8f47f7dad637385ff858cb482937.png"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Bolters</div></u><br/><i>“While Bolter weapons were finding their spot in the game we are making another round of very minor Bolter weapons buffs to make them viable on a new difficulty."</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bolt Rifle: Base damage is increased by 8%.<br/></li><li> Auto Bolt Rifle: Base damage is increased by 6%.<br/></li><li> Heavy Bolt Rifle: Base damage is increased by 5%.<br/></li><li> Bolt Carbine (SMG Versions): Base damage is increased by 7%.<br/></li><li> Bolt Carbine (Marksman Versions): Base damage is increased by 5%.<br/></li><li> Occulus Bolt Carbine: Base damage is increased by 10%.<br/></li><li> Instigator Bolt Carbine: Base damage is increased by 5%.<br/></li><li> Stalker Bolt Rifle: Base damage is increased by 7%.</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Grenade Launcher Rebalance:</div></u><br/><i>“Previously the artificer and relic damage values were set incorrectly, with a combination of buggy damage bonuses stacking from Auspex Scan. This resulted in insane damage values. While the damage reduction looks big on paper you can still obliterate entire waves with GL. However, with changes below, you won't be able to 1-shot bosses anymore.”</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced the damage amount for AUX Grenade Launcher version (from 25/100/100 to 25/50/75).</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Equipment</div></u><br/><i>“These changes are made to make Terminus enemies more resistant to explosive damage, so they cannot be killed by GL that easily.<br/>In return we are buffing equipment damage to make it more viable against Terminus enemies.”</i><br/><b>Melta Charge Damage Buff:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased Melta Charge damage amount from 201 to 221 <br/></li><li> Reverted reduced damage to bosses introduced in previous patches.</li></ul><b>Krak Grenade Damage Buff:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased Krak Grenade damage amount from 110 to 120.</li></ul><b>Bosses' Explosive Sensitivity Rebalance:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Changed bosses sensitivity to equipment and grenade launcher from ~0.4 to ~0.25.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><u>Gameplay QoL</u></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Kick votes can no longer be launched in the final stages of an Operation.</li></ul><b>Grapnel Launcher Ability:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Incapacitated enemies that were hit by Grapnel Launcher (which allows Vanguard to automatically finish off an enemy upon landing) can no longer be finished off by other players while Vanguard is being pulled<br/></li><li> Vanguard can no longer take damage when pulled to an enemy</li></ul><b>Jump Pack:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug with Assault flying up after using Jump Pack in some cases<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where character could hit the air when performing a ground pound in Story mode in some cases</li></ul><b>Other:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Gunstrike may get canceled during usage<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Heavy class couldn’t turn on/off Iron Halo ability during the sprint<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare issue where if Parry was pressed at the exact same time as melee attack - no action would take place</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">PvP</div></u><ul class="bb_ul"><li> PvP. Match Ending:<br/></li><li> Added short delay between post match screen and triggering of the win condition<br/></li><li> Added smooth fade-in on the screen and lock on all inputs from the player</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Heavy's Iron Halo could stay if activated right before the death in some rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare bug where Iron Halo was not disabled when enemy Vanguard hooked at Heavy.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where there was no shield sight mark while hitting the enemy shields with plasma.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Assault couldn’t hover on the jump pack after making a Ground Pound.<br/></li><li> Fixed an Infinite loading screen onto the Battle Barge after the end of a PvP match in some rare cases.<br/></li><li> Many small fixes in level geometry collision</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">AI</div></u><ul class="bb_ul"><li> AI Synaptic shock and AI friendly fire damage now scales with difficulty</li></ul><b>Zoanthrope &amp; Neurothope Gun Strike:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Perfectly dodging Zoanthrope and Neurothrope "beam" attacks will now trigger Gun Strike</li></ul><b>Neurotrope:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Neurothrope would freeze in the air when incapacitated after some attack</li></ul><b>Carnifex:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added more variations to his AI reactions to getting hit<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that would make Carnifex stay idle when getting shot</li></ul><b>Tyranid Warrior Lash Whip:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a rare issue making the enemy enter idle state during combat after getting hit</li></ul><b>Tzaangor Enlightened:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dodge desirability and cooldown are increased, now it will use dodge less likely when it is under aim and will dodge rarely<br/></li><li> Explosive spear attack damage reduced</li></ul><b>Rubric Flamer:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Flamer shooting distance is slightly decreased<br/></li><li> Slightly increased time for players to react the Flame attack</li></ul><b>Rubric Bolter:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Slightly Increased time for players to react on precise shot attack<br/></li><li> Burst fire attack length is slightly decreased</li></ul><b>Scarab Occult Terminator Ranged:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced the number of rocket barrages that Terminator can shoot in a row<br/></li><li> Increased desired range for rocket barrage, now terminator will less likely shoot rocket barrage in the player that are close to him</li></ul><b>Other</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Lots of minor animation fixes for various enemies.</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Operations</div></u><br/><b>Fall of Atreus:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug that would cause enemies to not spawn in some areas of Fall Of Atreus</li></ul><b>Obelisk:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added notification about the chalice forgotten on the holder when leaving the location<br/></li><li> Fixed VO bugs related in the cave part of the level.</li></ul><b>Vox Liberatis:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where dying on Vox Liberatis after interacting with the last altar may show Defeat Screen after Victory cinematic</li></ul><b>All:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Many small fixes in level geometry collision and Terminus enemies getting stuck in some areas</li></ul><br/><u><div class="bb_h3">Tech</div></u><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements<br/></li><li> General connectivity improvements<br/></li><li> Slightly optimised memory consumption<br/></li><li> Slightly improved performance<br/></li><li> Slightly improved texture streaming speed<br/></li><li> Improved Anti-Cheat</li></ul><u><div class="bb_h3">Render Improvements</div></u><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with capsule shadows tech</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #60 (1.6.7) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536593303852810323</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f25bd44022d68107336ddb85cf02b225ed6f8fff.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey everyone, </div><br/>We’ve got another quick update this week. Hotfix #60 (1.6.7) is currently rolling out and it’ll be available for everyone across our platforms today.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a server crash which could happen when players joined the Mourningstar.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where deaths which bypassed the downed state were not considered as failing the requirements of the "The Insane" penance.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Dev Note:</b> <i>“The Insane” penance: Complete a Havoc Assignment of 35 or higher without anyone getting downed.</i></li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue where the arms of the player character could disappear at certain camera angles when wearing the "Padre's Truskan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)" and "Truskan Sanctionite's Greatcoat with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)" upperbody cosmetics.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #59 (1.6.6) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592669875372717</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cd496fffc43c60ab11e722fa5cb0bcecbf0ffd98.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>As mentioned in our last post, Update on Hotfix #58 (1.6.5), there as an issue in the game that could cause some players to crash when interacting with the Sacrifice function at the Shrine of the Omnissiah.<br/><br/>This was fixed in today’s hotfix.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that would happen when accessing the Sacrifice or Discard menus without any available weapon to sacrifice/discard, or when returning to the above menus after having sacrificed/discarded all the available weapons for that character.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/529836636819686186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1"> Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/><b>New Year, New Content!</b><br/><br/>We hear you're hungry for content, and we're happy to see how excited you are about the game!<br/><br/>First off, please don’t forget to check the roadmap for 2025! Worry not, even if this roadmap ends in 2025, that doesn’t mean the game will not receive new content after that! But first things first, let’s focus on this year. If you missed it, the updated roadmap is here:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0d21154a89b3463d365f0e7355c8c3a332d35a70.jpg"/><br/>Secondly, we'd like to remind you that Space Marine 2 will continually be updated with content and technical support throughout 2025. <br/>You’ll progressively get new skins, new PvP and PvE maps, custom lobbies for PvP, the Horde Mode is coming this year as well, PvE prestige ranks and new weapons as well. 🔥<br/><br/>Community Events will also keep coming throughout the year.<br/><br/>The Datavault Update we’re about to break down will arrive in <b>February</b>!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">💙 <u>Thank you for your unwavering support</u></div>Space Marine 2 has been out for 4 months, and your continued enthusiasm means the world to us.<br/><br/>We’re not done with it! You can expect updates every two months. We’d love to do more, but we’re committed to delivering polished updates, which takes time and care! Thank you for your patience, understanding, and unwavering support.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NEW PVP MAP - TOMB</div>A new PvP map is about to be implemented in the 6.0 update! We already hinted that it will be set in a closed environment with many narrow passages pushing you to engage more in Closed Quartered Battles.<br/><br/>It takes place beneath the surface of Demerium, amongst the haunting structures of in a Necron tomb. It’s a closed environment with many narrow passages. Pay extra attention because there are blind spots. There’s also a wider area to let you switch combat style.<br/><br/><br/>❔ Which class do you think you will be playing on this new map?<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/862a7b9286a08a1774e99ef5ea5eefedfd0d406c.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/cecf8aeb84657488f907386491e649743daf7735.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0944da711460b17398eae901c8f477de837cb5a8.jpg"/></div></div></div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/85504f5e9b8ffe58f0ef7f70f537c40e61c43e46.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NEW ENEMY - BIOVORE 🦂</div>The Biovore is a new enemy in PvE, in all maps featuring Tyranids. It’s an Extremis enemy, a dreadful foe both in distance and melee combat. Beware of the Spore Mines ithe shoots.<br/><br/>Don’t forget to dodge and then aim at the Spore Mine to destroy them before impact. 💥<br/><br/>Do not falter, Brother. You’ve got this.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/81adbec012f346c50d1cf5e82667776ccc384592.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6d9012f8c0aeb73ce1137893578cb67d3b475b3e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/daecab1a0acf4c1a4d1de9b32da668b5e5e1fddf.jpg"/></div></div></div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9c491892d8237bbb7b76eb5c6bc0198efcf12de1.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SALAMANDERS CHAMPION 🦎</div>We announced it last month: The Salamanders Champion is here! One of the Loyalist First Founding Chapters of the Space Marines.<br/><br/>Available for the Sniper class, with both skins for your Champion and for your Bolt Sniper Rifle: adorn that green paint, those flames and go dominate the battlefield.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/67a1893fea1f5357fed8f127e395be289e75a43d.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1eeda2b0f655b1f3f5c6ffb27c18eeab47c73913.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/64ceaa4ecfa097d213288aeb032ca4b5cc6be565.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">RAVEN GUARD COMING! 🐦‍⬛</div>The Raven Guard are joining the fight! New cosmetics will soon be available with the season pass including the fan-favorite: ✨🦅 beaky helmet 🦅✨ (MK VI “Corvus”) and Raven Guard trinkets.<br/><br/>Take a first look at it:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ec80a47041d92b72324d6dca4171aa8161be0ee9.jpg"/><br/>The MK VI “Corvus” helmet comes both with and without the Raven Guard emblem, allowing you to customize your Space Marine for your convenience. ✨<br/><br/>❔ How excited are we about these cosmetics?<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7bb187d8fc927d0de45788aabf194a8de7655075.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/08c9841fb1e0ba442a6fa2e1466345b2e97d454b.jpg"/> </div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">DATAVAULT 📚</div><b>The Datavault makes its entry to the Battle Barge!</b><br/><br/>In this new area, you will find unlockable information on most elements from the game in the Research Centre, as well as cosmetic rewards. To unlock them, you will need a new special currency, earned via in-game achievements (called Ordeals), in all modes (Campaign, PvE and PvP). Time to challenge yourself! 🎖️<br/><br/>Those achievements will be listed beside the unlockable info.<br/><br/>Here’s the kind of Ordeals you’ll have to complete to unlock the currency:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Complete any Mission in Operations mode on Average Threat Level or higher.<br/></li><li> Knock back Spore Mines to kill Tyranids.<br/></li><li> Make a Carnifex stun itself in Operations mode.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">PERKS REWORK 🔧</div>In a past Community Update, we mentioned that we were not completely satisfied with the quality of perks. We’ve reworked some of them, and these enhancements will be introduced in the next update release. More changes will come on the perks in the future, and we hope this first change on the perks feel more satisfying and engaging. We’re all ears, so don’t hesitate to share your feedback!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FOV SLIDER FOR PC 🎥</div>You expressed how eager you were to get a FOV Slider since the launch. While implementing it has been technically challenging, we’ve finally managed to produce a slider worthy of our standards, introduced in version 6.0.<br/><br/>We hope this new feature will meet your expectations!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">For 16/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV Slider set at 1 (1920x1080p screen):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f01a34be12efa9e380d545fd89721d7420825fe3.jpg"/><br/></li><li> ​FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/581a5d77800e6ab12dca0f4ec2988b5be9f4174a.jpg"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/04e3bf9f62f3c8056c020fe27599d5495058816f.jpg"/></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">For 21/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV slider set at 1 (3440x1440p screen) (minimum, current version):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c46392d276bba98f7ff8a0051a98289a23d0cd37.png"/><br/></li><li> ​FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7e5d582239d1bcde39702ffdcd8845d444696443.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fd9dfeeed22ca2da239b5a5df006affc2ca248d5.png"/></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">For 32/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV Slider set at 1 (5120 x 1440p screen):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/31f1932d168b60c6a46ca2dcb43f86cc536ef2f3.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/613eafb92b8bf7f2f3eb5369fa333665b75f7edb.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c1c0b39582d2c56877c20ecc9c29505de427a34a.png"/></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">AND MORE ✨</div>New finisher animations on Zoanthropes, Scarab Occult Terminators and Rubric Marines.<br/><br/>A new functionality will be added, allowing you to upgrade your Master-Crafted and Artificer Armoury Data to Relic by trading them. You can also sell your Armoury Data to get Requisition Points.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/91ab5714125468ff04fa38f66029339a0bec4891.png"/><br/><i>Talk to this Tech-Priest to trade your Armoury Data.</i><br/><br/>A new difficulty mode with cosmetic rewards will be added for the braves able to successfully complete Operations in this more intense difficulty: a bloodstained Knife Combat and a new pauldron. Note that this new difficulty will only be available if you have completed at least 1 Operation in Lethal Difficulty. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/90db0516a4336ce773c4c33b8ce5bc6a2370b75f.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7e77aef3da9881186301fabc7586d1d71c0b9d89.jpg"/><br/><br/>Base Decals available for Right Pauldrons (This one’s for you, Deathwatch players)<br/><br/>A new option to share your skin between PvE and PvP modes will be added. You’ll no longer need to remake the same skin for both modes! This option also allows you to share your patterns between classes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fffe1d74dfaaede6def1ac4e011b56a6fb23a3b3.png"/><br/><br/>PvP Crossplay Toggle On/Off: allows console players to play with PC players. You now have the option to be matched with either PC players or Console players independently.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/40ed33697ff25a3933bae3ac724534fb7aa54c26.png"/><br/><br/>🕺 Emotes 🕺 Strengthen the bond with your fellow Brothers with the new emotes! So go ahead and use them without moderation.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9b98b9c43156bec5c0a4230aa5f389ff1c43facd.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">That’s it for this month!</div><br/>Don’t hesitate to provide feedback on the upcoming content in the comments below, or on our official Discord Server, where almost 60K Space Marines share their thoughts on the game and find PvP or PvE matches every day. We’re eager to hear from you.<br/><br/>We’ll see you next month for another Community Update.<br/><br/><br/><i>With love &amp; respect,<br/><br/>From Saber and Focus.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects ⭐</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
