<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: Dev Blog: Arbites Talent Tree</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/543360117038383433</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello everyone!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is one of several developer blogs centered around different aspects of the recently announced upcoming class, <b>the Arbites</b>! This dev blog will focus on the class’ <b>talent tree!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve interviewed Design Director Victor and Game Designer Gunnar to get their insight into its design, and the three distinct styles that can be found in it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I’m Victor, I’m the Design Director at Darktide. I’ve been at Fatshark for 16 years, working as a designer in different ways.” - Victor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Gunnar and I am currently a Game Designer, but I started at Fatshark in 2018 as a Gameplay Coder on Vermintide, and a few years ago I switched to become a Designer instead.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">What was the process for making the Arbites’ talent tree?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The class rework from <i>Patch #13</i> was our first dive into the style of talent tree that we now have, with plenty of choices and flexibility but also a defined design goal behind it. We’ve learned a lot since then, and we hope that reflects on the Arbites’ tree.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We looked at the existing talent trees and we considered what worked and what was necessary to build the core skeleton of the tree. Once that was done, we built from that foundation into the various talents and choices you’ll have available. We purposely aimed to not overextend with the amount of nodes available and tried to focus on making each node meaningful and impactful.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“As you’re going through the tree you’re not just looking at stat bonuses, you’re looking at ‘what would your Arbites in the Warhammer: 40,000 universe do or be good at.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A key aspect that guided the design of the tree is enabling different Player Fantasies, the cool thing that each individual player is seeking to do while playing Arbites. This is what resulted in the three distinct gameplay styles mentioned earlier, but it also made us focus on enabling anything in between. The system is meant to be flexible and players are encouraged to come up with their own variation of a build, and that goes for all of the existing talent trees.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s up to the players to figure out and come up with their own sort of playstyle of fantasy of how THEY think their dream Arbites (in this case) functions.” - Victor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">The Three Paths</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Due to the nature of the talent trees, players are free to mix and match whatever talents they wish, provided they have the points and can path their way down the tree. However, as with our existing classes, there are three distinct gameplay &amp; combat styles that the main branches of the tree embody, and players can focus on these paths to specialize in these styles.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While they don’t have an official name, for this dev blog we can refer to them as <b>Subjugator</b>, <b>Exterminator</b>, and <b>Investigator</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Subjugator</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Following the right side of the talent tree you will find talents that will allow you to dive into the thick of combat to break apart the formations of the criminal scum, tapping into an identity akin to riot police. <b>These talents focus heavily on melee, staggering enemies and tanking.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peak at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hammer of Judgement:</b> Increased Attack Speed when hitting multiple enemies with a single Melee Attack.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Suppression Protocols:</b> Hitting multiple enemies with a single Melee Attack grants Toughness Damage reduction.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Target the Weak:</b> Enemies staggered by your Melee Attacks take more damage from Melee.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Exterminator</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Then we’ve also always been keen on fulfilling the shotgun fantasy of being this unstoppable force… walking down a corridor… just blasting everything that gets within range.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Relevant talents for shotgun gunplay can be found all over the talent tree, but it is the middle branch that has the most focus on it. <b>This gameplay style focuses on high firepower at close range</b>, blasting enemies of the Law with unflinching and implacable impunity.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peak at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Withering Fire:</b> Improved Ranged Damage after Reloading.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Up Close:</b> Replenish toughness on Close Kill.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>March:</b> Increased Movement Speed on Ranged Hit.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Investigator</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Found on the left side of the tree, <b>this playstyle focuses on eliminating high priority targets. Elites, Specials, even Monsters.</b> It’s about being ‘on the chase’, relentlessly hunting down a perp and bringing them the Emperor’s Justice.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The talents here are quite varied and flexible. There’s a mix of melee and ranged talents, as well as some support nodes. This is also where most (but not all!) of the talents related to the <i>Cyber Mastiff</i> are (although you can easily build into the Investigator branch without picking them!)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peak at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>No Escape:</b> Improved Damage and Movement Speed after killing a Special or Elite.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Canine Morale:</b> Killing enemies Pounced by your Cyber Mastiff grants Toughness and Toughness Damage Reduction to Allies in Coherency.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Serrated Maw:</b> Your Cyber Mastiff applies Brittleness on attack.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“That was also an important point \[...] We wanted to make sure that no matter if you went left, right or middle, you could always create a build that interacted with your Mastiff - So that you didn’t lock yourself out of playing with your Mastiff just because you also wanted to be melee focused, or because you wanted to do well with the shotgun.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While there’s three distinct identities to be found for the Arbites if you focus on a particular talent tree path, it’s important for us that <b>the tree itself remains flexible</b> and <b>allows players to combine talents</b> as they wish and develop the playstyle that best suits them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">For that reason, we took great care in making sure that any of the three options for your Combat Ability, your Blitz and your Coherency aura are <b>easily accessible regardless of what path you’re going down, and easily connect to any of the three paths.</b> You can then think of them as independent of those three playstyles, even if there’s a niche that they fit best into.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Coherency Aura</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Base Coherency Aura: Ruthless Efficiency</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Simple, but effective: this is the initial Aura for the Arbites and <b>it gives</b> <b>you and your Allies in Coherency a bonus to reload speed.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Part of the Squad</div><p class="bb_paragraph">For those focusing on the Cyber Mastiff, this option <b>makes your loyal companion count as an Ally for the purposes of Coherency.</b> Additionally, this talent also gives every Ally in Coherency a small bonus to <b>Toughness Damage Reduction</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Breaking Dissent</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This Coherency Aura <b>increases the damage dealt</b> by you and Allies in Coherency against <b>enemies that are currently Staggered</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Blitz</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Base Blitz: Arbites Grenade</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The default Blitz that all Arbites players start with is a standard issue <b>Arbites Grenade</b>. Compared to the Veteran’s frag grenades, it packs a <b>stronger punch</b> but has a <b>smaller radius</b> and <b>explodes on impact</b> rather than after a delay.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Remote Detonation</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Remote Detonation Blitz requires some coordination with your loyal companion! Upon activating it, <b>an electric discharge will burst from your Cyber Mastiff’s position</b>, dealing damage and heavy stagger impact.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It has quite a powerful stagger as well, so if your Mastiff is in the middle of attacking a Monster, like on the Plague Ogryn’s back, and you use it, the Plague Ogryn will stagger forward, disrupting its attacks. So it’s a lot about timing and keeping track of where your Mastiff is to get the most benefit out of it.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This Blitz also recharges on a cooldown</b>, rather than by picking up a Grenade Box.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Voltaic Shock Mine</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Choosing <b>Voltaic Shock Mines</b> as your Blitz will allow you to set up proximity mines on the ground at spots of your choosing. <b>As enemies draw close to it, it will activate and shock anything that comes near it for a sustained duration.</b> Compared to the Zealot’s Shock Grenade, it has a smaller radius but lasts a lot longer.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s one of the first Blitzes that we have that allow you to actually prepare for what’s to come. So if you come into an event area and you know that they’re gonna come from that door, or that direction, you can set up before engaging with the event.” - Victor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Combat Abilities</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Base Combat Ability: Nuncio-Aquila</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The default Combat Ability for the Arbites is <b>Nuncio-Aquila</b>, which brings forth a booming loudspeaker on a specific point you aim it at. It will blast the word of the Imperial Law at full blast, <b>empowering nearby allies and debilitating nearby enemies.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s like that scene in a movie, where the bad guys are hiding in a house and the police turn on the speakers and start telling them ‘You better give up, you’re surrounded.’, so they start freaking out.” ~ Victor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Castigator’s Stance</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This Ability turns you into an unstoppable juggernaut, unleashing the Emperor’s Judgement on the enemy as you walk menacingly forward, unflinching and unphased. <b>Entering the stance removes your ability to sprint, but increases your base movement speed and massively reduces your damage taken</b> for a time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Break the Line</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This Ability makes your Arbites perform a <b>short lunge forwards and then bash</b> every enemy in front of you with your equipped Melee weapon, <b>staggering enemies in a wide area in front of you</b> but without dealing any damage.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This Ability is on a <b>very short cooldown</b> (the shortest in the game!) so make sure to use it often to clear the way and subjugate the criminal mob!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Design and Development</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Were there any noteworthy changes in design that happened during development?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Originally, the base Combat Ability was going to be the <i>Castigator’s Stance</i>! However, during playtesting we found that it was very unintuitive for players just starting out, as visually it doesn’t really convey all of the effects that it has and it’s hard to tell how it’s meant to be used or what it’s doing for you. <i>Nuncio-Aquila</i> is far more straightforward and easier to understand without having to read its description, while still being sufficiently iconic for the Arbites, so we ended up changing the default Ability to that one.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Another thing is that at one point, a chunk of the tree was dedicated to talents about picking your Arbites’ armour, based on various options from the lore or tabletop. So you’d pick things like what kind of visor your Arbites wore, or from what areas was the gear made, and so on. In the end we weren’t happy with how that was turning out in practice, but it was an interesting aspect that we explored.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">At the time of writing, the talent tree was on version #16, so it’s definitely been through its fair share of iteration and polishing! Granted, as we approach the end development, the later versions involved less drastic changes and more fine-tuning and adjustments.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">What was the most fun part of designing the talent tree for you?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s just very fun to path down a talent tree. \[...] I think it’s even more fun to build it yourself; it’s a creative process of mixing and matching nodes or creating these crazy structures \[…] I just think it’s a lot of fun to create a tree, in itself.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“This goes for pretty much all of them: the first time most of the nodes are working and you can for the first time actually start theory-crafting in the game. Like actually making your first build, not just in theory. \[...] That’s the most fun I think, ‘cause that’s very exciting.” - Victor.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Of all the talents, what’s your personal favorite?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I really like the shock mine. It allows you to sort of pre-emptively strike, which I think is really cool. I also really like the Nuncio-Aquila; it allows you to ‘place’ a buff and then you can move in and out of it and you can be tactical about where you place it. - Victor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“One that is quite interesting is the Coherency - the aura - that is related to the Cyber Mastiff \[...]. As one of its effects it will make your Mastiff count as one in the coherency pool, so it more easily chains and you get the increased regeneration… and, if you have four Arbites with that aura, you can up to a total eight in your Coherency pool.” - Gunnar</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>That’s all we have for today! Stay tuned for the next Dev Blog on the Arbites! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extended Arbites Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/610914203288469922</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Aspiring Arbitrators of the Lex Imperialis! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As we promised with the release of the <u>Arbites Gameplay Trailer</u> at the PC Gaming Show, we’re bringing you a 7 minute long video showing gameplay of Arbitrators and their terrifying cybernetically-enhanced companions in their element, dispensing the Emperor’s justice with ruthless efficiency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Give it a watch! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" aq_vdjolpsy?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5b8a0fa6df58683b86cf4c8b5862f60ba2b2cf87.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Regrettably, as this extended gameplay video is not a trailer nor, as it happens, a teaser, we were unable to stir the caption guy from his profoundly deep slumber - so you will have to do without this time around!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Emperor Protects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join us for the Total War 25th anniversary celebrations</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497197576207993840</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/be39422cd27a3116b3ce77f4d8e689be00aaaa91.png"/><br/><br/>Hey Total War fans,<br/><br/>25 years ago, in a small one room office just down the road from where I write this message, Total War was born. The vision was rooted in a love for both history and strategy gaming, with the aim of seamlessly mixing the best parts of grand strategy and real-time tactical battles into a single experience where you truly felt like the commander of a vast empire.<br/><br/>During those early years Total War’s identity formed. The team were focused on authentic recreations of the most pivotal moments in human history from the Age of Antiquity through to the emergence of the great naval empires. As the genre evolved and our teams changed, we expanded into new territory by leaping into the fantastical; meticulously recreating Games Workshop’s iconic Warhammer World as a truly unique strategy experience.<br/><br/>There have been triumphs and tribulations throughout the years, and we’re honoured and humbled to be one of the few video game franchises that get the chance to celebrate such a huge milestone. Without your support this would never have been possible – so a massive thank you from all of us on this special day!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/812d90ece1ee1c37fbff348098652ce711c15ce2.jpg"/><br/><i>[Early 2000's at the old South Water where games from SHOGUN - MEDIEVAL II were developed]</i><br/><br/><br/>Some of you may remember from my update last year that we had plans to celebrate this anniversary in a meaningful way. Our teams are hard at work fine tuning a program of content that not only shines a light on past games but builds the foundation for us to begin revealing what we have planned for the future of Total War. And yes, this means the reveal of new games and content.<br/><br/>25 years of Total War will begin with a look back at our legacy. Taking place from August until the end of November, we’ll journey through each series that has been released since 2000. Expect content like retrospective video interviews, developer livestreams, sales across our entire catalogue, as well as fantasy and historical multiplayer tournaments. We also want to make this a celebration you can get involved in, so we'll be hosting giveaway competitions, inviting you to ask questions of our developers, as well as spotlighting your favourite mods and content creators who have helped make the Total War community what it is today.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b6e5e77e23906595528f385a024b26b119fbd6cc.jpg"/><br/><i>[2013, the launch of Total War: ROME II]</i><br/><br/><br/>Beyond celebrating the past, we plan on welcoming the future of Total War in a big way. Behind the scenes, we’re in the early stages of producing the Total War: 25th Anniversary Showcase, the first video presentation of its kind in our history. Taking place in early December, this show will unveil the new games that you can expect to play in the near and distant future, as well as introduce you to the development teams making them. We’ll have more details to share as we approach the end of the year, but whether you’re a fantasy or history fan, there will be plenty to enjoy!<br/><br/>Alongside all of this will be more WARHAMMER III content. Patch 6.2 arrives next week with a focus on Magical Items, Tides of Torment's third and final faction will be revealed in July, and we'll unveil some long-awaited content at the anniversary showcase. It's incredible to think that this series is now in its ninth year, and we look forward to sharing what we have planned for the future.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/bc0af97b03b074b0aca1cb9053540cac1eca4871.jpg"/><br/><i>[2016, the launch of Total War: WARHAMMER]</i><br/><br/><br/>What’s especially important to me this year is celebrating everyone who has made Total War what it is today. This includes all of you reading this message who have helped create the best community in gaming. Whether you’re playing our games for thousands of hours, watching our trailers, submitting bug feedback, or commenting on our socials, all of this has helped us build a game we all love.<br/><br/>It also takes an army of passionate and talented staff to take our games from concept to completion. Many of them talk about growing up with Total War; how it gave them an interest in history or the deep lore of Warhammer, and how it created a desire for them to work at Creative Assembly. They’re fans making the game they love, and I want to thank each and every one of them, past and present, for their contribution to making this milestone possible.<br/><br/>We hope you’re excited for the future.<br/><br/>Happy anniversary to you all,<br/><br/>— Roger Collum, Vice President of Total War<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/6c60f48ca9e3596a90de8949ddad412389e63e62.jpg"/><br/><i>[2023, pre-launch set created for Total War: PHARAOH]</i><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord Bluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.2 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497197576207993519</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
​​<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8cc53b799d86ba87c47165708323697e50658921.jpg"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>Next week, we’re expecting to publish the full release notes for Update 6.2, as well as the Update itself. Ahead of its release, we thought we’d give you a heads up on what to expect in this update, direct from William Håkestad, Senior Game Designer on Total War: WARHAMMER III.<br/><br/>In Update 6.2, look forward to extensive revisions to Magic Items, an introduction of the AI Improvements tested in the proving grounds, the introduction of a few new Magic Items, and the arrival of two new units: The Hobgoblin Bolt Thrower, and Blood Knights.<br/><br/>Sit tight for the full release notes next week with all of our improvements and fixes, and more on those two new units, but in the mean time here’s William with the Sports and Weather (and plenty of insight on our revisions to Magic Items).<br/><br/><i>Adam Freeman // Head of Community</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 PATCH 6.2 DEV BLOG 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites - Dev Blog: The Voices of the Lex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254834881</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With the introduction of Arbitrators to the Mourningstar and to celebrate the upcoming release of our new DLC we’re going to talk a bit about the voice work. Matthew Ward, Michael Knight and David Wahlund tell us what it’s like working with Darktide’s cast and the process we go through to get the performances just right.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What does the audition procedure look like?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Matthew Ward: </i>The casting process for Darktide never really stops. We’re always adding new characters to the game, which means that we’re always in contact with new talent, either for specific roles or with an ear to getting them involved at some point in the future when something suitable arises. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">As to how we find our actors, it’s always a mix. Some are from blind casting processes where our studio partners source self-taped auditions in line with a casting brief that we provide. Others we approach based on their past work in one medium or another, and more via recommendations from the recording studios or existing cast members. It’s a broad spectrum approach that over the years has given us a great mix of industry veterans, rising stars and the odd member of video game royalty.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In almost every case, the casting process ends with a directed live audition session at one of our studios, where we hone the actor’s interpretation of the character and hopefully hit that sweet spot of what works for them and matches what we’re looking for.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Of course, sometimes we hear something we didn’t <i>know </i>that we were looking for, and that’s really where the magic happens.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Michael Knight</i>: I’m constantly blown away by the talent we manage to draw to our game. I think it speaks to the effort that’s always been put into the voices we feature in the Tide games.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are there many Warhammer: 40,000 fans among the contenders?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It’s not something that we stipulate, but it’s always a bonus when it comes together that way, as the accompanying knowledge and enthusiasm always shows. Greg Jones and Alex Jordan are some examples from our longstanding cast, Michael Geary from our more recent intake. And of course, we have several actors who are familiar with the Warhammer: 40,000 setting from their work on other projects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK:</i> We also often find people who’ve never interacted with the IP being fascinated by its depth (and darkness!)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How specific are the VO directions? I've seen footage of actors holding prop guns and running on the spot to get the right dynamic and exertion sound for the lines. Is there any more like that?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>Some of our actors - and they know who they are - would probably refuse to record if they didn’t have their stand-in weaponry to tote around. I’m almost entirely sure that’s healthy, and I’ll always say that if there’s any chance that they might be listening. Or armed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">But seriously, everyone’s method is different. We record almost exclusively with head-mounted microphones, which allow the talent to roam - or literally throw themselves - around the recording booth if they want. Others get the motion and inflection we’re looking for while standing still or perched on a chair. Whatever gets the results, gets the results.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the weirdest direction that has been given to a VA for this game?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>I don’t know about “weirdest”, but something that always gets good results is directing the actor to shout at the recording engineer. It’s nothing personal (at least I hope not) but that always gets a great result. As far as I know we haven’t yet traumatised an engineer. In fact, most of them tend to end up grinning. People are strange.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>David Wahlund: </i>A maybe unknown and odd part of voice work is the exertions, efforts or grunts. It's the vocals that are not verbalized. In an action game we have a lot of these. When you swing the sword or get hit by a bullet for example. We have 15 different categories. Some efforts or grunts can be used in several different situations. For example a jump grunt can be used when you get pushed etc. These are all quite private sounds. Sometimes, especially when time is short, you might need to give an example yourself. That’s certainly weird the first time you do it. But by doing it yourself you might also take the edge out of the weirdness in the situation for the actor.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How does the performance process for the monstrosities work? How do you decide, or communicate to the actor "that's what we want this thing to sound like"?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>DW: </i>As Matt mentioned earlier, the actor's interpretation is super important. We need to give them as much details and context as possible so that they can be creative<b>. </b>When it comes to creatures or monster-like humans, animations and graphics play a big part. So if you can give as much visual information as possible that will certainly help. What does the mouth look like? How does the creature move? All details matter.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the average length of a recording session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW:</i> Because we ask for a lot of shouting from our actors - “Darktide Conversational Level” has become a bit of a running joke because it’s really not that conversational - most sessions run for an hour, although some of our hardier actors are happy to record for longer sessions. It’s a style of performance that’s very demanding on not only the voice but the whole body.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How many lines on average are recorded in a session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>We plan for around a hundred lines a session. Often that goes higher - when the actor’s in the zone - and sometimes it goes lower, especially when it gets <i>very </i>shouty. It’s always a balance between speed, quality and the actor’s comfort, with the latter being the absolutely most important of the three.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>We’re always adding new voice lines. How often does Fatshark have recording sessions?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It varies depending on what we want to capture. The Arbitrator sessions have been pretty full on (roughly 150 recording hours since the start of the year), but for other updates where we only need to add more NPC lines, it might just take a couple of hours. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We might not invite an actor back into the booth for months (or even years), or sometimes they’ll be in for a couple of hours for several weeks (or months) in a row. It’s all about matching our needs to their availability. Most are very busy individuals, so we try to get our asks in early.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading our dev blog on what goes into the performances and the work behind your new Arbites Class, releasing on <b>June 23, 2025 </b>on all platforms. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll do our best to answer them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
