<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog - Hive Scum: Narrative &amp; VO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/618810005643068610</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Hardened criminals, ruthless bounty hunters, violent psychopaths: Tertium’s Hive Scum are coming to Darktide as the next DLC class.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>In case you missed it, check out the </i>reveal trailer here<i>.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This part of a series of dev blogs breaking down different aspects of the Hive Scum! <i>Check out the </i>previous dev blog here<i>.</i> For this one, we’ve interviewed our writers <b>Matthew Ward</b> and <b>Michael Knight</b> about the <b>narrative &amp; lore</b> of the class, as well as each of the <b>Personalities </b>that you can pick.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I’m Mike, I’m the Narrative Lead for Darktide, and I’ve been with Fatshark for 3 years. \[...] When I’m not Narrative-ing for Darktide \[...] I have a massive Warhammer 40,000 and Horus Heresy collections that are still staring at me at about 40-50% grey… Which I’m reasonably pleased about! Y’know, that’s still a lot of minis painted.” ~ Mike</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I’m Matthew, I’m the Lead Writer and VO (Voice Over) Director for Darktide, which means I write most of the words, I cast most of the actors and direct most of the recording sessions.” ~ Matthew</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">The Story</div><div class="bb_h2">Who are the Hive Scum?</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Born and raised in Tertium, the Hive Scum are true criminals. The real deal. Each is a high ranking and lethal footsoldier in service to one of the cartels that run the city’s underbelly.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The cartels feel that they are the true rulers of Tertium. And the Hive Scum are their blademen and gunsmiths. These are the guys that do the wetwork. They’re the ones that settle the ‘disputes’ with hyper-violence whenever required.” ~ Mike</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While most don’t have formal military training, a lifetime surviving on these streets have taught them all they need to know to be killing machines, using unconventional weapons, toxins and underhanded tactics. And while some might deem them untrustworthy, they’ve got plenty of reason to use those skills against the Heretics infesting Tertium.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“This is their home. More than any other character we’ve introduced, these guys are all from Tertium, they’re from the Hive. This is their home that’s being destroyed.” ~ Mike</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">But make no mistake, Hive Scum are still dangerous, hardened criminals. Some might only be in it for the money, but a good amount of psychopaths are answering the call as well. Between them they have more than a few loose screws and a bit too much of an interest in bloodbaths.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Their place aboard the Mourningstar</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The conflict in Tertium only keeps escalating. Every day there are new horrors to face, ever more virulent plagues, and a constant fight that seems to accomplish nothing but drain the Inquisition’s resources… Even with the Adeptus Arbites providing reinforcements, the Warband needs help. Rannick instructed Explicator Zola to use her connections to the Water Cartel, establishing contact with a conclave of Cartel leaders and leveraging the Inquisition’s influence and their mutual enemy to mobilize their forces.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“...At least that’s what Rannick’s telling people.” ~ Matthew</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since the Hive Scum don’t come from a single organization, but vying cartels and criminal operations, they don’t have a representative on board to act as a figurehead. Zola, however reluctantly, has proven the ideal shepherd of this unreliable flock, but the Mourningstar has no shortage of shady characters, and sooner or later they're sure to get involved.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“But initially Zola is being the front of all this, isn’t she? She’s the one with the connections, specifically to the Water Cartel, and if nothing else… I don’t think she’s going to trust them at all when they’re out of her sight. So, that’s certainly where things will pick up. But where things head from there, who can say?” ~ Matthew</i></p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>The Voices</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“All these characters are from Tertium and it’s given us an opportunity to shine a little light on some of the bits of Tertium that we haven’t seen before. Particularly when you’re building your character. \[...] There will be tons of things for the lore hounds buried in there.” ~ Mike</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Like most of our other classes, the Hive Scum have three distinct Personalities to choose from, with a male and female version of each. Each Personality, with their quirks, beliefs and opinions, have very different bonds or rivalries with the Rejects, their handlers, and with each other.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The Ogryns tend to get on with everyone, because of course the Ogryns tend to get on with everyone. One of the Ogryns in particular \[…] if anything, he’s a little bit meaner than they are. \[...] but the Arbitrators are not particularly pleased to see the Hive Scum at all. And vice versa.” ~ Matthew</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">The Outlaw</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i><b>Voiced by Gordon Cooper and Lizzie Wofford</b></i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Perhaps in other circumstances, in another life, the Outlaw might’ve been a Hero… Or perhaps that’s just what they want you to think. Whatever the case, this is one criminal that might make you believe that there can indeed be honour among thieves. Might be someone you’d enjoy having a drink with! Maybe. If you keep an eye on them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">The Bounty Hunter</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i><b>Voiced by Theo Spofforth and Lucy Forrester</b></i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Guided by greed or just self-interest, the Bounty Hunter is in it for the money. Ruthless and efficient, they always get the job done and have plenty of experience. Neither hesitating to get their hands dirty, nor relishing in it: This way of life is strictly business. And profit. Lots of profit. At least, that was the case when the Cartels were operating normally, and the Outlaw does not take kindly to the Heretics’ unwarranted disruption of their operations.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">The Anarchist</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b><i>Voiced by Ian Conningham and Jess Nesling</i></b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Were they drawn to the criminal life because of their lust for violence, or did they snap at some point along the way? Whatever the case, the Anarchist is chaos incarnate, and not someone that any sane person would trust… even if we’re all on the same side now. The last voice you’d want to hear behind you in a dark alley… And probably the last voice you’d ever hear if that came to happen.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Bonus: Favorite part of working with the Hive Scum</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Our male and female characters \[of the same Personality] share something in the region of 80% of the same script depending on what we’re talking about, but hearing how the separation comes in through performance is absolutely splendid. Jess’s version \[of the Anarchist] sounds terrifying. Ian’s one sounds like he doesn’t understand why people think he’s terrifying. And that’s lovely.” ~ Matthew</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I got to help Matt write some of \[the scripts] this time, which was quite nice. When we write the conversations we literally write them backwards and forwards. Like Matt will write a series of opening lines of conversation, then I will add in the next line and then Matt will reply to that. So we don't necessarily know where that conversation is going to go beyond the first line and they're really organic, but we get to throw in little nods to background and stuff like some of the other war band members asking about the Conclave \[...] It’s fun to throw those things in.” ~ Mike</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for today, but keep an eye out for our next Dev Blog, coming soon!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Hive Scum here:</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermintide 2 is FREE TO KEEP until November 24!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/600795607306601669</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re not done with the 10 Years of Tide celebrations just yet! <b>Starting today and until November 24, Vermintide 2 is <i>Free To Keep!</i></b> Anyone with a Steam account may add it to their library and keep it forever, for free!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/552500/" width="850"></iframe>
</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Whoever hasn't had the chance to play Warhammer: Vermintide 2 will now get to dig into the hectic, intense gameplay and discover the breadth of content that awaits them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Throughout the years since its release in 2018, Vermintide 2 has expanded greatly and more than doubled its original content with several free DLCs, Quality of Life Updates, and new Game Modes such as Chaos Wastes and Versus. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The latest addition to the game just released yesterday, with Return to the Reik - a fan-favourite location from Vermintide 1, expanded and re-imagined for Vermintide 2. <i>In case you missed it, you can </i>read all about it here<i>.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Fangtastic Fortitude</div><p class="bb_paragraph">And to have even more fun, we’ve temporarily re-enabled the infectiousness of the Fangtastic Fortitude portrait frame! <b>Starting today until November 30</b>, winning a match where a teammate was wearing this frame will infect your account, adding it to your collection!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/04a853c0138bbc6ac12555477883438efdd4f286.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">And don’t forget there’s <b>Double XP</b> running until November 30, as well!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.9.1 Patch notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/600795607306601667</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash when joining an ongoing match of Return to the Reik.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As a heads up, we also identified a guaranteed crash on Tower of Treachery on PC, and are temporarily disabling the level until we can solve it.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CREATION WORKSHOP Launching Next Week!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/603047407120285762</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Soon there will be a slick <b>Level Editor</b>, and a <b>Workshop</b> full of custom maps and racetracks to play!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">If you couldn't already tell from past blogs, we're <b>very excited</b> to be releasing this feature. It's truly game-changing having map-making and workshop support for the Speed Freeks community, giving players power over what - and how - they play. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've had so much fun testing custom maps, and can't wait to see what amazing creations the community comes up with.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>THURSDAY, NOVEMBER 27th </b>will be the launch of <b>Creation Workshop</b>! 🛠️</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">WATCH DIS!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>IGN</b> have posted an exclusive video of Chris (<i>Game Director</i>) talking through some crazy <b>custom maps</b>, the <b>Mek Workshop</b> community, and the basics of how to use the <b>Level Editor </b>in Creation Mode. It's a great preview for what's coming 🔥</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" ix6q4ykxaoa?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">https://youtu.be/7ebudMvhwKo</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We want to give a big thanks to community member, and level-building maniac <b>The Friendly Killa</b> for creating so many insane maps to go with the launch of this massive update. If we show off a custom map to you guys before launch, there's a 95% chance it is one of TFK's. A true Mekboy 🛠️</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks as well to community members <b>Only//</b> and <b>Cybercobra</b> for also making maps and being stellar testers, and to the internal testing group in general who helped us make sure this update is as bug-free as can be.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We can't wait for you gits to get ya grubby hands on it!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3">If you'd like to apply for early access to the <b>Level Editor</b>, feel free to ping <i>@ChugzRokkitFuel</i> or <i>@Wired Gary</i> on the official Speed Freeks <b>Discord</b> for a chance to get building before the update drops.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">(-DISCORD LINK-)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, that's for sticking with the game to continue krumping gits 💥 and giving it plenty of wazza 💨</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Next week we have such sights to show you 👀</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER I &amp; II: Immortal Empires Unlock</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/364360/view/606425106922603146</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/8548992/3516bbcf93fb79a403b80fed2af283e093fd6bfc.png"/><br/><br/>Hi folks,<br/><br/>We’re excited to announce that on December 4th, Immortal Empires will become available to all owners of Total War: WARHAMMER I and II.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qqhc3mK06r0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">I. What are we doing?</div><br/>We’re making Immortal Empires, as well as The Lost God prologue campaign, available for all owners of Total War: WARHAMMER I and II. If you own either of those games, Total War: WARHAMMER III will automatically be added to your library, with Immortal Empires and The Lost God campaign unlocked. If you already own WARHAMMER III, nothing will change for you.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">II. Why are we doing it?</div><br/>As we celebrate 25 incredible years of Total War - and look ahead to WARHAMMER’s 10th anniversary in 2026 - we wanted to do something special. Your passion and support for this trilogy have made Immortal Empires possible, and we couldn’t be more grateful. Now feels like the perfect moment to open its gates and invite everyone to experience a piece of the adventure.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">III. When are we doing it?</div><br/>On December the 4th at 1600 GMT.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">IV. How will it work?</div><br/>WARHAMMER I and II owners will have ‘Total War: WARHAMMER III’ automatically added to their libraries. Through this you will be able to access both The Lost God prologue campaign and Immortal Empires. Please note; even if you don’t own the full WARHAMMER III experience you can also purchase any of its associated DLCs to play in Immortal Empires.<br/><br/>There’s a lot more questions you’ll have about how this works and what’s changing. For further details please see our FAQ below. If your question isn’t explicitly answered there please head over to our Discord where the community team will be on hand to help.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>– The Total War Team<br/><br/><hr/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FAQ</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">1. When is Immortal Empires unlocking?</div><br/>December the 4th.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">2. Is Immortal Empires a standalone game?</div><br/>No, you must own either Total War: WARHAMMER I, II or III in order to access Immortal Empires, and it will be accessible through the Total War: WARHAMMER III application in your Library.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">3. Can I purchase any DLC from the trilogy regardless of which game I own?</div><br/>Yes! For example; If you own WARHAMMER I, you can purchase DLC for WARHAMMER II and/or III and enjoy it within Immortal Empires. This makes it even easier to expand and tailor the experience to your liking.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">4. What happens if I already own WARHAMMER III?</div><br/>If you already own WARHAMMER III, your game experience will not change, and there is nothing you need to do in order to continue playing your owned content (but we would recommend recruiting a friend or seven and getting a co-op campaign rolling).<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">5. What has changed with this update?</div><br/>The primary change in this update is that owners of Total War: WARHAMMER I &amp; II will now have access to Immortal Empires and The Lost God campaign from WARHAMMER III.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">6. How do I access Immortal Empires from within WARHAMMER I and II?</div><br/>You don’t. Immortal Empires will not appear as a game mode in WARHAMMER I or II. In order to access Immortal Empires you will need to launch Total War: WARHAMMER III from your Steam or Epic Games library, which will be added to your library as part of this update.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">7. What am I gaining access to if I do not own Warhammer III?</div><br/>No. If you only own WARHAMMER I &amp; II, you are only gaining access to the Immortal Empires campaign and The Lost God prologue campaign. If you wish to own the other WARHAMMER III content such as the Realms of Chaos campaign and the Legendary Lords and their associated features, you must purchase the Total War: WARHAMMER III Upgrade Pack.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">8. How do I get access to WARHAMMER III’s other content?</div><br/>If you only own WARHAMMER I and/or II, you can purchase the WARHAMMER III Upgrade Pack to expand your gameplay experience. This pack includes:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">10 Legendary Lords, and all of their associated units and features.</div><br/>The Realm of Chaos narrative campaign<br/><br/>Multiplayer campaigns: The Realm of Chaos, Something Rotten in Kislev and Darkness &amp; Disharmony <br/><br/>Mirrors of Madness game mode<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">9. How do I remove Total War: WARHAMMER III from my Library if I don’t want it?</div><br/>Follow the usual procedure for removing a game from your library by contacting Steam, Epic or Microsoft store support.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">10. How is Immortal Empires different from WARHAMMER I?</div><br/>Immortal Empires features a massively expanded map containing all of regions from the entire trilogy. Rebuilt from the ground up, its the biggest Total War sandbox ever made. is the culmination of a decade of the Total War: Warhammer franchise, and the ultimate way to play it.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">11. Does this mean my PC meets the requirements of WARHAMMER III?</div><br/>Please check the Total War: WARHAMMER III Upgrade Pack page to see the minimum specs needed to play Immortal Empires and The Lost God campaigns.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">12. Which parts of Total War: Warhammer III’s multiplayer can I now access?</div><br/>If you only own Total War: WARHAMMER I &amp; II, you can play Immortal Empires in co-op multiplayer with up to 7 friends.<br/><br/>If you wish to play multiplayer battles, you will need to purchase the WARHAMMER III Upgrade Pack.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">13. Does this impact Family Sharing via Steam.</div><br/>No, you’ll be able to continue sharing your Total War: WARHAMMER content via this mechanism as normal.<br/><br/>This list is not exhaustive and if you have any further questions please jump into our Discord where our community team will try to get any query answered as soon as possible. For any technical issues please submit a report through our Bug Reporting Forum here.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
