<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide in "Labor of Love" Category</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737316601</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/dc1031436ce4eba20e6fd78fc5e1e0b980d6c549.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominate Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader for Outstanding Story-Rich Game!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4453592738017837094</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
THIS IS NOT A DRILL<br/><br/>In the grim darkness of the far future, there is only Steam Awards 2024. The nominations are already open, and the Imperium needs you to join this fight.<br/><br/>Brothers and sisters, we kindly ask you to support us and nominate Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader for <b>Outstanding Story-Rich Game</b>!<br/><br/>The nomination voting is open until the end of the Autumn Sale.<br/><br/>Сommand headquarters expresses its gratitude to all our players. Your love and support burns brighter than the Astronomican. <br/><br/>Thank you for being with us.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/996f04d42894b2511080beafd6b1500a1ee2157f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Awards 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4464851103138185238</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Brothers and Sisters of the Imperium</div><br/>The time has come to make your voice heard! <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is contending for <b>“Game of the Year”</b> at the Steam Awards, and we need your support to claim this honor.<br/><br/>We believe <i>Space Marine 2</i> shows our dedication to the <b>Warhammer 40k universe</b>, it’s also a testament to the essence of gaming: epic stories, exhilarating combat, and unforgettable moments with your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8d256e7a6b8cf622a2ec52c07aa7435456603885.jpg"/><br/><br/>If you felt the thunder of a bolter, the weight of a chainsword, and the call of the Emperor, show your devotion by nominating us for <i>Game of the Year</i>. Together, we march to victory!<br/><br/><i>- The Space Marine 2 Team</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction Trailer Soundtrack Giveaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647304814</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Greetings Total War fans and music lovers!<br/><br/>Today we're giving away the Omens of Destruction trailer soundtrack for you to listen to whenever you like! 🎼<br/><br/>Claim it now in the Rewards section of the CA Community  👇👀<br/><br/>🔗 https://community.totalwar.com/rewards<br/><br/><br/>Enjoy!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/544391b73e1cf6128b3e629c5ac08b97841fe4d8.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lore Post: Skaven Chronicles Part 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954129476</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/4802c9c37e1bb84c6f1a9f24b89ae1838544cb26.png"/><br/><br/><i>Few things are constant among the Skaven, but their scheming and plotting is one of them. While our Heroes may have foiled Rasknitt, there’s plenty other vermin are eager to hatch their own devious plans. The farsqueaker, a verminous piece of Skryre engineering, allows some of these would-be masterminds to instantly communicate across vast distances with their networks of agents and spies.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Skaven Chronicles: Part 3</div><br/>Good news, master!<br/><br/>The warlocks have devised a new means of powering the farsqueaker. It runs now on warp energy harnessed directly from the collapsed Skittergate, with only the tiniest of chances of an explosion. Less than one in five! It is better than the scamper wheel they used before, they say, and I am minded to agree as listening to their huffing and whining at the controls while I try to think-speak was growing most tiresome. <br/><br/>But this is not the good news. No-no. The Gutter Runners we hired from Clan Eshin have finally made good on their promise to find-find the Furless Five. <br/><br/>Their leader, a treacherous shadow of a rat who calls himself Sly Scarpaw, claims to have followed two of the brigands’ number, the man-thing, Kruber, and his mulish companion, Bardin, to a drinking place in the nearby man-burrow of Bögenhafen. Naturally, I demanded to know what progress he had made in locating this ‘Taal’s Horn Keep’ that the locals we torture squeal so excitedly about, but he made his usual excuses. <br/><br/><i>‘It is home to a powerful magician.’</i><br/><br/><i>‘Illusions and shadows keep it from being found.’</i><br/><br/>And other such chitterings.<br/><br/>I sense your skepticism, master, and I share it. Clearly, Sly Scarpaw over-promised and now makes excuses for his failures (behaviour that would shame the tail off an honest skaven), but better a mouse in the hand than two in the burrow as my litter-mother used to say. So I found-sniffed my sword and my shield and gathered thirty of your fiercest clanrats and scurried off to Bögenhafen-place to see-smell for myself if Scarpaw squeaked true.<br/><br/>There, indeed, were Bardin and Kruber, engaged in the ritual consumption of weakly poisonous beverages and bouts of play-fighting that the furless races seem to find pleasurable. This was even better than I dared hope, master! Not only were the hapless duo separated by many miles from their mighty allies, but they were intoxicated to boot. I ordered the clanrats to secrete themselves around the tavern, ready to heroically slaughter any who dared stagger from its doors. <br/><br/>My plan was foolproof! <br/><br/>But if there is one thing I learned from the late, unlamented Skarrik Spinemanglr, it is to never underestimate a fool. <br/><br/>It is truly a testament to the visionary nature of your plan, master, the sheer audacity of it, the genius, that it occurred to quite a lot of other skaven as well. <br/><br/>It was while we were bravely seeking out hiding places that we found ourselves, in my case literally, treading on the tails of a second skaven war-party who had got there just ahead of us. These skaven followed a chieftain called Snifh Weeviltongue, who had with him a not-inconsequential host numbering well over hundred clanrats – did I say a hundred? I meant three hundred – supplemented by two dozen hulking stormvermin and a veritable arsenal of Clan Skryre weaponry. <br/><br/>To this moment, I am unsure if this was not some elaborate ploy of Sly Scarpaw to sell us out, for no sooner had a poisoned throwing star left his paw on its way to Snifh Weeviltongue’s left eyeball than a ratling gun started up from somewhere across the street and there were several hundred clanrat warriors squealing murder and going for it claw and tooth. <br/><br/>The tavern caught fire, I am not certain how, and before a rat could squeak Pestilent Brotherhood there was the Ubersreik Two with axe and halberd, carving their way through fearless skaven warriors still more intent on murdering each other.<br/><br/>I had, of course, bravely and selflessly distanced myself from the worst of the fighting, the better to report the good news to you, most demanding of despots.<br/><br/>The Furless Five live! To be kill-stabbed by you at some later time. <br/><br/>While they sleep, maybe.<br/><br/>Just a thought.<br/><br/><i>Your tireless and ever-loyal servant, Skratch Dirtnose…</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
