<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>To Become the Flagship's Blood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4607833411864881491</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/14b20a67abfdb5b81aa5a7988e5571b70dc2107f.jpg"/><br/>The Imperium is founded upon death and bloodshed, and maintained only by the further sacrifices of Humanity. There are those for whom death is a way of life, and death cults of many types can be found on worlds across the Imperium. They revel in holy slaughter, dedicating their victims’ souls to Him, offering up blood sacrifices to the God-Emperor so that He might answer their prayers.<br/>The practices of these Death Cults are dark and terrifying. Common folk maintain a superstitious fear of ruthless assassins who specialise in ritual murder, self-mutilation and bloody communion. Vague omens can make these zealots target seemingly innocent people just as easily as obvious enemies of the Imperium. <br/><br/>One such cult lurks within the bowels of the von Valancius flagship. For years, the ascetic and inscrutable servants of the Bloodspun Web have protected the dynasty from enemies aboard the vessel, stalking the threats hiding in lower decks and spraying the bulkheads with the blood of their victims.<br/>Kibellah is a masterful assassin whose talent and fanatical devotion to the Undying Emperor has earned her the title of the Second Spinner of the Bloodspun Web. Since childhood, she has dedicated herself to rigorous training of mind and body, perfecting the art of the blade dance and mollifying her emotions. Kibellah has no desires, only duty; no fear, only purpose. She is the perfect instrument of death, and this undying servant of the Undying Emperor has left the shadows to become the Rogue Trader's personal bodyguard.<br/><br/>Her specialised blades and ritualistic arts are at the Lord Captain's service, as is her sophisticated mind. She recognises the signs sent by the Emperor, even through the veil of mundane reality. Her world is a realm of riddles and blood that interweave and resolve into momentous insight. To that end, she bears the greatest relic of the cult: a sacred deck of the Emperor’s Tarot. The cards speak the will of the Undying One and reveal the names of those who must depart. Every new reading reveals ever more clearly that the greatest moment of her life is at hand. The Immortal Emperor holds an exceptional destiny in store for His servant, who is now ready to step into the future.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Unique Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4607833411861542500</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain! <br/><br/>It is time to fill the ship's log with impressions of your journeys. Please share with us of places vivid and memorable, that have marked your memories the most, in our location survey: <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/G3QFYXF</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a2e0b47f65aedcbc7468f87d3043385efe187499.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's what you need to know about Twitch Drops!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4595447878570873602</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Space Marines! ⚔️</div> <br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is almost out! For the release of the game, we partnered with Twitch and many streamers to reward you with exclusive content! From September 4 until September 30, you may earn up to 2 skins simply by watching <i>Space Marine 2 </i>content on any Twitch channel, and an additional one by watching a VIP partner. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c7b33a92e0ea3b312234f2fa3b0f11f67cc39516.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">How do I receive my drops? 🎒 </div> <br/>To receive the drops you earned, it’s very simple. You just have to link your Twitch and  PROS  accounts. If you do not have a Twitch account, you can click  here  and then on “Sign Up” to create your account. If you do not have a PROS account yet, you can create one  here  by clicking “Sign In or Register Now”!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Who should I watch to get these Twitch Drops? 🎥</div> <br/>As part of the Twitch Drops program, you will be able to obtain numerous skins for <i>Space Marine 2</i> by watching somebody playing the game. To earn the first two skins, you’ll have to watch any streamer showcasing <i>Space Marine 2</i> for one hour on two separate occasions from September 4 to September 30. The first one must happen between September 4 and September 16 (to earn the <b>Porphyr Shield Chainsword</b> skin), and the second must happen between September 17 and September 30 (to earn the <b>Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle</b> skin).<br/> <br/>A third skin, the <b>Porphyr Shield Powerfist</b> skin is obtainable if you watch one hour of content between September 4 and September 30 among the list you can find by clicking on the website   here. Just scroll a little bit, and you’ll find the VIP streamers list! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What cosmetics can I get? 💎</div> <br/>The <b>Porphyr Shield Chainsword</b> skin will be available as a Twitch Drop from September 4, 12:00 AM CET to September 16, 11:59 PM CET. To earn this skin, you will have to watch one hour of <i>Space Marine 2</i> content.<br/> <br/>The <b>Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle</b> skin will be available as a Twitch Drop from September 17, 12:00 AM CET to September 30, 11:59 PM CET. To obtain this skin, you will need to watch one hour of <i>Space Marine 2</i> content.<br/> <br/>The <b>Porphyr Shield Powerfist</b> skin will be obtainable from September 4, 6:00 PM CET to September 30, 11:59 PM CET. To get this skin, you will have to watch one hour of <i>Space Marine 2</i> content made by the Twitch Streamers with VIP drops activated (list available on  this website) during that time frame.<br/> <br/>Please note that it should be one hour in total, meaning that you won’t have to do it in one sitting. You can watch 20 minutes a day, 40 minutes the next, and it will count!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Support a Streamer and get an exclusive pistol skin! 🔫</div> <br/>If you gift a minimum of 2 subscriptions of any tier to any channel streaming <i>Space Marine 2</i> between September 4, 6:00 PM CET and September 30, 11:59 PM CET, you will receive a <b>Porphyr Shield Bolt Pistol</b> skin!<br/> <br/>You may find every information you need and answer to Frequently Asked Questions, as well as Terms and Conditions on this beautiful website  here.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4595447878567687876</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/>We can hardly believe it ourselves, but <i>Space Marine 2</i> is just DAYS away from launch! The excitement is truly palpable and it feels almost surreal to be this close to sharing the game with you after years of hard work, dedication, and passion from the entire team.<br/><br/>Humanity is about to witness the return of its fiercest defenders, and as we all gear up for the imminent launch of <i>Space Marine 2</i>, we wanted to provide you with some final insights and updates to prepare you for the epic adventure that lies ahead. 💥<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">A collaborative labour of love</div><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is the result of an incredible collaboration between Saber Interactive (the studio), Games Workshop (the Warhammer license owner), and Focus Entertainment (the publisher). We’ve all poured our hearts into this project, and we're incredibly proud of what we've created together. But what truly makes this journey special is the support and enthusiasm you've shown since the game was first announced back in 2021 at The Game Awards. Let’s all take a moment to relive this epic moment:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TgxVQRTXtz0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>And look where we are now! Our latest trailer, The Angels Of Death, just premiered today. We hope you loved it! In case you missed it:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/buT5yuGwg8s?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>For years, your dedication has been incredibly motivating and fueled us every step of the way, making the development process as enjoyable and rewarding as it has been demanding and challenging. And for that, we thank you. Our greatest hope is that when you step into the boots of a Space Marine, you'll feel the same thrill and excitement that we did while bringing this game to life. We can’t wait for you to finally experience <i>Space Marine 2</i> and we hope you will cherish it as much as we do.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Your remaining questions</div><br/>Over the past few months, we did our best to tackle your most urging questions in our Community Updates, and this one is no different. This month, we’ve also shared more about customisation and revealed <i>Space Marine 2</i>’s roadmap.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">About playing with teammates in all 3 different modes…</div><b>Will my progression be saved when playing offline?</b><br/><br/>Be reassured, in Campaign Mode, your progression will be saved on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X|S while playing offline.<br/><br/>For Operations Mode (PvE), you will need to be online to ensure your progress in PvE is saved. Offline progression will not carry over to your next session, so make sure you're connected to keep all earned perks, skins, and other rewards.<br/><br/><b>Does cross-platform save work well?</b><br/><br/>➡️Yes, cross-platform saves are fully functional through the platform Prism Ray Online Services (PROS).<br/><br/><b>Is PvE/PvP playable via LAN?</b><br/><br/>➡️LAN play will not be supported.<br/><br/><b>Will the game support crossplay, and can it be toggled off?</b><br/><br/>➡️Yes, full crossplay between Steam, Epic Games Store, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X|S players will be supported from Day One.<br/><br/>You will be able to play the Campaign and PvE modes without any restriction, but note that for fairness and balancing purposes, crossplay for the PvP mode “Eternal War” will be split between PC players in one pool (Steam &amp; EGS) and console players in the other one (PlayStation 5 &amp; Xbox Series X|S).<br/><br/>You will also have the option to disable crossplay functionality if you prefer to only play with those using the same platform as yours.<br/><br/><br/><b>Are there any restrictions for what classes can be played in “Operations” mode (PvE)? What about “Eternal War” (PvP)?</b><br/><br/>➡️Your squad may only include one Space Marine of each class in “Operations” mode. In “Eternal War” mode, there is a limit of two players per class and per team.<br/><br/>No all-Sniper teams, but you'll have plenty of strategic variety! 🎯<br/><br/><b>Is there friendly fire when playing Campaign, Operations or Eternal War modes?</b><br/><br/>➡️There is no friendly fire in either of the 3 game modes.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What are the performances like? on PC and on Console?</div><br/><b>On PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X|S, is there a performance mode, quality mode, and what FPS can we expect? And other specific details.</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Quality Mode: 4K resolution at 30FPS.<br/></li><li> Performance Mode: Up to 60FPS at 1080p.<br/></li><li> Please note that on Xbox Series S, the Quality Mode will allow for 1440p at 30FPS and the Performance Mode will not be available.</li></ul><br/><b>What kind of communication tools will we have in-game?</b><br/><br/>➡️There is a Voice Chat, a Communication Wheel with preset messages and a Text Chat (exclusive to PC versions) to facilitate your exchanges with your teammates.<br/><br/><b>Does the game support the haptic features of the DualSense controller?</b><br/><br/>➡️We support force triggers on the DualSense controller, but not haptic feedback at launch.<br/><br/><b>What about RayTracing, DLSS, and other PC-specific technologies?</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> DLSS2 / FSR2: Available at launch.<br/></li><li> DLSS3 / FSR3: Planned for post-launch.<br/></li><li> RayTracing / HDR: Not supported.</li></ul><b>Is the game compatible with wide screens?</b><br/><br/>➡️Wide screen support is planned. While it won't be available right at launch, we're working on implementing it by the end of September.<br/><br/><b>Will the game be playable on Steam Deck?</b><br/><br/>➡️We are working on official Steam Deck support, but it's not ready yet. We’re currently targeting the end of the year for full Steam Deck support.<br/><br/><b>Will the game have official mod support (e.g., NexusMods, mod.io)?</b><br/><br/>➡️We currently have no plans for official mod support.<br/><br/><b>What anti-cheat system is in place?</b><br/><br/>➡️We will be using Easy Anti Cheat on PC at launch.<br/><br/><b>Does the game use DRM software (ie. Denuvo…)?</b><br/><br/>➡️No.<br/><br/><b>Will the game be available Day One on GeForce Now?</b><br/><br/>➡️Yes.<br/><br/><b>Will the game be available through the Xbox Game Pass?</b><br/><br/>➡️No.<br/><br/><b>Can the HUD elements be removed? Is there a “Cinematic” mode available?</b><br/><br/>➡️Though there is no actual “Cinematic” mode available where all of the UI elements can be turned off at once, all of them can be individually displayed or removed through the Settings menu. Only the crosshair, enemy attacks and missions objective pop-ups will be visible.<br/><br/>Three options are available: ON, OFF or DYNAMIC, with “Dynamic” meaning that the UI elements you’ve chosen will appear when you need it most (for example, during combat) and disappear otherwise.<br/><br/><b>Will I be able to pre-load the game, and if so, when will pre-load be available?</b><br/><br/>➡️Your ability to pre-load Space Marine 2 depends on your platform of choice:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> On Xbox Series X|S: Pre-loading is already available. You will download the full game as soon as you pre-order either of the game’s versions. The game will unlock on September 5 or September 9 depending on whether you purchased the Standard, Gold or Ultra Edition.<br/></li><li> On PlayStation 5: Pre-loading will be available on September 3 at 11:00 AM UTC if you have pre-ordered the Gold or Ultra Edition, to allow you to play up to 4 days before the official release. If you have pre-ordered the Standard Edition, pre-loading will start on September 7 at 4:00 PM UTC and the game will unlock on September 9, the day of release.<br/></li><li> On PC: Pre-loading will not be available.</li></ul><b>Do I need to have played the first Space Marine to enjoy Space Marine 2?</b><br/><br/>➡️Having played Space Marine is absolutely not a requirement for playing and enjoying Space Marine 2. Both games’ storylines can be enjoyed individually, and both offer brutal third-person action gameplay. You may be missing some very specific references, but that won’t stop you from enjoying the bigger picture at all.<br/><br/><b>What are the game's accessibility options?</b><br/><br/>➡️You can enlarge the size of subtitles to make them easier to read, as well as 3 different colour blind modes.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><br/><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b5b0ae756c2171567017bd6a4bdf87ce24ce73d4.jpg"/> </div><div class="bb_table_td"> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0b8bc6ebb2fc69a25cb1d1cbf67d112370fed415.jpg"/> </div></div><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/af51f5b81e1a916d8d3371aba47dabb2cd12edc7.jpg"/> </div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c54660f656199cf8de06cdaf9597b66e9c503931.jpg"/> </div></div></div><br/><b>Which languages will be available?</b><br/><br/>➡️The game is fully voiced in 7 languages: English, French, German, Spanish, Russian, Japanese and Mandarin Chinese.<br/><br/>➡️All the texts are available in no less than 17 languages: English, French, German, Italian, Russian, Czech, Polish, Ukrainian, Spanish, Spanish (Latino-American), Japanese, Korean, Brazilian Portuguese, Mandarin Chinese, Traditional Chinese, Thai and Turkish.<br/><br/><b>At what time does the game release?</b><br/><br/>➡️Mark your calendars:<br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/46e95b4a522a9cf95003578f2a8f44221cbffd4c.jpg"/> </div><div class="bb_table_td"> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6c2c24009b14d11a81c195821a935baa8982a0cd.jpg"/> </div></div></div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e9e873b9212bae044fab53fb1bc5679a0bd59d4f.jpg"/><br/><br/>We hope we've answered any questions you may still have. Should you have any more, feel free to check our previous community updates or ask us directly on Focus Together, our community platform, or on the official <i>Space Marine 2</i>’s Discord server!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The final countdown…</div><br/>As we prepare for launch, we want to thank each and every one of you from the bottom of our hearts. Your support throughout development has meant the world to us, for years, and it has been a constant source of motivation to bring you the best possible game and successor to <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine</i>. On behalf of the entire Focus Entertainment team and Saber Interactive: a huge thank you. It’s been incredible and we can’t wait to see you take up arms as Space Marines.<br/><br/>Now, prepare your chainswords, charge your bolters, and get ready for the fight of your lives.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Emperor protects!</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Itemization Rework Q&amp;A Part 2 - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4613462277073357858</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><br/>As promised, here is the next batch of questions and answers regarding the Itemization Rework coming after summer. Again, we collected over 11 pages of feedback, questions and general concerns after the release of the last Q&amp;A dev post.<br/><br/>As a refresher, the two new systems are the Mastery system and the Empower system (formerly Expertise). (There is still a chance that these names change.)<br/><br/><i>Note: All of the questions we’re answering in this are pulled directly from the comments on the Forums, Reddit and Discord. We kept the players’ wording instead of writing our own questions.</i><br/><br/>In case you missed our previous comms:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Introduction to the Itemization Rework - Dev Blog<br/></li><li> Itemization Rework Q&amp;A Part 1 - Dev Blog</li></ul><br/>OK, let’s dive in!<br/><div class="bb_h1">Questions From Players</div><div class="bb_h2">Blessings / Transferring Weapons to New Systems</div><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>If one has a complete blessing library for a specific weapon type, could one expect to have their Mastery fully completed, or will you add mandatory grind?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>If you have a complete blessing library for a specific weapon, you will have all your Mastery for that specific weapon completed. There will be no additional grind added.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>How does the every Tier of one Blessing gets calculated into the ““head start in Mastery””? Do players get more points in Mastery from one single blessing if they have unlocked all Tiers of that blessing or does only the highest Tier count?"</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>All tiers are taken into consideration for the specific weapon family. With higher tiers being more important in the calculation. To reach max Mastery, you will only need 70-80% of all the blessings available.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>With the itemization rework can we expect a rework toward Melk with or after the update since most of us use it to gain higher tier blessings faster than anything else?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Yes, Melk will give higher-tier equipment than before (higher-tier referring to blessings and power of the weapon).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>In the new crafting system, you mentioned we can unlock the blessing that we want using the Mastery experience. If I want to unlock a Tier 4 blessing of a Lasgun, let’s say Ghost, do I have to unlock ALL Tier 1 to Tier 3 blessing of Lasgun to access the Tier 4 blessing page? Or I can simply unlock Tier 1 to 3 of Ghost and access Tier 4 Ghost without unlocking other blessings?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>No, you will not need to unlock all Tier 1 to Tier 3 blessings of a Lasgun to access the Tier 4 blessing page. There will be a minimum requirement of lower tiers blessing to be unlocked before reaching the next tier level, but it will not be all of the previous tier.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>How much my 1084/1214 blessing will contribute to weapon Mastery?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>All 1084 of your blessings will be taken into account, then. All unlocked blessings will be taken into consideration when transferring a weapon to the new system.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>What happens to my weapons in the inventory that have blessings on them i dont have unlocked? Will they just stay the same and i only cant use the blessing on another weapon?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Items will remain the same, therefore the unlocked blessings will not be taken into account when it comes to the translation of the blessings library into Mastery. Any unlocked blessings will exist on the weapon itself, and they cannot be transferred to another weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>When StrawHat said that players will begin with a headstart in the new system, does that mean that we won’t have access to blessings we did previously and therefore forcing us to grind for the tiers all over again? (This is from the last Q&amp;A post.)</i><br/><i>You did not answer my question regarding the transfer.</i><br/><i>I currently have collected all level 4 blessings for my favorite weapon. But I did not collect any level 3, nor any level 2, nor any level 1 blessing.</i><br/><i>After the transfer, will I still have access to all level 4 blessings?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Yes and no. It will depend on how you are building your new Mastery track. In the worst-case scenario, playing 1 or 2 games would be necessary to have it all. We saw that having T1/T2 blessings were less common for those at max level. It would feel too punishing if we put too much weight on asking players to have these lower tiers in order to reach max Mastery. Therefore, we will be weighing T4 blessings in such a way that you won’t encounter that grind.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question (More of a Comment)</b><i>That weapons are still locked at 380, and that you’ll still be hunting for the ‘perfect’ stat distribution base weapon is kind of insane, to be honest.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>With the new system, players will be able to freely change between marks of a weapon family as they progress in the Mastery track. This means the player will only be searching for the base weapon with the stats distribution they want, rather than searching for the preferred stats distribution on each individual mark.<br/><br/>That said, a player will be able to play with the best weapon they’ve found, and then with minor investment be able to change to a better weapon once it’s been found. And any progress within that weapon family will be transferred to the new weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question (More of a Comment)</b><i>Worse still, the ‘broken locks’ are time gated. Want to freely swap around T4 blessings? Gotta have maxed Mastery on that weapon family first.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b>This is incorrect. Players will get access to the best blessings before reaching the actual end of the Mastery curve.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Well it’s a pretty huge difference that you can’t change perks or blessings, nor can you cash in a blessing into a library. It’s all about the grind first.</i><br/><i>And depending on if Strawhat was careful with wording or not, you have to unlock all T1 blessings to unlock a single T2 blessing.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will not need to unlock all the T1 blessings to unlock a T2 blessing. Furthermore, you can change around the perks and blessings on a weapon as much as you want.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question (More of a Comment)</b><i>Also, allowing Hadron to still consecrate items to let people brute force it with enough currency is a good choice, but if you still need to unlock the blessings when an entirely new family of weapons comes out, that will still hamper people who like to experiment, even if the Mastery grind isn’t that long.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>As players are free to unlock the blessings they want (in whatever order they want), players will be able to fairly quickly unlock the blessing choices they want to experiment with after just unlocking a few tiers of Mastery of a weapon. Since we are adding more tiers to each blessing and making them all available at tier 1, players will quickly be able to unlock the gameplay potential of a blessing. This allows players to be able to create the build they want sooner. Though it will take a bit longer to unlock the most powerful version of that build.<br/><br/>We are also introducing a “sacrificing” system to allow players to sacrifice weapons to get Mastery experience for a weapon family. This gives players even more avenues to gain Mastery within a weapon family outside of only playing with the weapon. For example, when a new weapon comes out, players will be able to sacrifice ANY other unwanted weapon, even those from completely different weapon families, to get a headstart on Mastery. Note: If it’s the same weapon, more Mastery XP will be given versus if it’s a different weapon.<br/><br/>TL;DR: Weapons a player no longer wants can be sacrificed to get a headstart.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>When you say: This system will merge all weapon types/families, meaning players will be able to freely switch between different marks of the same weapon type. For example, once you own an Infantry Lasgun, you have the potential to unlock all the possible marks for this weapon and switch from one mark to another.</i><br/><i>What does this mean for weapons:</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>That are on their own: Staves and Kickback/Rumbler (Don’t share blessing, but do models)</i></li><li><i>That may not be on their own: Plasma; Bolter; Ogryn Power Maul; Crusher; Hack Shotgun…</i></li><li><i>Weapons that do share but still might get a variant: Stub Revolver; Chainsword; Chain Axe; Evicerator…</i></li></ul><b>Answer</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Weapons that share models/skins, but not blessings: These will be classified as different weapon families, therefore getting each their own Mastery track with separate blessings trees.</li><li>Weapons that currently have only one mark: These will still be classified as separate weapon families and get their own Mastery track, just without marks to unlock.</li><li>Weapons that have multiple variants: Variants of the same weapons are called “marks”, and will be included in the same weapon family. Each family will receive its own Mastery track. Different weapon families that are similar, like Chainswords and Eviscerators, will still have separate Mastery tracks. Some blessings will appear in multiple Mastery tracks, but each blessing needs to be separately unlocked in each blessing tree.</li></ul>One nice aspect of the new system is that if/when we do add more marks to a weapon family, they will be unlocked in the Mastery system instead of diluting the loot pool and making it harder for you to obtain the weapon you want from the loot system. Previously, every time we released a new mark for a weapon, we made it harder to get any specific weapon from the loot pool. This new system removes that problem and will make the addition of new marks purely positive.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Stats</div><b>Question</b><br/><i>"Every weapon is created with a pool of stat points that have been distributed in the different stat buckets, and every weapon has the same potential maximum number of stats that can be distributed.”</i><br/><br/><i>Is there a way to remove points from one “bucket” to be added to another? while still keeping the “investment” cap from expertise in mind?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>No, it will not be possible. Each weapon will be generated with varied maximum caps on each stat.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Is the overall power of weapons remaining the same, or will a newly-maxed-out weapon with this new system give more damage/power/stats?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The overall power of the weapons will remain the same as before.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>What makes a weapon go to 380?</i><br/><i>Let’s say I roll the dice at Brunt’s and get a 340 Force Sword. That sword can now go from 340 to 380? If so, how? By consecrating it?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Every weapon will now have the potential to reach 380. The Power system (formerly referred to as Expertise) is where you can make it happen by empowering your weapon through the use of crafting materials.<br/> <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>When viewing any weapon, it will show the weapon’s maximum potential stats. These stats will be randomly determined. It’s up to the players to decide if the weapon profile is interesting enough for them to commit and increase the stats until reaching this potential (which are then applied to the weapon through the Expertise system).</i><br/><i>Does this mean that we CAN choose to fill things from 0 to cap for each different stats?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You cannot select where the points are going exactly, it will be an automatic increase for each stat.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Empower (formerly Expertise) / Mastery</div><b>Question</b><br/><i>I think the gist is that the blessings we’ve unlocked get converted to ‘Mastery XP’ that we can then spend to put whatever we like on new weapons?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Correct, the blessings on a specific weapon are converted into Mastery XP for that weapon family. However, the Mastery XP is bespoke to the weapon family and it is not universal (to be applied to any weapon you like).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>So if I understood correctly, we long-time players skip “Mastery”, go straight into “expertise” and can attribute perks and blessings freely at material costs?</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The idea is weapons will be converted over to the new system. The Mastery XP is determined by the blessings that are unlocked on the weapon itself. The more blessings unlocked or the higher tier of the blessings unlocked, the more XP that is gained for that weapon family. Then, using crafting materials, players can Empower their weapons and apply the perks and blessings as they wish.<br/><br/>Also, we have mentioned above the ability to sacrifice unwanted weapons in order to increase Mastery XP at a player’s discretion.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>I was wondering to get the maximum amount of Mastery XP for a weapon group, do I need to unlock every single tier of every blessing for getting the maximum XP for that? I have all tier 4 blessings but never bothered with lower tier blessings.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Players will not need every blessing of a weapon family to achieve max Mastery upon introduction of the new system. We are looking at something like having all T4/T3 blessings will be enough to max Mastery.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Would it be possible to add a new item filter in the shops and crafting menu which sorts items from their max potential to lowest? That would help a lot when min maxing gear!</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Well, every weapon will have the max potential of 380. However, we will be adding a filter so players can sort by the current Power rating.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Is this update going to come with balancing changes? A lot of us feel the game is too easy, even on the hardest difficulties right now. Weapons like the plasma gun, revolver and knife makes the experience way too easy, for instance. I understand you guys try your best not to nerf players, but sometimes the players really do need it. Some enemy buffs would be welcomed also.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>We are aware of this problem and try to balance the game accordingly. Still, as different players will see balance changes differently, we want to be careful and try to respect all player’s investments in the game. Hopefully, the Mastery system will allow us to be a bit more forthright with balance changes, since it will make it easier for players to adapt to any new meta in the game without having to rely on RNG systems to do so.<br/><br/>We are also working on other features that will address this problem, but more news about them in the future when they’re in a more solid state to share.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Looks good! Genuinely hope there are cosmetic rewards for fully mastering a weapon. Come on FatShark! Just one free skin, just a scrap.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>There will be a cosmetic reward per weapon family.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/><i>Are curios also implemented in this system somehow? Currently you can’t even buy them from the Brunt’s store.</i><br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Curios are not a part of this overhaul. We are however thinking of ways to make curios more fun and engaging. We felt that we would tackle the bigger problem of weapons first and give curios the time and attention that they need to become a more interesting part of a player’s loadout at a later time. However, we will note that the locks will be removed from Curios, as well. This means players will be able to change anything at any time, aside from the base property of the item itself.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Alright, that answers the second batch of questions. If anything in this post is unclear, please let us know below. This will help us collect more feedback and ensure we answer them in our future posts.<br/><br/>Thank you!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
