<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked &amp; Loaded - Weapon, Blessing &amp; Class Changes Balancing Patch Notes - PT2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4567301015221694996</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9a6bdf70a892123b7c7274f8db99087850d015a7.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone,</div><br/>Ahead of our next update Unlocked and Loaded, we wanted to share these patch notes related to balancing for Weapons, Blessings and Classes within Darktide. The purpose is to give players a sneak peak at what to expect, as well as to receive feedback on what we’ve prepared.<br/><br/><b>Important Note: These are not the complete patch notes for the upcoming update, Unlocked and Loaded. We’ll have more to share on the release date, September 26. This is to simply give players a look ahead at the balancing!</b><br/><br/><i>Depending on player feedback, we’ll be able to tweak values for the changes below. If there are any larger reworks requested, we’ll likely be unable to make those changes before the update. However, we’ll be able to revert anything that feels out of place / doesn’t feel right for players and remove it from this patch.</i><br/>So, grab some tea or coffee and give this a read. Let us know what you think! We’ll be reading the comments.<br/><br/>There are 28 pages of notes here, so we’ll need to do a part one and part two. <b>This is Pt.2! </b> Please check out Pt. 1 here.<br/><br/><b>Important Note: These are not the complete patch notes for the upcoming update, Unlocked and Loaded. We’ll have more to share on the release date, September 26. This is to simply give players a look ahead at the balancing!</b><br/><br/><i>Depending on player feedback, we’ll be able to tweak values for the changes below. If there are any larger reworks requested, we’ll likely be unable to make those changes before the update. However, we’ll be able to revert anything that feels out of place / doesn’t feel right for players and remove it from this patch.</i><br/>So, grab some tea or coffee and give this a read. Let us know what you think! We’ll be reading the comments.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn</div><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn Talent Updates</div><b>No Pushover</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reworked. New Description:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Your Pushes have +250% Stagger. Can only trigger once every 8s.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Old ‘No Pushover’ was frankly not up to par. Maybe this spices things up a bit?</i><br/><b>Big Boom</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explosion Radius: 22.5% to 27.5%.</li></ul><b>Reloaded and Ready</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ranged Damage: 12% to 15%.</li><li>Duration: 6s to 8s.</li></ul><b>Bruiser</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Combat Ability Cooldown: 5% to 4%.</li></ul><b>Massacre</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration: 6s to 10s.</li></ul><b>Steady Grip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 3-5% toughness regeneration per second.</li></ul><b>Delight in Destruction</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage Resistance per Stack: 10% to 8%.</li></ul><b>Too Stubborn to Die</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Health Threshold: 25% to 33%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn Talent Tree Updates</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Swapped places of Toughness Damage Reduction Operative Modifier, and Suppression Boost Operative Modifier, on the Bottom Right part of the Tree.</li></ul><b>Thick of the Fray</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. It is now included in Point-Blank Barrage per default.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Additional Miscellaneous Talent Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Zealot class base Aura “The Emperor’s Will” remained active after selecting the “Loner” Aura talent.</li><li>Fixed an issue where an additional stack of the Psyker “True Aim” talent was gained when inflicting stagger to an enemy during the cast of “Brain Rupture”.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>A stack of the talent will still be gained when completing the cast.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the Psyker “Mettle” talent to only receive a maximum of 1 stack for each Critical attack, regardless of the amount of enemies hit by the attack.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Extended Availability of Weapon Families for Human Classes</div>As part of this update, we will extend the availability of specific weapon families to all human classes (Veteran, Zealot, Psyker).<br/>These weapons were previously locked to only one or two of the three classes, but will now be usable by all of them.<br/>However, we made sure that the weapons that are key to the identity of each class will remain uniquely available to that class.<br/>We hope that this will expand the gameplay experience and open up new interesting builds for players!<br/><br/><b>Detailed list:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Turtolsky Heavy Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Veteran and Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Maccabian Duelling Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Veteran and Zealot</li></ul></li><li><b>Orestes Assault Chainaxes</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Braced Autoguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Accatran Recon Lasguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Zealot</li></ul></li><li><b>Combat Shotguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li></ul><b>This is Pt.2! </b> <b>Please check out Pt. 1 here.</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked &amp; Loaded - Weapon, Blessing &amp; Class Changes Balancing Patch Notes - PT1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4567301015221622988</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9a6bdf70a892123b7c7274f8db99087850d015a7.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone,</div><br/>Ahead of our next update Unlocked and Loaded, we wanted to share these patch notes related to balancing for Weapons, Blessings and Classes within Darktide. The purpose is to give players a sneak peak at what to expect, as well as to receive feedback on what we’ve prepared.<br/><br/><b>Important Note: These are not the complete patch notes for the upcoming update, Unlocked and Loaded. We’ll have more to share on the release date, September 26. This is to simply give players a look ahead at the balancing!</b><br/><br/><i>Depending on player feedback, we’ll be able to tweak values for the changes below. If there are any larger reworks requested, we’ll likely be unable to make those changes before the update. However, we’ll be able to revert anything that feels out of place / doesn’t feel right for players and remove it from this patch.</i><br/>So, grab some tea or coffee and give this a read. Let us know what you think! We’ll be reading the comments.<br/><br/>There are 28 pages of notes here, so we’ll need to do a part one and part two.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weapons</div><div class="bb_h1">Weapon Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">Thunder Hammers</div><br/>The Thunder Hammer family of weapons suffered for being over-specialized into the Monstrosity-removal niche, while being very underwhelming against most other threats and in general failing at keeping up with the increased intensity of high difficulty missions.<br/><br/>With the following changes we aimed at rebalancing the weapon to preserve its single-target focus, but also to make it more well rounded and more exciting to use in all situations.<br/><br/>While the upper end of the damage on Special activated attacks against the Unyielding armor type has been lowered to prevent unhealthy 1-shots of Monstrosity enemies, the damage against Carapace Armour has also been significantly increased to conversely be able to more effectively handle Elite enemies like Maulers and Crushers (potentially dispatching them with a single well placed hit).<br/><br/>The Light activated attack damage profiles have been improved to reward weakspot hits and to more easily eliminate any human-sized enemy.<br/><br/>The self-stun after a Special activated attack has been significantly reduced on both marks, and differentiated between Light and Heavy attacks.<br/><br/>This will make it way easier to find a window of time to deliver its devastating activated blows without being overly punished by other enemies.<br/><br/>Also, most Light and Heavy attacks have been improved in their damage and reach, to make the weapon more reliable in dealing with lesser enemies when not activated.<br/><br/>Both marks of the Thunder Hammer weapon family have also received some additional targeted changes, explained just below!<br/><br/><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>It’s also a hammer.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All Marks<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the damage profile for Light Special activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from {2.0,3.0} to 2.0.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the damage profile for Heavy Special activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from {3.0,5.0} to 3.0.</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 1.0 to 1.5.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the headshot/critical damage bonus multiplier on all Light attack profiles:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Finesse boost from 0.3 to 0.5.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the damage of the Light Strikedown attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {150,300} to {180,350}.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the damage of the Heavy Relentless attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1st target attack power distribution from {150,300} to {180,350}</li><li>2nd target attack power distribution from {80,160} to {100,200}</li><li>3rd target attack power distribution from {50,100} to {75,150}.</li></ul></li><li>Fixed several windup and attack actions which could be canceled by sprinting.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Crucis Mk II Thunder Hammer</div><br/>The Crucis Mk II mark always boasted the higher damage compared to its Ironhelm Mk IV brother, but delivering that damage to the intended target was often difficult due to the horizontal direction of its Heavy attacks and the effective lack of cleave on Special activated attacks.<br/><br/>This led to not uncommon scenarios where a Heavy activated attack could be completely absorbed by a single intercepting Poxwalker, leaving the target enemy unscathed.<br/><br/>To give players more control on the situation, we added a new overhead Heavy attack to the weapon, only chainable after the Special activation action for a short period of time.<br/><br/>Also, a small amount of cleave was added to the Heavy activated attacks, meaning that the swing will be able to go through at least one lesser enemy.<br/><br/>These changes combined will make the weapon more reliable in delivering its devastating damage to the intended target.<br/><br/>Additionally, the damage profile of the Light 3 attack has been improved to reward players completing the attack chain instead of resetting it.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes - Crucis Mk II Thunder Hammer</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the Self-stun duration after connecting with a Special activated attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light stun from 1.3 to 0.3</li><li>Heavy stun from 1.3 to 0.5.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the hitboxes and damage windows for most attacks to be more aligned with their animations.</li><li>Improved reach for all Light attacks and the Push follow-up attack.</li><li>Tweaked the speed and chain time for the Light 1 and Light 2 attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slightly reduced the attack speed</li><li>Improved chain time to Light 2 / Heavy 2 attack start from 0.65 to 0.55.</li></ul></li><li>Light 2<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the attack speed.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li>Added a bespoke improved Light Strikedown damage profile to the Light 3 attack<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution {200,380}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured 0.75</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Slightly improved reach for all Heavy attacks</li><li>Changed so that the Heavy 2 attack chains into Light 3 / Heavy 1 instead of Light 1 / Heavy 1 to give an alternate access to the improved Light 3 attack.</li><li>Special activated attack changes:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a small amount of cleave to Heavy activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cleave distribution {1.0,3.0}.</li><li>Attack power distribution {400,800} when cleaving.</li><li>Cannot cleave through Elites, Specialists, Monstrosities and Captains.</li></ul></li><li>Added an attack start chain from the Special activate action, chaining into Light 1 and a unique Strikedown Heavy attack with a vertical animation.</li><li>Improved the duration of the Special activate buff from 4s to 5s.</li><li>Significantly improved the Light activated attack properties:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {300,600} to {400,750}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured from 0.3 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour from 0.3 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Maniac from 0.3 to 0.5</li><li>Overall Finesse multiplier curve from {0.25, 0.75} to {0.65, 1.15}.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Ironhelm Mk IV Thunder Hammer</div><br/>The Ironhelm Mk IV received few additional specific tweaks, but will still benefit greatly from the overall changes to the Thunder Hammer weapon family.<br/><br/>The improved reduction in self-stun duration after a Heavy activated attack will help in further distinguishing it as the more nimble and well rounded Thunder Hammer mark.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes - Ironhelm Mk IV Thunder Hammer</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the Self-stun duration after connecting with a Special activated attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light stun from 0.7 to 0.25</li><li>Heavy stun from 0.7 to 0.4.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the hitboxes and damage windows for most attacks to be more aligned with their animations.</li><li>Improved reach for all Light attacks and the Push follow-up attack.</li><li>Slightly improved reach for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 3 attacks.</li><li>Improved the Light activated attack properties:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {250,500} to {300,600}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured from 0.75 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour from 0.75 to 1.0</li><li>Overall Finesse multiplier curve from 0.25 to 0.65.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Boltgun / Bolt Pistol</div><br/>In this release we added a set of targeted buffs aimed to increase the overall reliability of the iconic Boltgun and Bolt Pistol weapons, but also to significantly improve their performance against specific enemy types and in various situations.<br/><br/><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are aware of some issues regarding the aim of the bolt weapons, particularly in the recoil and sway when shooting continuously.<br/><br/>Unfortunately the issues are rooted quite deeply in the interaction between multiple different systems, so a complete fix was not possible for this release. We are going to continue investigating a solution and provide an update on our progress at a later date.<br/><br/>In the meantime, we have added some tweaks on the Sway and hitscan behaviors which should at least alleviate part of the issue.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Both Families</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the intensity of the Sway from 1.0 to 0.3.</li></ul></li><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make the weapon to be overall slightly less unwieldy when aiming, and also make it less likely for the aim position to be significantly displaced when transitioning from hipfire to ADS.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extended the radius of the hitscan for the bolt projectiles.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will make the hitscan detection to be more generous and allow for shots that would have slightly missed the target to still be considered a hit.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the bolt properties to ignore limbs on non-Monstrosity enemies when the projectile trajectory would have also hit their torso or head.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will avoid situations where a bolt could be intercepted by the limbs of the enemies even when aiming at their center of mass, resulting in heavily reduced damage.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 0.4 to 0.5 (both near and far range).</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Infested from 0.5 to 0.9 (near) / 1.0 (far).</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Bolt-type weapons were penalized when shooting against Infested enemies. This tweak will normalize the damage in order to make them more reliable against this armor type.</i></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Locke Mk IIb Spearhead Boltgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the wield speed, from around 1.9s to 1.6s.</li><li>Improved the stagger properties of subsequent hits on the same target.</li></ul></li><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will make it easier to open up Bulwark shields and reach stagger thresholds on other hard to stagger enemy types.</i></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Godwyn-Branx Pattern Bolt Pistol</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added cleave properties to the bolt projectiles<ul class="bb_ul"><li>From no_cleave to {1.0,3.0}.</li></ul></li></ul></li><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it possible for the shot to hit the intended target instead of being fully absorbed by even a single minor enemy.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced some chain timings after the Special Push action:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Chain to hipfire Shoot from 0.56 to 0.4</li><li>Chain to Unwield from 0.54 to 0.4</li><li>Chain to Special from 0.9 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></ul><div class="bb_h1">Additional Weapon Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>“Devil’s Claw” Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extended the block property of the Special parry to remain active for a short period of time at the start of the riposte attack.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stamina is still drained as normal when blocking attacks during the additional block duration.</li><li>0.2s additional block duration.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is to avoid situations where the player could still be hit on a well timed parry if multiple attacks were incoming at the same time.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Slab Shield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added ranged block properties during the Push action, in addition to the already existing melee block properties.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Block properties of the shield were still maintained during a Push, but only against melee attacks. Now the Block properties of the Push action should also cover ranged attacks.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Special bash attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stagger_category from “melee” to “uppercut”.</li><li>Impact power distribution increased on the first 3 targets:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>[1] from {16,33} to {30,70}</li><li>[2] from {8,20} to {10,60}</li><li>[3] from {6,18} to {10,35}.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Branx pickaxe Special attack is a Bash instead of the Pull used in the other two lighter marks, but its stagger output was often underwhelming against bigger targets. After the changes, this attack should now be more reliable in staggering any kind of non-Monstrosity enemy, even when in groups.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.87 to 0.8</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 1.05 to 0.8</li><li>Heavy 2 into Block from 0.69 to 0.62</li><li>Push follow-up attack into Block from 1.1 to 0.9.</li></ul></li><li><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.63 to 0.6</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 0.9 to 0.7</li><li>Heavy 2 into Block from 0.63 to 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Reduced the windup time for the Heavy 1 attack when chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.8 to 0.72.</li></ul></li><li><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.56 to 0.55</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 0.75 to 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Reduced the windup time for the Heavy 1 attack when chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.71 to 0.6.</li><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Push follow-up bash attack when hitting a Weakspot.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it easier to quickly control single enemies with carefully aimed attacks, at the cost of some Stamina.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Agripinaa Mk XIV Quickdraw Stub Revolver</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the Cleave properties of the shots.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cleave distribution from {1.0,2.0} to {2.0,4.0}.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li><b>Rashad Mk II Combat Axe / Antax Mk V Combat Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the damage and stagger against Maniac enemies for all Heavy attacks.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 1</li><li>Armor impact modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The Heavy attacks of the Combat Axes were unfairly penalized against Maniac type enemies, to the point where it was often preferable to use Light attacks instead.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Achlys Mk VIII Combat Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned the Heavy 2 and Heavy 3 attacks to the Heavy 1 attack profile.</li><li>Tweaked the damage and impact modified against specific armor types for all Heavy attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 0.6 to 0.8</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from 2 to 1.75</li><li>Armor impact modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Heavy attacks of the Achlys Mk VIII Combat Axe are now all aligned to use the “spike” version of the attack profile, which also got some rebalancing with improved damage against Carapace and lowered damage against Unyielding. This will make the mark a bit more unique compared to the other two versions of the Combat Axe.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Lucius Helbore Lasguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the buffer time for the hipfire shoot input to avoid unintended inputs to be registered when exiting the ADS stance immediately after shooting.</li><li>Aligned the minimum ammo usage for minimally charged shots between marks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Mk I from 3 to 2</li><li>Mk II unchanged at 2</li><li>Mk III from 4 to 2.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li><b>Lucius Mk II Helbore Lasgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned the Sway values to the other marks.</li></ul></li><li><b>Tigrus Mk XV Heavy Eviscerator</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the windup timings for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attacks, depending on the attack chain:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 1 chained from base start / Light 4: 0.4 (unchanged)</li><li>Heavy 1 chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.76 to 0.65</li><li>Heavy 2 chained from Light 1 / Heavy 1 from 0.85 to 0.65</li><li>Heavy 2 chained from Light 3 / Push follow-up from 0.6 to 0.4.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>These changes will reward opting to use Heavy attacks when going further down into attack chains, instead of resetting the chain.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Orestes Assault Chainaxes</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slightly improved the Dodge Distance range on the Mobility stat, from {0.8-0.9} to {0.9-1.0}.</li><li>Slightly improved the Block cost.</li><li>Slightly improved the Sprint cost at lower Defences stat values.</li></ul></li><li><b>Orestes Mk XII Assault Chainaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the movement speed curve for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attack windups.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make the Heavy attacks of this mark more dynamic and easier to use in more situations.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Push follow-up attack.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This attack was meant to be a quick interrupt against enemy actions, but often failed at staggering key enemies like Ragers. The new values should allow to more reliably create space, still at the cost of Stamina due to the Push.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the hitbox of the Heavy 2 attack to be more aligned to the animation.</li><li>Shock Mauls<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the buffer time windows for attack inputs to be more lenient.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it less likely for Light attack inputs to be lost if performed too early after attacks with long chain times.</i><br/>Weapon Bug Fixes<ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Ironhelm “Hacker” Mk IV Assault Shotgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the aim direction could be incorrectly moved if switching to another weapon immediately after firing.</li></ul></li><li><b>Lawbringer Mk VI Combat Shotgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Special shell shots failed to be correctly scaled through the Damage stat.</li></ul></li><li><b>Force Staves</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Celerity Stimm would fail to raise the charge speed of the secondary charged attacks.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Blessings</div><div class="bb_h2">Updated Tiered Blessings</div>Blessings that were previously only available in 1 or 2 Tiers, have now been expanded upon to be available for all 4 tiers, with relevant values.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Pool Additions per Weapon</div>The number of Blessings available for the different Patterns has not been consistent, with some Weapons like the Blaze Force Sword having 12 different Blessings, while others like the Ogryns Power Maul only having 4. With the introduction of the new Itemization System we’re trying to make this more even between the Weapons. Going forward, all Weapons should have at least 8 different Blessings to choose from.<br/><br/><b>Braced Autogun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ceaseless Barrage</li><li>Roaring Advance</li><li>Inspiring Barrage</li></ul><b>Spearhead Boltgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puncture</li><li>Terrifying barrage</li><li>Fire Frenzy</li></ul><b>Assault Chainaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Heavy Eviscerator</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Tactical Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Slaughter Spree<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Guaranteed Critical Hit (Next Attack) on Weak Spot Critical Hit Kill.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Relentless Strikes<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+4-10% Power for 2s on Hit (Same Enemy). Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Agile<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Refreshed Dodge Efficiency on Weak Spot Hit. +2.5-10% Melee Weakspot Damage.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Heavy Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Chained Deathblow<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+5-20% Critical Chance for 3s on Weak Spot Kill.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Bladed Momentum<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hitting multiple enemies in one sweep gives 4-10% Rending for 2.5s. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li>Thrust</li></ul><b>Duelling Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Relentless Strikes<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+4-10% Power for 2s on Hit (Same Enemy). Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Agile<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Refreshed Dodge Efficiency on Weak Spot Hit. +2.5-10% Melee Weakspot Damage.</li></ul></li><li>Thrust</li></ul><b>Purgation Flamer</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Everlasting Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Critical strikes fill the current clip with 2-5 bullets from your ammo reserve.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Penetrating Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1-4% Rending on Burn Stacks.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Purgatus Force Staff</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Penetrating Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1-4% Rending on Burn Stacks.</li></ul></li><li>Showstopper</li><li>Blaze Away</li></ul><b>Surge Force Staff</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Transfer Peril</li><li>Sustained Fire</li><li>Surge</li></ul><b>Helbore Lasgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Hot-Shot<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Weak Spot Hits gain 20-50% Cleave.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Armourbane<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Target receives 2-8 Stacks of 2.5% Brittleness on Charged Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Heavy Laspistol</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Concentrated Fire<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to +2-5% Critical Chance on Chained Ranged Weak Spot Hit (Any Target).</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Desperado<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+5-12.5% Critical Chance for 2s on successful Dodge.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Latrine Shovel</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Smackdown<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+7.5-15% Critical Chance for3s on Special Action Hit (Staggered Enemy).</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Bully Club</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: No Guts, No Glory<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+50% Toughness Regeneration per second for 2-5s on Elite Special Action Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Grenadier Gauntlet</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Disruptive<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hitting at least 3 enemies with your secondary attack grants 15-30% bonus to Power on melee attacks for 3.5s.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Explosive Offensive<ul class="bb_ul"><li>6-15% Power bonus for 5 seconds after hitting multiple enemies with your weapon special explosion.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Gauntlet Momentum<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+2-5% Power for 1.5s on Chained Melee Hit (Any Target). Max Stacks 10.</li></ul></li><li>Point Blank</li></ul><b>Twin-Linked Heavy Stubber</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Terrifying barrage</li><li>Fire Frenzy</li></ul><b>Power Maul</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Power Surge<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Special Attacks on Armored Enemies cause an additional Shockwave. Special Attacks have +10-25% Explosion Radius.</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li><li>Perfect Strike</li><li>Supercharge</li></ul><b>Battle Maul &amp; Slab Shield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Last Guard<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Block Breaks push Enemies, 15s cooldown. -15-30% Block Cost.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Offensive Defence<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gain a stack for each stamina spent blocking. Your next attack gains +4-10% melee power per stack and consumes one stack. Last 3.5s. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li><li>Perfect Strike</li></ul><b>Rumbler</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Explosion Zone<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+3-6% Explosion Radius for every shot fired during continuous fire. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Shrapnel<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+1-4 Bleed Stacks from close range explosions.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Clonk<ul class="bb_ul"><li>15-30% Reload Speed for 3s on Projectile Weakspot Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Plasma Gun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Power Blast<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gain between 2-5% and 10-25% Crit Chance based on charge level when firing.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Energy Leakage<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increases power up to 7.5-20%, scaled on overheat.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Focused Cooling<ul class="bb_ul"><li>-30-60% Heat generation on Critical Hit.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Optimised Cooling<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased Charge Speed scaling inversely with Heat Level. 4-10% to 20-50%.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Crusher</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li><li>Thrust</li><li>Slaughterer</li><li>Thunderous</li></ul><b>Power Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Thrust</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Changes</div>To make all Blessings have a difference in strength between Tiers, we’ve changed the following Blessings.<br/><b>Unstoppable Force</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also provides 2.5-10% Heavy Melee Damage based on Tier.</li></ul><b>Power Cycler</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 2.5-10% Melee Stagger based on Tier.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Bug Fixes and Additional Changes</div><b>Punishing Salvo</b><br/><i>Specifically on the Infantry Autogun.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bug where the description was displaying the wrong values. “…14-20%…” to “…35-50%…”.</li></ul><b>Trauma</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed issue where the Stagger values were too low. Was 7.5-15%. Is now 14-20%.</li></ul><b>Headhunter</b><br/><i>Specifically on the Recon Lasgun.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bug where the description was displaying the wrong values. “…2-5%…” to “…3.5-5%…”</li></ul><b>Dumdum</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the stacks and duration could be refreshed by Damage over Time effects (e.g. Burn).</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Those effects will still be affected by the damage bonus of the blessing.</i><br/><b>Terrifying Barrage</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the blessing failed to trigger for secondary charged attacks of the Equinox Mk III Trauma Force Staff and the Nomanus Mk VI Surge Force Staff.</li></ul><b>Adhesive Charge</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the bonus damage of the blessing failed to be applied.</li></ul><b>Deflector</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the block cost reduction bonus to also be active when blocking melee attacks</li></ul><b>Overpressure</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also affects Damage over Time effects (particularly, Burn).</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Classes</div><div class="bb_h2">Psyker</div>When we started overhauling the Classes for Patch #13, we did it one Class at a time. The first one we tackled was Psyker. As a result, the Psyker ended up with a lot less Passive Nodes available compared to the others, resulting in less room to Customize your preferred build. In this Patch, we hope to remedy that.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Psyker Talent Updates</div><b>Scrier’s Gaze</b><br/>To further define this Ability as the go-to choice for those wielding non-Force Staff Ranged Weapons.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants Suppression Immunity for its initial Duration.</li></ul><b>Malefic Momentum</b><br/>To incentivize weaving between Warp Attacks and Regular Attacks<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants +4% Damage to non-Warp Attacks for 8s after a Warp based Kill. Stacks 5 Times.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Psyker Talent Tree Updates</div>With more nodes having to fit into the tree, we’ve restructured it a bit. All builds you have been playing up until now should still be available for you, but you might have to take a slightly different path to get there.<br/><b>Inspiring Presence</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">New Psyker Talents</div><b>Warp Unbound (As a modifier to Scrier’s Gaze)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Scrier’s Gaze prevents you from overloading from Perils of the Warp during its lingering effect.</li></ul><b>Charged Strike (As a modifier to Smite)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Your Heavy Melee Attacks electrocute enemies, damaging them, without stunning them.</li></ul><i>On the Left Side of the Tree:</i><br/><b>Perilous Assault</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to 50% Weapon Wield Speed (based on Peril).</li></ul><b>Channeled Force</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+30% Damage to Force Staff’s Primary Attacks after Fully Charged Force Staff Secondary Attacks. Lasts 5s.</li></ul><b>Empyric Shock</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6% Warp-Damage Taken by victims of your Force Staff’s Primary Attack. Max Stacks 5. Lasts 10s.</li></ul><i>On the Right Side of the Tree:</i><br/><b>Lightning Speed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+10% Melee Attack Speed.</li></ul><b>Warp Splitting</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to 100% Cleave, based on Peril.</li></ul><b>By Crack of Bone</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Melee Weakspot Kills Quell 5% Peril and Reduce further Peril Generation by 20% for 4s.</li></ul><b>Souldrinker</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Killing an Enemy with Soulblaze restores 5% Toughness and grants 5% critical Hit Chance for 5s.</li></ul><i>On your way to the Warp Siphon Keystone:</i><br/><b>Penetration of the Soul</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+10% Rending on Warp-Attacks when above 75% Peril.</li></ul><b>Empyric Resolve</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>-40% Peril Generation. -30% Toughness Replenished.</li></ul><i>On your way to the Disrupt Destiny Keystone:</i><br/><b>Tranquility Through Slaughter</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Non-Warp Ranged Critical Hits Quell 4% Peril.</li></ul><b>Surety of Arms</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+25% Reload Speed while below 75% Peril. On Reload, generate up to 25% Peril based on the Percentage of the Clip Restored.</li></ul><i>Above Empowered Psionics:</i><br/><b>Crystalline Will</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Overloading through Perils of the Warp no longer knocks you down, but you still take the appropriate Corruption Damage.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/462990330877a8383215cb4fbf599d5270a93510.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Veteran</div><div class="bb_h2">Veteran Talent Updates</div><b>Skirmisher</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration 5s to 8s.</li></ul><b>Opening Salvo</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>First Percentage of Ammo: 10% to 20%.</li></ul><b>Kill Zone</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ranged Damage: 15% to 20%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Veteran Talent Tree Updates</div><b>Vanguard</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. Replaced by ‘One Motion’.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>Vanguard wasn’t performing as we wanted, and it was mostly viewed as a blocker to the talents below it.</i><br/><b>One Motion</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+25% Weapon Swap Speed.</li></ul><b>Relentless</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. It is now included in Executioner’s Stance per default.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Relentless was pretty much a must pick for the viability of the Ability.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Zealot</div><div class="bb_h2">Zealot Talent Updates</div><b>Invocation of Death</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed from 1.5s Cooldown reduction on Melee Critical Strike to: +175% Cooldown Regeneration for 4s on Melee Critical Strike.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>We missed the mark on the last change to ‘Invocation of Death’, leading to frustration. We hope this brings it to a satisfying and balanced state.</i><br/><b>Sainted Gunslinger</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reload Speed per Stack: 3% to 6%.</li><li>Max Stacks: 10 to 5.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The purpose of these changes is to allow the talent to reach its full potential faster.</i><br/><b>Vicious Offering</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 7.5% to 10%.</li></ul><b>The Voice of Terra</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 2.5% to 4%.</li></ul><b>Fortitude in Fellowship</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness Coherency Modifier: 25% to 50%.</li></ul><b>Ambuscade</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage: 20% to 30%.</li></ul><b>Stalwart</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also provides 25% Toughness Damage Reduction while ‘Fury’ is Active.</li></ul><b>Perfectionist</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ability Cooldown Increase: 50% to 25%.</li></ul><b>Master-Crafted Shroudfield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration: 6s to 5s.</li></ul><b>I Shall Not Fall</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness Damage Reduction per Stack: 5% to 6.5%</li></ul><b>Restoring Faith</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heal 25% to 20%.</li><li>Time for Full Heal: 5s to 4s.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>These changes were made because Restoring Faith made taking stray damage a bit too forgiving.</i><br/><b>Swift Certainty</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprint Speed: 10% to 5%.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The Dodging effect of Swift Certainty is already a very strong effect. We’re lowering the movement speed slightly.</i><br/><br/><b>End of Pt. 1. </b><b>Please continue reading Pt.2!</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 NOW with the Early Unlock!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4238536974129786726</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Marines, </div><br/>Early Unlock is about to begin, but we've got a crucial message for you first. 📜<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">✉️ A few words from the devs...</div><br/><b>Dear players, </b><br/>You have already shown immense support and enthusiasm, it has made the whole making process so enjoyable. <b>We are ecstatic at the idea to see you play, have fun and to hear your feedback on the game. Our only wish is that you'll love it and cherish it as much as we do.</b><br/><br/>Space Marine 2 is a project we've been cherishing since day one, and we've worked very hard on for years. It is the result of a passionate collaboration between <i>Saber Interactive</i>, <i>Games Workshop</i> and <i>Focus Entertainment</i>, and all three parties are incredibly proud and thankful at the moment.<br/><br/>We know you have high hopes for the game. So did we. After the launch, we'll keep on updating the game, listening to your feedback and implementing it in the game as much as we can. We'll keep you posted every month with our community updates!<br/><br/>This was the occasion for us to sincerely <b>thank you all 💙</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f828b535b505aee502217168ab71a2ddf89b9077.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">And now, WHAT IS YOUR DUTY?</div><br/>Years of passion, dedication, and hard work have gone into the creation of this action-packed, guns-blazing third-person shooter where players will be defending the Imperium as one of humanity’s strongest warriors against the horrors of the galaxy. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch the Launch Trailer now! ⚔️</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5zcJKGdb0a8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Those who pre-ordered the Gold or Ultra Editions of the game now have early access to <i>Space Marine 2</i>!</div><br/>Across all modes, embody the brutality and superhuman skill of a Space Marine as you fight against the worst the galaxy has to offer. Smash xenos skulls in close combat with superhuman strength and a flesh-sundering chainsword.<br/><br/>Enjoy the campaign alone or with friends as every mode is fully co-op enabled, with customisable characters for PvE missions and PvP battles that can be upgraded as you play. <br/><br/>More content is also on the way with additional missions, new enemies, new weapons, and much more now in development for post-launch support! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">More details in our post-launch roadmap below.</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> officially releases worldwide September 9, 2024. Grab the Gold or Ultra Editions via online stores on Steam to play now.<br/><br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darktide 101: Enemy Design and Prototyping - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4567301015217998130</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4a6e15e4fbdad9ffa5ae9e29d97247efc4469b6f.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello Rejects! </div><br/>My name is Daniel, and I’m a Programmer and Designer at Fatshark. This blog covers parts of our journey in creating enemies for Darktide. Over the years, I’ve gathered many clips and screenshots and wanted to share some of the early development stages and explain our thought processes. Keep in mind that many of these clips and screenshots feature temporary assets (sorry artists!) since they were created early in the project to test gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/>For Darktide, the Combat team used a very iterative approach. We identified the most important features to include, made functional prototypes, tested them in co-op, found problems, and made adjustments to improve the feel. We repeated this process many times. Our core goals for Darktide combat were replayability and co-op. We believe these are best achieved with highly polished moment-to-moment combat and unique (and sometimes funny) scenarios to experience with friends or random players.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Roamer Enemies (Normal and Elite Enemies)</div><br/>To help decide what types of enemies we wanted in Darktide, we first created a combat prototype in Vermintide 2. We did this because we wanted Darktide to have similar combat to Vermintide, and it was easier to test concepts since Darktide had very few assets (models, animations, sounds, effects, etc.) at that point.<br/><br/>Our main objectives for the combat prototype were to evaluate:<br/><br/><ol><li> <b>Melee/Ranged Combat Hybrid:</b> How does Vermintide’s usually melee-focused combat work with a greater focus on ranged combat? How do we ensure melee stays important?<br/></li><li> <b>Ranged Enemy Positioning:</b> With ranged combat, our enemies need ways to position themselves. What kind of positioning systems should we implement?<br/></li><li> <b>Ranged Enemy Types:</b> What ranged enemy types should exist? For example, Vermintide 2 has horde enemies, roamer enemies, high damage elites, fast-attacking berserker elites, and shielded elites. What types should we have for ranged combat?</li></ol>First, we gave a Chaos Marauder enemy in Vermintide 2 a gun and made it shoot at players. We chose these enemies because we planned to make humanoid enemies in Darktide. Their similar skeletons meant we could reuse many of the assets, making it easier for us to use them in the final game.<br/><br/>Then, we wanted to position enemies in the world in a way that made sense for tactical units using ranged weapons. In Vermintide, most enemies use a “Slot System,” which moves enemies to slots around players to space them out, simulate collision, and help with performance.<br/><br/>Here are 2 clips of slot system functionality OFF and ON in Vermintide 2:<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/L3v4jsX32TU<br/><br/>This system wouldn’t work for enemies that don’t aim to engage in melee combat. So, we created two new systems that work together:<br/><br/><ol><li> <b>Cover System:</b> Like in many shooter games, enemies use cover to position themselves. This system guides enemy movement, causes enemies to interact with the environment, and helps level designers create interesting scenarios.<br/></li><li> <b>Combat Vector System:</b> This system calculates positions between players and groups of enemies to simulate a "direction of combat”. It prevents enemies from firing at players from all angles. This is the fallback system when no cover is available.</li></ol><br/>Here’s a later version of these systems in action:<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/9IlEK6V_vlw<br/><br/>For the cover system, we first made simple boxes and walls of different sizes, added nodes, and calculated cover positions. Enemies then picked the closest unoccupied cover with a position opposite the player.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/q-SyoPZRDAk<br/><br/>Next, we added animations and logic for enemies to peek, aim, and shoot from cover.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/tgP8UE4ByLk<br/><br/>As you can see, the animations are static, don’t line up well, and the enemies look confused. However, it was a good early test to see what behaviors and animations we needed.<br/><br/>We noticed early on that ranged enemies needed different behavior when players got close because it wasn’t fun to be shot at from close range. So, we developed the concept of “Combat Ranges,” where enemies change behavior based on their distance from the player and the player’s weapon. We gave marauders melee weapons to switch to if players got too close. When switching to melee, they behaved like regular melee enemies.<br/><br/>This created a fun hybrid combat loop, where players could shoot enemies at range or charge into cover to force them into melee combat, using mechanics like environmental line-of-sight blocking, dodging, and sprinting to minimize damage. This led us to implement mechanics like sprinting and sliding.<br/><br/>We also designed enemies that are extremes of this concept, like the Gunner, who has a powerful ranged attack and doesn’t switch to melee, making it a prime target for high-damage ranged weapons. We also have Shotgunner/Assaulter enemies that try to get close to players without engaging in melee to force them out of cover. The first prototype of Assaulter enemies was a Chaos Warrior with a plasma gun. He slowly walks up, shoots a plasma shot, and switches to a two-handed melee weapon when close.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/mSG9V4wFlxQ<br/><br/>With many enemies taking cover and hybrid combat being a core feature, we wanted to test mechanics allowing ranged weapons to interact with cover. One idea was Suppression, where high fire rate and sustained fire weapons could flush out enemies from cover even if the shots missed. We tested a mechanic where shooting close to the target would make them stop shooting and take cover for a moment.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/aXnFRSGtTZI<br/><br/>Here is a clip showing the above features in the Vermintide 2 prototype. We also got help from level designers to create whitebox levels with covers and layouts suited for ranged combat. It also includes a prototype of the Sniper specialist (later added).<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/9IlEK6V_vlw<br/><br/>In the end, the core roamer population was divided into three categories:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Melee/Fighters:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rush into melee, forcing players to kill them quickly or switch to melee combat.</li></ul></li><li> <b>Close/Assaulters:</b><br/> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Prefer to stay close to players (8-12 meters) and use fast-firing or hard-hitting weapons.</li></ul></li><li> <b>Far/Riflemen:</b><br/> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Stay at a distance, use cover, and take potshots at players. They are generally more defensive and force players to engage with them.</li></ul></li></ul>After finishing the prototype in Vermintide 2, we implemented it in the new Darktide project. The assets look more temporary here since we’re not reusing as many Vermintide 2 assets, and many mechanics are missing. Here’s a clip of the first implementation of cover users in Darktide:<br/>https://youtu.be/XXHafbMOMcU<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Horde Enemies</div>An important element in all -tide games is the Horde enemies. They are designed to be numerous, varied, and fun to kill in masses. For Darktide, our main Horde enemies are humanoids, with two variants: Poxwalkers and the Newly Infected. Here’s a clip of the first implementation of Poxwalkers (with non-functional ragdoll physics):<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/3HZL4rwNOVY<br/><br/>We wanted our horde enemies to vault over cover since levels would be filled with covers, and we wanted hordes to feel like a wave rather than individual enemies. Here’s a clip of one of the first implementations of cover vaulting:<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/Xw3bBsf7uCg<br/><br/>Another aspect we wanted to improve with the hordes in Darktide is their navigation avoidance at longer distances. Avoidance means enemies try to avoid walking the same path as others. This is more noticeable in our games at longer distances due to the slot system spreading out enemies when they get close. Here’s a before/after clip of improved avoidance for Poxwalkers:<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/oHmswSJzw2A<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Specialist Enemies</div>Specialist enemies in Darktide (and Vermintide) can be categorized into two groups:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Disablers:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> These enemies try to disable one player, forcing others to respond. Examples include Pox Hound and Scab Trapper.</li></ul></li><li><b> Scramblers:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> These enemies use mechanics to force players to split up or create chaos to disorient them. Examples include Bombers, Poxburster, Flamers, Snipers, and Mutants.</li></ul></li></ul>It’s crucial that specialist enemies have clear audio and visual cues. Their behavior should be simple so they are easily understood in chaotic situations. An important skill in our games is target prioritization, where players must quickly decide which targets to focus on while up to 200 entities are on screen and three other players are doing the same. Specialists play a key role because their impactful attacks can end a match if left unchecked.<br/><br/>We also allow players to “clutch” against all specials, meaning a single player can handle these threats alone if they take the right actions. Examples of handling a specialist individually would be pushing a Pox Hound/Poxburster, or dodging a Trapper net/Sniper shot/Charging Mutant. While this might seem against the idea of co-op, we found through playtests that the ability to clutch is crucial for individual skill expression, and skill expression is important in a multiplayer game. Not allowing a single player to survive alone would also result in a more toxic gameplay loop where players would give up as soon as other players were downed. It also simply feels rewarding to save the day and revive fallen team members.<br/><br/>Following are some examples of the specialists we created and how they looked at different times during the project.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pox Hound:</div><br/>The first special we added was the Pox hound. We chose the Pox hound because we knew that we needed a fast moving disabler enemy, and it was similar in frame/pose to the Gutter Runner from Vermintide, meaning we could build similar gameplay and be sure that it would work.<br/><br/>First step was to make it pounce on the players. Then, it needed animations and logic to handle its faster speed. We added turning animations (blended animations to simulate momentum etc.), running staggers (staggers that continue forward instead of stop) to help with this. Finally, we polished some of the landing and turning animations. The hound has had some issues with becoming a rocket dog, which was related to how we calculated the trajectories for the pounce, but that has mostly been fixed as of now!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mutant:</div><br/>One of the new Specialists in the -tide series is the Mutant, inspired by the Left 4 Dead charger. We designed it to be more of a scrambler than a disabler. Its role is to charge a player, grab them, deal damage, and then throw them unpredictably to create chaos. We found it needed more health to fulfill its role, making it tankier than usual specialists and a target for high-damage weapons.<br/><br/>Here’s a clip of the first prototypes, using a Chaos Ogryn model and temporary animations to test the mechanics. Once we had the Mutant model, we experimented with its animations. We realized that getting charged constantly got too tiring, so we added pauses after he threw a player, and an extra long opening when players succeeded with dodging.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/ZMyj86_ZWW8 <br/><br/>The animations, sounds, and visual effects were polished later to create the final version of the Mutant we have today.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Poxburster:</div><br/>Another specialist that got added was the Poxburster. We wanted the Poxburster to be a simple Scrambler that explodes when close or on death. Initially, it was supposed to be solely a high priority ranged target that didn’t have any counterplay when it entered melee range.<br/><br/>Starting off, we put a barrel on a Poxwalker and made it explode when close. Later, we added model/animations/vfx/sfx. We realized that players got annoyed by it in close quarters however, so we experimented with ways to deal with it in melee. In the end, we added the “fuse” followed by a window to stagger it in order for a well timed push/dodge backwards to avoid all damage. This turned out to be a fun alternative to kill it.<br/><br/>https://youtu.be/tJkZqOSIQyQ<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Conclusion</div>In conclusion, creating enemies for Darktide has been a detailed and iterative process aimed at making the gameplay exciting and varied. From early tests in Vermintide 2 to the final versions in Darktide, we continuously tested and improved on features. Our focus was on making both melee and ranged combat fun and challenging. We developed different types of enemies, from hordes that swarm and overwhelm to roamers that add variety and strategy. Specialist enemies further add strategy, requiring players to quickly decide which threats to focus on first. Our goal was to build a co-op experience that players will want to return to again and again. Thanks for reading!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 01 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4603329177923939527</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speedfreeks!,</b> we've been tinkerin' and changed 'sum 'dings<br/>Thanks again for all your feedback. This has allowed us to prioritize our fixes, improvements and future plans. For now, we have made live the following:<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cba4fd5062d5349b3515b2d7f42b7fb2a465da83.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added distance text with bomb icon so players know how far it is from them<br/></li><li> Added number of each vehicle used by teammates to ingame selection screen<br/></li><li> Reduced weapon impact forces while airborne to lessen frustration<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with vehicle explosions having extreme forces that would push players back violently<br/></li><li> Bot firing range has been reduced to a more reasonable distance, so they can no longer randomly snipe players from across the map<br/></li><li> Improvements made to melee weapon damage detection</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/33228b0aa5614f2a8762260094b61afdf182ba57.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Deff Rally</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Deff Rally mode now grants 12 points for kills instead of 15, for the team that controls the capture point<br/></li><li> Extra points per kill while holding the point reduced to 2 (from 5). <br/></li><li> Wave generation time (max seconds wait after respawning in Deff Rally only) increased to 6 from 4 seconds.</li></ul> This will make the runaway score problem less severe in Deff Rally while we take a deeper look at the game mode. The wave spawning time will now wait for slightly longer to create a larger mob to run back to the point with.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Kill Konvoy</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some collision issues in Kill Konvoy map Ded 'Ard Desert<br/></li><li> Kill Konvoy bots are now smarter, they no longer Leeroy Jenkins the Stompa, and also help with the bomb attack and defence more<br/></li><li> Fixed Kill Konvoy bombs briefly staying in the level after exploding</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1c24705979de19541dbd846b18d4a72e7b2a8484.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primary weapon max range reduced</li></ul> This change removes the spray-n-pray damage the Snazzwagon could deal with its primary weapon to cancel health regen at long ranges. This didn't fit the vehicle's identity as a short range health bar melter. The Snazzwagon now has a more identifiable weakness, its range. Tanks are still very vulnerable to the Mek Speshul in close quarters.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Looted Wagon</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Grot Bomm flight duration reduced from 20 seconds to 12<br/></li><li> Fixed Grot Riggers ability showing incorrect health bar value<br/></li><li> Fixed side turrets not rotating </li></ul> The Grot Bomm duration was extremely long, allowing players to miss, pull up, and come back around for another attempt, which doesn't fit the spirit of the weapon. This also makes it easier to tell when the Grot Bomm will expire (about 3 seconds after the flame particles stop).<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Deffkilla Wartrike</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Melee Klaw ability damage increased back to 50 from 45<br/></li><li> Grapnel damage increased to 5 from 1</li></ul> Giving the Wartrike more Klaw damage allows it to be more threatening in its role as a wounded target hunter, and the additional damage on the hook means the Wartrike puts on more pressure during drive-bys, ambushes, and bomb stops.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Rukkatrukk squigbuggy</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Health decreased to 130 from 150 <br/></li><li> Base and boosting speed increased</li></ul> As the healer, the Squigbuggy was way too tanky, and clearing out a Squigbuggy to then focus on their bomb carrier took too long based on average DPS and map size. To compensate, it gets a small speed boost to help it keep up with its healing targets.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Grot Mega Tank</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed Grot Riggers ability showing incorrect health bar value</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4f4e06decc20a6c6813d9204babb89fdfe00896c.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issue that caused WAAAGH! Path progression to reset. <br/>NOTE: Players may see unlocked items show again at the end of their first match played. This is normal.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue that caused Challenges progression to reset or unlocks to be not granted.<br/>NOTE: You may need to finish a match first before your unlocks/items are granted.  Some players may need to finish a match with each vehicle to see their challenge progress properly again<br/></li><li> Fixed issue that caused Daily Challenges to reset <br/></li><li> Fixed issue with inputs being stuck when respawning<br/></li><li> Fixed the awarding issues of the Skull kit for end of vehicle challenges<br/></li><li> Fixed prices shown incorrectly for Japanese players<br/></li><li> WAAAGH! Path screen now focuses on current level when opened, instead of starting at the beginning<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the scoreboard remained on screen when loading next match<br/></li><li> Pings on scoreboard now reflect more accurate numbers<br/></li><li> Speedboss on the scoreboard is now fully determined by only total Scrap<br/></li><li> Added bomb deliveries to stats and scoreboard<br/></li><li> Added bomb defence to stats<br/></li><li> Changed the “Kustomize” wrench icon to a paint brush icon to make it more obvious that an item can be painted<br/></li><li> Comms menu voice lines can be heard further from their origin now<br/></li><li> The players friends list will show in the party screen without needing to create a party yet<br/></li><li> Added notification for players to tell them what happened if they get kicked to the main menu<br/></li><li> Removed function for painting vehicles that automatically jumped to the paint swatch of the paint slot being selected<br/></li><li> Reduced end of match player recap screen timer by 10 seconds<br/></li><li> Updated Ork textures to look dirtier<br/></li><li> Updated ingame report link so it’s an easier to use form (temporary, until we implement something better in-game)<br/></li><li> Optimizations to various VFX<br/></li><li> Fixed not being able to paint certain parts of vehicle kits<br/></li><li> Multiple crash bug fixes, including one with a fatal error<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the pole gubbinz not showing properly for the Deffkilla Wartrike</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Top priorities still being worked on:</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hit registration/netcode improvements, and fixing issues where damage/healing is not registering<br/></li><li> Matchmaking improvements<br/></li><li> Team balance and fuller matches (less bots)<br/></li><li> A definitive fix for challenge issues<br/></li><li> Ping system for team communication</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/df7e155e9121d026236c6ea9a1bacd9c8d4416c3.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
