<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Who is the 100th Legendary Lord?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511318</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Four contenders, each staking their claim for the coveted title of 100th Legendary Lord™.<br/> <br/>Golgfag, Skulltaker, Gorbad, Arbaal. Who will come out on top? There's only one way to find out...<br/> <br/>FIIIIIGHT! ⚔️<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8EqoO8e7PJE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 15:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction is OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/514069779412157179</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/626689ac31ac99588fcf9927c551c3fa2a1f8238.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>The day is finally upon us! Golgfag, Skulltaker and Gorbad have joined the fray - Omens of Destruction has arrived in Total War: WARHAMMER III alongside Update 6.0!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/46584/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Omens_of_Destruction<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574900/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Gorbad__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130740/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Golgfag__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130750/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Skulltaker__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/><br/><b>PLEASE NOTE:</b> Although every effort will be made to get the bundle link up and running as close to 3PM GMT as possible, there may be a slight delay in the link being accessible. If you have trouble accessing the link at 3PM GMT please wait a moment and try again.<br/><br/>Check out the launch trailer now:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OD5lbyN-EG0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>If you haven't already, you can read the full release notes at the link below:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">UPDATE 6.0 RELEASE NOTES</div><br/><br/>Whose campaign will you be jumping into first? We look forward to hearing about your exploits!<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Bardin Goreksson &amp; Warpfire Thrower</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/509566731895701564</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>last</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun. This week's spotlight will be on the hearty <b>Bardin</b> and the nasty <b>Warpfire Thrower!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div>As said in the the previous post, we changed the end date for the event from Sunday to Wednesday, which was more than enough to reach and beat the new ambitious target of 250K kills!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/416bf23cd4e304f304252b63875723aac82853f0.png"/><br/>The rewards for the previous spotlight were delivered yesterday, so check your inventory! As a note, the Hero Pose might take a few restarts before it applies properly to your account. Sorry about that!<br/><br/>Congrats to everyone for your continued hard work! Now just the final stretch!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly, all earned by the community as a whole through completion of the Kill-Counter. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Bardin Goreksson &amp; Warpfire Thrower Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between December 12 - December 18.</b> All rewards will be granted after the end of the spotlight.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>An exclusive skin for the Warpfire Thrower!</b><br/></li><li> <b>120 shillings.</b><br/></li><li> <b>100 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A brand new Portrait frame.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A Hero Pose for Bardin!</b></li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a781e4c46cde9c74da545037248884a1429b3d3c.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Bardin Goreksson</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/38c89e690a980e66d78e96e544ae622a393a619f.png"/><br/>Bardin Goreksson introduced himself to the world as an unstoppable avalanche on the battlefield, an ale-swigging hurricane at the inn, and a steadfast friend by the campfire. A bulwark of comradeliness and good cheer, Bardin became the glue binding our unlikely band of heroes. <br/><br/><b>Learn more about Bardin Goreksson here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Warpfire Thrower</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/3a96fad476c7d4cdcdcc32596076eca8d71dcdbd.png"/>The The Warpfire Thrower is whispered of in many quarters – chiefly for the horrors it has wrought in the cramped confines of dwarfen holds. With the smouldering projector aimed, the simple flip of a switch births roiling clouds of warpfire that scours all from the gunner’s path.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Warpfire Thrower here!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #56 (1.6.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/512944432186654768</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/94ac16af1cc228c28d1dc88fcdac63c9a6042d4b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>Hotfix #56 (1.6.3) is currently rolling out across our platforms, and it should be available for everyone in the next hour or so. In the meantime, you can view the notes below.<br/><div class="bb_h2">Havoc Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some of the rewards for Havoc penances had the wrong rarity color displayed.<br/></li><li> If voting to deploy on a Havoc assignment results in the deployment being cancelled, no assignment charge will be consumed. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Dark Communion Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where enemies were able to damage players during the cutscene at the start of the end event in the Dark Communion mission.<br/></li><li> Updated the icons for Penances related to the Dark Communion mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the “Banishment” penance would list Groaners twice, preventing it from being unlocked.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description of the “Warp Slice” blessing would display incorrect values for all tiers (no change in the actual cooldown values in active gameplay).<br/></li><li> From 50/40/30/20s to 30/25/20/15s.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the “Bringing the Boom” and “Pox Burster” Penance frames were using the same frame.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the “Intra-Cranial Implant” cosmetic headgear would interfere with certain hairstyles.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the “Krieg Backpack (Standard Issue)” cosmetic was being incorrectly tagged as a Lower Body item instead of Accessory.  </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 News - 2024 Wrap Up 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/524203331331031095</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/147b1768aae9ac663c50a5fec47f3ba790647d05.png"/><br/>Oi Speed Freeks,<br/><br/>Firstly, we want to give you our greenest thanks to you gits for playing Speed Freeks during its Early Access phase. Since the launch in August, da Mek Boyz have nabbed and utilized your feedback to make a ton of fixes and quality of life improvements, plus changes to game modes, maps and vehicles.  This has led to a really solid foundation for the game, and it’s been truly humbling to see all of your positive comments and hear about all the fun players are having.<br/><br/>This week Early Access Update #4 landed which continues to grow and evolve the game into something we hope you’ll enjoy coming back to for a long time. This patch greatly improves Deff Rally mode, adding more racing and dynamic combat encounters, plus adds alternate weapons/abilities for some vehicles as a limited time mode, creating armament variety for each class.  It also brings the usual improvements we’ve been doing since launch in terms of bug fixes and quality of life stuff for the game. If you’ve not grabbed it yet, get on it!<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/302045a8e552b15b6f7bdba12f6cc56723b6a4b5.png"/><br/>We want your feedback!<br/><br/>Closing out the end of 2024 and looking to the future, we want to hear from our valued community as we continue to roar through the grimdark wasteland together. This new survey will help us better understand what is important to you gits, with the results directly influencing our ongoing development of the game. So please give it a shot below!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/dffc9865e78ec717e30a35320c40c6a47c727808.png"/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Click for Feedback Survey</b></div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/87acda9033493108f66ab7c96205a970c7120a29.png"/><br/>In terms of the next update, rest assured that we are hard at work developing new features and improvements, including a more traditional Combat Racing game mode prototype -  which we want to get into your hands to start playing as soon as possible. As usual, we’re going to develop this feature alongside your feedback, and especially in this case, where it will become a permanent mode for the game in the future.<br/><br/>Further on from that next patch, we’re speeding towards the full launch of this game out of early access and into version 1.0.  We’ve got some really exciting things coming with that version and will be sharing some info about it in the new year. We can’t say much yet, but there will be a lot to look forward to in 2025 and beyond, so keep yer enginez burnin’ n’ yer dakka ready! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/995ffe8e717de04ab7a9f557c54780e617c1da15.png"/><br/><br/>Our ultimate goal is to make Speed Freeks one of the greatest combat racing games of all time, and as we solidify the base game towards it’s full release, we’re confident it will be a rich and rewarding experience for Warhammer 40,000 Ork fans and general vehicular combat fans alike. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bff6e97958bf7cec3025c8f54db27b7e22dbc4ee.png"/><br/>Before we forget, here’s a bit of a sneak peek showing a new map coming your way next year called Da Dust Up! This map starts in an Ork fortress up on a big hill, then speeds down into the valley for some intense racin’ and fightin’.  We’ll drop more info about this map and others as we get closer to their release.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/45e28095664ec8f8352612f4ff3fe3b58e7e3b76.png"/><br/>Finally, a proppa big thanks again to all you’z gits for being a part of this important development period called Early Access. You’ve had, and will continue to have, a substantial impact on the game as a whole. As much as it can be difficult to have the game live during this time, we are truly thankful to have you on this journey with us and encourage you to keep helping us through this fun and experimental phase of game development. <br/><br/>It really motivates us to have such dedicated and crazed fans of the game already and also gives us confidence of where this game can go in the future.<br/><br/>As always, feel free to drop your feedback and suggestions in the comments or the usual social spaces linked below. If there’s anything you think really needs fixing or improving, or if you have a feature suggestion that you think will have a big impact on the game, we’re happy to hear about it. <br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks! <br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
