<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #62 (1.6.9) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499439875179679150</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/824ddc640957bcbcbcf3714772bf42d9ef0d3ce4.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>We’ve got another quick one this week to smooth out a few bugs. The hotfix is currently rolling out across our platforms and it’ll be available today.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash which could happen when moving the analog stick on controller during certain transitions in the Havoc menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the coloration of a few cosmetic items had accidentally been swapped from a forest/military green to teal   <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description of the Ogryn “Payback Time” Talent appeared as undefined text.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.3.2.13 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/502817574909644214</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>After the launch of the game on Xbox Game Pass, some game settings could function incorrectly. We are publishing a minor hotfix 1.3.2.13 to address that issue.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the Mark VIII Errant Helmet with no marking!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/515202473879669281</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Earn the Mk VIII helmet (without the emblem 🤩) by achieving victory in Operations mode with all six classes! Event runs from the 21st to March 3rd.<br/><br/><i>Note that you'll need to be connected to PROS to track your progress and earn the helmet. Some delay can occur between the completion of the mission and the tracking being shown on the website.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/876731048e75bea664881bc7949c13b396be58a9.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 11:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onslaught Series: Community run Charity Tournament event for Anniversary!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/532090972488599765</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>The Onslaught Series will be hosting a <i>Charity Tournament</i> in the name of APOPO ( https://apopo.org/ ).<br/><br/>APOPO is a social enterprise that researches, develops and implements detection rats technology for humanitarian purposes such as Mine Action and Tuberculosis detection. APOPO is a Belgian NGO, with headquarters in Tanzania and operations in Mozambique, Thailand, Angola and Cambodia.<br/><br/><b>The sign ups are open NOW for the Tiers:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tier 1 - C1DWONS and LEGEND DWONS<br/></li><li> Tier 2 - C3DWONS<br/></li><li> Tier 3 - C3DWONS+<br/></li><li> Tier 4 - C3DWUTCH</li></ul><b>The event itself consists of two tournament days:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 8th March 2025 Teams in Tier 1 and Tier 2<br/></li><li> 9th March 2025 Teams in Tier 3 and Tier 4</li></ul>Be quick, because there are only so many teams that can be shown live and the first to sign up and play live on tournament time will be the ones to be featured in the big event stream on the Fight The Tide Twitch Channel ( https://www.twitch.tv/fightthetide ).<br/><br/><b>Sign ups are open NOW until 6th March, 2025 4PM CET!</b><br/><br/>All players regardless of when they play in the week from the 3rd March 2025 - 9th March 2025 will be listed for everyone to check out!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Sign ups</div>You can sign up to participate in the event through the Onslaught Discord, link here: https://discord.gg/MS4vWSQrEh<br/><br/>The charity event is open for everyone, if you donate something you will be granted a digital gift. The rewards are set up in multiple categories:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>01 - 05$US:</b>  A new frame in Vermintide 2<br/></li><li> <b>05 - 10$US:</b> Crown of Purity, a Zealot hat skin for Vermintide 2<br/></li><li> <b>More than 10$US:</b> A digital vermintide 2 magazine with stories, pictures and articles about the game</li></ul><i>Note that a higher category will include all the rewards of the lower categories as well.<br/>All players in the tournament itself will be rewarded with the rewards of category 2.</i><br/><br/><b>You can find information on how to donate to the charity in the Onslaught Discord, link above.</b><br/><i>Expect digital gifts to be sent out by Fatshark by the end of March.<br/>The Fanzine PDFs will be distributed by the Onslaught team the day after the tournament ends.</i><br/><br/>The Onslaught Team would like to extend a big thank you APOPO for this opportunity!<br/><br/>Let's have a great ratty party with APOPO and 7 amazing years of Vermintide 2.<br/><br/><b>If you have any questions you can read their FAQ here</b><br/>Or ask them directly in the Onslaught Series Discord server: https://discord.gg/MS4vWSQrEh]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Event: Vermintide’s 7th anniversary!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/532090972488597664</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>Another year has gone by and it’s another year to celebrate the launch of Vermintide 2, with much merry, drinking, and rat slaying! Join us from <b>March 6</b> to <b>March 16</b> for our Seventh anniversary as we open the floodgates of the anniversary map <i>‘A Quiet Drink’</i> once more!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">A Quiet Drink</div>Celebrate with our Heroes by taking them on a bar crawl across what’s left of Helmgart in this returning, limited-time mission! There will also be challenges related to completing the mission and rewards, <b>including a brand-new portrait frame!</b><br/><br/>In addition, Lohner’s Emporium of Wonders will once again open the Event section for the duration of the event, allowing you to purchase old rewards from previous anniversaries for shillings in case you missed them!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Double XP</div>For the duration of the event, all experience earned while playing Vermintide will be doubled! Time to finish leveling up those Heroes, or getting a chunky boost in Versus ranks!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Versus map</div>And as an additional celebration, we can let you guys in on a little secret! The update will see the addition of yet another map to the pool of playable Versus maps! We can’t spoil which one it is yet, but we’re excited to show you!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Fatshark Livestream today - 17:30 CET</div><a class="bb_link" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Ftwitch.tv%2Ffatsharkgames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/b6936d8e706f64e0fa2c7a8637e1128edd2df60d.png"/></a><br/>Finally, while we have you here, we wanted to mention that we actually have a livestream later today for both Vermintide and Darktide! Our Art Directors will go through your submitted fanart to celebrate and pass judgement! The best pieces will net a reward, so make sure to submit your best! If you haven't already, make sure to find one of our Social Media posts about the contest and submit your piece as a comment!<br/><br/>Tune in later today on <b>our twitch</b>.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
