<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Server Disconnect Compensation 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797809444568</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Thanks for jumping in Speed Freeks Day 1 of Early Access. We had some server issues at release which caused some of you to be disconnected from matches. This has been fixed by the team with a new server roll out earlier today. <br/><br/>As a thank you for your support and to honor the playtime you lost due to server instability we will be sending out a 1 Day Scrap Boost through our email system, the same one we send our newsletter out with.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9fbb1b9ad50530626b697dac1fcc681be427c2a.png"/><br/> <br/>If you’ve already signed up for the newsletter you will be sent the Scrap Boost automatically. If you haven’t signed up yet fear not, it’s easy to opt in and you will also get the cute little Squig Gubbinz cosmetic topper when you follow. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2623f614a356cf931a23e04980689799fc1db4e8.png"/><br/><br/>To sign up for the newsletter simply log into your Speed Freeks account and click the follow button.<br/>https://prismray.io/games/speedfreeks <br/><br/>To redeem the Scrap Boost click the Redeem Code button in your profile and enter the code that was provided in the email. <br/>https://support.prismray.io/hc/en-us/articles/22351440941073-How-to-Redeem-a-Code<br/><br/> <br/>Sincere thanks for your feedback and support, and welcome to the WAAAGH!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back from Summer - Next Hotfix Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4353377496597045467</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Heyo everyone, <br/><br/>A quick message from us to say we’re back from summer break and we’ll have our first hotfix coming next week! The plan was for it to come this week, however we hit a technical snag we need to iron out first. 🙏<br/><br/>We’ll see you next week!<br/><br/>- The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Beginner's Guide 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162779945476</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Go from Git to Gork with this Beginner's Guide!</div>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KIK_rDcIbSA?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>Thanks to KroTukk for showing us the way.<br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks! <br/> <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🛠️ Disconnect Fix 🛠️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797808413685</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We have been investigating the disconnect issues that players have been facing and we believe that we have a solution to keep players from being kicked from the game. <br/><br/>Over the next hour, we will be terminating in-progress matches to roll out updated servers. You may be dropped back to the main menu while this fix rolls out. If this happens please restart the game and re-queue. <br/><br/>We apologize for any inconvenience this has caused and thank you for your continued patience and support.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT FIX is now live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162780890578</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI YOU'Z GITZ!<br/><br/>We've fixed a couple critical issues that plagued the release of the game:<br/><br/>- <b>Paid items</b> on the store were <b>disappearing </b>into smokey air, but this has now been fixed.  Rest assured that any items you've purchased are still yours and will show up with no problems now<br/><br/>- <b>Teef packages</b> are now properly represented on Steam, so feel free to grab some Teef if ya like<br/><br/>- <b>Localization of languages</b> has been disabled for now since it's not quite ready for use yet (will be in an update)<br/><br/>Thanks for your patience on this, and if you still experience issues with Teef or paid items (or anything else) please let us know here or the Steam discussions, or the Discord<br/><br/>Happy krumpin!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
