<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Protocols - New Weapons - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456969803786095501</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/bbed5becf1abfcc825f8a528adcf9b10fd503772.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Welcome to the first dev blog for our next update, Grim Protocols. Today, we’re talking about weapons. This dev blog will give you more of a behind the scenes look at creating these weapons for Grim Protocols. We’ll include more information about their special attacks work and in-game information in the patch notes at release.<br/><br/>We’ve got 3 brand new weapons coming to you with this update:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Two-Handed Power Sword (2 Marks) - Zealot</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade</li><li>Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade</li></ul><li><b>Two-Handed Force Sword (2 Marks) - Psyker</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Covenant Mk VI Blaze Force Greatsword</li><li>Covenant Mk VIII Blaze Force Greatsword</li></ul><li><b>Heavy Stubber (3 Marks) - Ogryn</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Krourk Mk IIa Heavy Stubber</li><li>Gorgonum Mk IIIa Heavy Stubber</li><li>Achlys Mk II Heavy Stubber</li></ul></ul>Remember the Itemization trailer? 😉<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3568582a97a0e1629a2c58e522fbc5197ce5432e.png"/><br/><br/>For this dev blog, we’re going to talk to some devs about the general design direction, creating the animations, formulating the sounds, and bringing them to live through visual effects. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">General Design Direction</div><br/>For the design direction of these weapons, we spoke to Matteo A., Game Designer on Darktide, who worked on them. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is the design target for the Heavy Stubbers? Was it difficult to place when the Twin Stubber already existed?</div>The design intent for the heavy stubbers was to give Ogryns some more precise long-range capabilities. Since we already had the Twin Linked Stubbers, it didn’t sound super interesting to only make them a less rapid fire version. Instead, we went with another approach. <br/><br/>Ogryns being Ogryns, we imagined them using the Heavy Stubber as a sort of DMR (marksman rifle) weapon. This would allow them to lay down supportive fire with the primary fire and be very precise with the alternative fire. This broadens the Ogryn player's toolkit, enabling them to take on a wider variety of roles within the team.<br/><br/>We’ve also added a flashlight to the Heavy Stubbers for the big guys, because they’ve been in the dark too long.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Why is the Two-Handed Power Sword on the Zealot, when the Veteran already has the One Handed Power Sword?</div>The Two-Handed Power Sword is a giant greatsword with barely contained energy: its huge, sweeping swings and a unique sprinting Heavy stab attack, it just asks to get stuck in melee while frantically lobbing off the heretics' heads.<br/><br/>The weapon also sports a new bespoke activation mechanic: instead of having a fixed, stable amount of empowered swings (more appropriate to the ex-Guard regimented Veteran), a Heat gauge will increase while the weapon is activated. Upon reaching the Heat limit, the weapon will overheat and lock the player out of the Special activate for a short period.<br/><br/>Controlling the rising Heat while engaged in the thick of combat felt very much suited to the playstyle and fantasy of the Zealot: melee-focused, unbridled and overwhelming power. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">I’ve noticed Veterans haven’t received a weapon this patch. Will we be left hungry?</div>Veterans won’t be left out for too long. They’ll be receiving more next year. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What about the Force Swords? </div><br/><i>&gt; Drops a video of the Force Greatsword special attack</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c4103e3b68a4bb41560ba343547bbff73b1d4dc7.gif"/><br/><br/><i>&gt; Refuses to elaborate further<br/>&gt; Leaves</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Animation</div><br/>Next up to speak about animation for the new weapons is Jonas B., one of our Gameplay Animators.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What was the process like to animate the two-handed swords compared to the other swords in game? </div>It was quite a similar process actually! Although this time around, I had to think more about weight shifting and gripping both hands instead of just one. Especially since they're, you know, pretty big. Usually, when I animate new weapons, I try to re-use and adjust some of the old animations if they’re similar or fitting enough to be something new. This time around it wasn’t the case, though. <br/><br/>In the very beginning, I collected some references of HEMA (Historical European Martial Arts) / Sword dueling videos. I also looked a bit into sword stances to gather inspiration. In the end, a lot of these inspirations were a bit subdued, or they were changed a bit for the sake of highlighting the personalities of the Psyker and Zealot. But changes were also made to make the weapons unique and fun with the weapon specials in mind. <br/><br/>Specifically, the Two-Handed Power Sword is more forceful, reckless and heavy (Emperor guide my path!). Conversely, the Two-Handed Force Sword has more “flowy” finesse and flair to its movements, which  showcases Psykers using psi-assisted techniques instead of proper training. <br/><br/>In other words, you could find me posing and swinging around prop swords sometimes at my office desk or in the animation room to get a feeling of how to animate and handle the swords. (I'd like to think I looked pretty cool acting as a reckless and fervent Zealot, but it was probably quite silly. Maybe you can bribe StrawHat to show it to you one day.)<br/><br/>(<b>NOTE</b>: Also I want to shout out Oliviero M., for making an awesome solid groundwork for the Two-Handed Force Sword.)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How long have you been working on these weapons?</div>Hard to say to be honest. All the weapons have been in varying stages for a long time. Some were more functional than others. I think animation-wise the new Heavy Stubbers have been in a good place for a while. (<b>Note</b>: This only refers to animation-wise. We still needed to do testing and tweak numbers to make sure they felt right in-game.)<br/><br/>I started working on the Two-Handed Force Sword full-time a few months ago. It had quite a lot of solid groundwork done during the prototyping stage and functional stage. I think the groundwork was done earlier. <br/><br/>The Two-Handed Power Sword had its very basic groundwork a while back, but we wanted to focus on other weapons first. Coincidentally, I started working on the Two-Handed Power Sword roughly at the same time as the Two-Handed Force Sword. <br/><br/>In general, these weapons have been worked on bit by bit. It’s taken time, because they’ve both gone through quite a lot of reworks and iterations. We’ve changed how the weapon special attacks worked. We began taking a new approach by adding unique conditional actions that lead to different attacks depending on whether a player is running, sprinting or sliding. This meant I had to return and change some animations and transitions on these weapons to make sure they worked as intended.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What were some of the challenges you faced while working on the animations?</div>The biggest challenge this time around was probably making sure the Two-Handed Power Sword Weapon Special did not feel disruptive in the attack chain flow, yet still be visible enough for activating and deactivating. Considering how the activation system works for the Two-Handed Power Sword, it meant that the weapon needed an activate/deactivate animation for most cases after swings (left-side, right-side, idle, sprint). <br/><br/>But it also needed support for activate/deactivate when sprinting due to being able to start attacks while in a sprint. There were quite a few custom animation transitions made for the activate/deactivate animation to make sure it could blend into the action from any point in the gameplay, such as hitstops, shield-hitstops, blocks, etc. <br/><br/>Another challenge for both the swords was that we allowed them to be able to start charging a heavy attack while being in a sprinting state. This itself is not a very large deal, but this change caused a lot of unexpected animation bugs leading into attack chains, which needed to be addressed.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Any comments or thoughts on what it was like to animate the Ogryn stubbers?</div>It’s always a treat to animate Ogryns. There’s something magical about them when it comes to animating them. I think it might be because they’re such brutes that allow you to animate ridiculous, but lovable actions. You’ll see an example of this when you turn on the flashlight for the heavy stubbers. Most of their problems are usually solved by brute force or heavy firepower. <br/><br/>That said, it was very satisfying to animate a weapon that is quite heavy and powerful in fire-power and brutish in handling such a weapon.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Are there any fun bits of trivia?</div>In the very beginning the Two-Handed Power Sword was known as the “Ogryn Jousting weapon” amongst some of the animators of Fatshark. This is mostly because the unique sprinting pose very much resembled someone charging forward ready to strike. We joked around about how the humans were piggy-riding on Ogryns with the swords pointed forward, in a joust-like fashion. <br/><br/>Also, the sprint stab animation (Sprint &gt; Heavy Stab attack) on Two-Handed Power Swords was just a fun prototype thingy, which kinda led us to add conditional attacks for the weapons, things such as attacks made from equip, slide and such. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Sounds</div><br/>Our next section is about building the sounds for the new weapons. For this, we have Jonas H. entering the blog!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What was it like designing the sound for the new Power Sword and Force Sword? Did you do anything to make them distinct? What was your thought process?</div>My first focus was to make both two-handed swords feel heavy, so I needed to make foley* and hit sounds that gave that feeling.<br/><br/>(* You might be asking what foley means: Foley is the sound for handling the weapon. It’s all about the small details: like touching and grabbing the sword, the small clinks and clanks when you walk, etc.)<br/><br/>For the Two-Handed Power Sword special attacks, I wanted it to still feel like it was in the same family as the 1H counterpart, but I tried to embrace the fantasy that when activated it should both feel and sound cool when hitting enemies. And as the window of the activation was fairly short, I could make the hits a bit louder, while not making it tiresome in the long run.<br/><br/>The Two-Handed Force Sword took the longest to make because the way the special worked was changed a lot during development (like the other Jonas mentioned above). I wanted the wave and the explosive hits on the enemies to also feel satisfying, so it took some time to find a good balance. It was also important to me to make the warp sound design surrounding this weapon to feel connected to its sibling, the 1H Force Sword. A lot of experimentation was done to find the right vibe in swings and activation information for this weapon.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">When it comes to designing guns for Ogryns, are there any differences compared to designing the sounds for the human classes?</div>Compared to the swords, the stubbers are more grounded.  I tried to make them feel different from the faster Twin Stubbers. I did this by making more mechanical sounds in the background while shooting, and adding another flavor to the shots. They are slower and heavy, and that was the goal sound wise, as well.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Visual Effects</div><br/>To round this BTS dev blog off, we’ve got Felicia K., one of our VFX Artists, to talk to you about her process. <br/><br/>Hi everyone, I’m Felicia and I work with visual effects (VFX) for Darktide. To start off, for those who don’t know what a Visual Effect Artist does at a game studio, I create effects for both environment and combat. For the environment, it can be things like rain, fire, dust, smoke, steam and much more. For combat, it’s more muzzle flashes for guns, impact effects on enemies like blood and explosions, the list goes on. I work very closely with a lot of different roles at the studio. Most of the time my role comes in later in the process, since I need to know what is happening in the levels or the combat to be able to brainstorm my part of the process. <br/><br/>When I started to work on the new swords I was very hyped. I knew that these weapons would be a little bit different from what I’ve worked on before, especially the Two-Handed Force Sword.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Two-Handed Force Sword</div><br/>I heard from the combat designers that the Two-Handed Force Sword would have a force cleave coming out of the sword that you would charge up. Almost like a wind slash in some other games. But of course we would need it to look much more brutal and more Warhammer 40,000. <br/><br/>From here, the brainstorming begins for me. How does the effect feel? How does it behave? What is it? What is the style for this effect? So this is what I wrote down as the description: <br/><br/>Style/Mood: Wispy/Souls to separate the Force Sword from the Power Sword that already has lightning. The Power Sword feels a lot more “rough” than the Force Sword. Make it “Wispy” in the effects as a whole. <br/><br/>I wanted the Two-Handed Force Sword to be soft and smooth but still feel very powerful. It has 3 different stages on the cleave depending on how powerful the charge is. To show this visually, I made them different sizes and added some extra effects on the most powerful one, like smoke and sparks.<br/><br/>After the cleave was done, I worked on the charge that you do on the sword itself before you can shoot the cleave. There was some back and forth on how it should look. We knew it should indicate that you can have enough power to charge up the cleave, and to make that clear I created a screen space effect (AKA an effect that spawns on the screen). I also added a small blue fire-like effect that would spawn on the sword when you have enough power. <br/><br/>It’s always a challenge when working with visual effects to make sure you as a player understand what is happening, but not take over and be too much, so you can focus on your gameplay. It needs to be balanced. You don’t want effects all over your screen just to indicate something. But you still need to see the effects enough, so you can understand “oh I have enough power to charge my forcesword” even in the middle of an intense combat fight.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/722a5f00c0ae055bc2ba908a87156380163d22a3.png"/><br/><br/>My own beautiful (not so beautiful) sketch of the indicator of when you have reached a certain charge. It turned out a little bit different when I actually started to work on it, but it’s always good to go back to your mood board/description to not lose track of what you’re aiming for, because you can easily forget along the way. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Two-Handed Power Sword</div>So if the Two-Handed Force Sword would feel smooth and powerful, I wanted the Two-Handed Power Sword to feel more rock ‘n’ roll. I wanted this sword to feel more rough when it comes to the effects. To accomplish this, the lightning is spawning and it is pretty big when you activate the weapon. <br/><br/>You also have a time limit before it overcharges. For this, I thought it should look/feel like an engine on a car that’s failing and there’s smoke coming out of it to indicate “you should probably de-activate so it doesn't break”. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/07fe648515acd5f0c07897b5221bc980d80f7991.png"/><br/><br/>This is another example of a sketch I did. It’s for when you’ve reached the overcharged. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Heavy Stubbers</div><br/>But hey, let’s not forget the new Heavy Stubbers! As a hardcore Ogryn player, I was super happy to get some more ranged weapons for the Ogryn, and even more happy to be able to work on them. <br/><br/>First of all, when you work as a visual effect artist, you have a lot of odd search history. I look at a lot of military videos as reference when working with guns, and also explosions. The Heavy Stubbers are big and powerful, and like I’ve written before, I need to decide: how do the effects feel? How do they act? How much of the effects do you see when you shoot? <br/><br/>When researching for the Heavy Stubbers I looked at a lot of 50.cal weapons, like in this video: <br/>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UFB7-bvVKs8<br/><br/>When you look at the video, the gun is so powerful that you can almost only see smoke, almost no muzzle flash at all. But since this is a video game, we need some more feedback than just smoke when shooting. For this, I added a very small muzzle flash and smoke for the heavy stubbers to indicate that this weapon has such force when shooting, that you can’t see a lot of fire like when shooting a shotgun (and shotguns also have more spread when shooting in general). <br/><br/>Hope that you find this interesting and that you like the new weapons, it was a blast to work on them!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Alright, that’s our BTS dev blog on the making of the new weapons coming to Grim Protocols on December 3, 2024. <br/><br/>On release, we’ll include more information about how the weapons work in-game and their special activations. <br/><br/>Let us know if you have any questions for the team in the comments below!<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction Arrives 12th December!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458095703696083664</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/a8a1bf6d352b822510c4c1f23aa403a333a9bcbb.jpg"/><br/><br/>Oi gits!<br/><br/>It's the moment you've been waiting for! Omens of Destruction, a showdown of daemons, delinquents, and detestables, featuring Khorne, Ogre Kingdoms, and Orcs &amp; Goblins arrives in Total War: WARHAMMER III on December 12! 💥<br/><br/>Over the next few weeks we'll be talking more about the Legendary Lords, battle units and campaign features in our blogs and gameplay showcases, as well as the awesome free content that you can look forward to with this upcoming DLC and game update.<br/><br/>Watch the trailer:<br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/83chO9NuWAg?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Just like with Thrones of Decay, you'll have the choice of purchasing each faction's content individually, or the full Omens of Destruction package as a bundle.<br/><br/>Wishlist now:<br/><br/>Golgfag: https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130740/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Golgfag__Omens_of_Destruction<br/>Skulltaker: https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130750/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Skulltaker__Omens_of_Destruction<br/>Gorbad: https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574900/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Gorbad__Omens_of_Destruction<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Havoc Q&amp;A - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456969803786092919</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1203d0447080a2a770ff3e7bf219d31282777589.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div> <br/><br/>A couple of weeks ago, we released an Introduction to Havoc dev blog. Similar to when we released the Introduction to Itemization dev blog over the summer, we’ve received a lot of comments and questions. <br/><br/>For Itemization, we answered these in the form of a couple of Q&amp;A posts, and we thought it would be a great format to use for discussing Havoc, as well. <br/><br/>We’ll compile the most common remaining questions after this post and we’ll answer them in the patch notes when it is released on 3 December.<br/><br/>Something that has changed since the last dev blog is the nomenclature used in this game mode. From now on we will be calling what was previously known as a Havoc Order a Havoc Assignment (aka the current mission a player is assigned), and what was previously known as your Havoc Rank will now be known as your Havoc Clearance Level (the highest Havoc Assignment you’ve cleared - whether it’s your own or through the party finder).<br/><br/>We’d also like to say these are the answers we have NOW. Our plan is to evaluate further after release and read player feedback to the game mode. From there, we can see if anything needs to be adjusted or changed by working with the community. We see this as the start of a long journey and will keep tweaking it just like any other system in the game.<br/><br/>Thank you for your passion for Darktide and we hope we can answer the most burning questions we’ve seen. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Are FS concerned about people alt-F4ing this? For the Auric titles it was just the title but this is an entire game mode.<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>“Alt+F4:ing” to circumvent the system is something we’ve taken into account, there are two solutions to this issue, one which is bespoke to Havoc and the other a general solution. If a Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) owner leaves mid-mission <b>without reconnecting</b> it will automatically count as a loss regardless of the result of the mission for that player. It will also mean that the player receives no rewards for the attempt, and it will use up one of the three attempts for that specific Havoc Assignment level.<br/><br/>However, players who remain in the Mission will still be able to complete the mission; if they do, it will count as a win for the remaining players.<br/><br/>ALT+F4:ing to circumvent being “downed” to complete harder penances has been an issue with the Auric penance, and to this end, we’ve introduced more checks when players reconnect.** Players will now respawn back with the health count they had upon leaving, instead of being spawned with a minimal % of hp, and players who ALT+F4 to get around being downed will now spawn back hogtied.<br/><br/>**This is a game wide change coming with Grim Protocols, it is not exclusive to Havoc.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do we select the 1-5 difficulty level when playing Havoc or are these missions working on a completely different system, where difficulty is fixed?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc has its own difficulty structure that is loosely based on the normal difficulties. The way players can choose difficulty is by either starting their Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) by gathering some friends or by starting a group through the party finder. Likewise if you fancy another mission configuration you can look through the party finder and join one there.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>If I complete my Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) as soon as it’s available, do I have to wait a week before I’m given a new one?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You can complete as many Havoc Assignments in a row as you like. The only thing that is on a weekly cadence is the weekly reward which is based on the highest Havoc Assignment you were able to complete during the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I’m confused about how the decay system works for Havoc.<b><br/><br/>Answer</b><br/>Yes, let’s clarify the fluid ranking system using the new nomenclature written in the intro of this dev blog. It has changed a bit since the last dev blog after reading feedback.<br/><br/>A player’s Havoc Clearance Level will update on a weekly basis based on the highest Havoc Assignment they completed the previous week (whether it was their own Assignment or played through the Party Finder). <br/><br/>As long as a player is active within the Havoc system during any given week they will not automatically decay at the end of the week. We will however keep an eye on how this system plays out in reality and adjust the rules accordingly. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Can you replay your completed Havoc Assignment levels? Like if I was at level 20 but wanted to bust down to 5, could I do that on my own? Or would I need to find someone with a level 5 Assignment to join?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You cannot replay depleted / completed missions since the missions are uniquely generated. If you’d like to take a break and play a lower-rank Assignment you can instead find a compatible team on the party finder with the Assignment you like. The same goes for the opposite: if you want to try your hands on an Assignment that is higher than the one you currently own, you can find a team that is playing a higher one and ask to join them.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Is Havoc level character locked like Melk contracts (well trust level is, so…) so we’ll have to level our 4 characters at the same time each week?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc is not locked to a specific character, “ergo” Havoc is account-wide. With Havoc our intent is for players to adapt to the Havoc Assignment at hand by selecting the correct character, talents, weapons, blessing and curios to best take on the challenge. However, your character still needs to be level 30 to be able to join a Havoc mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Will new garb be also character locked then? (Level up operative to gain access to new Moebian cosmetics for that class).<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The cosmetics from Havoc are account-wide. (The same as any other cosmetic in the game.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>What determines the max difficulty that I can currently play?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>As long as a player is level 30 and can find a group that is willing to take them along, a player could in theory play any Assignment level at any time. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do I get access to a difficulty, based on my current highest completed? Can I access all difficulties &lt;= my current max, or only 1 diff at a time?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>At all times you have access to your own Assignment. If you feel like playing a lower Assignment level the way to do so would be to find a party with a lower Assignment level in the party finder and vice versa if you are looking for a higher Assignment level than what you currently own.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does my max available mission difficulty get reset every week?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Your maximum available mission difficulty will move forward with you into the next week. Each week players will get a new Havoc Assignment based on the highest Assignment they completed the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do i need to play from diff 1-40 within a single week in order to get to rank 40, unless i just join someone else's high diff mission?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>No, you will continue the next week at the same level that you left off the previous week. The only thing that is weekly dependent is the weekly reward that is based on the highest-ranked mission you completed during the week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>What happens when my rank drops? Do I lose access to the higher difficulty missions?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will always be able to play any Assignment Level that you want to play and are able to find a group that will play with you. Your own Havoc Assignment only dictates which mission you can start yourself. But if you can find a group that is playing a higher-ranked mission that you can join you will be able to do so. Your weekly reward will be based on the highest-ranked mission you have completed. Next week your Havoc Assignment will be set to the highest mission you have completed the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>To clarify, I’m pretty sure the modifiers at levels 1-40 are fixed for all players (possibly forever?). The only thing different for each player at the same level is the mission and mutators?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc Assignment’s difficulty is composed of two components, one is the static negative modifiers we apply per Level basis and are additive so each Assignment will include everything from the previous one, the other part is generated per Assignment basis and includes the Mission, Theme, and mutators. <br/><br/>Over time we’ll continue adding more mutators into the pool, but more on that at a later time…<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I don’t understand how matchmaking is going to work with this. There is no quickplay, but you can just queue into it? What does that mean for matchmaking? will it try to find 3 other players who are close to your ‘level’?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Due to the vast amount of permutations in the mode, there will not be any matchmaking in this game mode. Also the difficulty is so significant that you will want to tailor the group more specifically than a matchmaking service could do effectively. This is one of the reasons we created the Group Finder, which we hope will see a significant increase in use with the release of this feature.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does this mean that it will take at least 40 weeks for the first players to reach Hacoc Clearence Level 40?<br/><br/>Assuming the answer to the previous question is no, (ie, that when you gain or lose an Assigment Level you can immediately attempt your new Assignment Level), if you are demoted from Clearance Level 20 to 19, but then beat Level 19 and move back up to Level 20, will your new Havoc Assignemnt 20 still be the same as it was the first time?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will be able to reach Havoc Clearance Level 40 as fast as you and your team can complete the Assignments required to do so. There is no time gating happening when it comes to the number of assignments possible to complete in a given week. When you complete a Havoc Assignment, a new one will be designated to you by Darinda Dukane as soon as you report back to her. The new Assignment will not be the same as the previous one if you go up or down in Assignment level.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I would like to ask what happens to a player’s Havoc rating if they quit before the match completes?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Leaving before a Havoc mission ends will result in a loss for the player. It will also lock you out of starting another Havoc (only Havoc mission) until the mission has ended. If you are the Assignment holder, you will lose one of the attempts at the Havoc Assignment level. <br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="width=624,height=29"/>https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdoZbRX-cWzyCOZVGm0HA7aXYhRTHwCSnWS65GCU3lJziMFiKYWK2f-zBsLcIVWUzBwW_rtxlhaOPlE_NV7-XXy2XHS_ssiNhTV7F4pjZ2Sjnre3eJXNe5XmHI4nZKnk_ojRnPMPqwMOxUk1R_6LHwSRlmF?key=m0osxNPqksATxB0XbddLg6p3<br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does this mean your Havoc Clearance Level (“Rank”) will never go down, but that your access to Havoc Assignments will?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The Havoc Rank will display the highest Clearance Level a player has completed and is not directly linked to the current level of that player's Havoc Assignment. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Will there be a way to see what the current havoc rank of a player is? With rewards on the line for mission completion, I just get the feeling that people not ready for the latter half of havoc ranks will just try and join as many high ranking parties they can, looking to get carried through it.<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will be able to see the Clearance Levels of all prospective applicants to your group to be able to make the best informed decision.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>OK, that is our Q&amp;A! Thank you to everyone who wrote questions on our previous dev blog. As mentioned above, we’ll compile any of the common remaining questions after this post and we’ll include them in the patch notes for Grim Protocols on 3 December. <br/><br/>Thank you for your passion and we look forward to everyone getting their hands on Havoc and the rest of the update. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Kruber &amp; Ratling Gunner + Hotfix 6.0.4 + Hotfix 6.0.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490746800993468496</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>second</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div>But first, congratulations is in order! The first week's spotlight, Kerillian VS Gutter Runner, was a smash hit! The target for the Community Challenge was surpassed in no time, reaching a whopping 270,000 out of 40,000 by the time the event had ended, and was just shy of a million before the reset today! That's a lot of Heroes slain, you devilish Pactsworn!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a91509932b0c354b2376df02549dd83f6bd1332f.png"/><br/><br/>For everyone who played during the last spotlight, you've earned this Kerillian Hero Pose and this portrait frame (provided you accumulated enough playtime!):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/c688fb003f164b523d0f5554d50eac8cfe945716.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly through the Kill-Counter and personal rewards to unlock through a small ‘win-track’. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Kruber &amp; Ratling Gunner Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between November 21 - November 24.</b> All rewards will be granted the following week. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock an <b>exclusive skin for the Ratling Gunner.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Spotlight-track</div>Meanwhile, the win-track rewards will be unlocked depending on how much time you spend in Vermintide 2. Don’t worry, it won’t be too difficult, we promise. You can play Adventure, Chaos Wastes, Weaves, or Versus to unlock the rewards*. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/8de201cdceef319a43210aca4b34665957a53850.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Playing for at least half an hour earns you 60 shillings.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least an hour earns you another 60 shillings as well as 30 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least two hours additionally earns you a brand new Portrait frame and 70 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least three hours additionally earns you a Hero Pose for Kruber!</li></ul><i>This playtime is tracked across all game modes, but is only tracked while in an actual match.</i><br/><br/><i>*You cannot actively check on your track progression. All rewards will be granted the following week</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Kruber</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/aeb5353b2fbeeea8c3ced31be7947db1490b9c5f.png"/><br/>Although still world-weary and marked by his experiences, Kruber has found purpose in the aftermath of Ubersreik. As a soldier first, last and always, he understands that some battles have to be fought, no matter the cost. And who better to fight them than Markus Kruber?<br/><br/><b>Learn more about Kruber here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Ratling Gunner</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/84ce6edc1a9b95f76f5c01e1e8fa190cc8a148a6.png"/><br/>The Ratling Gun is a six-barreled monstrosity of unparalleled fire-rate, powered by warp steam and operated with a hand crank. This fearsome weapon is normally operated by a Clan Skryre weapons team, but lighter, experimental versions have been sighted in the Reikland. These variants require only a single ratman to act as crew, with little apparent trade-off.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Ratling Gunner here!</b><br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.0.4 - 20th of November							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Tweaked the power of items received from crafting:</b> Each Hero level past level 30 increases the minimum power of crafted items by 1. This means that at sufficiently high levels, crafted items are guaranteed to be 300 item power. Only the level from the highest level character is considered.<br/></li><li>	(Versus) <b>Tweaked the Helmgart Sellsword Marks received from playing matches:</b> Players now receive 5 coins for playing a match, plus another 5 if they won.<br/></li><li>	Tweaked the rarity of some of the Skaven skins.								<br/> </li><li>	Added the ability to equip Hero Poses on the Deprecated UI.								<br/> </li><li>	Removed fade to black when exiting the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Increased the window where players will count as having assisted or caused an enemy player kill based on how long it's been since you've last dealt damage to them.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Various quality of life improvements to the Custom Game lobby:								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Added the option to create private versus custom lobbies.</b> Private games can be joined by friend joining through Steam or the in-game friend UI.<br/></li><li>	Added more sound effects to various actions in the lobby.							<br/> </li><li>	Added the option to make the level random.							<br/> </li><li>	Added gamepad support for the custom game menu and lobby.							<br/> </li><li>	Changed so your team is always blue and the enemy team is red.							<br/> </li><li>	Added Steam avatars in custom game lobbies.							<br/> </li><li>	Changed the position of the leave button so it is harder to misclick.	<br/> </li><li>	Added an message for when a player-hosted VS lobby cannot be started (eg. everyone is on the same team).</li></ul></li><li>	(Versus) Made improvements to how versus lobbies are displayed in the lobby browser.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Slightly reduced the XP gained from winning matches, completing matches, and eliminating heroes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Added another ladder back up on the first bridge to more easily revive downed Heroes								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Pactsworn can no longer hear key pickup on Against the Grain.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue where the Pactsworn keybind prompts would overlap with the subtitles.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a missing sound when clicking the 'continue' button on the end screen.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue where the text would overlap in the end screen in some languages.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a bug where destroying all 9 chains in Screaming Bell would progress the related challenge by 10 instead.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where some cosmetics on Lohner's Emporium would say "Equippable by all Heroes and Careers" when they weren't.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed various issues in Righteous Stand, including a spot where players could get stuck, a potion that was hard to pick up, some visual bugs, and more.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed the rumbling sound effect not stopping if you die while shooting as a Warpfire Thrower.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the Mission Select tutorial showing up in non-Adventure keeps.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed DLC rewards and handbook popups showing on top of each other.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a visual glitch on the pagination buttons in the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug that made it impossible to open the handbook with controller in the pause menu.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where you couldn't scroll the text on handbook popups using a gamepad.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where the talents where half transparent in the tab menu.								<br/> </li><li>	Made bots in Versus always use default loadouts in both Dedicated Servers and player hosted games, avoiding various crashes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Custom Game) Fixed gamepad input description being incorrect.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Custom Game) Fixed confirm input not being confirmed when selecting a map.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the reward tooltips in difficulty select showing the best earned chest instead of the chest the player would earn at their level.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed crash that could happen when a player left while in a loading screen.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Added a lever to open the Ruins in Engines of War to avoid the mission being soft-locked.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue with Bile trolls portrait frames not showing the correct description								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a visual glitch on the next/prev page arrows in the handbook when using a controller								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed strings not being uppercased in a locale-dependant way (eg. `Botín de guerra` was `BOTíN DE GUERRA`).								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Fixed a bug where Skaven players can get soft-locked when they Q to Heroes that are AFK in the safe zone								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Added a fix to prevent Skaven players from entering the Hero safe zone before the round starts								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Added a fix to prevent Hero players from leaving the safe zone before the round starts								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Climb point improvements								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where allies that left the game early would be shown in the enemy team's scoreboard.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed bug where pact sworn climb points blocked interactions for heroes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Chaos Wastes) Fixed a crash caused by the damage sharing curse.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash caused by joining a match and trying to sync things that the joining player hadn't loaded yet.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where "Player eliminated" badge showed to the Sienna player when Sienna dies from overheating. As hilarious as it was.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed an issue where the cannon balls can get stuck in the elevator								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed an issue where players can not pass the destroyed Ram gate easily on both sides								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed some areas where players can get stuck or end up inside geometry								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Versus lobbies now show the difficulty as 'Versus' in the browser.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue that could cause player-hosted VS lobby level selection to sometimes fail saving.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash when trying to reserve a spot in a custom versus game before joining.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash that could happen when closing the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed kill and knockdown confirmation badge in Versus not properly showing when players are credited eliminations but are not dealing the final blow.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash when spawning as a DLC career if purchasing it while the game is running. Purchasing a dlc career no longer prompts the user to restart.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed victory and defeat sound stingers being muffled at the end of a match</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Status update for the players who lost progression during the update:					</div> <br/>		Hey all,<br/><br/>Apologies for the wait on an update to this issue. We hear your frustrations and concerns, understandably.<br/>We are still working with our backend service provider in an attempt to restore missing player data. A list of all affected player accounts has been provided to our backend service provider, and they are working to provide a snapshot of the lost player data before the issue occurred (which would be the fastest resolution); with which we can merge this back into your post update-6.0.0 account progression.<br/><br/>However, to be fully transparent, we have been informed that this is not guaranteed. It will take a little more time to know for sure. We appreciate this is concerning to hear, and we want to reassure affected players that <b>we have a plan B should it be needed.</b><br/>Our second option, involves using other existing logs and data we have, to create a ""backup"" that can bring your account data as close as possible to what is was prior to update 6.0.0, and then merge this with your post update-6.0.0 account progression. This is an extensive task and will take longer to deploy - so we are hoping it won't come to this.<br/><br/>In the meantime, this hotfix includes a part-fix to unlock Cataclysm again for any players who previously had it unlocked.<br/>We'll continue to provide updates and share more information as soon as we can. Thank you for your continued patience.		<br/><br/>You can follow our progress on this issue through this thread on our forums. <br/><div class="bb_h3">Known Issues</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Selecting a map in Custom Game and then switching to Random Map will crash the host.<br/></li><li> Players joining a Custom Game that is in the Hero selection phase will crash.</li></ul>We’re hoping to get those issues fixed as soon as possible.</blockquote> <br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.0.5 - 22nd of November							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed a bug that caused the Warrior Priest to not gain any fury from nearby enemies dying when playing as client.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the issue that allowed a Grail Knight with the 'Virtue of Audacity' talent to interrupt the second swing of the career skill to avoid going on cooldown.								<br/> </li></ul>	We've also applied all of the rewards from last week's spotlight! It might be necessary to restart the game a couple of times to get them applied, sorry about that!										</blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.14.3 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4465977003046076524</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/>The team is currently hard at work. We'll have news about new content soon.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.14.1</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Version 1.14.3 </div><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed crash when melee attackers kill an Umbra.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 13:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
