<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.3.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/519726998179807814</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/2027196109ff58d3699af1d84a8bc203663ba1c8.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just rolled out Hotfix 6.3.2 to Total War: WARHAMMER III, implementing the changes we’ve been working on in order to rectify the issues with Lizardmen and Tomb Kings AI.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll be keeping a close eye on your experiences with these changes and their effectiveness, but our testing has produced positive results in addressing the issue for these factions. If you missed our blog detailing more about this, you can read it here. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks for your patience!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Hotfix 6.3.2</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>What was wrong?</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The recruitment issues present with the Lizardmen and Tomb Kings races where the Campaign AI was not recruiting units correctly and was consequently blocked from taking other actions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>How did we fix it?</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 6.3.2 corrects two errors. Firstly, where the Campaign AI was not made aware of pooled resource restrictions on unit availability, and secondly adds an update to a previous change that caused a mishandling of stat gathering for zero cost units.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>How will it impact me in game?</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With this update and the application of this fix, the Campaign AI will take those pooled resource restrictions into account, and will properly assess the value of the units they’re recruiting which in turn means you should see Lizardmen and Tomb King factions recruiting armies, expanding and fighting it out.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Next Steps</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now that we’re deploying this hotfix for the Tomb Kings and Lizardmen, we’ll be closely monitoring your feedback to identify any emergent problems that require further investigation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you run into any other issues after updating to 6.3.2, please be sure to raise them in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The Total War Team </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Fest has begun!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/528734197434548760</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Steam's triannual festival of demos starts today, and Mechanicus II is taking part.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The demo's been out just over a week now, and the response from the community has been really encouraging. Thank you for the support, feedback and bug reports – we’ve been reading it all!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just pushed an updated demo build with the following fixes and improvements:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added controller support.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor optimisation improvements – investigating this has been and continues to be a priority.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues caused by changing difficulty mid-skirmish.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug causing Skitarii Rangers' faces to disappear.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a soft lock when exiting to the main menu at the exact moment a tutorial triggered.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed font rendering issues in French, Simplified Chinese, Japanese, and Korean.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed UI issues on 16:10 displays.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an error caused by alt-tabbing between windows.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added missing loading-screen quotes in several non-English languages.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">New to the community? Join us on Discord to discuss the game with us and your fellow acolytes of the Machine God, and maybe even take part in our character colouring competition, in which you could win prizes worth over £600!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFFKOPTA GOES BRRRRRRRR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/542244996316659850</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deff is comin' from above</b> on <b>ORKTOBER 23rd</b>!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Deffkopta is by far the most unique vehicle in the game now - it's <i>really</i> different, and awesome to fly. We've been having a proppa time zipping around the maps and using it in the much improved <b>Creation Mode</b>, which is also coming later this month.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We can't wait to get the vehicle into your hands so you can do the same.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Today we reward you patient gits with some teasers of the Deffkopta in action</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aa060504adc1f5408379761f8359379dd94e9bfd.gif"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph">BRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">BTW, only one person guessed correctly when we asked what you thought the next vehicle would be, and that's <b>ML_Paladin888</b> 🧠⚡</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Congrats, you get a free Soundtrakk, ya git!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll be disclosing the Deffkopta's weapons/abilities when it launches with the update in a few weeks ːsteamthumbsupː</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Flyboyz among you will rejoice</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, another GIF?</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3d00d6013eb6ec4e6ccf44adcbb2c1bd5a3e6f5b.gif"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph">We love this lil' guy.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">ORKTOBER IZ 'ERE 🔥</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We're not done showing things off to you lot. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As we've said before, the Orktober 23rd update will be the biggest the game has ever seen, and our next post we'll be revealing the new <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> in Creation Mode</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some testers have already been creating wild race courses that we never thought we'd see in the game, so we're really pumped to find out how the broader community uses these tools. It's a literal game-changer with how creative you can get.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">More details coming soon, but here's a little teaser of a race level made by community member "Only//" with the game's level editor 💪</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7e4bc8fed084a851365bfafe4533a48d2687491f.jpg"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0da4102c5d72896f02525f05662d2f3aea9836b6.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The ORKTOBER celebration continuez next week, so be sure to keep yer peepers on dis page ya?</p><div class="bb_h3">This update will be massive </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, feel free to chat in the comments below or join our Discord to jump ingame with other gits<br/>https://discord.com/invite/speedfreeks40k</p><div class="bb_h1"></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 10.3 is live</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/507342099205586984</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Dear players,</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Patch 10.3 has just been deployed. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that this update simply brings technical compatibility with the upcoming Demo starting October 16. 😌</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h2">Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">added compatibility with the Demo version (to be released 16/10)</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 09:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #79 - 1.9.3 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499459531596630319</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8adc8b2f787c92985d2046fbca56a1846780bafe.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hotfix #79 (1.9.3)</b> is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below. <i>As a heads up, this hotfix will be somewhat heavier than previous ones due to various changes to sound files (~3.3 GB)</i></p><div class="bb_h2">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Scab Plasma Gunner</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New charge sound</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New “Scope” VFX and “Scope” SFX</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">These should make dodging more consistent</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shot cooldown lowered from 2.4 to 2.0</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lowered dodge window from 0.7 to 0.6</p></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a rare crash that could occur in Havoc when spawning enemies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with subtitles displaying over menus.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug that could cause multiple voicelines to play at the same time in the Mourningstar.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Veteran “Rangefinder Goggles” headgear cosmetics would cause a small patch of balding.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some timing issues with the Plasma Gunner’s sound effects.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Force Staves would fail to shoot the projectile that triggered the Perils of the Warp state.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Veteran's Infiltrate would not end when damaging an enemy in the first 0.5s of entering stealth.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Psyker's Soulblaze from Perilous Combustion and Venting Shriek could be applied to un-aggroed Daemonhosts, waking them up.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Relic Blade</b> - Fixed an issue where it was not always possible to immediately chain an attack after performing a Special activate/de-activate action while sprinting.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note:</b> <i>thanks to players arkanian1210, aroth68 and CobaltNinja (among others) for bringing this to our attention!</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash caused by the visual effects of Rotten Armour enemies.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note:</b> <i>we thought we had fixed the same crash in our previous hotfix, but it was only a partial fix. This should solve all occurrences of the issue.</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where players could path upwards from specific nodes in the Veteran talent tree.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re aware of increased disconnects and server instability since the 1.9.0 update. Hotfixes have provided some improvements and we’re monitoring closely; restoring full stability will take additional time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some players might experience a rare crash occurring when trying to equip items to a character. This is affecting players with old loadout preset data. For players experiencing this issue, creating a new loadout preset should bypass the crash. A fix will be deployed soon to address the crash, which will in some instance delete the character loadouts.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your patience and your understanding!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 09:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
