<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>New Archetypes in the Void Shadows DLC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4265557936889641697</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
In the upcoming DLC, the Lord Captain will come face to face with an Imperial Death Cult. These masters of assassination demonstrate their devotion to the God-Emperor by studying every facet and aspect of death: their grotesque rituals and bloody sacrifices conceal, like a sheath, the sophisticated art of slaughter's honed blade. To understand first-hand the lethal grace of their craft, simply examine the arsenal of abilities possessed by Kibellah — a Death Cult representative seeking to join your retinue. The new archetypes available at character creation were specifically designed to reflect the terrifying efficiency of the Death Cult.<br/><br/>Let's take a closer look at the new archetypes in the Void Shadows DLC: the first-tier archetype — the <b>Bladedancer</b> and the second-tier archetype — the <b>Executioner</b>. Both are primarily focused on attributes desirable for any melee combatant. These new archetypes not only complement each other excellently but also open up numerous lucrative synergies with existing character-build options.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"><b>Bladedancer</b></div><br/><b>Available Second-Tier Archetypes: </b>Assassin, Master Tactician, Arch-Militant, Executioner.<br/><b>Characteristics: </b>Weapon Skill, Strength, Toughness, Agility.<br/><b>Skills: </b>Athletics, Medicine, Carouse, Awareness, Demolition.<br/><br/>The Bladedancer is an elusive acrobat, skillfully manoeuvring through the battlefield in a deadly dance. With each kill, they gain charges of<b> Death From Above</b>: an ability allowing the Bladedancer to perform a short jump, dealing damage to all enemies in the impact zone. <b>Death From Above</b> damage scales with Agility and Weapon Skill. If such a display of prowess isn't enough, the <b>Death Waltz </b>heroic act enables the Bladedancer to repeat this pirouette multiple times in succession: the more Agility the character has, the longer they can continue this dance of death. And when deep behind enemy lines, completely surrounded, the Bladedancer can effortlessly return to the cell where they began their turn by utilising the<b> Acrobatic Artistry</b> ability, leaving bewildered foes unable to punish the bladedancer’s incisive incursions. This impressive arsenal will satisfy anyone looking for ease of strategic positioning and manoeuvrability across the battlefield, such as a Master Tactician or Arch-Militant.<br/><br/>But what if the "death" in <b>Death Waltz </b>attracts you more than the "dance?" The Bladedancer is ready to shed blood, whether it be that of their enemies, allies, or even their own. Performing a blood sacrifice, forfeiting their own life force, the Bladedancer strikes swiftly and precisely, critically injuring their foes. This deadly focus can also serve as a defensive measure: the Bladedancer's mastery with two-handed and dual-wielded swords is so great that they can conceal themselves in a literal <b>Blade Shroud</b>, reflecting incoming shots back at their enemies, albeit at the cost of overstraining and damaging themselves.<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/827877966616854558/1273203232520404993/reaper-2.gif?ex=66bdc269&amp;is=66bc70e9&amp;hm=08c0695f86290252e0f3f200a518fde87c53e05b61a2bc6932ee7b49faaabdb1&amp;"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"><b>Executioner</b></div><br/><b>Available First-Tier Archetypes: </b>Warrior, Operative, Bladedancer.<br/><b>Characteristics: </b>Weapon Skill, Strength, Toughness, Intelligence.<br/><b>Skills: </b>Athletics, Medicine, Lore (Imperium), Lore (Xenos).<br/><br/>This archetype is available to Warriors, Operatives, or Bladedancers who revel in the heart-wrenching screams of their victims. The Executioner specialises in manipulating damage-over-time effects, vastly increasing their potency and converting them into debilitating injuries. Each of the Executioner's strikes is meticulously calculated to maximise the deadliness of afflictions on their enemies: comprehensive knowledge of anatomy allows this gruesome warrior to dismantle foes piece by piece, deepening lacerations and intensifying haemorrhaging as their knowledge of Medicine increases.<br/><br/>The Executioner is perfect for characters with the Biomancer or Pyromancer Psyker origins. Connoisseurs of incendiary bombs, toxic grenades, flamethrowers, needle weaponry, and other exotic instruments of pain will also find the Executioner especially delightful.<br/><br/>With <b>Reckless Abandon</b>, the Executioner carelessly plunges the entire battlefield into excruciating agony, sharing in the torment themself and enhancing damage-over-time effects at the cost of their own health. The Executioner can then hurl all opposition into peril with their heroic act: <b>Carnival of Misery</b> — foes are set ablaze, poisoned, and suffer heavy bleeding. But that’s not all, for the Executioner's heroic act doubles the damage over time of these effects! And after all their foes are burning, poisoned, and bleeding, you can savour in their agony until they fall silent, for the terrifying master of torture draws power from their very suffering. By way of the <b>Gift of Torment</b> ability, the Executioner receives bonuses to armour, evasion, and deflection, scaling with the number of enemies afflicted by damage-over-time effects.<br/><br/>And, finally, the Executioner’s <b>Where It Hurts</b> initiates the toccata-finale in their wonderful symphony of pain. After using this free-action ability, the Executioner’s next attack immediately triggers a burst of multiple damage-over-time procs on the target, ending those effects along with the lives of their hapless victims.<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/827877966616854558/1273203232134402069/reaper-1.gif?ex=66bdc269&amp;is=66bc70e9&amp;hm=a1593cb5e6233152a40d1b70864590c5c00415f69c5d654b6cecdacdb934f51e&amp;"/><br/><br/>Be the fiercest adversary your foes have ever encountered — call forth a typhoon of blood with a whirlwind of attacks and let them tremble in your wake! Armed with new, powerful abilities, you and Kibellah will paint the battlefield in the noble hues of the Death Cult: an exhilarating performance for you and a convocation of doom for those who dare to confront you. See you in the first DLC amidst the Void Shadows!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #45 (1.4.11) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4286950035120168147</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ee5d213b366d8e366fa7947809f92a640041d3b3.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div><br/>As promised yesterday, here is hotfix #45 (1.4.11). It is live now on Steam and it will shortly go live on our other platforms. <br/><div class="bb_h2">Fixes </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a server crash issue related to a player taking damage from a projectile or the environment when they were dead or knocked down. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Orthus Offensive special assignment where one of the twins could double spawn.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We have a known issue of certain blessings (like Shattering Impact) showing an undefined text description. The cause has been identified and we’re working on a fix for this, as well. <br/></li><li> We also have a known issue of certain advanced circumstances not working properly (e.g. No Ammo modifier). We are working on a fix for this. In the meantime, we're going to disable these on the mission board. </li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Hit-Reg Improvements &amp; Much More ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797829891536</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Oi Speed Freeks,</b><br/><br/>Today, we've released an update that addresses many player's top concerns. In our testing we've noticed significant improvements and we hope you will now too.<br/><br/>Here are the details:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improvements to weapon and ability hit registration over the network<br/></li><li> Improvements to aiming synchronization over the network<br/></li><li> Optimized Shokkjump Dragsta Shokk rifle VFX to be much more performant. This might fix the stuttering issue during play for some people<br/></li><li> Deffkilla Wartrike unlock challenge set to 50m kill proximity instead of 10m and improved kill proximity detection<br/></li><li> Removed sound effect for PROS message of the day cycling<br/></li><li> Reduced Stompa arm-mounted gatling gun knockback, increased damage slightly<br/></li><li> Looted Wagon Grot Bomm damage reduced to 60 (from 70)<br/></li><li> Boomdakka Snazzwagon Billowing Smoke duration decreased to 4 seconds (from 5), Mek speshul primary accuracy decreased slightly<br/></li><li> Fix for saw sound effect not playing at recap progress.<br/></li><li> Fix the remaining time display for daily challenges in the UI<br/></li><li> Fix for daily challenges being reset<br/></li><li> Burna Valley finish line time increased by 10 seconds<br/></li><li> Changed Teef icon colour to yellow<br/></li><li> Playtime bonus Scrap per minute increased to 575 (from 500)<br/></li><li> Adding dialogue box confirmation when leaving the game during a match, which explains that teams are randomized in the next match and that Scrap gained from this match will be lost<br/></li><li> Locked vehicles now shown at the KUSTOMIZE and in-game spawning screens, with message saying that they can be unlocked through challenges<br/></li><li> Increased Latest Loot to 12 items in the store<br/></li><li> Fixed challenges screen to work properly with 16:10 aspect ratio<br/></li><li> Fixed audio issue where sound entered another, terrible dimension when set below 25%<br/></li><li> Some audio mix adjustments and overall volume lowered 2 db since it was a bit loud<br/></li><li> Vehicles now always have full boost when respawning<br/></li><li> Explicitly added vehicle compatibility to item descriptions in the store<br/></li><li> Increased available search window time for matchmaking<br/></li><li> Various improvements to controller management to avoid conflicts <br/></li><li> Added vehicle abilities screen to KUSTOMIZE menu<br/></li><li> Fix for achievements with no rewards showing at the end of match recap.<br/></li><li> Fix for challenge sets showing incomplete information at the end of match recap.<br/></li><li> Bots now use dash and are more aggressive with their initial combat engagement</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9c04148e5c2b05df99b1ea46c5b553e77574520.png"/><br/>Some of the highest priority tasks we’re working on still:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fix issue with vehicle challenges seemingly resetting progress and not unlocking items<br/></li><li> Fix issue with Teef not showing up after they have been unlocked through progression<br/>    - If this has effected you try this:     https://playersupport.plaion.com/hc/articles/20848220459037<br/></li><li> Fixing an issue with Scrap Boosts not showing up after they have been unlocked through progression<br/></li><li> Fixing issues with not being able to create/join a party and/or matchmake as a party <br/></li><li> Making sure matchmaking puts you in your region (server provider issue – they are being contacted)<br/></li><li> Improving matchmaking to make fewer but more full lobbies<br/></li><li> Adding servers in Oceania, South America (server provider has been contacted to allow us to do this)<br/></li><li> DeffKilla Wartrike front guns may fail to deal damage if a players ended a game in the wartrike and continues to use it in the next game without switching vehicle. Switching to another vehicle and then back to the trike solves this issue for that game.<br/></li><li> Further improvements to netcode / hit-reg</li></ul><b>Thank you for baring with us and all those who have helped us hone in on these issues. </b><br/>We're pleased with these additions and refinements. But of course, this is an on going process and we're looking forward to seeing your feedback and make future adjustments.<br/><br/>Until then, Happy Krumping.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #44 (1.4.10) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4353377496618128723</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/87b20a41134ebed69cbc9a1b6c0973ec475f75e7.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><i>Note: As a heads up, this hotfix includes routine updates to our audio software, which resulted in a chunkier sized update compared to normal.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New In-Game Event: Herald of Admonition</div>Rolling blackouts are plaguing sectors of the hive. Worse, we’ve heard reports of someone, or something lurking in the darkness. We need devoted rejects to get down there and sort this mess out.<br/><br/>Play and complete missions with a new Special Condition, “Terror in the Dark” to earn rewards. This condition will only be available during the event!<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, August 15. The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1a1fe4c4b6fe80a9ec0e09ba85ee249b162c25e6.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes and Changes</div><div class="bb_h3">Weapons</div><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tweaked the animation for the Heavy 1 attack windup when chained from the Heavy 2 attack to be more aligned to the actual attack being released.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Light 4 attack was receiving an incorrect scaling from the Cleave Damage stat.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Performance</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved performance in the Clandestium Gloriana mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Mission</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Minor fix for subtitles in a VO at the start of Enclavum Baross.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Cosmetics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issues with the mouthpiece deforming improperly when using certain faces when the Veteran “Metalfab 97 Worker’s Mask” headgear was equipped.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the Lasgun “Accatran Pattern Mk IV Lasgun (Betalis Night)” weapon skin where the 3D ammo display would not update appropriately.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 12 - Kustomize ‘Ya ride 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338739528793079279</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Get ready Speed Freeks, the finish line is in sight! </div>Cross it in style, by using ‘ya battle loot to look Snazzy <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2fb2aec78e6ce309bdfbf419582bc020cad5854a.gif"/><br/><br/><b>Scrap </b>and <b>Teef</b> are the two resources that you can use to unlock cosmetics in Speed Freeks. <br/><br/><b>Scrap</b> is collected by fighting and finishing matches. It drives your progression through the WAAAGH! PATH while unlocking plenty of items along the way.  <br/><br/><b>Teef</b> are purchased with real money and can be spent in the Mek Shop to buy cosmetics. <br/><br/>Purchasing the Loot Pass with Teef allows you to earn a ton of extra items in the WAAAGH! PATH. It also lets you skip the latest vehicle's unlock challenge. Please consider purchasing the Loot Pass to unlock a lot of cool cosmetics as well as early access to the latest vehicle!<br/><br/>It’s important to note that all vehicles featured in the WAAAGH! PATH can also be unlocked simply by playing matches and there are also no time limited cosmetics.<br/><br/><b>There are no pay-to-win features in Speed Freeks</b>. Cosmetics (and Scrap Boosts) are the only thing you can buy with real money, whether that's buying the Loot Pass to unlock more items as you play or by buying them directly from the Mek Shop.<br/><br/>Scrap Boosts on the other hand, are progression boosters that allow you to unlock cosmetics faster and have no effect on gameplay.<br/><br/><b>Right now, customization in Speed Freeks is cosmetic only</b>. In the future, we might explore other types of customization options, but we will never lock those options behind a paywall, and we are committed to respecting the time of our non-paying players. <br/><br/>Read on for a walkthrough of the myriads of options available to you to truly express your WAAAGH!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3cb6b08e8b1cc515a13ee1b70db5ce4a314c3d3f.png"/><br/>The Kustomize screen allows you to piece together wild creations, paint them in whatever colors you choose and then take them onto the battlefield to flaunt your spoils of war. <br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Let's put the snazz into our snazzwagon.</b></div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 1: The most important part of customization is the kit</div>A kit is a modified version of the vehicle's default chassis. These can range from small adjustments to full-scale reworks. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e4fd7cbbe05c588ac68920ca3235a5fdae254ca7.png"/><br/>Let’s go with the Spikey Wagon kit. We want this thing to look mean, while sticking to the classic look of the Snazzwagon. You can also buy this kit with Teef as part of the Boomdakka Snazzwagon Pack in the Mek Shop. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 2: Next, the paintjob</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5afbbc00b48b46c374232aaa2a26784b51a38449.png"/><br/>We'll start with the Goff clan paintjob as a base. You can unlock all the clan paintjobs by completing vehicle challenges. For the Goff paintjobs, it's all about racking up kills and assists, because Goffs love getting stuck in!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/874fb2a73bb78a46cb911ef6fb816ae7c61c7c2f.png"/><br/>Let’s now click on the wrench icon to customize the colors. Nothing crazy, we'll just swap the red highlights for some green and yellow. Green, we all know, is best, and yellow because it’s the color of dakka. Of course, this wagon packs a whole lotta dakka.  <br/><br/>Those players who took part in our alpha and beta playtests will notice a lot more paint colors in the above screenshot! <b>There are currently 153 to choose from, including metallics! </b><br/><br/>While the Ork adage goes <b>'red wunz go fasta'</b>, this belief is not yet true at Early Access launch for Speed Freeks because the color of paint you choose won't affect your vehicle's stats. We don't want players to feel restricted in how they paint their vehicles to receive a certain buff. However, we will keep our eye on community feedback about this, so drop us a comment on our Feature Upvote page [link] if you have suggestions about our Ork color theory.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 3: Now it's time for the rims</div>These ones are nice and spiky. If you buy our Loot Pass, they’re unlocked right at the start of the WAAAGH! PATH. But remember, there is no time limit, you can complete the WAAAGH! PATH at your own pace, and at any time!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8fa1978bf0fe954d79f30612fca6d610d34f276b.png"/><br/>Selecting the gear icon again, we can mess with the rim's colors to make them better match the rest of the vehicle. Every good model painter knows how important the details are! If you want to learn more about how we referenced real painted models to define the art style of this game, check out Dev Blog 06!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b5812babd1a2941ed8299b66027f2647a79f56e7.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 4: The tires are already good and spiky</div>...so we’ll move right on to the Gubbinz.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bd9c87ae9c245ced977ab726b329cffd0f984342.png"/><br/><br/>Let's stick the Dakka glyph on there, which is unlocked for all vehicles by completing a Boomdakka Snazzwagon challenge and paint it yellow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 5: Here, we'll choose the Squig Pole</div>It's fully animated, so to really appreciate it gnawing the life out of that metal bar you'll have to check it out in game.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e50a1d483f2706e6e774197609eb6dacdb72cfd5.png"/><br/>The Squig Pole is available in the Supporter's Pack within the Mek Shop. Buying this pack also gets you a loyal Grot companion to go with you in your Krumped Kam taunt screen and several other menu screens. If you want to support this game, please consider picking up the Supporter's Pack!<br/> <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Et Voilà, as Orks don’t say.</div>Compared to the default look, here on the right is our finished vehicle! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aeb97ab24ecd493ad258cbc3ce39c0db08ef23c8.png"/><br/>We hope that the customization features in Speed Freeks will bring more joy to your inner Mek! <br/><br/>Personalization is a huge part of the hobby, and the kit-bashing culture constantly leaves us in awe. For those of us without bits boxes and workshops, please enjoy this Orky digital sandbox. While a videogame could never match the creative spirit that has fuelled the Warhammer 40000 community for decades, these options are our closest digital approximation of that hobby feeling <br/><br/>We can’t wait to see the manic machines you’ll bash together in Speed Freeks. Join our Discord and its dedicated customization showcase channel, #da-snazzlounge, to post your creations. We also want to see them in all our other social spaces: <br/>X/Twitter<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/28cfb7a3e2161a12b6d6b2c156e458adde567bde.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/>  <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>X/Twitter<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
