<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/515199580404450038</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0d41133979c8b72557fa31089016b21ea98c7b5d.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks!<br/><br/>As alluded to earlier in January, we're back with another hotfix for Total War: WARHAMMER III. Hotfix 6.0.4 introduces a plethora of fixes and tweaks to improve your gameplay experience. Here's a couple of highlights from this hotfix:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Lords would not disengage from a settlement after selecting certain post battle options. This includes, but is not limited to, The Changeling when establishing a Trickster Cult and the Vampire Coast when establishing a Pirate Cove.<br/></li><li> Ogre armies can now recruit Regiments of Renown when they are within the circle of influence of an Ogre Camp.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where reinforcing AI units will be given the same order location and will clump together as they all try and pile on to complete their order.</li></ul>Read on for the full list of changes...<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when attempting to reset skill points for female characters. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when changing the factions on the left side of the Intrigue of the Court panel while playing as the High Elves. <br/></li><li> Fixed a possible crash that could occur when saving and reloading a save file after a manual battle. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when trying to imprison a Military Convoy Lord. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that would occur when trying to select an Ogre Lord with over 100,000 Meat resource. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when using Eltharion’s Athel Tamarha imprisonment mechanic on an Ogre Tyrant or a Caravan Master. <br/></li><li> Fixed a very rare crash caused by a frame-based issue that would occur when triggering a VFX particle system e.g. artillery demolishing a structure during a siege. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash in The Lost God Prologue campaign caused by selecting Spartak Matrosov in the Beacon settlement and pressing attack target.  <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when clicking or hovering over the zoom to army location button in the Challenges of Khorne screen while dragging the map.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Lords would not disengage from a settlement after selecting certain post battle options. This includes, but is not limited to, The Changeling when establishing a Trickster Cult and the Vampire Coast when establishing a Pirate Cove. <br/></li><li> Resolved an issue where Concealment Bombs were granted innately in the campaign, ensuring that the skill to grant them is now relevant/useful.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where armies obtained via Allegiance (borrowed from allied factions) with Scrap/Aspect/Mutation upgrades had access to those upgrades. Viewing the upgrades is now limited to cases where they exist, are not locked/excluded, or the army is loaned. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue so that AI factions will now hire mercenaries from your Ogre camps. <br/></li><li> Eternal War spawned armies no longer trigger Daemons Reforged, aligning with the intended design. <br/></li><li> Ogre armies can now recruit Regiments of Renown when they are within the circle of influence of an Ogre Camp.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where WAAAGH! armies would erroneously execute underway interceptions. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the Manufactory panel being inaccessible if no further upgrades were available. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug for Orcs &amp; Goblins where the Scrap Upgrades button would grey out when a unit is instantly recruited. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a tooltip explaining that settlements razed by Khornate factions are blocked from occupation wouldn’t appear. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Orcs &amp; Goblins or Wood Elves could access Scrap or Aspects on Skaven units, causing Throt's Lab UI to appear broken. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with Challenges of Khorne battles where Challenge armies on the campaign minimap didn’t have icons. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with Challenges of Khorne battles so that players can now know if the Challenge army will be reinforced beforehand. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Recruitment cost reduction rewards for Arbaal's Challenges were missing from event notifications, despite appearing in the Challenges of Khorne screen. Notifications now correctly display all rewards when receiving or completing a Challenge.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">BATTLE </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved some instances where ranged units will clump while reforming but we're still looking into further issues with this.<br/></li><li> Improved Gotrek and Felix’s initial survivability in ‘The Adventures of Gotrek and Felix’ quest battle (to Gotrek’s dismay).  <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where replays wouldn’t have projectile upgrades saved into them e.g. Elspeth’s Helstorm rocket batteries upgraded in the Imperial Gunnery School would fire 3 instead of 4 rockets in a volley.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Unyielding Assault failed to prevent Melee Attack reductions from Fatigue.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">AI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where reinforcing AI units will be given the same order location and will clump together as they all try and pile on to complete their order.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">AUDIO</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Kholek was missing persistent VFX sounds in campaign. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Vampire Counts Corpse Carts were missing sound effects. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Foundry of Bones - Chaos was missing the lava lake and river sounds. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where certain environmental loops did not stop after a cutscene. </li></ul><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues or bugs after updating to Hotfix 6.0.4, please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update on Hotfix #58 (1.6.5)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592036258645103</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/465a2dc3a25ffc297e2644fa2f8b52ce9307794e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hi Everyone,</div><br/>After our latest hotfix went live today, we noticed a crash can occur when some players access the Sacrifice area with Hadron and the Shrine of the Omnissiah.<br/><br/><i>For now, we recommend players to avoid Sacrificing any weapons.</i><br/>We are already working on another hotfix to address this crash. It will be coming out ASAP.<br/><br/>Thank you,<br/><br/>The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Trader Collector's Editions - last batch available at merch.warhammer.com</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503940938959160344</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>A new message has arrived from your companion, Jae Heydari. The smuggler reports that she has managed to arrange the perfect deal, one truly worthy of a Rogue Trader.<br/><br/>A limited run of the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader Collector's Edition has become available at merch.warhammer.com. If you haven't yet had the chance to buy your copy, then you won’t want to miss this final opportunity to do so!<br/><br/>https://merch.warhammer.com/products/warhammer-40000-rogue-trader-collectors-edition?_pos=1&amp;_sid=28856c25a&amp;_ss=r<br/><br/>In it, you will find a beautiful statue of your Lady Navigator, Cassia Orsellio, a game Art Book, a legendary Warrant of Trade, and so much more!<br/><br/>Hurry, Lord Captain, for these are the last Editions available!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/f5051e8af8a7f14fd24b0b2b20572d29511eacb0.jpg"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #58 (1.6.5) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592036258645046</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/465a2dc3a25ffc297e2644fa2f8b52ce9307794e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>We’ve got our first Hotfix (#58 aka 1.6.5) for the year ready for everyone now. It’s begun to roll out across all of our platforms and it’ll begin to be available shortly. Players might want to relog to access the new servers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Re: Stalls and disconnects on console. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We are continuing to investigate the increased rate of stalls causing disconnects on console. We’ve seen this happens more frequently in high intensity missions such as higher levels of Havoc and Auric Maelstrom missions. We have some initial ideas on what might help with these disconnects and we have included those fixes in this patch. <br/></li><li>We have additional fixes in the works for the next update as well. As the hotfix rolls out, we’ll continue to monitor player comments to see if there have been improvements, as well as checking data on our end.</li></ul></li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> [Console] Fixed a rare crash which could happen when suspending the game immediately after launching it. <br/></li><li> Fixed an uncommon crash which could happen when a player joined a Strike Team through the Party Finder due to the game failing to retrieve their profile data.<br/></li><li> Small improvements to memory usage for UI code. <br/></li><li> Improved presentation of the Weapons and Curios icons. The icons will now appear smaller, but better aligned and with more of the item visible. <br/></li><li> Fixed UI crash that can happen while showcasing the mastery progression in the end of round. <br/></li><li> Fixed some typos and incorrect translations.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description text of the Special action was overlapping with the UI in the Inspect screen for the Blaze Force Greatsword weapon family.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Quickplay “Select Threat Level” UI element was misplaced in the Mission Board menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where an incorrect image could be displayed when receiving a Party Finder invitation while already participating in a mission.<br/></li><li> Fixed a missing texture issue that sometimes resulted in a crash.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with missing physics and stretching materials on the Veteran “Desert Hood (Dune camo)” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the eyebrow would be removed while wearing the Zealot “Votarist's Pot Helm with Rebreather” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed the scaling of the decal on the side of the Psyker “Krieg Witch Mask (Krieg 143rd, Shadow Ops)” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the eyebrow would be removed while wearing the Ogryn “Mark XII Brute Model Cranial Implant (Size XXXXL)” headgear cosmetic.  </li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 10:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"DLC of your dreams" community survey - give us your feedback!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503940938959160186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We've asked you about this in Pathfinder, and the time has come to do the same for Rogue Trader. <br/><br/>What would a perfect DLC be for you, should we make more of them?<br/><br/>Let us know by participating in the "DLC of your dreams" survey: <br/><br/>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/3NCWL3B<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/1c5bca97ec02029f65b72f4e34db061a66df2d4f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
