<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 10.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/507340197095015470</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2"><b>​Hello Space Marines,</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A new hotfix is now live on every platform. It fixes critical issues such as the Assault’s Ascension perk dealing friendly-fire damage, Stratagems having more Battlefield Conditions than listed and more. Also, the Sniper’s Camo Cloak activation cost change (which was initially planned for 11.0) has also been pushed on this update. Read the complete patch notes below:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>PATCH NOTES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>GAMEPLAY AND BALANCING TWEAKS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heroic Chainsword:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rebalanced base stats.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reworked its perk: Light-&gt;Heavy-&gt;Heavy combo now ends with a Stomp attack.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">All Heavy attacks damage increased by 15%.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Stratagems:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Daily Stratagems could have more Battlefield Conditions than listed.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Camo Cloak's activation cost:</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The activation cost of the Sniper ability has been changed. Now it works this way: </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The first three uses of Camo Cloak in a row do not take away energy by themselves (the ability consumes energy, as before). The fourth activation takes away 5% of energy instantly, each subsequent one takes away a little more. After the last use, there is a 10-second timer, after which the activation cost again becomes zero.</p></li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>With the right perk set up, you can still do 5-6 cloak cancels in a row. Cloak cancel will still be very rewarding to learn and to do, but you won't be able to abuse it endlessly while staying invisible and invulnerable to enemies.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Spawn Director:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The number of Chaos Spawns in packs is slightly reduced and now matches Tyranid Warriors.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>GENERAL FIXES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed damage for the Power Backstep attack when the Power Wave perk is selected for Power Axe.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved flame weapons VFX visibility for allies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that prevented bots from entering elevators in Exfiltration operation.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed perks dealing friendly fire damage.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed PvP connectivity issues.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor localization fixes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor UI fixes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">ESRB update pop-up: A pop-up will appear on the main menu to inform you of an update of the ESRB rating. This pop-up will only appear once. </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Please note that this update of our rating is just here to properly reflect what was already in-game for several months. There has been no change to our monetization system, and no changes are planned.</i></p></li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.3.1 Beta</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497205828189685820</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/64ff70b24e924c153e9f87802775353c8b32701f.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey there folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Next Tuesday, September 23rd, we’ll publish Hotfix 6.3.1, our final planned game update prior to the release of Total War: WARHAMMER III: Tides of Torment and the release of Game Update 7.0.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve focused this Hotfix on bringing further improvements to many of the changes brought with Patch 6.3 and offering some refined balance changes for both Lizardmen and Tomb Kings. This Hotfix also helps to address an unintended AI behavior that was causing AI controlled factions to poorly budget their resource, and result in instances of low stack armies on your campaign maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There’s a host of additional changes, fixes and improvements detailed below, but if you’d like to check out the changes for yourself, <b>players on Steam can switch their client to the Beta branch</b> and play these changes right now. You can find instructions on how to do this at the bottom of this post.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Here's some highlights from today's release:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Highlights</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Two new frontend toggles for Unusual Locations as well as balance changes and bug fixes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lizardmen factions that have mechanics to spawn in Blessed units now gain double the Spawning Sequence from performing actions compared to the 6.3 release.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">All Lizardmen factions have a method of increasing the capacity of Blessed Spawning units.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tomb King factions can now begin researching technologies from Turn 1, even on Legendary difficulty.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Vampiric Corruption values from technologies have been reduced with additional effects added.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved some AI calculations on recruitment, though there is more to come in the future to fully resolve this.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the full list of changes, check out the full Release Notes at the link below:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">HOTFIX 6.3.1 RELEASE NOTES</p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The Total War Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">How to download the Beta branch</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ol><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Open your Steam client and go to your Library.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Right-click on Total War: WARHAMMER III and select 'Properties'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Navigate to the 'Betas' section.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">In the drop-down menu, select <b>'hotfix_6.3.1_beta - Hotfix 6.3.1 Beta'</b>.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Steam will then download the necessary files and begin the patching process to install the Beta.</p></li></ol><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The download and patching process usually doesn't take very long. Once its installed, you can jump in!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaderboards Reset + ORKTOBER Is Coming</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/542243094205038599</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3"><b>ORKTOBER IS COMIN'!</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">"Wotz da big guff, ya git?"  </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Orktober</b> is when we start dropping details about our <i>massive</i> update coming for <b>Warhammer Day</b> in late October<b>🤘</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Stuff like:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Creation Tools</b> for building levels/races, plus online workshop support to share them</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New <b>Vehicle</b> (revealed in Oct)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New <b>Maps</b> for all modes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New <b>WAAAGH! Path</b> with some very cool unlocks</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">+ More</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">This will probably be the game's biggest update yet, and will mark a time where Speed Freeks is the bestest, most greenest, most Orkiest game that ever Orked - and will be the best version so far.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We're really excited to get it into your hands, and not just saying that as a standard PR thing, we <i>really</i> want to see what people do with the Creation Tools. There's already some pretty wild community made Kustom Rally races out there and we've only had a handful of people engage with it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Once you'z get the <i>real</i> tools, it will open up a wealth of possibilities. Like we mentioned last time, this is the first Warhammer game ever to have level building tools like this. MAKE GORK N' MORK PROUD, LADZ!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>LEADERBOARDS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">It's been a long time coming, but the issues with posting scores to the leaderboard have now finally been addressed, and the leaderboards have bee fully reset, so now the records on there will hopefully be more accurate moving forwards. Plus, this gives all players the chance to get their name up high on the boards now ːsteamthumbsupː</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We wanted to do this work a while ago, but it needed to sync up with some backend data stuff that has just been finished (multiplayer games be hard, y'all), so now that it's done we can have lasting leaderboards.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">if you still notice issues though, please mention to us and we'll get onto addressing them</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bound by Duty - Teaser Trailer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/706624027566801004</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" mbm0_aceqqs?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A new Theatre awaits... </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">'Bound by Duty' is Darktide's next update — more details coming soon!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barktide: The Pets of Fatshark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/507339561744990504</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">You’ve met Molly in our Introducing: The Cyber-Mastiff - Dev Blog so we thought it was time we introduced you to the rest of the pets of Fatshark!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Monty</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1aa441e1aa77fd0799bd21b28a59b7a0d0dd6595.jpg"/><b>Name:</b> Monty aka Monster or Egg<br/><b>Age:</b> 3<br/><i>Monty’s Owner is Kitefin!</i><br/><b>Bio:</b> Monty is a little mixture of several breeds (4, and I bet you can’t guess them all!), he is somehow super energetic and also the laziest dog I have ever met. He’d happily spend all day in bed if he could and actually runs away from me when I pick up his lead to take him out, but at the same time goes absolutely nuts for fetch and any kind of ball game. For a little while as well he did doggy agility and was not too bad at it despite his little legs. He refused to really do any of it until the day I bought cheese with me as a reward and then he decided he actually did know how to do it and was just being stubborn. Go figure.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> One of the naming choices for your Cyber-Mastiff is after Monty.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Scooby</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d66e01021c425b1d4fdaef2986b9785e96d0963.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Scooby (Scoobster/Scoobert/Bubek)<br/><b>Age: </b>7<br/><b>Bio: </b>Scooby is a mini Jack Russell that thinks he’s the star of his own cartoon. Anxiety? Absolutely. Goofy snack gremlin? Also yes. Training him to roll over was like teaching a goldfish to ride a bike. But once he got it, he started rolling for funsies and now assumes every spin deserves a treat. Classic Scooby logic. His hobbies include cuddling, snacking, and being everyone’s emotional support goofball.<br/><b>Fun Fact/Bonus talent: </b>Professional mushroom detective. Mushroom pickers have nothing on Scooby.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bobby</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d902981f1ad53bb08ea884fb7f1229d2b1c151e4.png"/><b>Name: </b>Bobby<br/><b>Age: </b>2<br/><b>Bio: </b>Bobby is a British Shorthair with the relatively rare lilac ticked coat variation. His personality is truly special—he’s almost like a little person. He follows me everywhere I go in the apartment, waits outside the bathroom for me, and, best of all, he absolutely loves playing hide-and-seek.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Every evening, I hide behind the bed and wait for him to jump out and ‘scare’ me. When he does, he lets out a proud little meow, his eyes sparkling with excitement, and then he dashes off to hide so I can find him.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Bobby has two favorite positions he loves to sit or lie in. Often, we’ll find him lying on his back with his belly up, which is his unique way of asking for attention. He also likes to sit upright like a little squirrel, with his front paws resting in front of him.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">One of Bobby’s favorite treats is boiled egg yolk—he usually pushes the egg white aside. His favorite time of day is when he gets to lie in the sun on the balcony.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> He has an Instagram account: @mr_bobby_thecat.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Dexter</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ba152b9b486c26c097383012ecebf84183aebc2b.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Dexter aka Fatboy or Lupu<br/><b>Age: </b>7<br/><i>Dexter’s owner is Lev!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>Dexter is a swish tuxedo gentleman. He was rescued at 3 years old from a hoarder’s home having been neglected, and has an amusing habit of licking plastic, likely due to these earlier years. I was actually catfished by Dexter, as his adoption photo was very outdated, and when I went to collect him he was a much chonkier boy!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">A classic cat - he lives for food, comfort and mischief. He’s incredibly affectionate (has no concept of personal space) loving cuddles and snoozing under a duvet. On the odd occasion that he isn’t being lazy, he’s pushing his luck with questionable parkour and zoomies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hands down the most vocal cat I’ve ever encountered. He’ll always remind you when it’s time for food, often 2 hours before for good measure.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> His favourite toy is his shark. Great taste!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Duo Duo</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f66a48fd6971ff8c149984a6db2e08dc7dc61b45.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Duo Duo<br/><b>Age: </b>11<br/><b>Bio: </b>I picked this piggy up from the streets thinking I did him a favor. Now he just sunbathes and screams for shrimps. No dignity remains.<br/><b>Fun Fact: </b>He will only eat poached shrimps from a specific brand.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Mochi &amp; Tai</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4a42413e005862fc5dfdf281cef86c2d75e3b797.png"/><b>Names: </b>Mochi (Left) &amp; Tai (Right)<br/><b>Ages: </b>8 Months (They’re both rescues, Mochi was found when he was around 2 months old, Tai was found about a month later. From what we can tell they’re the same age but it’s hard to tell when you find them on the street.)<br/><i>Mochi &amp; Tai’s Owners are Quickpaw!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>They’re SUPER close! While Tai was extremely scared of Mochi for the first couple of days, by the third day he realized he wasn’t aggressive and just wanted to play and they’ve been best buds ever since, they bonded really well! They’re always playfighting together or cuddling and grooming each other.<br/><b>Fun Facts: </b>Mochi is a climber, while Tai is a jumper.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Reymond</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/33836af815b475085ea6662ae1ba840f9b654ea3.jpg"/><br/><b>Name: </b>Reymond<br/><b>Age: </b>Around 5<br/><i>Reymond’s Owner is Catfish!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>He was a foster cat of mine but fell in love with him and now he is staying! He was found in someone’s garden living off birdseed.<br/><b>Fun Fact: </b>He couldn’t meow when he first got to me, but now has learnt a very squeaky meow to communicate that he would like food.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">These are only a small handful of the amazing pets of Fatshark, we hope you enjoyed meeting them!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We know many of you are eager to see what’s coming next. We’ll be sharing more about the upcoming update soon, so keep an eye out for our next blogs!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
