<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Abelard, introduce the third gargantuan update: 1.3.0.47!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/509566179781641091</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Abelard, introduce the third gargantuan update 1.3 to the players! </b><br/><br/>This major update contains over 1000 changes, focusing on QoL improvements, new content and bugfixes to make all aspects of your experience better!<br/><br/>For your convenience, we’ve combined the smaller ones together into broader categories.<br/><br/>Highlights:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Co-op mode is now available on consoles! Explore the Koronus Expanse together.<br/></li><li> Multiple new cutscenes and a major rework of some old cutscenes;<br/></li><li> Major increase in availability of conviction points;<br/></li><li> A lot of new voiceover, including companion banter, voiced cutscenes, etc. Fixed problems with many voiced lines and pronunciations;<br/></li><li> Many narrative updates on colony events and a rich selection of new rewards for them;<br/></li><li> Multiple encounters have been redesigned and made significantly more challenging based on community feedback;<br/></li><li> Rebalance of equipment and loot tables in Act I-II for better progression;<br/></li><li> 12 new Force swords were added to the game;<br/></li><li> Over 20 other new items were added to loot, rewards and vendors;<br/></li><li> Updated character models for Heinrix, Abelard, Kibellah and Argenta to better match their portraits;<br/></li><li> A lot of updates to French and German localization as well as consistency pass on abilities and tutorials for all localizations;<br/></li><li> You can now rotate the Grand Strategist zones using the R key ("▢" on PS5, and "X" on Xbox);<br/></li><li> Demons summoned by Uralon can now properly attack and use their abilities;<br/></li><li> Many items previously unavailable to Yrliet and Marazhai can now be worn by them;<br/></li><li> And a lot more!</li></ul><br/>Read the full patch notes on our website!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 10:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #55 (1.6.2) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/512943879502168920</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/feae1865d50558a9f35d2a3aabe0182079198c66.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>Hotfix #55 (1.6.2) is currently being rolled out across our platforms and it should be out everywhere in an hour. You can read the notes below!<div class="bb_h1">Audio Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue that caused audio stutter and performance degradation when using virtual surround functionality on Console and PC (e.g. the audio crackling).</li><li>Merged fixes for the audio stutter and stall issues that were first introduced in the “Path of Redemption” update. These were made much worse recently with the issue introduced in 1.6.1. These specific fixes were the ones we tested on the experimental branch on Steam.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed priorities for file reader queues, meaning audio will have higher priority than other file reads.</li><li>[Audio System] Removed code for cancelling a read request since it could stall/deadlock for some users.</li><li>[Audio System] Made “open” and “cancel” async so the audio thread is NOT blocked if open is slow.</li><li>Improved reporting of stalls.</li><li>Proper initialization of BypassIO support for direct storage. We are now checking properly for Win11, NVMe and NTFS in order to support it.</li><li>Deadlock detection for all platforms (Previously only active on PC).</li></ul></ul><div class="bb_h1">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the "Purging Flame" Penance didn't increment correctly. <br/></li><li> New items marker now properly shows in the inventory for emotes. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash which could occur when a cosmetics vendor UI got forcibly closed (e.g. while browsing cosmetics in the Commissary asa mission was about to start). <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Penance icons for the Dark Communion mission used a fallback icon.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Heat UI indicator for the Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade remained displayed also when the weapon was not wielded. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some visual effects were missing for the Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade had an incorrect chain-timing from Block to Special activate/deactivate. Chain-time has now been changed from 0.68 to 0.35.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade played the incorrect Special activate animation when activating the weapon after performing a Push follow-up attack.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where equipping the Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade or Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade in the Inventory applied an offset on other weapon animations when switching between weapons and loadouts.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Havoc Fixes </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Players on the Mourningstar that are stuck with an ongoing Havoc mission can now cancel it from the Havoc terminal, at the expense of a deployment charge.</li><li>If a player cancels an ongoing deployment and no more attempts remain, the player will get demoted One Assignment Rank and get a new assignment.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Cancelling a Havoc deployment will provide a refund of the charge used to start the Assignment if it's done in the first 60 seconds of attempting to start a deployment. Afterwards, a player will not receive a refund for the charge spent.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Players can demote an Assignment Rank to get a new Assignment that is one rank lower.</li><li>Havoc mission participants now appear on the Havoc menu when a player starts a mission session. No participants outside of that list can be in the party for the mission to take place.  </li><li>Updated the “Cry Havoc!” event text to fully match properly across all languages.  </li><li>Fixed remaining overlapping text in multiple languages in the Havoc menu.</li><li>Unobtained Havoc cosmetic items will now show up in the corresponding list in the Cosmetics menu. </li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the Veteran “Lucius Mk IV Death's Head with a Skull Mask (Krieg 143rd).” headgear cosmetic being incorrectly assigned another name.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the cosmetic item rewards from an event would not show up in the Inventory until after logging out and back in again. </li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 10:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 5.0 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4464851965270032697</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello, Space Marines!</div><br/>The 5.0 update is now live, bringing the long-awaited Dark Angels Chapter Pack, the new “Obelisk” Operation, a new Majoris enemy, new customisation options, and various gameplay and balancing tweaks.<br/><br/>Read the full patch notes down below for further details.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NEW FEATURES</div><div class="bb_h2">New Operation: Obelisk</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/727b446bd3b2e17cf3f2bfdf707045d4539821df.jpg"/><br/>In this new Operation, you’ll be sent to Demerium and your mission is to rotate a replica of the obelisk to disrupt the flow of energy protecting the Aurora device. This operation takes place in parallel to the final events of the campaign.<br/><br/>To reach the console control of the obelisk, you’ll have to make it through a tomb plunged into darkness.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Enemy: Tzaangor Enlightened</div><br/><b>A new Majoris enemy can spawn in all Operations featuring the Thousand Sons.</b><br/><br/>Note from our Game Director: “<i>The Tzaangor Enlightened is a disk-flying, melee/ranged-hybrid unit. They are fearsome opponents, especially when met in greater numbers. However, catching them after parry or during a long animation makes them an easy target.<br/><br/>We strongly advise you to use Target Lock to face this enemy!</i>”<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1b3ff8e018017f3a0bb18d09629dd2fc065b9fd0.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Season Pass Content: Dark Angels Chapter Pack</div><br/><b>Added:</b> Dark Angels Successor Chapters cosmetics<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3e1d5d216b97ac72447bef274374296646fddf2e.jpg"/><br/><b>Added:</b> Dark Angels Champion skin (Bulwark)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1d5b0cd4e5ee5ec970e205b820f844dc3cf161a8.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Added:</b> Dark Angels–themed weapon skins for:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Auto Bolt Rifle<br/></li><li> Plasma Pistol<br/></li><li> Power Sword<br/></li><li> Bulwark’s Storm Shield</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/24adf9938e02a0fa566f531759b291c317d83028.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">GAMEPLAY &amp; BALANCING TWEAKS</div><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Melee</b></div>Note from our Game Director: “<i>The melee system has been our main focus recently. The issue that we saw is that, on higher difficulties, the melee combat relied too heavily on the “Parry -&gt; Gun Strike” flow. This also made Fencing Melee Weapons a universal choice for almost all situations, and we want to give players more options. To try and achieve that, we’ve made the following changes.<br/><br/>First, <b>normal Melee Damage has increased across the board</b>, so there will be more options instead of just Parry -&gt; Gun Strike.<br/><br/>Second, <b>we are drastically changing how Blocking Weapons work</b>. In short, by blocking enemy attacks, the player will accumulate up to 3 stacks of Melee Damage buffs. Attacking while having those stacks of buffs will spend them and will result in massive AoE Damage discharge.<br/><br/>With these changes, Fencing Weapons will still be great versus limited numbers of enemies, Balanced Weapons will be good versus big crowds, and Blocking Weapons will become ‘damage dealer’ type weapons.</i>”<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Perfect Block</b></div><b>All Block Weapons have been reworked with a new mechanic: Perfect Block and Adrenaline Surge</b><br/>Perfectly timed blocks grant up to 3 Adrenaline Surge stacks. Adrenaline Surge stacks greatly increase Melee Damage and are consumed after the next melee attack.<br/><br/>Attacking with 3 stacks of Adrenaline Surge deals massive AoE Damage, staggers enemies, and restores 1 Armour Segment.<br/><br/><u><b>Fencing Weapons:</b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Perfect Parry AoE stagger radius slightly reduced.</li></ul><u><b>Balanced Weapons:</b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Perfect Parry AoE stagger radius greatly increased.<br/></li><li> Master-crafted versions: Damage increased by 10%.<br/></li><li> Artificer versions: Damage increased by 10%.<br/></li><li> Relic versions: Damage increased by 10%.</li></ul><b><u>Blocking Weapons:</u></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Master-crafted versions: Damage increased by 20%.<br/></li><li> Artificer versions: Damage increased by 20%.<br/></li><li> Relic versions: Damage increased by 20%.</li></ul><b><u>Unarmed/Firearm Melee:</u></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Stomps can now be chained indefinitely.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">FIREARMS</div>Note from our Game Director: <i>“We are quite happy with recent updates to firearms. Pretty much all firearms are viable on the hardest difficulties now, and our win rate/pick rate data shows drastic improvements.<br/><br/>Still, there are a few weapons that are better than the others, and minor tweaks will be coming with Patch 6.<br/><br/>Further into the future, with <b>Patch 7</b>, we are planning to focus on reworking Weapons Perks. Weapons Perks are underwhelming compared to Class Perks right now, and the issues with some weapons are actually a result of them having a bad Perk tree rather than their basic stats.<br/><br/>The other big outstanding problem that we have is the Grenade Launcher. There are quite a few bugs/misconfigurations that make it the way it is.</i><br/><br/><br/><i><ol><li> Due to a bug, a certain Perk restores its full Ammo when it shouldn’t.<br/></li><li> Due to a misconfiguration on our side, its Artificer and Relic versions deal 4x more damage than the Master-crafted version, which was not intended.<br/></li><li> Due to a bug, Perks that increase Auspex Scan damage stack buffs inconsistently. Normally all damage stacks buffs additively, thus providing consistent and predictable results. This bug results in crazy damage numbers with Auspex Scan Perks depending on the order they were activated. This is why bosses get erased by Grenade Launchers with certain builds.</li></ol>If we approach this directly and fix all 3 bugs, it will make the Grenade Launcher useless and will hurt the entire Tactical class. We will be very careful with how we address this issue. <b>We do want to keep the fun element of destroying entire waves of enemies with the Grenade Launcher</b>. At the same time, no other weapon can match a Grenade Launcher with potentially unlimited Ammo.<br/><br/>Because of these complications, we want to take the time to carefully analyse and make the best decision possible about the Grenade Launcher, so we’re not modifying it in this patch.”</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/faba46643d0f9fad29ee65b876488aeeb8d82fea.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3">Neo-Volkite Pistol</div> Note from our Game Director: “<i>We unified enemy sensitivity to Volkite Damage with Bolter Damage. This means a massive damage buff to certain Majoris and Extremis enemies that were more resistant to Volkite Damage than others</i>.”</div></div></div><b>Volkite Damage sensitivity has been increased from 1 to 1.5 for these enemies: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Devourer Tyranid Warrior<br/></li><li> Barbed Strangler Tyranid Warrior<br/></li><li> Venom Cannon Tyranid Warrior<br/></li><li> Rubric Marine<br/></li><li> Flamer Rubric Marine<br/></li><li> Zoanthrope</li></ul><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8cd35d796f16904c9c943e6d1ca4dbda20a34a90.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3">Bolt Carbine:</div> Max Ammo of all SMG-type Bolt Carbines increased by 1 magazine.</div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">EXTERMINATION BONUS</div>Note from our Game Director: <i>“This change simply increases the amount of XP players are getting in Operations mode if they are zealously exterminating enemy waves. </i><br/><br/><i>This aims to:</i><br/><ol><li> <i>incentivise players to not skip encounters, without punishing those who want to skip, and</i><br/></li><li> <i>makes the game less grindy in preparation for new features coming down the line (e.g., Prestige Ranks).”</i></li></ol><b>Added a new feature that increases the amount of XP players gain based on % of enemies killed during an Operation:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rank A: killing more than 85% spawned enemies grants +120% XP pre-patch value.<br/></li><li> Rank B: killing more than 60% spawned enemies grants +110% XP pre-patch value.<br/></li><li> Rank C: killing less than 60% spawned enemies grants +100% XP pre-patch value.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5ab2bf9b4145c96c74d52c57f737d43d3afe4872.jpg"/><br/>*The rank is common to the party, everyone gets the same.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">GAMEPLAY QOL</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dodge invulnerability logic is now client sided, meaning that Dodges will be responsive and more accurate with higher ping.<br/></li><li> Players are now invulnerable to new instances of damage while in Knockback animation.<br/></li><li> Added 10 frames of invulnerability at the start of Jump Pack launch animation (Campaign and Operations only).<br/></li><li> Dodge and Parry sound notification clarity has been greatly improved.<br/></li><li> Heavy’s Barrier can be activated in more player states (e.g., during stagger animation).<br/></li><li> Player controls are slightly more responsive after using Vanguard’s Grapnel Launcher.<br/></li><li> Added spawn protection in PvP. <br/></li><li> Added Neo-Volkite Pistol in PvP.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">AI</div><u><b>Zoanthrope: </b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shielded Zoanthrope will now attack much less frequently.</li></ul><u><b>Enemy Spawn Director:</b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You will no longer fight Extremis-level enemies on your first encounter right after the start of a Mission.<br/></li><li> Lots of minor animation fixes for various enemies.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">CUSTOMISATION</div><br/><b>Added:</b> Lenses colour customisation.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d9630bdb7172f9efbf708bc1d3f9751275018435.gif"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed shading of Balthasar Gold and Ushabti Bone colours.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5ed758daa89efc4e9ba3fd5a2ea37787d50b0b70.jpg"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of small bugs with certain armour pieces not applying colours correctly.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">OPERATIONS</div><div class="bb_h3">Fall of Atreus:</div>Made adjustments to scripting to make this level shorter and more in line with the duration of other levels:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The second sequence with the Dreadnought (Repel the Assault) is randomised now and may not happen.<br/></li><li> The fusion battery needs to be charged only once in the final sequence.</li></ul>Large amounts of small fixes in level geometry collision and Terminus enemies getting stuck in some areas.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">PERKS</div>Note from our Game Director: “<i>In this patch, we are only fixing bugs with existing Perks, but trust me, we are seeing the issues with them. A lot of the Class Perks are not as good as we wanted them to be, and some Perk tree choices are really more efficient than others. With Patch 6, we are planning to massively rework a bunch of lacking Perks to make more builds viable.”</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">GENERAL FIXES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Getting kicked out of a session will still grant kicked player XP rewards based on checkpoint completion.<br/></li><li> Exiting the Turret Charging Wheel in the “Termination” Operation is now quicker.<br/></li><li> Improved a few enemies counting for Purge Them All Achievement.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Combat Knife charged attacks would occasionally Heavy Hit every time without charging.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Heavy’s Primary Weapon was not shooting after joining in progress.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where party leader could get stuck on a loading screen in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed Hierophant’s damage sensitivity to certain weapons (it can still be damaged by normal weapons, but the damage is reduced).<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Heldrake was not taking any damage from shots in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Heldrake could be knocked off its pedestal by shots from an under-barrel Grenade Launcher.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Imurah would not take any damage from shots in the final mission in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare bug where players were shown a long black screen instead of death screen in PvP.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where players could not see each other's customisation in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Neo-Volkite Pistol would deal damage further than its actual visual FX.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where enemies were able to pierce Block stance with double attack.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with Bulwark’s Armour of Contempt Perk not triggering correctly and dealing friendly fire.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Neo-Volkite Pistol would sometimes trigger a chain of explosions and cause performance issues.<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare bug with Vanguard’s Zone of Impact Perk not triggering correctly.<br/></li><li> Fixed Perks that grant player immunity to Heavy Hits and Knockback during charging melee attacks not working with charged attacks unlocked via Weapons Perks.<br/></li><li> Combat Knife charged attack buffs from other Perks (e.g., Sniper's Shadow Stab) are now correctly applied on both damage instances.<br/></li><li> Large number of minor fixes in Perks, how they stack, and how they trigger in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Minor UI fixes and improvements.<br/></li><li> Localisation fixes.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">TECH</div><br/><b>Added</b>: FSR 3 / DLSS 3: Support of "Frame Generation" component for DLSS and FSR. For more details about FSR and DLSS, check our FAQ.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.<br/></li><li> General connectivity improvements.<br/></li><li> Slightly improved performance.<br/></li><li> Slightly improved texture streaming speed.<br/></li><li> Improved Anti-Cheat.</li></ul><br/><b>Mod Support</b><br/><br/>Please note that starting from 5.0 update, mods will no longer be supported in public lobbies. You can find the complete explanation here. <br/><br/><br/>“<i>That’s it for the 5.0 update! We hope you’ll like the new Operation and you’ll have fun customising your Marines with the new items available! <br/><br/>Let us know your thoughts on the new gameplay tweaks we made, especially on the revamped melee mechanics. As we previously said, your feedback is invaluable to us as it helps us pinpoint what you really want and would like to see in the future.<br/><br/>Enjoy this update, and have happy winter holidays! <br/><br/>The Emperor protects.</i>”<br/><br/><b>—Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director</b><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 10:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultima Founding DLC: join us for Slitherine Next</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/521951078763201278</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Get ready to be the first to discover the new DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Gladius, Ultima Founding. <br/><br/>Join us for Slitherine Next event <b>December 10th at 6:00 PM CET</b>.<br/><br/>Make sure to save the date:<br/>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bNMPY51noiw?si=FTa3mq0ivM2Uso6K<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction - Meet Gorbad Ironclaw</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4476109467940814900</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/92d39fdf82c96b48b8db81f6cf959c1b5884b2ca.png"/><br/><br/>​Greetings, Total War community!<br/><br/>This week da boyz are back in town as we discuss warrin’, Warbosses and WAAAGHS! - please welcome Omens of Destruction’s final Legendary Lord, Gorbad Ironclaw. Packing a terrifying mix of strength and intelligence (for an orc), he’s an Emperor slaying Warboss who burned Solland to the ground and is back to show the rest of the WARHAMMER world how to get ‘invasions done propa’.<br/><br/>As always, if you happen to have missed our previous blogs about Skulltaker, Golgfag or Arbaal, then just click on their respective names to check them out now!<br/><br/>We'll be back tomorrow with Gorbad's gameplay showcase which premieres at 3PM GMT, so remember to check back then to feast yer eyez on 'iz video!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HMrBhXDjamE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Until then, let's dive in to Gorbad's introduction...<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 GORBAD IRONCLAW 👈</div><br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
