<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.2.0.28 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999222388333</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! A hotfix 1.2.0.28 is live! <br/><br/>In this hotfix we're getting rid of multiple mysterious 'hidden' lines and character names across the game and adding missing localization strings to multiple languages. <br/><br/>We really appreciate the bugreports you send us, and already busy investigating the problems you reported. Thank you, and keep it coming!<br/><br/>We also kindly remind you to update your mods, as they are often the reason of the issues you may encounter.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 22:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Itemization Rework - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097450538498</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7db9445966d6e8369efb770d6fff65df600abf3a.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello again Devoted Rejects, </div><br/>It’s time to talk more about itemization (a.k.a. crafting) and what players can expect. <br/><br/>We’ve been reading your comments, your posts, your threads and your topics. <br/><br/>One of the challenges for tackling Itemization was to propose a new experience to the players which felt authentic and natural within the actual live system. We did not want to rush this, as it was important to consider all the progress and time put in by current players of the game, too. <br/><br/>Our goal is to improve player agency. We are putting the focus on giving players a clear path to get the weapons and gameplay they want. <br/><br/>Part of this agency will be achieved by removing the locks on Blessings and Perks.<br/><br/>The rest of the player agency will be achieved through the introduction of two new major systems for itemization: Mastery and Expertise <b>(final names pending)</b>. These systems will make the players journey in the game more rewarding and customizable. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mastery</div><br/>This is the core progression system that is tied to the weapon type / weapon family itself. As players use a specific weapon, they’ll gain more experience. This unlocks new blessings, perks, marks and a special weapon cosmetic along the way via the reward tracks. As players progress, the potential quality and stats of the weapon also increases. <br/><br/>This system will merge all weapon types/families, meaning players will be able to freely switch between different marks of the same weapon type. For example, once you own an Infantry Lasgun, you have the potential to unlock all the possible marks for this weapon and switch from one mark to another. <br/><br/>When viewing any weapon, it will show the weapon’s maximum potential stats. These stats will be randomly determined. It’s up to the players to decide if the weapon profile is interesting enough for them to commit and increase the stats until reaching this potential (which are then applied to the weapon through the Expertise system). <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/035926fb276cdb5f826e116b577433213a65f049.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8122a0ae3344ed25b8256ebe257508da8de35e14.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Expertise</div><br/>While the Mastery system is where a player unlocks the potential for a weapon, the Expertise system is where the players apply those changes via crafting. This is when the players create an actual relationship with the weapon. Players will be able to configure the weapon, change the Blessings or Perks, and increase the stats. Players will no longer be locked after making two changes on Perks or Blessings.<br/><br/>This is also when the player uses resources to make these changes happen. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f1a83420efa5044482005748d892db0e0c161430.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What About Resources?</div>While we were planning this itemization rework, there were a lot of discussions around this topic. Creating an entirely new resource is a bit easier for balancing, but we don’t want to start a new grind for players. We wanted to have a system which respects players’ time. As such, we decided to keep plasteel and diamantine steel as the resources for changing weapons, but we worked on balancing. <br/><br/>We wanted to give a new life to diamantine. As diamantine is a resource introduced at a higher level of game play, it is also the required resource for achieving higher levels of Expertise on a weapon. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What Happens to My Existing Inventory?</div>When designing itemization, we wanted to commit to ensuring fairness for all players, new and old. As such, we’re implementing a migration system to convert players' current weapons and blessings into the new system. <br/><br/>Here’s how it works: The blessing library of the weapon family will be converted into mastery progression. This means players will start the new systems with a head start in mastery, giving them the chance to unlock previously owned blessings (as well as the chance to unlock some blessings players never had before the update).<br/><br/>Our aim is to preserve players hard-earned progress and make this shift as smooth as possible.<br/><br/><b>What about Curios?</b> Curios will have their locks removed but they will remain unaffected beyond this change.<br/><br/>We are continuing to optimize this system in the coming weeks and we look forward to reading your feedback on the process outlined. We’ll collect any questions below so that we can release further communications on the topic as we make progress.<br/><br/>Thank you!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Cult Introduction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4185613970227358983</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>In “Void Shadows” you will not only meet new enemies, but also new allies. One of them is a secretive Death Cult that worships the Emperor in his most merciless form, the god of death. Sounds intriguing? Then take a look!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_pwCNWrK0co?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4265553497823189748</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
​Hey Folks, <br/><br/>As revealed only a few short weeks ago, our next DLC for Total War: WARHAMMER III brings Khorne, Ogre Kingdoms, and Orcs &amp; Goblins to the centre stage.  <br/><br/>Today we’re thrilled to be sharing more insight into what you can expect when this content releases at the end of 2024, the Legendary Lords that are set to lead each faction (alongside some sneak peeks at a couple of key units), and how we’re using this time between now and the launch of this DLC to cast our eyes back onto the core game experience and to ask ourselves, and you, what changes and experiences we can bring to that.<br/><br/>Watch the full conversation with Senior Community Manager Steve Coleman, Senior Game Director Rich Aldridge, alongside DLC Lead designer Sean Macdonald, and Associate Game Director Victor Dosev right here 👇 👀 <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fix3FvsmplA?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>As talked about by Rich in this Development Update, our next DLC takes place entirely within Immortal Empires, and won’t feature a new campaign for The Realm of Chaos. We’ll continue to support campaigns in The Realm of Chaos regardless in our updates and hotfixes, ensuring that the experience is always fun, balanced, and available to old and new players alike, but we wanted to make sure everyone understood our direction for the game moving forward.<br/><br/>It’s also been a while since we talked to you so directly in this style of content, so please do share your thoughts and feedback on the format of videos like this too as we’d love to hear from you, and love to keep showing up on your screens just like this in the future.<br/><br/>We’ll return in the late summer with another development update from the teams, letting you know how we’re getting on with our work and to lift the curtain some more on the work we have in progress.  <br/><br/>Meanwhile, we’ve just launched Update 5.1 for all players, bringing best boi Karanak to the roster alongside a tonne of fixes, balance passes, and improvements to the game. In the coming weeks, we’re looking to release a Hotfix to help tidy up a few latent issues we’ve spotted since the Update went live, and we’ll keep you updated on future our releases as we roll out each one. <br/><br/>We’re otherwise especially keen to hear how you’re feeling about today’s news, so please do join us over on the Official Total War Discord, and the Total War Forums to share your feedback, and pose all-new questions for us to look at answering in the future.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefields, <br/>Freeman // Head of Community  <br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #41 (1.4.1)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4270057097449329352</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b7392c313fea97398ea2feda9bdf4be9a21a30ee.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Devoted Rejects,</div><br/>Hotfix #41 (1.4.1) is now live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a server crash which could happen when updating player stats if any stat reached a very high value.<br/></li><li> Fixed a server crash which could happen if an Ogryn with the “Feel No Pain” talent equipped was hit by a projectile which was about to be destroyed.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Branx Pickaxe attack startup animations would be incorrect if starting an attack immediately after interrupting a Special attack by sprinting.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Antax Mk V Combat Axe was playable but showed incorrect stats.<br/></li><li> Fixed the following in the new mission Clandestium Gloriana:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the backdrop would be incorrect when setting the volumetric quality settings to Low in the new mission.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players could get stuck in the doors of the horizontal elevator as they were closing.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players could walk behind the horizontal elevator gantry and fall through the map.</li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue related to triggering VO which caused banter to happen less frequently than intended.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where subtitles in the Mourningstar could overlap during the Path of Trust cinematics.<br/></li><li> Fixed inconsistencies for spelling for Ogryns Pickaxes.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description of the “Torment” Pickaxe blessing would appear in undefined text in languages other than English.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the wrong inspect animations played for Ogryn Pickaxe in third person.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the second line of Zola’s intro for The Orthus Offensive special assignment was not playing.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Zola’s VO lines are over the radio in The Orthus Offensive special assignment menu.<br/></li><li> Added a smoother transition screen when loading into a video or cutscene, instead of just showing the operative.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 12:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
