<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Sale is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/509592630758212254</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Autumn Sale has begun!<br/><br/>Lord Captain, it's a great time to begin your epic journey through the grim darkness of the Koronus Expanse! Claim your Warrant of Trade, embark on your mighty space vessel and expand your influence and wealth as you seek to uncover the legacy of the von Valancius dynasty.<br/><br/><b>You may consider the following options:</b><br/><br/>1. Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration:<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>2. Gain access to two major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis, and expand your campaign with two new companions, exciting new storylines and new interesting mechanics, receiving over 30 hours of content at an additional discount:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/>3. For the most ambitious Rogue Traders! Get the base game, Season Pass 1, Digital Artbook, Digital OST, Wallpaper Pack and a selection of in-game items for the ultimate experience:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/36542/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Edition/<br/>4. The story does not end with the first two DLCs! Get Season Pass 2 to instantly gain access to new character customization options, and a future access to two more upcoming expansions, both of which offer 15 hours of gameplay: In DLC III - The Infinite Museion, you will delve into a secret vault curated by Trazyn the Infinite himself, and in DLC IV - Processional of the Damned, you will venture into the Processional — a massive, otherworldly graveyard of ships lost to the void:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3650060/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>These are just some examples of the available content for the game - check out its page to find out about more options!<br/><br/>Your crew awaits you, Lord Captain!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/507340830949769704</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1"><b>Greetings Space Marines,</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Let's rewind a little on what's happened this month and let's see what's coming!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>FIRST ANNIVERSARY 🎂</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>September marks the first anniversary of Space Marine 2! 🎉🎈</b> We wanted to thank you all for the continued support and the enthusiasm you’ve shown for each update. Your devotion and passion has been a blessing and a source of motivation to us. We value your feedback and enjoy working in collaboration with you like we did through this first year.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Both Saber and Focus are incredibly fond of this project and we’ll continue to cherish it. We cannot wait to see how this second year rolls out.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Again, <b>thank you</b> so much for siding with us. 💙</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c1005e4d0b52a6bd57c7e1e77511eaa9b51991c6.jpg"/><b></b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>You will see that this month our Game Director has left a few personal notes in the Community Update, giving away hints on the development of the game</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>LATEST NEWS 🗞️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This month we released the 10.0 - Anniversary Update, including new free and DLC content such as 2 new games modes: Helbrute Onslaught and Stratagems, new weapons like the PyreCannon, the Power Axe and the Hero Weapon Variants, the Chaos Spawn and the Mutalith Vortex Beast, along with improvements and balancing on both PvP and PvE.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>​<b>PATCH 10 STABILITY</b></i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Patch 10 was our biggest update for the game and unfortunately a lot of minor, yet super game breaking issues or balancing misconfigurations got in it. I would like to apologize for the inconvenience caused. Normally, we would catch the issues during the PTS phase, but we didn’t do PTS for Patch 10 because we simply didn’t have time for it, plus we didn’t want to spoil the surprise. </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>PTS will return for Patch 11 and all subsequent patches (unless we do another huge anniversary patch 😊).</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dmitriy Grigorenko - Game Director</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Regarding the issues with Battlefield Conditions that have occurred since the implementation of Stratagems (i.e: “Equipment Malfunction” blocking the progression on Exfiltration), we were made aware of that and are currently working on it to prevent this scenario from happening again in the future. Sorry for the inconvenience.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i><b>​STRATAGEMS</b></i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Our objective with Stratagems was to add the hardest content in the game and we are not planning to make Weekly Hard Stratagems easier. However, we are going to continue to address some of the issues with Daily Stratagems in Patch 11. </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>First of all, Daily Stratagems are random, this is why some of the Battlefield Conditions combinations do not make any sense or are too punishing or restrictive for no reason. The truth is that there are not enough Battlefield Conditions right now. With Patch 11 we are going to add a second batch of Battlefield Conditions (~50 of them). Having more Battlefield Conditions will allow us to remove some that don’t work on their own from the Daily rotation pool.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Weekly Stratagems are completely different. Each Weekly Stratagem has a pre-made Battlefield Condition combination + level attached to it. All 52 Weekly Stratagems are hand crafted and are designed to be either hard or fun depending on the week. The key here is to make sure that it's different every week and, ideally, players have to alter their play style.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We are working on allowing players to toggle Battlefield Conditions manually in Private Lobbies so players can come up with their own fun combinations. Siege mode will eventually see Battlefield Conditions integrated into it for increased replayability.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dmitriy Grigorenko - Game Director</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In this Community Update we’ll tackle Patch 11.0 with a sneak peek, a new limited edition for the game, the upcoming demo and the Discord Quest.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>UPDATE 10.2 ⚙️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In September we rolled out 2 hotfixes, the latest is 10.2. It fixes critical issues such as the Assault’s Ascension perk dealing friendly-fire damage, Stratagems having more Battlefield Conditions than listed and more. Also, the Sniper’s Camo Cloak activation cost changed. If you want to read the changelog, you may find it here.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>UPDATE 11 TEASING 👀</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The upcoming Update 11 will be released aound late-November and will bring 2 new cosmetic DLCs! As announced in our roadmap, the next Champion Pack will be the Blood Angels’ and it will be associated with the Tactical class. Yes, Tactical. Now, before all Blood Angels come to our office searching for Horus, please note that the Champion Pack will also come with its own unique Jump Pack, and its individual parts can be used separately like with other champions. We will reveal its design in the October Community Update. 🩸 </p><p class="bb_paragraph">As for the Salamanders Cosmetic Pack, it will include the heraldry of various Salamanders Successor Chapters, as well as different armour parts. 🦎</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Regarding gameplay additions, the next PvE Operation will be an off-planet mission introducing a new boss fight. 🦇 Here’s a preview of the inside and the outside of the area:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/12e93112ff98c12edc18ff1b109974767c41967a.png"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c2ecd6dc6a5e71e03065ffab51d1f2e1d2611360.png"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve also seen that you’re having many questions regarding the Heroic Weapons. We will keep adding new Heroic Weapon with the major updates, starting with Update 11. We can’t show you them yet, but we can already tell you that the Thunder Hammer will be among these weapons.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Lastly on the Update 11 topic, a long-awaited feature will be added: <b>Bots Customisation!</b> ✨ When launching a PvE Operation with bots, they will automatically equip one of your loadouts. We will detail this new feature later on, so bear with us.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Oh and here’s more news to rejoice to: <b>there will be a Public Test Server for Patch 11.0!</b> Stay tuned 😉</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>HEROIC ITEMS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We are going to continue adding more and more Heroic items to the game, both Armour and Weapons. With weapons, the objective is to have at least 2 Heroic weapons per archetype. Overall Heroic weapons are meant to allow different playstyles, they are meant to be a sidegrade for existing relic weapons. Powerful only when played in a specific way.<br/><br/>Also, there will be more ways to obtain Accolades, but only via playing the game.<br/><br/>Dmitriy Grigorenko - Game Director</i></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>SIEGE MODE</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Siege mode will get a lot of additions to its sandbox gameplay and there are going to be reasons to come back to it. We are not done with it.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i> </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dmitriy Grigorenko - Game Director</i></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>CUSTOMISATION</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Over the course of the year, we are going to continue expanding customization options, not only with the new parts but with new options as well. Without spoiling the surprise, here are some hints about what we are going to implement:</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>1) Something we should have done long time ago</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>2) Something we said we are going to do, but nobody noticed</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>3) Something we said we are never going to do</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dmitriy Grigorenko - Game Director</i></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>NEW LIMITED EDITION ✨</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A fresh, brand-new limited edition is here!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Ultima Limited Edition contains the Base Game, an exclusive SteelBook®, Season Pass 1 and Season Pass 2 and the Macragge’s Chosen DLC. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d0fffb5fac4e07d16f3c05f0b7522738cebdf866.jpg"/><i>Available in physical version at participating retailers.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i></i></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>OCTOBER COMMUNITY EVENT</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">“The Vortex Scouring”: from October 2 to 16, team up with your fellow Space Marines to collectively bring down 500,000 Vortex Beasts. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you successfully complete your mission, you'll get the <b>Infiltrator Helmet for the Vanguard and Sniper classes</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>​</i><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4e2eff16fa5f49b3ce61d5e074f31fee7a76b1af.jpg"/><i>Please note that PROS is required to claim the item.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>TELL YOUR MATES TO PLAY THE DEMO! 🎮</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">From October 16 to October 20, a demo for players who haven't played <i>Space Marine 2</i> yet and are curious will be available on <b>Steam and consoles!</b> 🎉</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This demo will give you a first look at the <b>Campaign: Rain of Terror and Skyfire, PVP modes</b> (except Helbrute Onslaught) will be playable and <b>three Operations will be available: Inferno, Decapitation and Vox Liberatis.</b> All classes will be playable, and all weapons available. Rest assured, if the demo convinces you and you decide to purchase the game: your progression will be carried to the full game!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Dates of availability of the demo vary depending on the platform. Here’s the schedule (The demo starts and ends at 9AM UTC):</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">STEAM : October 16 to 23.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>DISCORD QUEST</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you want to kill two birds with one stone, complete the <i>Space Marine 2</i> Discord Quest by playing the game on Steam! For 15 minutes of playtime, you get to unlock the <b>Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle</b>. Discord will provide you with a code, to redeem your reward in the full game.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Non-owners: play the demo for 15 minutes to earn the reward.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Owners: play the full game for 15 minutes to earn the reward.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This event starts on October 16</b>, at around 3PM UTC and ends on October 23rd at 9AM UTC.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/12a1089430f031130cabeb9704442de2b0bfe52f.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH!</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your support. Join the community on our official Discord Server, where 80K chit-chat everything <i>Space Marine 2,</i> share their thoughts on the game and find PvP or PvE matches every day. We’re eager to hear from you.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Emperor Protects ⭐ </p><p class="bb_paragraph">- Saber and Focus</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #77 - 1.9.1 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499459531596628464</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ad86cc89f0b0243274d8a3fb5a930166c04cba55.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #77 (1.9.1) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated text of Veteran Penance “Fire Down Range” to more accurately reflect the criteria needing to be fulfilled.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where mission images would disappear when swapping between difficulties in the Campaign Playlist.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where mission tiles in the Mission Terminal could incorrectly display the “Event” tag while not possessing any event modifier.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a rare crash that could occur when opening the Mission Terminal.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur in the Meat Grinder when switching loadouts while having ability cooldown reducing effects active.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur when opening the Penances screen while having completed tracked penances.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur when looking at another player's Inventory while they disconnected from the game.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur when opening the Inventory or switching between loadouts while having specific loadout items equipped.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the shooting and explosion sound effects for the Boltgun Mk III and Bolt Pistol Mk VI would play incorrectly for other players.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the 3D model appearance for the Bolt Pistol Mk VI could be inconsistent after equipping Commissary weapon skins.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue which could lead to client and server crashes during missions related to the “Smuggled Munitions” event.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Event: Smuggled Munitions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499458897750264665</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Live Event: Smuggled Munitions</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" jbyofafcvzm?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Forces of the Traitorous 6th have raided local plasma weapon caches. Root out these dangerous squads and dispatch them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, kill Captains in missions with the Outgunned condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event is <b>LIVE NOW, until October 13.</b> The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.</b> Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic portrait frame.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e1a026b8057506d394615ddb250474b5793ea150.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cd25106c4011eb0dde3a61cd6314f03d6d974545.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.3.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/519725096071334645</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/64ff70b24e924c153e9f87802775353c8b32701f.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey there folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 6.3.1 is now out of Beta and live for all players. This will be our final planned game update prior to the release of Total War: WARHAMMER III: Tides of Torment and the release of Game Update 7.0.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve focused this Hotfix on bringing further improvements to many of the changes brought with Patch 6.3 and offering some refined balance changes for both Lizardmen and Tomb Kings. This Hotfix also helps to address an unintended AI behavior that was causing AI controlled factions to poorly budget their resource, and result in instances of low stack armies on your campaign maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There’s a host of additional changes, fixes and improvements detailed below, so hit the button down below for the full list of changes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Highlights</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Two new frontend toggles for Unusual Locations as well as balance changes and bug fixes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lizardmen factions that have mechanics to spawn in Blessed units now gain double the Spawning Sequence from performing actions compared to the 6.3 release.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">All Lizardmen factions have a method of increasing the capacity of Blessed Spawning units.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tomb King factions can now begin researching technologies from Turn 1, even on Legendary difficulty.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Vampiric Corruption values from technologies have been reduced with additional effects added.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved some AI calculations on recruitment, though there is more to come in the future to fully resolve this.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For the full list of changes, check out the full Release Notes at the link below:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">HOTFIX 6.3.1 RELEASE NOTES</p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The Total War Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
