<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing "Rolling Steel" - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4656248375959823389</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ce2a39a98fd7783c3294f5ffe3fecee04da0ad13.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello, Everyone!</div><br/>We heard you wanted some trains… It’s time to unveil the newest mission coming to our Unlocked &amp; Loaded update this month: Rolling Steel. For this dev blog, we interviewed a Level Designer and Level Artist from our team who were in charge of bringing the vision to life: Jacopo and Roberto.<br/><br/>Our goal of this blog is to tell you about the new mission and how it formed, etc. without spoiling all the fun of playing it the first time for yourselves. We’ll have to leave some things out, because we want players to still be surprised when they load into the mission for the first time. <br/><br/>Let’s get rolling. 🚂 (I’m a comical genius -Straw)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Where Did the Idea for This Mission Start?</div><br/>The idea for “Rolling Steel” began about a year and a half ago, following the release of Ascension Riser 31. In that mission, we experimented with creating a more dynamic end event where players fight atop an ascending platform in a massive vertical shaft. After completing that challenge, we wanted to create something with even more movement. A mission to explore more visually dynamic and immersive events. <br/><br/>Our devs continued working on this with the latest mission, Clandestium Gloriana, where players are in the lateral elevator.<br/><br/>A key moment that influenced this concept was a scene from the “Rejects Will Rise” trailer, where a train crashes and explodes into a station. This powerful visual helped solidify the narrative and set the pace for the objectives in the mission. <br/><br/>It was intimidating to start. While we had worked on similar movements with Ascension Riser 31, we knew this would require a tech investment to create the movement we wanted players to feel. We didn’t want the background to be a constant loop of the same elements.  At first, the endeavour was put on hold. However, we saw the community's interest in a mission involving a train. This reignited our enthusiasm for the idea and it led us to resume development.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5c624624ee53490adfd468e7dd75346ef863d1c0.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What Will Players Be Doing in Rolling Steel?</div>In Rolling Steel, players are thrust into a high-stakes scenario where they must stop a moving train hijacked by cultists who have repurposed it with tox bombs onboard to spread the Nurgle plague. The mission immediately begins with high-octane adrenaline as players are dropped directly onto the speeding train. From the beginning, players are immersed in the action. <br/><br/>The primary objective is to prevent the train from crashing into its destination and releasing tox gas. To do this, the players must work their way through a series of train cars. Each car presents unique challenges and escalating threats. Cultists will relentlessly defend the train, and the players will need to stick together and push forward quickly.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What are the New Objective Types?</div>Yes, we said quickly. One of the most significant additions to this mission is the timer as an overarching objective. We wanted to introduce this mechanic to create a stronger sense of tension and urgency throughout the mission.<br/><br/>The timer in "Rolling Steel" is intended to force players to move very quickly, adding a layer of pressure that should elevate the intensity of the gameplay. Our goal was to offer a new harder challenge that requires players to work more closely together to succeed. It is not like the classic missions where there is a mid-event and an end-event. Rather, it’s one full event from beginning to end. <br/><br/>We wanted to see what happens when you break the rules, or at least suspend them.<br/><br/>Additionally, we're experimenting with a potential new auspex minigame that also plays a part in the importance of teamwork and communication in the mission. (We’ll leave this for you to learn more about through playing.)<br/><br/>Additionally, Rolling Steel is part of our effort to experiment with a different mission format, which we call Operations. It is a shorter mission than we’ve created historically. By introducing shorter, more cinematic experiences, we hope to offer a fresh alternative to the normal types of missions in Darktide. Something else to sink your teeth into when you have the urge to slay heretics, but you’re more limited on time.<br/><br/>As this mission is somewhat of a test, we’re eager to hear feedback from our community. Your input will be invaluable in determining how we evolve these new types of missions in the future. (Thank you ahead of time!)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/bfd4ff8e3e88099c4d4033c2fbd8faf640f9945e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Any Learnings From Past Missions?</div>Absolutely, we’ve learned a great deal from designing past levels, but with "Rolling Steel," we also wanted to challenge ourselves and try new things.<br/><br/>One of the most significant changes is the level topology. Unlike our previous missions, which often feature wider environments, "Rolling Steel" has a highly linear layout, which naturally funnels players into more close-quarters combat scenarios. This shift strongly affected how we design encounters and balance the overall experience, especially considering the added pressure of a time constraint and how all these elements impact our combat director.<br/><br/>In many ways, "Rolling Steel" is informed by our past experiences, but it also represents a step towards new possibilities and gauge how these innovations resonate with our players.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Inspiration for the Environments</div>As mentioned, the Rejects Will Rise trailer was one of the inspirations. This Nurgle train is based on an industrial cargo train which creates more room for slaying. Then a heavy coating of 40k grimdark, as always! (That’s the best part). The art team did a tremendous job providing a variety of assets for us to include throughout the mission, and we look forward to players trying it out.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Music</div>When we told Jesper about the new type of mission and the timer, he was really excited. He said he immediately had some ideas in his head of what he could create for players to add to the rising tension. He delivered a certified banger, as always. It is a blend between a standard and a high intensity track, so when the heat ramps up, players will definitely feel it. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Future Missions</div>We are expecting players to ask if we’ll have more missions on a train. The answer is…we’ll see! 😉 Let us know what you’re feeling. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>We can’t wait for players to start running this mission and trying out the new objective. Let us know how it feels and we’ll be reading the feedback! <br/><br/>Until next time. May the Emperor protect!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEGA Publisher Sale is now on!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4601078645996410357</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3ede2b38abd5c4a5f517779019d23c463e5f3d3a.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks!<br/><br/>The SEGA Publisher Sale is now live on Steam! Grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles from now until 26th September!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">TAKE ME TO THE DEALS!</div><br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's the second episode of Titus Talks: What is a Space Marine?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4699032572421700692</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!!</div><br/>The grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000 can be daunting to dive into! This is why we're are thrilled to introduce the second episode of the “Titus Talks” a 3-part video series presented by Lieutenant Titus himself, Clive Standen, and dedicated to welcoming newcomers to the rich expanse that is the 41st millennium. ✨<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Watch Episode 2: What is a Space Marine?</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t25T47O01lc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">This episode focuses on introducing players to the Space Marines themselves.</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Who are they? <br/></li><li> How were they originally created? <br/></li><li> What is their story? </li></ul>Presented by Clive Standen, who voices Lieutenant Titus in the game, today’s video lecture serves as an introduction to a multi-part series. <br/><br/>An upcoming part three will come later. It will discuss what it all means in the grand setting of the game itself.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/95c6c33219c5664bd4a2cc2f61e9ba8fb83754bb.png"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available now on PC. Get the Gold or Ultra Editions to secure your Season Pass!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 16 - Megatrakk Scrapjet 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/6537626672201296146</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e509e3f2a1db368e15d959f76cfd1801500be1d9.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/26237265df439826df90ad4a6c57f37bb8252f96.png"/><br/><br/>The Megatrakk Scrapjet is an Ork vehicle that resembles a crashed aircraft that’s been hastily converted into a land vehicle.  It is bristling with weapons and built for high-speed, destructive assaults.<br/><br/>A very fast and versatile vehicle, where only the skies are the limit of your game-play possibilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7ba2bfcef2a4cf5006562ce4a44848f55bda9e6b.gif"/><br/><br/>In Speed Freeks, the Megatrakk Scrapjet is at its best when utilizing its speed to be where your team needs you to be. Having an ability which increases your speed helps you stay at high speeds. <br/>You are the hunter/seeker!<br/><br/>Keep your target in front of you and use your front mounted shootas and homing rokkits to grind them down. Then, finish them off with one well aimed Rokkit Kannon shot.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/ad185bcd4da91a001cb2f844d8422e944bec8e1e.png"/><br/><b>Shootas and Missiles -</b> Dakka spits from the front and rear of the vehicle depending on where you’re aiming. Missiles track the enemy you’re aiming at.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/286a26c1cdc69232478abea90a89109edc882f96.png"/><br/><b>Rokkit Kannon - </b> Fire a large Rokkit that deals high damage. Use it to finish off foes and its massive recoil to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5d01fb1502925d79eb9ee6e6826f570a73c26971.png"/><br/><b>Nose Drill -</b> Spin up the drill and charge! Ram straight through enemies in your path.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/10f81d44f5ff8313ee330da0d2389ace04f7e7fa.png"/><br/><b>Dash -</b> The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming will determine where the vehicle will go.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2396d4899d5423a188fb0ef8defe5bc3228147c3.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Your highest priority as the Scrapjet is figuring out what your team needs from you. Do they need an extra bomb carrier? Or someone to chase down that pesky Deffkilla Wartrike who’s been giving your Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy trouble. With the drill, you have an extra ability to keep the momentum that you’ve gained from dashing. To become a speed demon with the Megatrakk Scrapjet, use the dash to accelerate up to high speeds or change directions, then use some of your boost, so that you don’t waste momentum, followed by using your drill. Alternate between Dashing, Boosting and using the drill.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/176e82cb2bb7c58632db9e6dac371af80302e87b.gif"/><br/><br/>The Rokkit Kannon has a strong knockback effect on your vehicle. If you want to take your skill to the next level practice spinning your car in the air and shooting the Rokkit Kannon downwards/backwards to give yourself a boost and fly further.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-ups</div><b>Shokkjump Dragsta –</b> When playing Kill Konvoy, work together with a Shokkjump Dragsta to deliver the bomb. Together, you can become an unstoppable force as you use your sheer amount of speed to approach the enemy Stompa.<br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon –</b> Working with a Looted Wagon, you can become a deadly combo by watching for when the Looted Wagon cripples someone with their Grot Bomm. You can then quickly swoop in and finish them off with your Rokkit Kannon.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0541ac8355379153a2cdc7548f4f2b13cdc7858a.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against</div><b>Deffkilla Wartrike –</b> Because you can maintain your speed for longer and have more tools to accelerate with, the Deffkilla Wartrike will struggle to catch you. Get behind them and they won’t be able to escape once you’ve gotten your eye on them. The homing missiles will make sure you hit your target as you run them down.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weak Against</div><b>Kustom Boosta Blasta – </b>Kustom Boosta Blasta doesn’t care about how fast you’re going and with their mid-long range gun they can shoot you while you’re flying through the sky. A good Kustom Boosta Blasta will stop your momentum with its grenade.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cea39c73b401847e4769131ef9bcf104856771f6.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Message to the community - a first Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6356356787200103703</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Dear players,</div><br/>We recently launched our new community-oriented platform - Focus Together - and you’ve made good use of it! ✨<br/><br/>Join <b>Focus Together</b> here:<br/><br/><br/><a class="bb_link" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Flogin.focus-entmt.com%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fec44739cc231ee0e0f0b4631eb2aa240e1fea0f.png"/></a><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">We’ve started reading your ideas, so here’s a first Q&amp;A!</div><br/>You, the players, were invited to help us improve the game by submitting your ideas and upvoting others’. And you flooded the forum with posts! Don’t feel left behind if you’ve posted feedback on Discord, Reddit, Steam, or Twitter: we also check all other platforms. But Focus Together is our main platform for feedback! We are so glad to see such enthusiasm and dedication coming from the community. <br/><br/>But these ideas are wasted if we don’t address them! So here are a few answers to your hottest topics!<br/><br/>Before you read this Q&amp;A, many of the submitted ideas are features planned for the future and have already been communicated via the roadmap. If you missed it, make sure you take note of it here: <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">CONNECTIVITY ISSUES</div></u><br/>We know some of you are experiencing server issues, loss of saves or impossibility to connect with friends. We are ramping up our server capacity to reduce the load on them, and are working day and night to reduce the issues. This is a top priority for the team. A bigger patch is planned soon to improve this topic further, alongside new content.<br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">AI BOTS</div></u><br/><b>Question: Bots are regularly mentioned as inefficient, making solo games significantly harder, and you suggested we work on them. According to you, they don’t participate in focusing on objectives or don’t do enough in tense situations.</b><br/><br/>Answer: Bots seem a bit passive because we don’t want them to take the spotlight from the player. However, they can sometimes be a bit too passive. In the next patch, we have a few improvements of their behavior against boss fights in the campaign. We are also considering improving their involvement during specific objectives in the campaign for a later patch.<br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div></u><br/><b>Q: Veteran difficulty is said to be too hard in solo as the bots don’t help with the objectives.</b><br/><br/>A: We will adjust Veteran difficulty in a future patch. It will remain challenging but it will be slightly more fair because we will tweak AI aggressiveness on this difficulty. Other difficulties will remain untouched.<br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">ABOUT PVE…</div></u><br/><div class="bb_h3">BALANCING</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Q: Assault is often listed as less powerful than other classes: the jump pack in PVE loses its versatility compared to the one in the campaign</b>.<br/></li><li> A: We are still collecting data on this issue to see how we can work on it.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: The Blocking weapon trait is seen by the community as a bad thing for melee weapons as it removes the potential for mastery (because there is no “perfect” parry window). </b><br/></li><li> A: We fully agree that this is a bummer, and we’ll definitely make changes in a future patch.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Bolt Rifle family is underperforming while Melta Gun is considered OP</b><br/></li><li> A: We have noticed a bug where the Melta allows the user to heal above the contested health, we aim to fix this in the next patch. As for the rest of weapon balancing, we hear you, and some weapons can underdeliver on the power fantasy at higher difficulty levels. We also recognize that enemies can be too bullet spongy on higher difficulty, which is not much fun. That’s the core issue, rather than the bolters themselves. For now, we are testing some tweaks in difficulty to make the enemies have less health but keep the engaging difficulty.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">QUALITY OF LIFE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Q: You asked to be able to have several of the same class, in Operations mode. There is also frustration in matchmaking when two players want to be the same class</b>.<br/></li><li> A: For now, we are focusing on improving matchmaking so that you will not matchmake with players of the same class. This is not an easy fix, so it will take us some time to roll it out. As for using the same class, we don't want to change that rule for regular matchmaking, but we are considering it as an expansion of private lobbies in the future. It will take us time to finish it.<br/><br/></li><li><b>Q: It was observed that players tend to show toxic behaviors as they get kicked late during a game made by a group of friends to let their friend get the XP.</b> <br/></li><li> A: We understand this is unfair, and each player will receive XP based on his actual involvement in the mission.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Saved loadouts don’t include skill tree customization, making them less relevant</b>.<br/></li><li> A: This is not a priority for us at the moment.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/08c2fc08db5591229d46435f3671ee8d884ed1b0.jpg"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">ABOUT PVP…</div></u><br/><div class="bb_h3">MATCHMAKING</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Q: You have suggested making it possible to tag as a squad of 6.</b><br/></li><li> A: We understand this need. We want to add custom PvP lobbies and give players more control over the match (for example: frag limit, class restriction, etc.). It's not that easy to make and it takes time! So please bear with us while we work on it, and we will let you know when we have clearer visibility on when it will be released.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">BALANCING</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Q: It was brought to our attention that shock grenades are OP. Also, many of you consider melee to be underpowered.</b><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Assault is considered weak in PVP. Bulwark is overpowered in capture zones. And, Heavy is overpowered: too much damage for its durability.</b><br/></li><li> A: Regarding pvp balancing, we are currently reading and crunching the data. We don't want to make rash decisions before seeing the global picture. At the moment we are checking the most common topics such as melee balancing, shock grenades, bulwark &amp; heavy being too present in capture game modes. Expect some tweaks in the first big content patch but not before.<br/></li><li> <b>Q: No team balancing after matches creates unbalanced matches for several matches in a row.</b><br/></li><li> A: We have heard this many times, and we want to improve this in future patches. We are looking into it!</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SPAWNING</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Q: Spawning locations can create spawn-kill situations.</b><br/></li><li> A: This will be tweaked with some parameters in a future patch. We will implement spawn protection.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a52fb9bb939884e854a211c37021a4b5b07ee02.jpg"/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">MOST UPVOTED TOPICS ON FOCUS TOGETHER</div></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Q: Are we getting new colors for the lenses?</b><br/></li><li> A: New lens colors are planned and coming soon in the next big patch!<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: You asked to pick the Chaos Space Marines Legions you want for every classes:</b><br/></li><li> A: There are many lore restrictions preventing us from doing this (For instance: We cannot make a sniper with a World Eater armor). It is very tricky to match armor pieces for Chaos. Armor pieces have different sizes and styles, will clip through each other, etc. Also, in PvP it is important to be able to recognize an enemy’s class, and we want to keep the visual identity of each of them. Now, we will not keep it as it is and would like to expand Chaos customization, but the reality is they won't be as modular as the Loyalist.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Many of you have asked for new classes: </b><br/></li><li> A: That is definitely something we are heavily discussing. Adding a new class is quite heavy on production as we also need to create all the customization, PVP Chaos model variant, and animation set depending on what we go for. We'll keep you updated about this topic.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: About the missing armor colors: </b><br/></li><li> A: We aim to expand specific color masks, such as hand, decals or facemask, in upcoming patches. We will be adding all successor chapters eventually. ;) <br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Adding new melee weapons: </b><br/></li><li> A: New melee weapons would definitely be an extremely cool addition. Making a weapon and designing it is fine, but we need to make all finisher animations for it. It will take time.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Customizing your Marine’s face: </b><br/></li><li> A: Not a quick fix, but we will add an option to change your Marine’s face!<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Optimizing PvP Crossplay: </b><br/></li><li> A: We need more time to discuss that. Custom PvP lobbies will solve a good part of the issue.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Thunderhawk Customization: </b><br/></li><li> A: Doing full Battlebarge and Thunderhawk customization is very cool but not up in our priority list. We prefer to focus our art teams on creating new maps.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Pyreblaster in PvE or PvP: </b><br/></li><li> A: We will add it but it will take time because of visual and gameplay progression. We’ll keep you updated!<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: To be able to customize the AI squad mates: </b><br/></li><li> A: Still in discussions.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Delete Custom Armor Profile: </b><br/></li><li> A: We worked on this. In the next patch, you will be able to overwrite a custom preset with a default one.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: FoV Slider and Left / Right Shoulder swap: </b><br/></li><li> A: FoV slider is not something we are comfortable with, as it can degrade the visual aspect of the game. And on top of that, it is very complex. Our game is not a first person shooter, the camera that we have is very cinematic and constantly changes position and FoV based on what you are doing. Still, we understand that is a very popular request so we are considering it anyway. <br/></li><li> As for the shoulder swap,if we are to implement shoulder swap we will need to support it for all melee animations and transitions because everything in melee combat was made based on the fact that you hold pistol in the left hand and melee weapon in the right hand (because it looks badass). Nevertheless, shoulder swap is a feature we will not add in the game.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: Get rid of class restriction on cloaks and tabards:</b><br/></li><li> A: These are part of class identity; you get to recognize snipers because of those elements.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Q: I-Frames on gun-strikes: </b><br/></li><li> A: Gun-strikes are a risk/reward action, and it is very easy to spam. We specifically did not put an i-frame on it for balancing reasons, and we are not looking to change this intention.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/cc3aed7958211debea435753e0cc3a461dae6b59.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">We hope this first batch of Q&amp;As has answered your hot topics! Stay tuned on our socials and sign in to Focus Together to ensure you remain updated on the latest <i>Space Marine 2</i> news! </div><br/><i>For the Emperor,<br/>The Focus Team</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 15:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
