<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 1.10.4 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/523114213613243538</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3ac134291d4b08e1a1b0a6fd05a18804f08516ea.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Warband, </div><p class="bb_paragraph">This patch comes with several technical improvements that we hope will increase stability and network performance in the game. It should also improve playing on slower and/or unstable network connections. In addition we also improved memory usage to help performance on lower-end devices. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We will continue to work on improvements, and we urge you all to keep sending in crash reports, as they really help us to find further solutions. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Patch 1.10.4</b> is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Bug Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Several improvements and fixes to stability and network performance. </b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Improved memory usage to increase performance on lower-end devices.</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug where the Mission Board and the Special Assignments would have mismatching ordering on the campaign missions</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the server to crash when players would step in specific locations in several missions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a memory leak when generating player portraits for UI presentations.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the second damage instance of multiple-hits Heavy attacks on the Chirurgeon's Mk IV Bone Saw was not using the correct profile when having the Brittleness coating applied.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash which could happen when another player disconnected just as Rampage! ended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the Stimm Supply to get stuck in the player's hands after trying to place it.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed crash that could happen if the player leaves missions while particle effects still are active.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that could happen when a player left the game from the menu causing the slot for another player to join to be locked for a certain amount of time. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed "Well Oiled Killteam" penance not progressing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the last blessing point for the Shredder Autopistol to remain unspent.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Auspex Drill penance wouldn’t track towards completion.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a lighting issue where the light would turn from dark to very bright. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the mission’s fog would disappear completely when using a stealth ability.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where certain language fonts had issues rendering correctly on the Aquila Purchase screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed bug where when using a controller and starting a campaign mission from the Special Assignments view would also start the debrief video.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reverted an unintended change introduced in 1.10.3 that made weapon specific dodge linger time affect incoming ranged attacks. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reverted an unintended change that allowed dodge stats from talent trees to also impact incoming ranged damage.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed color name in item title of the Hive Scum Hood (KHAKI) to the correct color.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed graphical issue where the white skull decal did not show up on the MK IVM Pot Helm With Gas Mask (XXXXL).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed headgear clipping with the ears on some faces - Steel Legion Flak Helmet (Parade Polish).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed deformation issue with implant - Commando Beret With Augmetic Implant (Green).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issues with face - Athonian 98th Pilgrim's Warhelm (Red).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with backpacks clipping with the cloak - Athonian 98th Fatigues.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rolling Bones trinket now shows as expected when showcased in the UI screens.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping with strap and head on Slasher Hivescum Headgear </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed distortion in Commando Beret with Augmetic Implant (Green).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issue with leg armor on Krieg Vigil Greatcoat (Krieg 143rd).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed physics on Votarist's Pot Helm with Rebreather </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issue with leg armor on Imperius pattern Psykana garb.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Additional Changes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Corrected the penance conditions of some missions with misgiving information.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbites' Remote Detonation now has the correct icon in the HUD.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Dual Autopistols didn't have shell casings ejected from the weapons when firing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed muzzle smoke for Dual Stub Pistols and Stub Revolver moving in unintended directions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing Dual Stub Pistols magazines to cast unintended shadows when they ejected.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for today! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techmarine Gameplay Breakdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/541128612120628436</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Greetings Space Marines!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In today’s blog, we’ll give you a complete presentation of the upcoming new class, the Techmarine!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4261e602a6a09eafb84f4f0e85a726ee4f60c83e.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Playstyle</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Techmarine is a specialist in crowd control and zoning. His arsenal can hold off both crowds of enemies and individual dangerous opponents while his allies safely deal damage. Gameplay-wise, the Techmarine is a mixed class with a slight melee bias. Unlike the Bulwark, who also keeps enemies away from attacking classes, the Techmarine is more focused on pressuring enemies with wide AoE melee attacks and mid-range firearms.</p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Abilities</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">His special ability, the Servo-Gun, unleashes a powerful volley on nearby enemies. Additionally, the Techmarine can detect and activate Tarantula Sentry Guns on the levels. They will attack enemies until they run out of ammo or are destroyed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" toifh45vdxk?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' width="850"></iframe>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" v7ffzxlyfpu?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">A unique characteristic of the Techmarine is the integration of the Servo-Gun during Gun Strikes. This allows for greater movement freedom compared to other classes during these actions, for instance you can perform melee attacks while using a Gun Strike.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e07c126cac8270b4d18fe8dac6ae96b2b87d2bbb.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Arsenal</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Techmarine can use the following weapons: </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Primary Weapons</u>:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Auto Bolt Rifle</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bolt Rifle</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Bolt Rifle</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Occulus Bolt Carbine</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Plasma Incinerator</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Secondary Weapons</u>:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bolt Pistol</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavy Bolt Pistol</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Plasma Pistol</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Inferno Pistol</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Neo-Volkite Pistol</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Melee Weapons</u>:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Combat Knife</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Power Sword</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Power Axe</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Omnissian Axe</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">As you can see, the Techmarine’s unique array of weapons includes the standout Omnissian Axe. This new melee weapon is exclusive to the Techmarine, and it’s perfect for handling multiple smaller enemies simultaneously due to its wide AoE attacks. It also has a special move, the “Omnissian Rush”, which makes the Techmarine rush forward, impaling the enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" mdml0ee_v7a?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Perks</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">We thought that you might be interested to know the perks the Techmarine will have. You can check out this short video and pause to read all the perks effects, but keep in mind that some values can still change until the release of Patch 12.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" endtiqym_a0?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">That’s it for our Techmarine blog! We hope it gave you a complete overview of this new class, and that you’re excited to test it when Patch 12 releases! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">- The Emperor protects</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darktide - Wrapping up 2025 and looking ahead!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/523114213613242322</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Warband,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With 2025 wrapped up, we wanted to take the opportunity to look back at the year and all the happenings in Darktide!  We released more content than ever for Darktide, so let's take a walk down memory lane.  </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve had <b>four major free updates</b>, each coming with an assortment of features and changes!</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Nightmares &amp; Visions</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Battle For Tertium</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Bound By Duty</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>No Man’s Land</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">We also released <b>two new DLC classes!</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites, announced at Warhammer Skulls! </b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hive Scum</b>, our final release in December last year!</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Complete opposites, both in playstyle and what side of the law they operate on. Both still added new ways for the Mourningstar’s forces to battle the ongoing threats on Tertium. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1f12d6eb28275fc8bd5dacb27085293f25fcee65.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Eleven events were released in 2025</b>, just slightly missing the mark to make them a monthly occurrence. All but one of them were also brand new.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Waking Giants</b> </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Unrelenting Hordes</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>A Day at the Theatre</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Communication Breakdown</b> </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Admonition Ascendant</b> </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Inferno</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Rotten Armour</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light the Fuse!</b> </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Smuggled Munitions</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Stolen Rations</b> </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Day of Atonement</b></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1fa9379386b7e97459ce1ce15ab88cda58fcaf79.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some other new things we added included a brand new Elite enemy, the <b>Plasma Gunner</b>, who quickly began to terrorize players during missions. We’ve added a <b>new Weapon Family</b> in the <b>Power Falchion</b> and two <b>new weapon marks</b>, one for the <b>Boltgun </b>and one for the <b>Bolt Pistol</b>!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There were also <b>sweeping balance changes throughout the year</b>, polishing up weapons and fleshing out entire talent trees for all of the base classes!</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Talent tree reworks for Ogryn, then Veteran, Zealot and Psyker</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reworks and improvements to x weapons</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ogryn Cleavers, Shovels, Clubs, Power Maul, Grenadier Gauntlet, Ripper Guns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Autopistols</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Devil’s Claw Swords</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blaze Force Greatswords</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tactical Axes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shock Mauls</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Eviscerators</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Helbore Lasguns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Combat Shotguns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Double Barreled Shotguns</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Assault Chainswords &amp; Chainaxes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Vigilant Autoguns</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked <b>pacing and enemy balance</b>!</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve had an assortment of <b>quality of life changes</b> and improvements throughout the year!</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated the <b>Havoc</b> game mode, overhauling the ranking system, adding campaigns, new modifiers and tuning the existing ones.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Reworked the mission board</b>, allowing you to choose missions and difficulty separately and reworking how difficulties are unlocked! Auric was also turned into its own difficulty, rather than a modifier on top of Damnation</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Increased the total Operative slots to 9</b>!</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a <b>Dodge Counter</b> to the HUD and reworked the <b>Stamina Bar!</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added <b>so many</b> <b>bonding conversations</b> and banter!</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added the ability to <b>de-select talent tree nodes</b> without having to deselect the talents linked to it below!</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We added an <b>Aquila Welcome Offer</b> to the Commodore’s Vestures, a one-time purchase for players to receive an Aquila pack for a heavily discounted price.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">And as of the latest free update in December, we added a <b>brand new Operation: No Man’s Land and</b> a <b>new Ogryn Personality, the Heavy</b>, voiced by Tim Bentick!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ff1948eafc8f556e42a7a1140ae67adc024feadd.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">So to wrap up, we landed on four major updates, two new classes and multiple quality of life and balance fixes. 2025 has been a busy year for us on the Darktide team. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We are happy with last year's releases, and we are not aiming to slow down in 2026!  To tease a bit, we can tell you that the next class has already been in the works for quite some time now, and we can’t wait to show you more when the time is right! <br/><br/>Before that we will have another release though, so you will have to wait a bit, but we are pretty sure you will like this one too. Darktide is certainly going places in 2026! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re super thankful to you, our community, for sharing our passion and excitement for this game and bringing it to life together this past year. We can’t wait to see what you think of what’s coming this year”</p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for now.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you in the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius | 1.17.2 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/493840816042672275</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.17.1</i> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Balance</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Increased Kommando melee attacks from 1 to 2 (affects Stikkbomb).</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed game potentially not starting due to incorrect IGD initialization handling (this is likely to have happened in offline mode).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed Dialogus' Verse of Holy Piety not reducing The Emperor's Deliverance cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed missing Plague Spewer sounds.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed Armiger Helverin barks not showing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Armiger Autocannon now benefits from Scriptorum Ordinatus research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Blight Grenade now benefits from Daemonbone Casings research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Tank Commander research now unlocks the Additional Heavy Bolters research.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Updated missing mentions of units in researches descriptions.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/489630/" width="850"></iframe>
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.0.3 Now Live for All Players</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/563646078927241788</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">​<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0be0bd2770edbec3191d6c5054934a9e515bbabe.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 7.0.3 is now out of Beta and has rolled out to all players. Thanks to everyone who checked out the Beta and shared their feedback and bug reports over the holidays and in these first weeks of January.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve added a number of additional fixes to the full release which are listed below, as well as in their respective categories in the full release notes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue introduced in the 7.0.3 Beta where the option to Subjugate a faction would sometimes not appear after defeating them.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with Elspeth’s Gunnery School missions and progression issues.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Norscan Marauding actions would incorrectly have a 5 turn cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Pleasurable Acts for N'kari and The Masque would incorrectly having a 10 turn cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed broken Encampment stance for Dragonship horde armies (Aislinn unaffected).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue so that the Nemesis Crown dilemma should no longer display a placeholder image.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where you could only select 1 spell after resetting skill points for Kairos Fateweaver.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Kairos couldn’t change spells in Fragments of Sorcery once confederated.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Multiplayer would crash if any player was playing as Kairos.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed performance issues when using Chinese Text language on high UI Scale (160% to 200%) on 4K Resolution.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">👉 Read the full Hotfix 7.0.3 Release Notes here 👈</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, should you run into any new issues after updating to Hotfix 7.0.3, be sure to raise them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve, Pingu &amp; Freeman // TW Community Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
