<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction: Mortis Trials - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520834687966380114</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8189710bbc0ebae80f039434fba5e8b741870a45.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone! </div><br/>As promised, we are back this week with another dev blog for the next update for Warhammer 40,000: Darktide - <b>Nightmares &amp; Visions</b>, which <b>releases next week</b> on <b>March 25, 2025. </b><br/><br/>This week, we’re focusing on new content coming to the game in the form of <b>Mortis Trials.</b> This <b>feature </b>has been designed to be a unique, replayable activity whereby players will mash through <b>waves of enemies in visions induced by Sefoni</b>, the Mourningstar’s mysterious Psyker. <br/><br/>With the arrival of Commissar’s Moebian 53rd and the escalation of the Battle for Tertium, Rannick has grudgingly decided that they need to step up the Rejects’ training regime from, well, <i>nothing</i>, to something. <br/><br/>With resources tight and the warband’s operatives more than a little… varied in their approach to combat, he and Morrow have turned the matter over to Sefoni. Which makes sense, given that she’s the creator and maintainer of the <i>Mourningstar’s </i>Meat Grinder - a psychically generated oubliette where Rejects can familiarise themselves with new weaponry. <br/><br/>To make this possible, she’s manifested a new nightmarescape that Morrow calls Sefoni’s Reverie.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What is Mortis Trials?</div><br/><i>Unlocked from Trust Level 13,</i> Mortis Trials is a new activity in Darktide where players can experience something they wouldn’t encounter in normal missions, something with crazy wave compositions and roguelike elements. The fickle nature of these psychic manifestations has ensured that no two trials are alike, and only those who adapt will prevail. By accessing Sefoni’s Reverie on the Mourningstar, players will be transported to the Theatres of Mortification. These are the arenas where players will face the challenges Sefoni has created for them.  <br/><br/>At the end of a successfully completed trial, players will return to Sefoni’s Reverie.<br/><br/><b>Havoc </b>is a <b>game mode </b>with multipliers upon multipliers, and stacked mutators; which has been designed for late-game players to face a challenge. The experience of an <b>activity </b>like <b>Mortis Trials </b>is designed to be chaotic, with easy access for immediate fun. That said, players will face horrors in these theatres, where there is no escape or surrender. Only by standing your ground and fighting with unwavering determination will players emerge with victory. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What will the game play loop look like for Mortis Trials?</div>Unlike some other experiences in Darktide, Mortis Trials offers more modular pacing rather than non-stop action. Pacing is key, with the difficulty increasing over time in a fun and expandable way. <br/><br/>Each trial consists of 12 waves of heretics to clear. These waves will be broken into three waves of three, and then a final set of three heretical-filled waves straight from Sefoni herself. <br/><br/>When launching Mortis Trials, players will first select the difficulty level they wish to try. From there, the players will assemble in a central theatre. <br/><br/>Before facing the initial wave, players will receive a small buff. The buff they receive is based on the “indulgence” that is chosen before this first wave begins. <br/><br/>Each indulgence has a specialization which will define the type of small buffs player will get during the play through. These include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Pyrokinetic</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in dealing fire damage, or improving combat effectiveness while attacking burning targets.</li><li><b>Voltaic</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in dealing electric damage, or improving combat effectiveness while attacking electrocuted targets.</li><li><b>Fulminator</b>: This Indulgence Archetype combines elements from both Pyrokinetic and Voltaic disciplines. It applies both electric and fire effects on enemies and can improve combat effectiveness when fighting electrocuted or burning enemies.</li><li><b>Death Dealer</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in close-quarters shooting and melee. Quick swapping between weapons and quicker reloads.</li><li><b>Colossus</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in survivability, focused on close-quarters melee combat.</li></ul>Based on the archetype selected, the players will receive <b>another </b>small buff for the second wave. Every third wave, the players will be required to move around the arena and complete a designated task. These are the “<b>objective</b>” <b>waves</b>, which happen on the 3rd, 6th and 9th waves.<br/><br/>Upon completing the objective, Rejects are granted a cache of ammunition and supplies to aid in the trials. Further, players will then <b>pick </b>an additional stronger buff. This buff, along with the others, will continue to stack after each wave is successfully cleared. After each objective wave, players will <b>pick </b>an additional stronger buff. (These buffs are often amplifying player abilities, grenades, etc.) Only the most devout and blessed will survive.<br/><br/>After the last objective wave is completed (i.e. wave number 9), Rejects must endure a final set of three waves surging with enemies.  These are the waves where the players are the strongest. We want to give them plenty of time to enjoy their power to the fullest.<br/><br/>After successfully completing one round of the Mortis Trials, players must return the Mortis Relic to Sefoni in her Reverie. The strain of these Trials pushes her to her limit, causing stray thoughts and memories to slip out of her head. Attentive players might glean unintended insights into key members of the Mourningstar crew, so you better pay attention.<br/><br/>Repeated playthroughs of the Mortis Trials promise different play experiences, with new Indulgences to try and new conversations to unlock.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"> Narrative Focus: Mortis Trials </div><br/>To learn more about Mortis Trials from a narrative perspective we are handing the dev blog over to our Narrative Lead, Michael Knight and our Lead Writer, Matthew Ward.<br/><br/><b>Sefoni’s one of the first characters a new Reject meets, but we don’t know much about her. Is that about to change?</b><br/><b>Michael Knight:</b> Yes and no. Sefoni’s delighted that she’s got new playthings to torment - the Rejects probably treat her better than most of the rest of the warband - but she’s also very secretive. That said, generating the Trials of Mortification places Sefoni under enormous pressure, and fragments of her past have a tendency to manifest without her knowing.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>Not just her past.<br/><br/><b>MK: </b>I’m pretty sure that we’re not supposed to talk about that. Grendyl wouldn’t like it. Safe to say, the Trials of Mortification offer the Rejects the opportunity to learn a lot more than Rannick intends. That probably won’t end well for Sefoni, but again, I doubt she cares.<br/><br/><b>How do the Rejects complete a Trial?</b><br/><b>MK:</b> Each Trial of Mortification is effectively a beefed-up exercise in a section of the Meat Grinder. The Rejects need to defeat the waves of enemies being projected by Sefoni, accomplishing tasks along the way. If they win, they’ll unlock a relic and get one step closer to being initiated into the Mourningstar’s elite cadre of Mortis Operatives. Fail, and… you can guess the rest.  <br/><br/><b>MW: </b>But Sefoni isn’t entirely heartless. The Meat Grinder’s her world. It follows her rules, so she’s prepared to offer the Rejects a series of indulgences (in-game buffs) that will help them meet the challenge.<br/><br/><b>MK:</b> Rannick isn't going to like that.<br/><br/><b>MW:</b> There’s definitely a sense that she’s not answering to Rannick any more, if she ever did.<br/><br/><b>You said something earlier about the Rejects having a chance to learn things that Rannick doesn’t want them to know. Can you tell us a little more about that?</b><br/><b>MK:</b> Well … Sefoni’s a psyker, a pretty rare and formidable one. And she’s been with Grendyl a long time. She’s overheard a lot over the years. Chances are, she knows a lot more about the warband than even Rannick. How far that goes - and how deep it goes - remains to be seen.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>One thing’s for sure… As time goes on, she’s going to get bolder.<br/><br/><b>MK: </b>Unless Rannick catches her.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>Unless that, yes.<br/><br/>Hmm…there is a lot to be unpacked there. I’ll leave that for the community theory crafters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Thank you for reading our dev blog on Mortis Trials, part of the new content coming alongside the Nightmares &amp; Visions update slotted for release next week on March 25, 2025. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll make sure we answer them in the patch notes. <br/><br/>Remember, the Emperor protects. But He also demands sacrifice. <br/><br/>We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.5.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/606402352818161401</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.5.3 - 17th of March							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Bot Improvements: (note, these changes were missed from patch 6.4.0 patch notes)								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Bots now avoid healing Zealots.						</li></ul> </li></ul> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed social wheel messages not working in Versus.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Weaves was inaccessible for some players.							</li></ul> </blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updates to Havoc - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/573751255204102938</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b1d315e3e07a887b1c68ca2e6c2cd6dc4ffdb8c2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>When Havoc Mode was first released at the end of 2024, we mentioned it would be a system we’d continue to hone with community feedback. <br/><br/>Over the last couple of months, we’ve been reading tons of input from the community on Havoc through player comments, threads, videos, memes, etc. <br/><br/>Now as the first dev blog for our next update, Nightmares and Visions, we’d like to tell players all about the work we’ve been doing on Havoc and the changes we’re bringing to the game mode in March. <br/><br/>First of all, we upped the pacing a bit to keep things fresh. Players might notice there is less time to regroup than there was before. There are other larger changes we’d like to touch on in this blog, though.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Rank Overhaul</div><br/>One of the biggest points of feedback we received had to do with progressing through different Havoc Assignment Ranks. <br/><br/><i>(As a quick refresher, <b>Havoc Assignment Rank</b> is the current Havoc Assignment a player has access to play in the game; <b>Havoc Clearance Level</b> refers to the highest Assignment a player has completed. <br/><br/>A player’s <b>Havoc Assignment Rank </b>currently changes after each mission or after each weekly reset. It can go down if a player <b>only plays</b> lower Assignment Rank missions that week. However, a player’s<b> Havoc Clearance Level</b> only goes up over time as a player completes higher Assignment Ranks.)</i><br/><br/>As it stands in the game now, before playing a game of Havoc, the party needs to choose which player’s Havoc Assignment they’d like to attempt to complete. After finishing the game, only the owner of that Havoc Assignment would see their own Clearance Level go up. The remaining players would need to wait until the following week to see their Havoc Clearance Level go up. We read the feedback saying this part of Havoc was frustrating and unclear.<br/><br/>Further, there were worries of “boosting” other players through the initial system we laid out. <br/><br/>We’ve made some changes. <br/><br/>With this update, we’ve changed it so everyone who participates in a Havoc game will rank up their Assignment Rank. That is, upon winning the mission, <b>all the players of equal or lower Assignment Rank to the chosen mission</b> will be ranked up. <br/><br/>All players who participate get the mission reward, as well.<br/><br/>To make it fair, everyone who participates in a mission for Havoc will be eligible to be penalized upon failure (i.e. lose a charge), too.<br/><br/>These changes were made to ensure everyone who participates in Havoc will feel rewarded post-mission. <br/><br/><b>How do we determine how many ranks a player will climb after completing a Havoc mission? </b><br/><br/>It is determined by the difference between the player's Assignment Rank and the Assignment Rank being played (shown in the chart below).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4ac08cd45ba331c5620247fcbe2a71343b5e8389.png"/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A gap of<i> less than or equal to 5 </i>gives an increase of (1) Clearance Levels.</li><li>A gap <i>between 6 and 9</i> gives an increase of (2) Clearance Levels.</li><li>A gap <i>greater than or equal</i> to 10 gives an increase of (3) Clearance Levels.</li></ul>A player’s Assignment Rank is no longer determined by the highest completed Havoc Assignment Rank from the previous week. Instead, as long as a player is active each week, the player will retain their current Assignment Rank. (A player is considered “active” as long as they attempt at least (1) Havoc mission in a week. The player does not need to win the game in order to be considered an active player.)<br/><br/>Now, the only way for a player’s Assignment Rank to go down is if they lose all three charges or they are inactive for a certain period of time (i.e. a player does not play at least (1) Havoc mission after a weekly reset).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"> Havoc Campaigns </div><br/>Along with Nightmares and Visions, we are introducing something to Havoc called Havoc Campaigns.<br/><br/>Havoc Campaigns is what we’ve opted to call the rotation of the mission pool and mutators within Havoc, we want players to be able to learn and adapt to these combinations while also changing things up over the period of the current Havoc Campaign. It’ll begin from this update!<br/><br/><b>Maintenance Announcement:</b> <i>With Havoc Campaigns, we’ll be introducing new balancing to the game mode. Ahead of Nightmares &amp; Visions, Havoc will be “off-Campaign” and unavailable to play from the Sunday, March 23 until the day of release on March 25.</i><br/><br/>During this off-time and to reflect the balance changes made, we’ll reset everyone to their nearest threshold depending on the highest they reached the previous Havoc Campaign period. (Please see the chart below.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1d361f3998fe57239e7e8839cfedd29dd715fc08.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2"> New Mutators </div><br/><b>Heinous Rituals: </b><br/>Reports indicate that the Admonition has begun creating more Daemonhosts in this area, disrupt these rituals before it’s too late.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e9908421c6702eff9c2d581def59ff25d47becf1.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>The Encroaching Garden:</b><br/>Marked Enemies will heal affected allies in proximity. <br/>If these enemies are not dealt with quickly, they will rapidly regenerate the enemy forces. <br/><br/><b>Rampaging Enemies: </b><br/>Enemies in this sector are rampaging. They grow emboldened upon witnessing the death of another of their kind gaining increased defence against attacks.<br/><br/><b>Enraging Elites: </b><br/>Elite enemies will upon taking critical damage become enraged, increasing their attack speed, movement speed, and give them complete CC (crowd control) immunity. <br/><br/><i>These four mutators will replace the current four mutators in Havoc. </i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>This summarizes the first wave of changes we’re bringing to Havoc for 2025. We still have more ideas we’d like to explore and bring to the game mode this year.<br/><br/>We’ll be reading the comments across our platforms in response to this blog, so please join the conversation and let us know what you think!<br/><br/>Thank you for reading and playing.<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Spring Sale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497188710547195118</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/4b14ef5c2ebe68711fa45e2cf52ff4551baafe9a.png"/><br/><br/>The Steam Spring Sale is here! From now until 20th March grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War: WARHAMMER and historical titles!<br/> <br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
    Total_War_WARHAMMER<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/> <br/>Whether you're a Total War veteran, a newcomer to the series, or simply want to complete your collection, this is the perfect opportunity to grab a deal!<br/> <br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends Thursday, March 20th @ 6PM GMT/11AM PT</div></div><div class="bb_code">
— The <i>Total War</i> Team

<div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Spring Sale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/594570/view/519707341539510876</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/28300675/4b14ef5c2ebe68711fa45e2cf52ff4551baafe9a.png"/><br/><br/>The Steam Spring Sale is here! From now until 20th March grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War: WARHAMMER and historical titles!<br/> <br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
    Total_War_WARHAMMER<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/> <br/>Whether you're a Total War veteran, a newcomer to the series, or simply want to complete your collection, this is the perfect opportunity to grab a deal!<br/> <br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends Thursday, March 20th @ 6PM GMT/11AM PT</div></div><div class="bb_code">
— The <i>Total War</i> Team

<div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
