<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Vermintide 2 for "LABOR OF LOVE" category - Steam Awards</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954130273</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/5848bdeced11770459f6a76c959ad46ac1013dd9.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>November Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4464851737096749903</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">​​Greetings Space Marines!</div><br/>The end of the year is approaching, to celebrate this wonderful year that has brought so much joy to us and to the players, we have a few surprises for you! ⭐<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>But first, let’s recap the past month a bit!</b> </div><br/>On November 12 we released Patch 4.5. This update was important as it brought a brand new weapon: The Neo-Volkite Pistol, as well as loads of balancing tweaks on several weapons (Plasma Incinerator / Bolt Sniper Rifle / Occulus Bolt Carbine / Bolt Carbine (SMG) / Auto Bolt Rifle). <br/><br/>To read the entire patch note, click here. <br/><br/>How cool is it? 😎<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f182956c202bc3bccf61cc89a68d1560ae830eda.gif"/><br/><i>Note that the Neo-Volkite Pistol will be available in PvP starting from the 5.0 update.</i><br/><br/>As for every month, we keep reading your feedback closely, and reviewing the ideas submitted onto Focus Together! There’s more and more each week, which gives us plenty of ideas to work with! We want to thank you for that. We keep reviewing them but it takes time!<br/><br/>To see the answers devs have already provided, check it <b>here</b>. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">WE REACHED 5 MILLION PLAYERS!</div><br/>5 million Space Marines have joined our ranks to purge Xenos &amp; Chaos! 🎉<br/><br/>Huge thanks to everyone who's joined the fight. It’s been incredible to see the community grow (and to keep seeing it grow)! Here’s to many more battles ahead. ⚔️<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a26727765eb7835dd67a4402047056ff7717101c.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">SECRET LEVEL EVENT</div><br/>As you may have seen, the story of Titus continues in Amazon Prime Video’s Secret Level series!<br/><br/>A new trailer dropped to tease the upcoming episode.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YMZffM5bKmg?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>The series will start on December 10. One episode will be fully dedicated to Warhammer 40,000. Stay tuned, it’s gonna be epic! 💥<br/><br/>To celebrate this incredible occasion, exclusive rewards will be available from December 10 to December 31 through Twitch drops! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/34e218704addcc335ae9dca9dc88b29e6b5079a3.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PATCH 5.0</div><br/>The 5.0 update will be released in the first half of December! This update contains the very much awaited Dark Angels Chapter Pack, alongside another Operation: Obelisk. <br/><br/>The Dark Angels Chapter Pack features the Dark Angels Champion, which is a unique armour set and banner for the Bulwark Class.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39308af705c0b0ffd996813ea1e63517d7240aba.jpg"/><br/><i>Please note that this set can’t be customised</i><br/><br/>Three weapons will also receive exclusive visuals based on the Dark Angels Chapter: the Auto Bolt Rifle, the Plasma Pistol and the Power Sword. The Bulwark class will also get a unique Dark Angels Storm Shield.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/172ef8cfa6ebf3ecc4b2dab4ca0b96317548aee4.jpg"/><br/><br/>The Dark Angels Chapter Pack includes the heraldry items of the Second Foundings and Successor Chapters of the Dark Angels: the Angels of Absolution, the Angels of Redemption, the Angels of Vengeance, the Unnamed, the Blades of Vengeance, the Cowled Wardens, the Bringers of Judgement and the Angels of Defiance.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/213028c7c3da38554a114261beb6f898505316fd.png"/><br/><br/>New armour pieces will also be  added, including a fan-favourite helmet: the Mark VIII Ravenwing! All these items will be available to unlock as part of an heraldry cosmetic.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/88753ecbf0f7c215104223a1c96567e5e4cf5ad6.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e67c16b96c4959046ba7287f20decb19b6bce8c3.jpg"/></div></div></div><br/>Last addition to the customisation menu, the colour lenses are finally here! Choose among 15 different colours to customise your Space Marine even more!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d9630bdb7172f9efbf708bc1d3f9751275018435.gif"/><br/><br/>This update does not only bring new customisation, a new Operation will also be added! Called “Obelisk”, you’ll be sent to Demerium and your mission is to rotate a replica of the obelisk to disrupt the flow of energy protecting the Aurora device. This operation takes place in parallel to the final events of the campaign.<br/><br/>To reach the console control of the obelisk, you’ll have to make it through a tomb plunged into darkness. To make your progression even tougher, the Chaos forces see a new addition to their roster: the Tzaangor Enlightened, a new Majoris enemy! They will now appear in every PvE Operation with Chaos.<br/><br/>Finally, on the tech side, the 5.0 update will bring Frame Generation DLSS and FSR 3 support.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">AWARD NOMINATIONS</div><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> has been nominated in 2 categories at The Game Awards!<br/><br/>You can show your support and vote for us as Best Multiplayer Game and Best Action Game!<br/><br/>Also, we're so glad to announce that <i>Space Marine 2</i> has been nominated for the Steam Awards in the "Game Of The Year" category! ⚔️You can vote <b>here</b>.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/20277988624c0024db09d909f106d17100c7d3d7.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/19bac84722b4fd32d8fb4d2dd04526fd9abbeac5.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/55ade687a4f3888925d33d23c21db5275e32c40f.jpg"/></div></div></div><br/><div class="bb_h2">FANART CONTEST WINNER</div><br/>Huge congrats to @MendesWithAnS for winning the <i>Space Marine 2</i> fan art contest! Your work left us in awe! It really captures the essence of the Warhammer universe. This win is well-deserved, Brother! 🫡<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0e19ba47b6ef5ee9c7842ef2bdf63adf3b601f34.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mod Support - A Message From the Game Director</div><br/>In case you missed it, our Game Director expressed himself on the mod support on <i>Space Marine 2</i>. You’ll find the complete message <b>here</b>. In short, starting from the next update, mods will no longer be available in public PvE sessions, but will remain the private ones. <br/><br/><br/>That’s it for this month! Thanks again for sticking with us. See you again in December! ⚔️<br/><br/>The Emperor protects.<br/><br/><i>The Focus and Saber teams</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Sienna &amp; Poison Wind Globadier + Hotfix 6.0.7</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954130128</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>third</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div>You guys continue to smash through these! The target for the Community Challenge was surpassed in no time and so the community as a whole has unlocked the Ratling Gunner skin.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/3ea68ee2cab38208bfa5f32cd14e6778277ebc45.png"/><br/><br/>For everyone who played during the last spotlight, you've earned these goodies, depending on your playtime:<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/00b9b596726df042809c1735fe934ec9e09b57ad.png"/><br/>The rewards for the previous spotlight have just been delivered, so check your inventory! As a note, the Hero Pose might take a few restarts before it applies properly to your account. Sorry about that!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly through the Kill-Counter and personal rewards to unlock through a small ‘win-track’. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Sienna &amp; Poison Wind Globadier Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between November 28 - December 1.</b> All rewards will be granted the following week. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock an <b>exclusive skin for the Poison Wind Globadier.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Spotlight-track</div>Meanwhile, the win-track rewards will be unlocked depending on how much time you spend in Vermintide 2. Don’t worry, it won’t be too difficult, we promise. You can play Adventure, Chaos Wastes, Weaves, or Versus to unlock the rewards*. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/1d38639ce3b3183aabd68a633dde44cdc250bd55.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Playing for at least half an hour earns you 60 shillings.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least an hour earns you another 60 shillings as well as 30 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least two hours additionally earns you a brand new Portrait frame and 70 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least three hours additionally earns you a Hero Pose for Sienna!</li></ul><i>This playtime is tracked across all game modes, but is only tracked while in an actual match.</i><br/><br/><i>*You cannot actively check on your track progression. All rewards will be granted the following week</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Sienna</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/d8a983590b02a4604f47d39b982f1b0aeb025cdd.png"/><br/>Sienna Fuegonasus is an addict, forever torn between her will to control the destructive magics of Aqshy – the Wind of Fire – and a burgeoning desire to set the world alight for no other reason than the rush of magic in her bones. Another being might succumb to such temptations, and indeed, many have. But Sienna’s compassion and wry sense of humour keep her grounded.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about Sienna here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Poison Wind Globadier</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/ba6d0a80e74cf114a8f0a058d43a96c7ddf5fe5d.png"/><br/>Tattered robes and ramshackle gas masks grant Poison Wind Globadiers a sinister silhouette. This is a harbinger well-deserved, as are the rasp of rotting lungs and the acrid stench of warp-gas that sours the air about them.<br/>Globadiers care nothing for the lives of their fellow skaven, and will happily slaughter dozens of their own kind to fell a single foe. Life is cheap in the Under-Empire, and victory forgives all.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Poison Wind Globadier here!</b><br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.0.7 - 28th of November							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed an issue that made it so that Hero levels past 30 did not continue increasing the minimum item power from gear received from crafting, as introduced in a previous hotfix.</li></ul>	We've also applied all of the rewards from last week's spotlight! It might be necessary to restart the game a couple of times to get them applied, sorry about that!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Status update for the players who lost progression during the update:</div>Our Backend Service Provider have now confirmed that they are unable to restore/provide us with a snapshot of the missing account data, sadly. Though, we would like to reassure you that after working with them on this issue, new measures are in place that should a similar issue arise in future (we certainly hope not!) that we will have the necessary data backups in place.<br/><br/><b>What does this mean?</b><br/>We will be proceeding with our plan B to restore the missing account data.<br/><br/><b>What will Fatshark be doing?</b><br/>Our backend developers will be working with our analytics team to rebuild the missing account data ourselves, and then merge this into your current account data.<br/><br/><b>How long will this take?</b><br/>It's difficult to give an ETA currently, as our teams are planning the most effective way to proceed, and it is a lot of account data. We'll hopefully have a clearer idea of this soon, and will continue to communicate on the issue as regularly as we can.<br/><br/><b>Is it safe to continue playing on my account with missing progression?</b><br/>Yes. We will be merging the missing account data into your current data - so any recent progress should be kept.<br/><br/><b>Are there any risks?</b><br/>There is a small risk that merging the missing account data with current account data may lead to some slight discrepancies and cause minor elements of recent progression to be lost. Though, this would be far less than the current missing progression, and we will do our best to assist anyone should this happen. Though we will be doing all we can to best avoid this.<br/><br/>You can follow the status on this issue here: https://steamcommunity.com/app/552500/discussions/9/4631483655073586117/</blockquote>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction - Meet Skulltaker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4476109467940814902</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/bc590248b93bd851f5839c7a50bedb8e6376efb8.png"/><br/><br/>Ere, you lot! <br/><br/>The first of our Omens of Destruction Legendary Lord blogs is all about daemons, decapitation and hero-dueling as we cower before Khorne’s newest servant. Known as ‘the slayer of kings’, ‘the blooded wanderer’ and ‘Khorne’s champion’, Skulltaker is a character as infamous as he is deadly given his fearsome reputation for defeating the strongest foes throughout the world and adding their skulls to his cloak in an act of eternal torment.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Read the full blog here!</div><br/><br/>Join us tomorrow for the premiere of our first gameplay showcase where you'll get to see Skulltaker in action!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HSCGDfZnupk?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Next week we'll be back with our next blog focused on Golgfag Maneater and the changes coming to Ogre Kingdoms, so keep an eye on our channels for more!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord Bluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Sale 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4453592738017837701</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains and Crusaders!<br/><br/>The grand event of this fall has come — the Steam Autumn Sale is in full swing! Celebrate the arrival of winter in your favorite games and universes. Don’t miss this long-awaited event and explore the sales on Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous.<br/><br/>There’s no time to linger — the Steam Autumn Sale and the Steam Awards nominations will last only till December 4th! Learn about the awesome sales and nominate the games for the Award right now.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Just yesterday you were nothing, but fate ordered otherwise. Now you are the chosen one of the Emperor Himself, an explorer of the dark space, the ruler of an entire trade empire. You are a Rogue Trader. Choose the path you will take and lead your subjects and get Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader with a <b>40% discount</b>! Become a paragon of Humanity, a merciful leader, or bring chaos to the galaxy.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>The adventures in the Koronus Expanse don't have to end, because Your Lord or Ladyship still has much to do! Pay attention to what’s happening on your flagship, word in the compartments is something very dangerous is dwelling inside. Meet a new companion, try new archetypes, and eradicate the infection in the Void Shadows DLC, by getting the Season Pass at <b>40% off</b>. Moreover, you’ll get access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Your Rogue Trader deserves it. An alternative throne, Cherubim pet, a Firestorm-class frigate model, an epic weapon set, and digital add-ons (artbook, wallpaper set, game soundtrack) are waiting for you in the Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack with a <b>40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>Lead a new crusade against demons and protect the country of Mendev! Ten unique mythic paths, ten companions, twenty-five classes, and one hundred sixty archetypes are already waiting for you in the game. Get Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Enhanced Edition with a <b>70% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Get Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Game of the Year Edition with a <b>10% discount</b> and get the base game with all six premium expansions and four free DLCs available after the game's original release!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/sub/1171676/<br/><br/>Three major DLCs — Inevitable Excess, Through the Ashes, and The Treasure of the Midnight Isles are waiting for you in the Season Pass 1, which you can purchase with <b>70% off</b>! Continue your adventures in the lands of the World Wound!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Yet another three exciting DLCs are available as a part of the Season Pass 2 with a <b>50% discount</b>. The Last Sarkorians, The Lord of Nothing, and A Dance of Masks will completely change your game experience!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
