<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The big annual community survey is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/501699281359470977</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The big annual community survey is here!<br/><br/>Our proud parliament of owlcats keeps growing, with more amazing people joining us and sharing our passion for deep, story-rich games. We’d love to get to know you better! <br/><br/>Take part in this survey to help us understand our community and shape even more incredible projects together:<br/><br/>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/P9XHP2L]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your brief for the May Community Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500572747038984445</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Brace yourselves, Space Marines!</div><br/>The May Community Event starts on May 14 and ends on the 21st! <br/><b>Throughout the event, Requisition rewards are increased by 50% </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0c6aed77a0edc514b63620a6501272028dedf3be.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlesector &amp; Gladius will take part in Warhammer Skulls Festival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/511831746088536160</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We are excited to announce that <b>Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector &amp; Gladius</b> will be taking part in the Warhammer Skulls festival.<br/><br/>We can't wait to show you what is coming: The Warhammer Skulls showcase will begin on Thursday May 22nd 5pm UK time,  and the festival will last a whole week until Thursday May 29th.<br/><br/>Games Workshop is going to kickstart the festival with a showcase on their Twitch channel, so make sure to tune in on Warhammer Twitch channel at <b>5 pm BST on May 22nd</b>.<br/><br/>Discover more about the Warhammer Skulls festival here.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tune in at Skulls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520838945346423088</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cnS4KrViqyQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>Tune in during Skulls to find out what is coming next to Warhammer 40,000: Darktide! We cannot wait to reveal what we have in store for you!<br/><br/><b>May 22 - 18:00 CEST / 09:00 PT</b><br/><br/>http://twitch.tv/warhammer<br/>http://youtube.com/@officialwarhammer<br/><br/><b>Find out more about Skulls.</b><br/>-Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Void Meets The Hive – Darktide X Rogue Trader Crossover Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520837698904130286</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
A new trinket, a limited-time bundle, and a meeting across the 41st millennium. Starting April 30, we're celebrating the grimdark collision of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide and Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader! Fatshark and Owlcat Games are teaming up to bring a crossover event that nods to both games, and invites you deeper into the far corners of the 41st millennium.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Koronus Charm – Prestige of House Von Valancius</div>Adorn your gear with this relic of a noble lineage and show your allegiance aboard the Mourningstar.<br/><br/><br/>This ornately-wrought charm is thought to have once belonged to a prominent member of the storied Rogue Trader dynasty House Von Valancius. Though knowledge of its function has long been lost to posterity, whirring mechanisms can be heard inside if you listen closely. Players will simply have to log into Warhammer 40,000: Darktide from April 30, to claim their reward. <br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Sapper Shovel: A Symbol of Survival</div>Once wielded by the desperate Rejects of Atoma Prime in their fight against heresy, the Sapper Shovel now finds its way into the hands of a mighty Rogue Trader. Heavy, brutal, and unrelenting, this weapon is more than just a tool, it’s a testament to defiance in the face of annihilation. Players can claim this fearsome tool in the Upperway location in Act I. Those who progressed further in the game will be able to claim the item from their chest.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Limited-Time: The Void and Hive Crossover Bundle</div>For a limited time, you can grab both Darktide and Rogue Trader in a single bundle. Whether you're leading a rogue trader dynasty among the stars or carving through heretics in the hive, this is your chance to experience the Imperium from two very different fronts.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/53107]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
