<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Victor Saltzpyre &amp; Packmaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954130758</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>fourth</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun. This week's spotlight will be on good ol' One Eye <b>Saltzpyre</b> and the cruel <b>Packmaster!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div><b>An update on the way the rewards are handed out:</b><br/>Due to feedback from the community, as well as some technical issues on our end regarding this, we've decided to change how rewards for the Spotlight are given out.<br/><br/><b>All rewards for the spotlight will now be earned upon completion of the kill counter.</b> That means all of the currency, portrait frames and Hero poses will be unlocked for the community (alongside the Pactsworn skin, as before). <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/19dc4fb35544431416ee2b9e8fdf27660a633542.png"/><br/><b>This change is retroactive and will also affect the rewards of the first weeks of the spotlights.</b><br/><br/>The rewards for the previous spotlight have just been delivered, so check your inventory! As a note, the Hero Pose might take a few restarts before it applies properly to your account. Sorry about that!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly, all earned by the community as a whole through completion of the Kill-Counter. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Saltzpyre &amp; Packmaster Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between December 5 - December 8.</b> All rewards will be granted the following week.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>An exclusive skin for the Packmaster!</b><br/></li><li> <b>120 shillings.</b><br/></li><li> <b>100 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A brand new Portrait frame.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A Hero Pose for Saltzpyre!</b></li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/94aaeb04ac74619e028983a5fbc3b90728422f8d.png"/><br/><br/>Since all rewards are tied to the kill tracker, and since you've all been smashing through every target so far, we've decided to up the ante and increase the target kills from 40K Hero kills to 250K! Get crackin', players, that's a lot of Heroes to kill.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Victor Saltzpyre</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/89d0e4175586a7e1fae30ac1d0d28aa379dda7df.png"/><br/>For Victor, life has ever been a never-ending battle against heresy and destruction – the beleaguered Reikland is but a vaster stage upon which to strut his hour. Though it is hardly in Victor’s nature to trust such outcasts as are his companions in these dark days, he accepts that righteous work can sometimes be accomplished by stained souls and soiled hands.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about Victor Saltzpyre here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Packmaster</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/dc614ed00590381e3c2746c9e78af6084dcc48bb.png"/><br/>The Packmasters of Clan Moulder excel in driving packs of ravening beasts into battle, but in the crush of the swarm they favour other tactics. Clan Moulder is ever seeking new subjects to further its vile breeding experiments, and every Packmaster covets the bounty paid for a particularly noteworthy prize.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Packmaster here!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Golgfag Gameplay Showcase</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647305592</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Loud, Boastful, In-charge.<br/><br/>Become the greatest Mercenary and shape the outcome of conflicts across the world as Golgfag Maneater 👹<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AUGNU2wx0zw?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #54 (1.6.1) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317703</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6870f09498b86f6c0d9b088896a54fa9cd36e4d7.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>Hotfix #54 (1.6.1) is currently being rolled out across our platforms. You’ll find the patch notes below. <br/><div class="bb_h2">Havoc Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Temporary fix for the Error 9999 associated with Havoc.</li><li>If obtained, the Havoc Clearance Level will now be displayed in the Mourningstar over player characters instead of the Trust level.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Only for characters who have reached Trust level 30</li></ul><li>Fixed an issue where some text strings could be overlapping in the Mission Vote Details and the Tactical Overlay screens for Havoc missions.</li><li>Fixed an issue where several text strings could be overlapping in the Havoc terminal in some languages.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Commissar Dukane could fail to greet players when interacting with the Havoc terminal.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Commissar Dukane could repeat the first access greeting also on subsequent visits.</li><li>Added the Havoc rank unlock information to the rewards details of Maelstrom missions.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Only when interacting with the Mission Board while not having yet unlocked Havoc mode. Please note this will be fully implemented in 1.6.2 and a broken parameter will display.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added an objective marker to guide players to the Havoc terminal when first unlocking the game mode.</li><li>Added images behind the mutator tiles for the current Assignment in the Havoc terminal.</li><li>Updated the UI and animations when receiving a reward, a new assignment or a demotion after interacting with the Havoc terminal.</li><li>Updated the sound effects when navigating the UI in the Havoc terminal screens, and during the promotion and demotion animations.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Havoc icon would appear as misaligned in the mission lobby screen.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the objective to interact with the Havoc terminal to unlock the game mode could be displayed even if the player already interacted with it using a different character.</li><li>Fixed an issue where an incorrect Havoc Clearance Level update could be displayed in the End of Round screen after failing a Havoc Assignment.</li><li>Fixed an issue where some text strings in the Havoc terminal would appear in English also when playing in other languages.</li><li>Fixed bug where a second character was still asked to do the Havoc unlock quest after having already completed it on the first character.</li><li>Combined the end of round information for Havoc to one card.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash that could happen while using a Zealot Relic Blade when trying to interact with an object (e.g. a Medicae station battery) while in the Block animation.</li><li>Fixed a crash that could happen when accessing the Tactical Overlay if a temporary Event had expired in the same session.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the End of Round rewards could be skipped in rare situations when failing to retrieve the data for the participating players.</li><li>Fixed an issue where an incorrect generic Backend Error message was displayed to players who tried to access the game after having received a ban.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players revvin’ up any chain weapon and sawing could get stuck in the sawing animation for a short period.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Additionally, fixed an issue where the controller vibration would continue to play indefinitely for players who got disabled/downed during that period of time.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Play button in the Mission Board could occlude some of the mission details</li><li>Updated the gore settings restrictions applied to specific countries:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>(All platforms) Only for players in Germany and Austria, post-death Ragdoll Interaction will be disabled.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On death ragdoll and other gore settings will remain available.</li></ul><li>(Certain Consoles only) Only for players in Japan, the Blood Decals, Gibbing, Enemy Wounds and Ragdoll Interaction gore settings will be disabled.</li></ul></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the attachment point for weapon trinkets would be positioned incorrectly for the Double-Barreled Shotgun weapon skin obtained from its Mastery penance. </li><li>Fixed an issue where the attachment point for weapon trinkets would be positioned incorrectly for the Ogryn Heavy Stubber weapon skin obtained from its Mastery penance.</li><li>Fixed issues with certain hairstyles clipping on multiple mask-based Zealot cosmetic Penance headgears.  </li><li>Fixed an issue where the lower body would clip through select parts of the Veteran “Krieg Greatcoat (Krieg 143rd)” upperbody cosmetic.  </li><li>Tweaked some decals on the arms of the Ogryn “Krieg Greatcoat, XXXXL (Krieg 143rd)” upperbody cosmetics to remove thin white lines present on the sleeves.  </li><li>Fixed instances of hands clipping through the armwraps on the Zealot “Krieg Vigil Greatcoat (Krieg 143rd)” upperbody cosmetic.  </li><li>Fixed instances of hands clipping through the gloves on the Psyker “Storm Witch's Redemption Raiment” upperbody cosmetic.  </li><li>Polished up the fit on the Veteran “Flak Helmet (Tresian Night)” headgear cosmetic.  </li><li>The fire mode indicator on the Branx Minor Forge-Livery Boltgun skin should now properly light up.  </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Console Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added the Brightness and Motion Blur settings in the Video Options.</li><li> Fixed a rare issue where Imperial Edition content and/or Aquilas could fail to be redeemed when accessing the Mourningstar.</li><li> Fixed a rare crash which could happen if the player lost connection to the network while game data was being processed.</li><li> Fixed an issue where the game could fail to reconnect to the voice and text chat channels after console activity resumed from a Rest mode period.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live NOW - Cry Havoc!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317557</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Commissar Dukane has ordered the Warband to support the Moebian 53rd's latest offensive, so that untested fighters can be forged into reliable soldiers and soldiers into trustworthy veterans.<br/><br/>To celebrate the second anniversary of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, and the free update Grim Protocols, the game is hosting an event that will reward players with crafting materials - such as dockets, plasteel and diamantine - as well as a unique weapon trinket. To earn these rewards, players have to complete Havoc Missions or win a mission where at least one team member is below level 30. (by completing any mission in which any team member - including the player - levels up).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/348a6ce4a2681feae810c0225b860072caf2386a.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/72898b546bfe298a32f6c983e2867164068d0755.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 17:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havoc Update - Known Issues and Changes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317555</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/180e8ccebcbe8431233856e754a6cae1c42a9ec5.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"> December 4, 2024</div><div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Since the release of Grim Protocols and our new game mode Havoc yesterday, we’ve received reports from some players experiencing error 9999 and subsequently being unable to continue playing Havoc. We found a few reasons causing this lockout to happen, mostly related to team composition changing before the mission starts. <br/><br/><b>We have implemented a temporary fix that will prevent this error 9999 from happening. </b><br/>This is a temporary fix that might have unintended effects. We are working on a more complete fix which we are aiming to have fully implemented for Hotfix 1.6.2 next week.<br/><br/>We’ll be continuing to monitor the situation to ensure everyone can boot up and take on the challenge of Havoc. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2"> December 3, 2024</div><div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Thank you to everyone jumping into Grim Protocols. We’ve been reviewing the comments from all the players who are trying out Havoc and we’ve made a tweak on something. <br/><br/>To unlock Havoc, players are required to play a Maelstrom mission. If they play an Auric Maelstrom, they are boosted to Assignment Rank 10. <br/><br/>We’ve been monitoring feedback and we don’t believe this boost was enough. <b>We’ve made a change to the backend where players who complete an Auric Maelstrom are now boosted to Assignment Rank 16. If you’ve already been boosted to Rank 10, you should be able to play another Auric Maelstrom to boost to Rank 16.</b><br/>We chose Assignment Rank 16 because that is the level Auric Intensity is activated with the Emperor’s Fading Light. <br/><br/>To support the different skill levels that might be able to complete a Havoc-equivalent Maelstrom mission, we don’t want to boost too high. Some players who complete an Auric Maelstrom mission might’ve thought it was easy, while others struggled through it. <br/><br/>We’ll be continuing to monitor players to see if this is an adequate boost in levels or not. We’ll be monitoring the other feedback for Havoc, as well. <br/><br/>P.S. If you are having trouble finding parties for Havoc, make sure to select E in the Party Finder to clear your selected tags. We’ve found some players have tags selected that are mutually exclusive from Havoc and it prevents them from seeing the open parties. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
