<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Titus Talks: Episode 3 is here... and it's about Space Marine 2!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696781406112877915</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!!</div><br/>The grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000 can be daunting to dive into! This is why we're are thrilled to introduce the second episode of the “Titus Talks” a 3-part video series presented by Lieutenant Titus himself, Clive Standen, and dedicated to welcoming newcomers to the rich expanse that is the 41st millennium. ✨<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Watch Episode 3: What is <i>Space Marine 2</i>?</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8uRz5UBuZaQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">This episode focuses on introducing players to game itself.</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> What is the backstory of Titus from <i>Space Marine 1</i>? <br/></li><li> What is Space Marine 2's gameplay like? <br/></li><li> Once I'm done with the campaign, what are mulitplayer modes like? </li></ul>Presented by Clive Standen, who voices Lieutenant Titus in the game, today’s video lecture is the conclusion to a three part series you can find on the Focus Entertainment YouTube channel.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/95c6c33219c5664bd4a2cc2f61e9ba8fb83754bb.png"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available now on PC. Get the Gold or Ultra Editions to secure your Season Pass!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>To get the latest info about <i>Space Marine 2</i>, follow our socials and:<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's dedicated on Focus Together<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's Discord server]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209662413241</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f10181aa79fa2bdf71a6979ab8aee441f9ed739d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) is now live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added Penances for completing the Rolling Steel mission and for completing Operations missions.</li><li>Added a shortcut to the Party Finder menu from the mission board.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the game could fail to retrieve the latest Mastery data from the backend when opening the Loadout screens.</li><li>Removed the “Stand By For Action” and “Rapid Response” penances, which were incorrectly added with the 1.5.0 release.</li><li>Fixed an issue where both marks of the Assault Chainsword family could be purchased from Brunt’s Armoury when playing as Veteran.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “new” marker could be displayed incorrectly in the Masteries menu.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Blessings could still be purchased while hidden when the focus was on the lower rewards track.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Power Rating value for Curios could be incorrectly displayed in the Emperor’s Gift tile after completing a mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Sort by Name” feature was not correctly sorting items.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the selection focus could be missing when performing operations in the Discard and Sacrifice screens while playing on controller.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the weapon name could overlap with other text and UI elements in the Sacrifice screen.</li><li>Tweaked the icon for the selected weapon in the Sacrifice screen to be slightly smaller.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the tooltip for the Frame Generation could display undefined text.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the coat of the Darinda Dukane NPC could clip with the legs.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the weapon cosmetic obtained from the Power Sword Mastery penance was missing the rarity and “obtained from” information.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Rolling Steel Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a rare server and client crash which could happen in the Rolling Steel mission when a player joined the mission while no other players were alive.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when pressing the “-” key in specific moments during the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Tweaked the matchmaking values to avoid players joining too close to the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is to limit the chance of joining an already ongoing mission, without the ability to affect the success of it due to the timer already being close to expiring.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed so that in the Rolling Steel mission no success audio effects are triggered when destroying the cogitators in the last carriage after the mission timer had expired.</li><li>Tweaked the spawn locations of the batteries in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where parts of the geometry would still shake after the train was stopped.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where players could clip through closed doors before completing the related minigame.</li><li>Fixed instances where pickups could be clipping with the geometry in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an instance of missing hang ledges in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where rain could fall inside the locomotive at the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Tweaked geometry on a ramp in the Rolling Steel mission to make it easier to navigate.</li><li>Fixed an issue where bots could fail to properly board the extraction Valkyrie at the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the thruster VFX from the enemy Valkyrie could remain visible even after it went away.</li><li>Tweaked the fade to the Valkyrie cutscene after winning the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where multiple characters could share the same seat in the Valkyrie cutscene after winning the mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed some mask clipping issues on the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burnt Sulphur” and “Illius Noctis Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetics</li><li>Fixed some issues where the tubes from the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic would clip with high-collared upper bodies .</li><li>Fixed an issue where some beards would clip through the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic would clip with lower bodies while in the operative screen.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the shoulder area of the “Kinetic Witch’s Redemption Raiment” upper body cosmetic could look deformed on female characters.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li><b>Mastery Level Value is Missing in The Marks Swap Screen</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>When in the Marks swap screen, the Mastery level value required to obtain locked Marks may fail to be correctly displayed.</li><li>The issue is only visual, and the locked Marks will be correctly available upon reaching the required Mastery level in the weapon family.</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Information in the Sacrifice Weapon Screen Tooltip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The tooltip in Sacrifice Weapon screen incorrectly states that only Anointed (blue) rarity weapons (or higher) are able to be sacrificed.</li><li>The issue is only in the tooltip text, as the minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li>This is a rounding issue, however the actual stats total will always effectively be 380 for all weapons.</li></ul></li><li><b>Auspex Tooltip in Rolling Steel Localization Issue</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The “Move” text in the HUD tooltip when using an Auspex for the new hacking minigame in the Rolling Steel will appear localised in English but is missing in other languages.</li></ul></li><li><b>Zealots are Unable to Purchase Recon Lasgun from Brunt’s Armoury</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Zealots are currently unable to purchase Recon Lasguns from Brunt’s Armoury.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Warp Unbound Having Inconsistent Activations (Added after original post)</b>:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>The "Warp Unbound" Psyker talent is not working correctly when using the Electokinetic and Inferno staves, as a Perils of the Warp explosion may still be atriggered while the talent is active.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>"Kinetic Flayer" Psyker Talent (Added after original post)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The "Kinetic Flayer" Psyker talent is not working correctly as it can still be triggered by enemies that are not Specialist, Elites or Monstrosities."</li></ul></li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.2.1.12 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805561491109</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! A new hotfix is deployed, to deal with some more of the reported issues.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Consoles will receive the same update within ~24 hours.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Sometimes the Rogue Trader's voidship could lose the capability to move and use weapons or could use movement and weapons indefinitely, instead - fixed;<br/></li><li> Characters could become stuck after using the Veil of Blades ability - fixed;<br/></li><li> Under certain circumstances, an existing saved game could be converted into Grim Darkness mode, which shouldn't have been possible - fixed;<br/></li><li> Death from Above ability sometimes failed to deal damage - fixed;<br/></li><li> Wildfire sometimes didn't reduce the AP cost of attacks as intended - fixed;</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805557883738</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>We’re proud to inform all of you that we’re participating in <b>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</b> which has already begun! Be sure not to miss this entertaining event, as well as pleasant discounts on our titles - <b>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</b> and <b>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous</b>!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c5109ca10883ecfe4e76748b32c1258dc786545c.jpg"/><br/>There’s no time to waste, explore the event right now. Note that the Fest will be held till October 7th!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>The grim and dark universe of Warhammer has never been so close. Don’t miss your chance to grab the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game with <b>40% off</b>! It’s time to guide your people through the challenges of the Koronus Expanse!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Get the Season Pass and try the just-released first DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader – Void Shadows! Explore the sinister secrets of your voidship with a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Get Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock unique in-game items, digital add-ons, and the legendary voidship model!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>A journey full of danger, new friends, and foes lies ahead! Feel the true RPG experience and embark on a mission to save the world from a great peril in Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous with a <b>70% discount</b>. Choose your path in the story and explore where it leads you!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Unlock the ultimate experience of three DLCs full of new content by getting Season Pass 1 at a <b>70% discount</b>. Make your Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous unforgettable.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>The more DLCs, the merrier! Another three DLCs can be obtained as a part of the Season Pass 2 with <b>50% off</b>! Continue your journey as the Knight Commander, meet new companions, and explore new archetypes!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Please note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grim Darkness Challenge comes!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805558231855</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>To celebrate the launch of the Void Shadows DLC and the introduction of Grim Darkness (“Ironman”) Mode for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, Owlcat Games is happy to announce a large competitive event: <b>The Grim Darkness Challenge!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is The Grim Darkness Challenge?</div><br/>It is an intense competitive event for streamers, where, over the course of two weeks, participants will compete live in beating (or making it as far as they can in!) Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader on <b>Daring difficulty in Grim Darkness mode</b> - a newly introduced brutal gameplay mode where only a single save is allowed and is rewritten every time a player exits the game. All decisions and consequences in this mode are final, reloading is impossible, and if the party is defeated—the game is over!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Registration</div><br/>In order to participate, you need to either be a streamer that is already a part of our partnership program Owlmates, or have a channel on Youtube or Twitch with at least 5000 subscribers and a reasonable number of views on recent videos. We’re ready to discuss corner cases (for example, some leeway may be given to non-English-speaking streamers with national audiences), but also reserve the right to deny registration without explanation if we consider it necessary.<br/><br/>For registration and all questions, contact Owlcat CM Starrok (Starrok on Discord or u/OwlcatStarrok on Reddit), or Owlcat CM Nathillien (Nathillien on Discord or u/OwlcatNathillien on Reddit).<br/><br/>Registration will remain open until October 14.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Victory conditions</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Winner is determined by beating the game or reaching the furthest Act without the player’s party ever being defeated.<br/></li><li> If multiple players have reached the same act or have beaten the game, tiebreakers are resolved by the number of quests completed (you can check completed quests in the journal).<br/></li><li> If still tied, the victory is determined in favor of the player who spent the least in-game time on their playthrough. </li></ul><br/>The challenge will begin on <b>00:00 GMT October 22</b>, and last for 2 weeks until <b>23:59 GMT November 4</b>, or until all players have successfully completed their playthroughs or were eliminated. <br/><br/>And remember: in the Grim Darkness of the far future, there is only one winner, and their feat will be rewarded with a unique prize!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">In-game Rules</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Grim Darkness mode must be enabled;<br/></li><li> Daring Difficulty must be enabled;<br/></li><li> Void Shadows DLC must be installed and enabled;<br/></li><li> All free and cosmetic DLCs can be enabled;<br/></li><li> Any background or character-selection choices are allowed;<br/></li><li> Any ship type is allowed;<br/></li><li> Only single player is allowed;<br/></li><li> No mercenaries are allowed (only story companions);<br/></li><li> No mods can be used;<br/></li><li> It is prohibited to shutdown or alter the game in any way in order to prevent a death, make a different choice, or redo a skillcheck. Live with the consequences of your choices!</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Technical Requirements</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After each game session, the participant must upload the following stats to the provided Discord channel:<br/>- Time played this session;<br/>- Total time played in campaign;<br/>- Current Act # reached<br/>- Number of completed quests (visible in the quest log)<br/>- Party setup that was used most of the time for this session (companions and archetypes). Builds don't need to be uploaded, but must be available on request.<br/><br/></li><li> Playthroughs must happen strictly LIVE, with the streams and their records saved in case a need arises to check them. If you have connection issues, please save the game and continue when your connection is restored.<br/><br/></li><li> All participants must manually make a backup of their save after every session (by default it is located in C:\Users\ <username> \AppData\LocalLow\Owlcat Games\Warhammer 40000 Rogue Trader) to prevent unexpected progress loss due to power outages, Steam Cloud issues, bugs, and other force majeure factors.<br/><br/></username></li><li> If continuing or finishing the playthrough is impossible due to a non-gameplay related reason (a bug, power failure, hardware or software issues, etc.), contact the organizers. We may be able to let you continue from a previous backed-up save or restart the game, depending on the circumstances.<br/><br/></li><li> We strongly urge all participants to use the #GrimDarknessChallenge hashtag in their media.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Cheating and Exploits</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It is forbidden to exploit bugs and a clearly unintended use of game mechanics to gain a gameplay advantage. If you are in doubt as to whether the situation can be classified as such, contact the organizers.<br/></li><li> No mods or external software may be used to modify the game or save or to alter them in any way.</li></ul><br/>Participants who break any of the rules above may be disqualified at the organizers' discretion.<br/><br/>Good luck!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
