<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Bomb Rush - Timed Mode 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4550415957644981246</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks, time for some firewerkz!</b><br/><br/>For this weekend, we've a new Limited Time Event game mode, Bomb Rush, <br/><br/>Bomb Rush is Kill Konvoy with the bomb spawn rate turned up by x4!<br/><br/>This is an extra, optional game mode that sees players constantly racing to reach new bombs and detonating them on the enemy Stompa. It's much a faster paced game mode where defence is much more difficult, but speed and racing provide more of the focus.<br/><br/>This mode will apply to all 8vs.8 Kill Konvoy maps and will end on Monday <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2c4494b2dea4a5c3d9b764ca454c1d2fc66c6461.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! <br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4472730495692570698</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines! 🫡</div><br/>This month we released new content: the new Termination map and the new Lethal difficulty. We’ve loved seeing you provide feedback and challenge yourself with the new difficulty. We also took into account the constructive criticism and have implemented some balancing features and tweaks into the game. We truly hope you’re enjoying the game.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">4.5 M PLAYERS 🎊</div><br/>Let’s start this off with great news: we are now over 4 and a half million Space Marines defending the Imperium!<br/><br/>Seeing the community grow so wide, so fast, makes us incredibly proud. We’re working hard to provide new content for you, listening closely to your feedback, and we cannot wait for you to discover what’s next for <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>! <br/><br/>So, thank you, four and a half million times 💙<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/45d0ddb201ff3076925d7d50bab0eaa025335886.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">IMPROVEMENTS BROUGHT TO THE GAME</div><br/>As for every single release, we closely read the feedback from the players. Therefore, we’ve seen that the new content did not meet everyone’s expectations and that the adjustments disappointed many of you.<br/><br/>To make amends and fix the issues that Patch 4.0 brought, we released a hotfix (4.1), which you may find right here. It brings gameplay and balancing tweaks on weapons, difficulty, AI and much more. Make sure you read the patch note! ⚙️<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">UPCOMING CONTENT</div><br/>Another update is coming soon with a brand new weapon: The Neo-Volkite Pistol! <br/><br/>The Neo-Volkite Pistol is a thermal weapon with accumulative damage. Its heat rays have a deadly impact on organic matter, incinerating flesh into ash with explosive force and jets of flame. A weapon of choice against Tyranids! ☢️🔥<br/>The Bulwark, Assault and Vanguard will have access to the Neo-Volkite as a secondary weapon.<br/><br/>On top of this addition, this update will also come with buffs for several firearms.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f182956c202bc3bccf61cc89a68d1560ae830eda.gif"/><br/><br/>Later this year – around early-December – will come the much awaited<b> Dark Angel Chapter Pack</b>, along with a new enemy, the Tzaangor Enlightened and a new PvE map set on Demerium: “Obelisk”.<br/><br/>On another note, we’ve seen your feedback about “Blocking” weapons feeling unsatisfying to play with, and are currently in the process of reworking them!<br/><br/>Be patient Marines!<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39308af705c0b0ffd996813ea1e63517d7240aba.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/dc429323ea2a1546c6cc36077ac8fb4c0b132860.gif"/></div> </div></div><div class="bb_h2">YOUR IDEAS</div><br/>You are constantly submitting new ideas on Focus Together to our great delight. Let’s answer some of them:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CONTENT ADDITIONS</div><br/><b>New Melee weapons</b><br/>→  Adding a new melee weapon is something we’d love to have later. However, it also takes a lot of time and production resources to integrate. Be sure that we’ll let you know once we’re more advanced on that subject.<br/><br/><b>More Campaign missions</b><br/>→ We’re currently not thinking about adding new campaign missions in Space Marine 2. We rather focus on creating new Operations and Eternal War content.<br/><br/><b>Eternal war party size</b><br/>→ We’re currently working on implementing custom PvP lobbies. You’ll be able to invite your friends, alongside various other options to customise your experience (score limit, time limit, class limit and so on)..<br/><br/><b>Heretic Astartes playable in Operations</b> <br/>→ This will not be implemented due to Space Marine 2's specific setting, how Operations are designed and even the game as a whole. All of the dialogue is written as Astartes talking to other Astartes for example. Missions are also designed so that our characters fight to help the Imperium's war effort.<br/><br/><b>Add the possibility to replay the Campaign Prologue</b><br/>→ Whilst not a priority at the moment, this is something we might consider in the future.<br/><br/><b>Consider adding a bonus reward for players using quickmatch</b><br/>→ This is something we are considering adding in the future.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CUSTOMISATION</div><br/><b>Colour lenses</b><br/>→ We are ready to release the colour lenses with the next big update, which will bring the Dark Angels Chapter Pack.<br/> <br/><b>More than 4 customisation slots</b><br/>→ This is not a priority right now, we prefer to focus on developing other features at the moment. We’ll come back later on this.<br/><br/><b>Customisation add-ons</b><br/>→ More customisation will come in the future. More precise customisation options is a must have as well.<br/><br/><b>More helmet customisation and patterns</b><br/>→ This is something we’re actively working on. It will arrive in the lifespan of the game.<br/><br/><b>Ability to recolor cloth pieces / tabards</b><br/>→ We can consider adding this option later down the line. But creating a satisfying level of quality for this feature is harder than it looks.<br/> <br/><b>Lieutenant colour customisation</b><br/>→ This has been greenlit. More customisation is coming for helmets, corresponding to other Chapters.<br/><br/><b>Change the skin colour of your Marine</b><br/>→ We’re currently working on an option to add head customisation to your Space Marines.<br/><br/><b>Allow Deathwatch icons to be placed on the right shoulder</b><br/>→ Yes, this is something already in the works.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">LET’S CELEBRATE HALLOWEEN 🩸🕷️</div><br/>Our VP community is very prolific so let's do a quick shoutout to some creators, by highlighting the GORE in <i>Space Marine 2</i>!!<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Titus crushing Tyranids as a Deathwatch warrior, shot by @JoniTrasel on X.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6fa155144e88d8bf98a0606862e4460187858626.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">In the midst of a battle on Avarax, Titus strikes a pose among his victims. Shot by @MaraKnightVP on X</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1d270b1a5660c432472a38340b3dc8cadc38e0e8.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">@Selka_VP shared this shot of Titus ripping a Lictor in half! How cool.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e4cfdef589e0bb27ac3124f99ee170cd32d3d3e1.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Last but not least: A Helbrute covered in organic matter while getting slayed by a Space Marine. Shared by @foxhoundrep on Discord.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c29de88392942b9bf9299a6412622550cb65a8d9.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">THAT’S IT FOR OCTOBER 🦇 </div><br/>To keep yourself updated on the latest news about Space Marine 2, make sure you sign up to Focus Together! And join an already-wide community of players on the official Discord!<br/><br/>See you next time.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For The Emperor. ⚔️</div><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 5.3 LIVE NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4532401922169036853</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/180c2dd62b5276afc0d59af5e57b941107e00cc6.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/><b>​Patch 5.3.0</b> for Total War: WARHAMMER III is now live!<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tackle your monsters head on with the Grave Guard (Halberds) free unit for vampire counts.<br/></li><li> Ogre camps now offer more varied units for hire depending on their tier.<br/></li><li> Find 16 new Magic Items for ranged characters and 6 new zesty unique ancillaries for everyone else!</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉Read the full 5.3 patch notes here👈</div><br/><br/>Thank you for your continuous support. If you run into any issues after updating to 5.3, please be sure to report them in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum. See you on the battlefield! <br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Patch 5.6.0 - Geheimnisnacht &amp; Double XP Live now! + Hotfix 5.6.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4465975096247320629</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h2">Hotfix 5.6.1 - November 4th</div><div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash when cancelling Host Migration.</li></ul> </blockquote><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><br/>The most ill-omened night of the year is finally upon us! The green glow of Morrslieb in full moon heralds it: Geheimnisnacht has arrived!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Geheimnisnacht event</div><b>Starting today and until November 10th,</b> there will be Double XP for all actions taken in Vermintide 2, along a spooky makeover of the Keep, new challenges and rewards for Geheimnisnacht, and the return of old Geheimnisnacht rewards in exchange for shillings at Lohner's Emporium! For more details, please read the original announcement here:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4512135360811161102<br/><br/>But to sum up, play the event, complete the challenges, earn the rewards, have fun!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Developer Stream - 17:00 CET today!</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/3a4155fda824b438280f9fdd34da2d9b27ca56ec.png"/><br/>Join us <b>today at 17:00 CET</b> on <b>our Twitch!</b> <br/><br/>We'll be hosting a stream with Developers Tom, Emil and Theodor to celebrate Geheimnisnacht and talk about upcoming changes to Vermintide, including the upcoming Progression &amp; New Player Experience rework that will arrive with Versus!<br/><br/>Come hang out and ask questions or just chill with us! Looking forwards to seeing you all there!<br/><br/>Without further ado...<br/> <div class="bb_h2">	Patch 5.6.0 Patch Notes		</div> <br/> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks		</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Enabled the Geheimnisnacht event and Keep decorations.								<br/><i>The Skull of Blosphoros will be active in the following locations:	</i> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>	Against the Grain		</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>	Athel Yenlui		</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>	A Parting of the Waves		</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>	Convocation of Decay		</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>	Halescourge		</b> </li></ul></li><li>	Enabled double XP for the duration of the event.							<br/> </li><li>	Added the rewards from previous Geheimnisnacht in-game events to Lohner's Emporium of Wonders.	</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes		</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed bot priorities not saving when exiting the game.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where players would not get that week's rewards after a Host Migration during a Chaos Wastes Weekly Expedition								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed some Cataclysm challenges not being greyed out in Okri's book for players who don't own the Winds of Magic DLC.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Outcast Engineer's talent 'Ingenious Ordnance' would exit cooldown early. Woops.							<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	More changes to come!</li></ul></li><li>	Fixed bosses not taking damage from Ungor archer arrows. Now only player controlled bosses are immune to friendly projectiles. That friendly fire was a bit TOO friendly.								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	This also makes it possible to complete the related Minotaur challenge once again.					</li></ul></li><li>	Remastered the dialogue for Drachenfels and Dark Omens to fix a few audio issues and to bring the quality in line with other level VO.</li></ul> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commissar Report I &amp; II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157956347822483</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<i><div class="bb_h3">[1]<br/>MILITARUM WARZONE MISSIVE ALPHA-ONE<br/>TO: Astra Militarum (Moebian) Command Staff<br/>FROM: Dukane, D. Commissar<br/>++via astro-node x-sym-226-aleph++</div></i><br/><br/>My honoured lords militant. I am now in rapid transit to the capital world Atoma Prime, lacking as I am updated orders from you. I intend to build upon the instructions you have already blessed me with, which is to say to inject fire and disciplined determination into our beleaguered forces in the face of this wretched traitor uprising.<br/>	There is no time to regroup for direct consultation. In the last few months (relative) the Traitorous 6th have committed sundry crimes of violence and treachery across the Domain. This would be unacceptable from any adversary, but when this horror is perpetrated by soldiers of the Astra Militarum, it is a crime and an outrage against our highest honour. I do not have the words to express my disgust. These were our own people. <br/>	The 53rd Steelheads are proud soldiers, impeccable in their loyalty. Moreover, as I need not remind you, they are Branx-born. Like their birth world, they are young and aspirational. Atoma Prime has ruled the Domain for too long. It has grown fat and lazy, and slumped into privileged corruption. How else can one explain the gross deviation of their infamous 6th? Atoma, and the Lord Margrave, has allowed this treason to breed. Yes, Atoma must be freed and delivered. Yes, the traitors must be expunged without delay. But beyond that, I believe that the ancient hive must be soundly purged. The uprising must be put down and the enemy eradicated, but the soil from which this infamy sprang must also be cleansed with fire. <br/>	It must be the Astra Militarum that achieves this. I trust, my lords, that you will concur with my intent. The direct military deployment of the Steelheads, their honour bruised and their pride mauled, is the most expedient solution, and it is the most just. Let us clean our own house. Let the Guard restore its own dignity. <br/>	I am told, by coded transmission, that an Inquisitorial warband leads the reclamation effort on Atoma. On the one hand, I am reassured by this. On the other, I am dismayed by the lack of material strength. A warband is merely paramilitary. This outrage requires a response of the full force of the Astra Militarum on a formal war footing. Rest assured that, under my direction, the 53rd will execute the matter with the strictest and most steadfast discipline, a credit to the Throne and the Aquila banner.<br/>	I invite your response and instruction, but until any such is received, I will press on with my intent as stated above and bring legitimate war and restored honour to the hive of Atoma.  The Emperor protects, and the Guard prevails. <br/><br/>[affirmed by my sigil] - Dukane.    <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><i><div class="bb_h3">[2]<br/>MILITARUM WARZONE MISSIVE ALPHA-TWO<br/>TO: Astra Militarum (Moebian) Command Staff<br/>FROM: Dukane, D. Commissar<br/>++via astro-node z-ki-787-talos++</div></i><br/><br/>My honoured lords militant. Upon Atoma, in the great and ancient hive of Tertium, things are worse than we feared. The Traitor forces, all soldiers of the once vaunted Moebian 6th, now deplorably transformed by heresy and corruption, have wrought great damage and hardship and, further, have claimed significant areas of territory. <br/>I have conferred with the Inquisitorial undertaking, in the person of one Rannick (though not directly with their Inquisitor himself, an individual known as Grendyl). I fear this Grendyl may be trying to keep me and the Steelheads at arm’s length, out of concern that we might fall as the 6th fell. The Ordos clearly have little faith in the Astra Militarum. Rannick, for his part, insists to me that the corruption of the very Warp itself has lodged within the hearts of the traitors, and that we face a foe empowered by forces beyond mortal limit. I remain unconvinced. I believe we face an enemy driven by disdain, by privation, and by idolatry, and an enemy that has been allowed to breed thanks to the venal weakness of a hive and a ruling society that has fallen prey to its own luxuriating entitlement. I have declared to Rannick that the Steelheads are born of greater mettle, and thus can be fully trusted, for they are not prey to such infantile whimsy.<br/>	Of the Inquisitorial warband itself, I have little to remark. They are, for the most part, thugs and rejects, who seem little better or more disciplined than the very traitors we combat. They are ill-tempered, and regulation-shy. They are not soldiers, and they certainly lack the numerical strength to achieve any lasting compliance. Further, their loyalty to the Throne appears shabby and forced, not bright and willing as is the case with the Astra Militarum Steelheads. I will, in fairness and balance, record that this “warband” has fought hard and at great cost thus far, achieving some gains against the enemy. But it is not enough, and they are not enough, and I fear that their morale will soon snap as thoroughly as the loyalty of the Traitorous 6th. I will take field command of their endeavours, and have my trusted sergeants train their rabble squads to something approaching military composure.<br/>	This is a perilous situation. For all its wrongs and its canker, Atoma cannot be allowed to fall and give this enemy a foothold in the Domain. The Emperor protects, and in his name, the Steelheads will prevail. <br/><br/>[affirmed by my sigil] - Dukane.  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Interested in learning more about Commissar Dukane? Check out our latest Vox Intercept</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fZqECA5-Rx8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><b>Don't forget to <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="The URL that was linked here has been removed by our filters.  Usually this is done to prevent phishing and malware attacks.">{LINK REMOVED}</span>join our newsletter to stay up to date with all things Darktide!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 19:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
