<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Advanced Movement Guide ⚡</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162780106167</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Check out this guide to Mork-like movement:</div>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eZrD_dFJZC8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>Jon, Lead Game Designer, takes you through some of his top tricks and tips to speedin' with style.<br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.2 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4272313336331763397</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/c1ea5e7215dc0e25afbd65ccb03858663af4248f.png"/><br/><br/>​​Hi everyone!<br/><br/>I'm Mitchell Heastie, Design Director on Total War: WARHAMMER III, and today I want to share with you some of the things I've been working on. This will be a developer diary that gives you a look into what is coming as part of Patch 5.2 and this time around I'll also talk a little bit wider than that about what to expect going forward for our updates and how you can help shape them.<br/><br/>First though a bit of backstory. When I think back to the very first DLC we ever made for the Total War: WARHAMMER trilogy, Call of the Beastmen, there was a moment where Rich and I discussed adding the moon cycle mechanic to the race. At the time this seemed like a tiny addition, and indeed it was compared to the kind of features we do now, but I always consider that moment monumental as for me it was the first instance of us pushing a boundary, trying to do something a little bit different that we hadn't done before, to add more than was originally planned, and we did it just because it was cool, we thought players would like it and we wanted the DLC to be as special as it could be.<br/><br/>I think it's that moment that set us on a path to try to do more for all new content, to keep pushing our own expectations for what new content for the game could be, to always be on the lookout for what special idea we could do next, and I really do believe it's that precedent that created a mindset for what got us here now with the absolutely insane scale of content we have. This way of working, to always be pushing, meant that over the years we tried a lot of new things, some that didn't work so well, others that were massive successes, but all the while our content was growing in scope and complexity, and we were learning.<br/><br/>This you will all know by now has had a few effects; I think our content got better over time, which is fantastic, but this improvement has meant that the content we created in the past grows more outdated as time progresses, either because it was made without the knowledge, lessons, or technology we now have. This is where your, and our, desire for the old content to be reworked or updated comes from - not failure, but progress and success. It's something we've been cognizant of for a long time, hence our many reworks and updates, and it's something we want to continue to do going forward.<br/><br/>I think it's a blessing to be able to have such a vivid view of how you as a designer, and as a team, have improved in your craft over the better part of a decade, but of course that does mean we have some work to do. Let's talk about that work.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3"><b>📜 Read full 5.2 Dev Blog here</b></div></div><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Archetypes in the Void Shadows DLC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4265557936889641697</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
In the upcoming DLC, the Lord Captain will come face to face with an Imperial Death Cult. These masters of assassination demonstrate their devotion to the God-Emperor by studying every facet and aspect of death: their grotesque rituals and bloody sacrifices conceal, like a sheath, the sophisticated art of slaughter's honed blade. To understand first-hand the lethal grace of their craft, simply examine the arsenal of abilities possessed by Kibellah — a Death Cult representative seeking to join your retinue. The new archetypes available at character creation were specifically designed to reflect the terrifying efficiency of the Death Cult.<br/><br/>Let's take a closer look at the new archetypes in the Void Shadows DLC: the first-tier archetype — the <b>Bladedancer</b> and the second-tier archetype — the <b>Executioner</b>. Both are primarily focused on attributes desirable for any melee combatant. These new archetypes not only complement each other excellently but also open up numerous lucrative synergies with existing character-build options.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"><b>Bladedancer</b></div><br/><b>Available Second-Tier Archetypes: </b>Assassin, Master Tactician, Arch-Militant, Executioner.<br/><b>Characteristics: </b>Weapon Skill, Strength, Toughness, Agility.<br/><b>Skills: </b>Athletics, Medicine, Carouse, Awareness, Demolition.<br/><br/>The Bladedancer is an elusive acrobat, skillfully manoeuvring through the battlefield in a deadly dance. With each kill, they gain charges of<b> Death From Above</b>: an ability allowing the Bladedancer to perform a short jump, dealing damage to all enemies in the impact zone. <b>Death From Above</b> damage scales with Agility and Weapon Skill. If such a display of prowess isn't enough, the <b>Death Waltz </b>heroic act enables the Bladedancer to repeat this pirouette multiple times in succession: the more Agility the character has, the longer they can continue this dance of death. And when deep behind enemy lines, completely surrounded, the Bladedancer can effortlessly return to the cell where they began their turn by utilising the<b> Acrobatic Artistry</b> ability, leaving bewildered foes unable to punish the bladedancer’s incisive incursions. This impressive arsenal will satisfy anyone looking for ease of strategic positioning and manoeuvrability across the battlefield, such as a Master Tactician or Arch-Militant.<br/><br/>But what if the "death" in <b>Death Waltz </b>attracts you more than the "dance?" The Bladedancer is ready to shed blood, whether it be that of their enemies, allies, or even their own. Performing a blood sacrifice, forfeiting their own life force, the Bladedancer strikes swiftly and precisely, critically injuring their foes. This deadly focus can also serve as a defensive measure: the Bladedancer's mastery with two-handed and dual-wielded swords is so great that they can conceal themselves in a literal <b>Blade Shroud</b>, reflecting incoming shots back at their enemies, albeit at the cost of overstraining and damaging themselves.<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/827877966616854558/1273203232520404993/reaper-2.gif?ex=66bdc269&amp;is=66bc70e9&amp;hm=08c0695f86290252e0f3f200a518fde87c53e05b61a2bc6932ee7b49faaabdb1&amp;"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"><b>Executioner</b></div><br/><b>Available First-Tier Archetypes: </b>Warrior, Operative, Bladedancer.<br/><b>Characteristics: </b>Weapon Skill, Strength, Toughness, Intelligence.<br/><b>Skills: </b>Athletics, Medicine, Lore (Imperium), Lore (Xenos).<br/><br/>This archetype is available to Warriors, Operatives, or Bladedancers who revel in the heart-wrenching screams of their victims. The Executioner specialises in manipulating damage-over-time effects, vastly increasing their potency and converting them into debilitating injuries. Each of the Executioner's strikes is meticulously calculated to maximise the deadliness of afflictions on their enemies: comprehensive knowledge of anatomy allows this gruesome warrior to dismantle foes piece by piece, deepening lacerations and intensifying haemorrhaging as their knowledge of Medicine increases.<br/><br/>The Executioner is perfect for characters with the Biomancer or Pyromancer Psyker origins. Connoisseurs of incendiary bombs, toxic grenades, flamethrowers, needle weaponry, and other exotic instruments of pain will also find the Executioner especially delightful.<br/><br/>With <b>Reckless Abandon</b>, the Executioner carelessly plunges the entire battlefield into excruciating agony, sharing in the torment themself and enhancing damage-over-time effects at the cost of their own health. The Executioner can then hurl all opposition into peril with their heroic act: <b>Carnival of Misery</b> — foes are set ablaze, poisoned, and suffer heavy bleeding. But that’s not all, for the Executioner's heroic act doubles the damage over time of these effects! And after all their foes are burning, poisoned, and bleeding, you can savour in their agony until they fall silent, for the terrifying master of torture draws power from their very suffering. By way of the <b>Gift of Torment</b> ability, the Executioner receives bonuses to armour, evasion, and deflection, scaling with the number of enemies afflicted by damage-over-time effects.<br/><br/>And, finally, the Executioner’s <b>Where It Hurts</b> initiates the toccata-finale in their wonderful symphony of pain. After using this free-action ability, the Executioner’s next attack immediately triggers a burst of multiple damage-over-time procs on the target, ending those effects along with the lives of their hapless victims.<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/827877966616854558/1273203232134402069/reaper-1.gif?ex=66bdc269&amp;is=66bc70e9&amp;hm=a1593cb5e6233152a40d1b70864590c5c00415f69c5d654b6cecdacdb934f51e&amp;"/><br/><br/>Be the fiercest adversary your foes have ever encountered — call forth a typhoon of blood with a whirlwind of attacks and let them tremble in your wake! Armed with new, powerful abilities, you and Kibellah will paint the battlefield in the noble hues of the Death Cult: an exhilarating performance for you and a convocation of doom for those who dare to confront you. See you in the first DLC amidst the Void Shadows!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #45 (1.4.11) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4286950035120168147</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ee5d213b366d8e366fa7947809f92a640041d3b3.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div><br/>As promised yesterday, here is hotfix #45 (1.4.11). It is live now on Steam and it will shortly go live on our other platforms. <br/><div class="bb_h2">Fixes </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a server crash issue related to a player taking damage from a projectile or the environment when they were dead or knocked down. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Orthus Offensive special assignment where one of the twins could double spawn.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We have a known issue of certain blessings (like Shattering Impact) showing an undefined text description. The cause has been identified and we’re working on a fix for this, as well. <br/></li><li> We also have a known issue of certain advanced circumstances not working properly (e.g. No Ammo modifier). We are working on a fix for this. In the meantime, we're going to disable these on the mission board. </li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Hit-Reg Improvements &amp; Much More ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797829891536</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Oi Speed Freeks,</b><br/><br/>Today, we've released an update that addresses many player's top concerns. In our testing we've noticed significant improvements and we hope you will now too.<br/><br/>Here are the details:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improvements to weapon and ability hit registration over the network<br/></li><li> Improvements to aiming synchronization over the network<br/></li><li> Optimized Shokkjump Dragsta Shokk rifle VFX to be much more performant. This might fix the stuttering issue during play for some people<br/></li><li> Deffkilla Wartrike unlock challenge set to 50m kill proximity instead of 10m and improved kill proximity detection<br/></li><li> Removed sound effect for PROS message of the day cycling<br/></li><li> Reduced Stompa arm-mounted gatling gun knockback, increased damage slightly<br/></li><li> Looted Wagon Grot Bomm damage reduced to 60 (from 70)<br/></li><li> Boomdakka Snazzwagon Billowing Smoke duration decreased to 4 seconds (from 5), Mek speshul primary accuracy decreased slightly<br/></li><li> Fix for saw sound effect not playing at recap progress.<br/></li><li> Fix the remaining time display for daily challenges in the UI<br/></li><li> Fix for daily challenges being reset<br/></li><li> Burna Valley finish line time increased by 10 seconds<br/></li><li> Changed Teef icon colour to yellow<br/></li><li> Playtime bonus Scrap per minute increased to 575 (from 500)<br/></li><li> Adding dialogue box confirmation when leaving the game during a match, which explains that teams are randomized in the next match and that Scrap gained from this match will be lost<br/></li><li> Locked vehicles now shown at the KUSTOMIZE and in-game spawning screens, with message saying that they can be unlocked through challenges<br/></li><li> Increased Latest Loot to 12 items in the store<br/></li><li> Fixed challenges screen to work properly with 16:10 aspect ratio<br/></li><li> Fixed audio issue where sound entered another, terrible dimension when set below 25%<br/></li><li> Some audio mix adjustments and overall volume lowered 2 db since it was a bit loud<br/></li><li> Vehicles now always have full boost when respawning<br/></li><li> Explicitly added vehicle compatibility to item descriptions in the store<br/></li><li> Increased available search window time for matchmaking<br/></li><li> Various improvements to controller management to avoid conflicts <br/></li><li> Added vehicle abilities screen to KUSTOMIZE menu<br/></li><li> Fix for achievements with no rewards showing at the end of match recap.<br/></li><li> Fix for challenge sets showing incomplete information at the end of match recap.<br/></li><li> Bots now use dash and are more aggressive with their initial combat engagement</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9c04148e5c2b05df99b1ea46c5b553e77574520.png"/><br/>Some of the highest priority tasks we’re working on still:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fix issue with vehicle challenges seemingly resetting progress and not unlocking items<br/></li><li> Fix issue with Teef not showing up after they have been unlocked through progression<br/>    - If this has effected you try this:     https://playersupport.plaion.com/hc/articles/20848220459037<br/></li><li> Fixing an issue with Scrap Boosts not showing up after they have been unlocked through progression<br/></li><li> Fixing issues with not being able to create/join a party and/or matchmake as a party <br/></li><li> Making sure matchmaking puts you in your region (server provider issue – they are being contacted)<br/></li><li> Improving matchmaking to make fewer but more full lobbies<br/></li><li> Adding servers in Oceania, South America (server provider has been contacted to allow us to do this)<br/></li><li> DeffKilla Wartrike front guns may fail to deal damage if a players ended a game in the wartrike and continues to use it in the next game without switching vehicle. Switching to another vehicle and then back to the trike solves this issue for that game.<br/></li><li> Further improvements to netcode / hit-reg</li></ul><b>Thank you for baring with us and all those who have helped us hone in on these issues. </b><br/>We're pleased with these additions and refinements. But of course, this is an on going process and we're looking forward to seeing your feedback and make future adjustments.<br/><br/>Until then, Happy Krumping.<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/12dbd116f20ee59d98b4292c6403c29d7a9fc127.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
