<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment - Aislinn Gameplay Showcase</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/807959368541668080</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Dutiful. Ruthless. Driven. Aislinn’s campaign is a sweeping saga of naval ambition, and his gameplay has plenty to offer!<br/><br/>Check out the full Gameplay Showcase now!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CVfKmVgUG9w?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class reveal delayed to November 18</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/614305130088499507</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">To ensure we meet the quality standards of our marketing assets, we have had to make the difficult decision to <b>delay the announcement of our new class until November 18, 2025.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We are working hard to resolve this and be ready for <i>next week </i>to showcase the new class in the light it deserves.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Rest assured, <b>this does not affect the release date</b> which we are happy to announce is <b>December 2, 2025.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We<i> </i>thank you for your patience and continued support. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">- The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment: Meet Aislinn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535302981</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/f216ed8d2262d143e42319f3be2f20e651572b12.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings, all!<br/><br/>Welcome to the first instalment of our Tides of Torment deep dives! In today’s blog we steer our attention towards the fortunes of Ulthuan and its noble people, the ancient race of the Asur.<br/><br/>Or rather, let us look far, far away. For the adventures of Aislinn, Ulthuan’s greatest naval commander, begin in the south-eastern quadrant of the Immortal Empires map, in the waters of the Eastern isles. It’s the other side of the world from Ulthuan, but distance is no object to Aislinn’s loyalty. Leading the High Elf Sea Patrol, Aislinn is about to uncover a Druchii plot to invade his beloved homeland, and only the commander of the fabled Dragonships has the naval expertise to counter this existential threat.<br/><br/>Aislinn is the hero Ulthuan needs, though perhaps not the one its cultured (and altogether privileged) nobles desire. ‘Aislinn the pernicious’, some label him, on account of the brutal zeal with which he executes his office. However, his grasp of fleet tactics, shipboard discipline, naval assaults, and his command of the denizens of the deep, put him above reproach. He is one of Ulthuan’s greatest champions; though given his reputation, maintaining the support of the influential Elven Lords when far from home is ever a challenge for him.<br/><br/>Dragonships are no mere naval vessels. They are vast war-platforms, capable of developing their own infrastructure, mustering and housing many thousands of troops, and transporting them at pace to precisely where they are needed. To meet and defeat the Druchii invasion, Aislinn will need to gather the rare resources required to build a fleet of these floating behemoths. This is no mean task: he’ll need to curry favour with Ulthuan’s greatest war-leaders, by capturing settlements and handing them over for stewardship, in order to gain the vital assistance and unique benefits that each Lord offers.<br/><br/>Embracing the full freedom of the seas like no other, Aislinn’s campaign is one of tremendous mobility. His forces perform lightning coastal strikes, capturing settlements and developing Elven Colonies and Outposts, expanding Ulthuan’s interests and enhancing his own capabilities and forces, before the High Elf Sea Patrol tackles the Druchii invasion head-on.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ FULL BLOG HERE 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment Trailer Soundtrack Giveaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/807959368541668046</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/80f6038c888e8cc8dc0a3d67b914f5f49d8b24c8.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings Total War fans!<br/><br/>For all the music lovers amongst you, we’re delighted to give away the soundtrack from the Tides of Torment announcement trailer 🎼<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 Claim it now in the Rewards section of the CA Community 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment arrives on 4th December</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535302985</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/ac94b5045e13b8a8fbd6b97e27ff31baec418906.png"/><br/><br/>​The time has come to reveal that our next Total War: WARHAMMER III DLC, Tides of Torment, arrives on December 4th! This pack includes a terrifying trio of Legendary Lords for the High Elves, Slaanesh and Norsca, and it will be released alongside Update 7.0, which introduces new battle units, campaign features and narrative, free content, and tweaks and fixes for all owners of the game.<br/><br/>You’ll be able to purchase the Tides of Torment as a complete bundle or as individual Legendary Lord content packs, allowing you to decide how you purchase this DLC.<br/><br/>And now, it’s time to see the Tides of Torment trailer:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rhJ1ps1n65k?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ FULL BLOG HERE 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
