<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>A Launch Day Update from Caged Element &amp; Wired Productions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689831535</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/279b1bfeef8269e1ab24fcb3f2bc68f2b5baa623.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks. <br/><br/>Today we officially launched Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks on Steam, and whilst the game is now officially out of Early Access, we know the transition has not gone smoothly for many of you. <br/><br/>Connectivity problems caused by our shift from dedicated servers to a player-hosted system have made it difficult for players to find and join matches consistently. We deployed an update shortly after launch today in an attempt to address some of these issues, but unfortunately it did not resolve the core problems. <br/><br/>The development team is working through the night to bring the game back to full online functionality as soon as possible and fully focused on identifying and implementing a reliable fix. <br/><br/>We’re hugely grateful to the community for your patience, feedback, and support. Every bug report and shared log is helping us move faster towards a solution. <br/> <br/>We’ll continue to provide regular updates as work progresses. Please do continue to report bugs, issues and any hiccups you have had so far &amp; we'll continue to answer questions in the discussions as we see them.<br/><br/>Thank for your your patience.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTFIX for Connection Issues</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689831518</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Back again - hopefully with good news...<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>This latest patch should fix <b>some </b>network/connectivity issues in the launch build, as well as the game trying to join full matches when it should not.<br/><br/>There's <b>still an issue with seeing games in other regions than your own</b>, but if there's a game up in your region with space to join, you should be able to join it<br/><br/>If you can't seem to join a game in your region that is showing in the browser, please <b>restart the game</b>.  This should only be necessary to do once, after loading the new update for the first time<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>We are still looking into fixing the issue with <b>not being able to see/join games that are outside of your region</b><br/><br/>Apologies for the issues and we hope everyone's been having a great time, regardless ːsteamfacepalmː <br/><br/>We'll update again once we've done something more with it.  Thanks for playing and sticking with the game!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Imperialis is coming out on June 24, 2025, and Season Pass II is announced!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040875201</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Bring Justice to the Koronus Expanse with Lex Imperialis Expansion!</div><br/>Lex Imperialis, the second major expansion for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, thrusts players into the iron grip of Imperial Law. A new 15-hour storyline introduces the Adeptus Arbites, a faction of incorruptible enforcers, and a new companion — the grim and relentless Solomorne Anthar. With battle Familiars like cybernetic eagles and cyber-mastiffs, this DLC enriches the gameplay and narrative layers of Rogue Trader and will be available to all players on <b>June 24, 2025.</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FHDfU-iQRhI?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3622820/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Lex_Imperialis/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Stories Come to Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader with Season Pass 2</div><br/>Also announced is Season Pass 2 for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, bundling two new expansions and an appearance customization pack. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The third major addition to the game will allow players to enter a <b>Necron vault curated by the iconic Trazyn the Infinite</b>, challenge ancient guardians, and uncover relics tied to the Von Valancius legacy. <br/></li><li> The fourth one will let them explore the <b>Processional of the Damned</b> — a surreal voidship graveyard, in a descent into madness and mystery. </li></ul><br/>Each of these DLCs will feature a new companion character, new quests deeply integrated into the main storyline, new mechanics, and deliver around 15 hours of gameplay. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/1b504a409ff6f341b702a69ef4518731b8e04646.jpg"/><br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3650060/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Players who pre-purchase the new Season Pass right now will receive an exclusive Appearance Pack. This includes new hairstyles and augmetic implants that become instantly available for customizing their Lord Captain:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/b479dcd49603754665f3ab762b2a3c81201fd495.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/448b1983c77dd13f34250c7ef4009b28b11d0249.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/09e23f40f72e171d6896c7ce41441bc8a4024572.png"/><br/><br/>Last but not least, the Warhammer Skulls sale is live, so use your chance to get Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and its DLCs with up to 50% discount if you still don't own them!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.2.28 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040875136</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Abelard, bring me the mirror! <br/><br/>A special mirror has been delivered to the Lord Captain's quarters, allowing free change of portrait, appearance and voice for the Lord Captain at any given time. Traverse the Koronus Expanse in style and make your appearance match your decisions:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a4af8d04cb5a64c5dc6e321a1806f145b476f63b.png"/><br/><br/>And for the owners of Season Pass 2, the available appearance options will be expanded by 7 new hairstyles and 4 new augmetic implants!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/ca659eccb6b455b16757065e0be6af4832891bf4.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/39479d99bbce4e97c4d9734c27093af0c226b5c8.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/5c437fd20c3bf18f01ab3265c7edb5a5ddf2f80a.png"/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Skulls Festival - Deeds of the Fallen DLC &amp; Onslaught Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/511833014974546335</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Battlesector and Gladius are taking part in the Warhammer Skulls Festival, with a new narrative campaign and a major free update for Battlesector and a DLC release for Gladius.<br/><br/>Let's take a look! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Warhammer 40,000: Gladius</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">Free-to-keep week</div><br/>Gladius is going to be free-to-keep on Steam for the duration of the festival. <br/><br/>It is the perfect occasion to try Gladius if you haven't: it is the ultimate 4X strategy game set in the grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000. <br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/489630/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Onslaught Pack</div> <br/>Deploy 8 brand-new units with the Onslaught Pack on the battlefields of Gladius Prime. <br/><br/>The new units will bring a new offensive layer and will unlock new strategic options for commanders.<br/><br/><b>Canoptek Reanimator - Necrons</b> <br/><i>Support walker unit that regenerates friendly Necrons units.</i><br/><br/><b>Mandrake - Drukhari </b><br/><i>Light skirmish infantry that causes fear and teleports to disrupt enemy formations.</i><br/><br/><b>Vyper - Craftworld Aeldari</b> <br/><i>Fast reconnaissance skimmer unit with a multipurpose missile launcher.</i><br/><br/><b>Attilan Rough Rider - Astra Militarum</b> <br/><i>Fast melee cavalry unit.</i><br/><br/><b>Sicarian Ruststalker - Adeptus Mechanicus</b> <br/><i>Elite melee infantry which excels in prolonged battles.</i><br/><br/><b>Rubric Marine - Chaos Space Marines</b> <br/><i>Elite psyker infantry.</i><br/><br/><b>Squighog Boy - Orks</b> <br/><i>Heavy cavalry unit that excels at taking down large prey.</i><br/><br/><b>Norn Emissary - Tyranids</b><br/><i>Elite Synapse monstrous creature bred to annihilate strategic enemy targets.</i><br/> <br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3743110/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Onslaught_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector</div> <br/>We are really excited to announce that the first narrative campaign DLC, <b>Deeds of the Fallen</b>, is now available on <b>Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector</b>. Featuring 12 new missions and 3 new units for the Sisters of Battle, it's time to bring the fight to Warzone Chaltnath. <br/><br/>On top of this new DLC, we are realising also a new free major update for everyone who owns the base game. The new major update adds a new game mode, Crusade, and also two free units. <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5nA4MyRAmN4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
 <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Deeds of the Fallen DLC</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39808373/e4a262857d1b7ad49c91eb781f8f1a2a956fc585.gif"/><br/><br/>There hasn’t been new story content from us since our initial release, but this changes today, with the arrival of our new Story Campaign, <b>Deeds of the Fallen</b>.  <br/><b>Deeds of the Fallen</b> contains twelve missions, where fans can play as the Sisters of Battle through a story-driven campaign against the Orks. The Adepta Sororitas will receive three new units, Imagifier, Castigator Battle Tank, Zephyrim - to fight in the name of the Emperor.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39808373/aef90630c96a4d972037e3f640255692d11fd6ec.gif"/><br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3577600/Warhammer_40000_Battlesector__Deeds_of_the_Fallen/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New major update</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">New game mode - Crusade</div><br/>The <b>Crusade Mode</b> is a new game feature that will challenge players to start with a basic army and fight their way through hordes of enemies, to earn the opportunity to expand both their forces and firepower. The mode also adds a new way to level up the troops, with a new experience system based on the ferocity of the battle, with a variety of ways to upgrade entire classes of troops.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39808373/4eb07d248003068690534f6eb1c71ed63b079466.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">New free units</div><br/>For this year’s Skulls we wanted to give you some new free units. Last year we sent new forces for Necrons and Tyranids. This time Sisters of Battle and Orks will reap the benefits.<br/><br/>The Adepta Sororitas can now count on the Dominions. The Dominions are specialist assault infantry who excel when making rapid deployments against enemy forces.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/31278649/a7f5a420ad11c691fec659375b4188b976223ad6.gif"/><br/><br/>While the Orks are gaining the much requested melee version of the Boyz as the lads with Choppas and Sluggas are here and ready for a scrap. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/31278649/5be86dff6b5e5e0b9adb335c32a102a8df6b8973.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Future</div><br/>2025 is going to be yet another stellar year for Battlesector. We’ll be regularly updating the game with feature updates and faction balance changes as we go through the year.<br/><br/>There will also be something new, exciting and a bit chaotic coming towards the end of the year…<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39808373/627e08658558dd743de63dd64ff2833fdf714b79.gif"/><br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1295500/Warhammer_40000_Battlesector/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Warhammer Skulls Festival</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39808373/dd0fc6f241cf82421cfceb1ae0005f419f9b6474.png"/><br/><br/>Warhammer Skulls is the celebration of all digital games about Warhammer.<br/><br/>There are loads of amazing discounts and new announcements from other studios, too. So we hope that you will check them out <u><b>here</b></u>.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
