<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Twitch Drops - Exclusive items</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720136550730</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>As the Grim Darkness Challenge arrives in the Koronus Expanse, so too does the exclusive Twitch Drops campaign!<br/><br/>To activate Drops and receive items, you will need to link your PC account to Twitch. Simply enter the game and locate the special chest inside the Lord Captain’s quarters. Click on it to interact and then follow the instructions on our website to link your account. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/61f7e5ef9349ae20e4a0bce2db66d1ed4da84b7a.png"/><br/>Once your account is successfully linked, all you need to do is watch any of the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader streams on Twitch with Drops enabled for at least an hour, and the rewards will be yours to enjoy!<br/><br/>There are <b>three unique in-game items</b> up for grabs: a pack of mind-twitching grenades, a helmet of tactical superiority, and a special servo skull (rumour has it, the skull has a few words for those who decide to click on it). The items will be dropped right into your inventory - no need to do anything! Also, these items are not limited to one playthrough and will replenish if you choose to start a new game.<br/><br/>The campaign starts with the Grim Darkness Challenge on <b>October 22nd</b> and will end on <b>November 4th</b>.<br/><br/>Find more detailed information on our website:<br/>https://roguetrader.owlcat.games/drops<br/><br/><br/>May luck follow our Grim Darkness Challenge contestants, and may the Emperor protect them on their perilous adventures!<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grim Darkness Challenge is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720136624929</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The Grim Darkness challenge is here!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1wCja-jxGv4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is The Grim Darkness Challenge?</div><br/>It is an intense competitive event for streamers, where, over the course of two weeks, participants will compete live in beating (or making it as far as they can in!) Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader on Daring difficulty in Grim Darkness mode - a newly introduced brutal gameplay mode where only a single save is allowed and is rewritten every time a player exits the game. All decisions and consequences in this mode are final, reloading is impossible, and if the party is defeated—the game is over!<br/><br/>The challenge will begin in just a few hours, on 00:00 GMT October 22, and last for 2 weeks until 23:59 GMT November 4, or until all players have successfully completed their playthroughs or were eliminated. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Participants:</div><br/><ol><li> Amm0ni	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Arkcard	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> ArmiaStars	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> BearlyTactical	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> BringItDon	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> coredumped	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Daily Dose of Warhammer	(Twitch)(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Flynnflytaggart	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Game kNight Plays	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> GruntarTV	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Kaerenai	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Kommissar Azura	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> kormakrtv	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> Mirianatir	(Twitch)	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Mortismal Gaming	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Nightharrow	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Otrod1e	(Twitch)	<br/></li><li> Remortis Gaming	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Revan	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Slandered Gaming	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> TangerineBlade	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> TheCriticallyClueless	(Youtube)<br/></li><li> Unknownhost	(Twitch)<br/></li><li> The Station	(Twitch)	(Youtube)</li></ol><br/>Watch your favourite streamer best the hardest trial or fail on the road to the grand prize!<br/><br/>Full rules of the challenge can be found here!<br/><br/>May luck follow our Grim Darkness Challenge contestants!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.2.1.19 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4557171720122109386</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>We're deploying a new routine update where we've fixed a number of mechanical and narrative issues, improved visuals for the Freight Line and adjusted a certain Act IV fight in the Void Shadows DLC to be a bit less frustrating. <br/><br/>The same update will be coming to consoles within ~24 hours.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Watch out for possible spoilers below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">System and stability</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It's no longer possible to Quick Load in Grim Darkness mode;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After defeating the Aurora, instead of the usual cutscene on the voidship, the player could sometimes receive the bathing dialogue instead, causing the game to break in wild ways - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a broken trigger in a dialogue with Nemesite which could lock the quest progress. Players who have already experienced this, will have the quest automatically switch to the next stage;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that caused one of the dialogues with Marazhai on the arena in Act III to break. Those who already had this happen will need to restart the event;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where after defeating the main enemy of the Void Shadows DLC, the Rogue Trader could be teleported outside the Voidship bridge, unable to come back;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where failing A Card Inverted quest could make it impossible to talk to Kibellah in Act IV;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you could incorrectly add Marazhai to your party right after he accepted your offer to join your retinue. That caused a number of odd story issues and could make you lose some of the other companions. He will now wait in the Pit as intended;<br/></li><li> In the Ablution in Blood quest, Jocasta's investigation report could suddenly stop, locking the quest progress - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some uncompleted quests from Act III didn't fail after proceeding to Act IV and cluttered the journal - fixed, they will now fail correctly;<br/></li><li> Removed an empty Ulfar’s comment in Act IV;<br/></li><li> say something You could receive the Three Phalanges quest even if you denied the aid of the Death Cult - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mechanics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dogmatic — Adherent "Absolution" ability now correctly counts the attacker as the character who applied Burning, instead of the player character;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few more cases with enemies becoming invincible with 1 wound remaining if the player had a certain set of values for Custom difficulty selected.<br/></li><li> The difficulty of the prone check in the fight with the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Forceful Genestealer</span></span> in Act 4 has been reduced by 25 to reduce the necessity of building specifically for this encounter;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a combination of talents (such as Heavy Gunner) that reduced AP costs didn’t interact correctly with Soldier’s Heroic Acts. Fixed, the costs will now calculate correctly;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Well-Maintained Chainsaw could disappear from the player's inventory. Don't worry, Lord Captain, your belongings are back and Jocasta Sauerback is already working with those responsible for this outrageous theft;<br/></li><li> Kibellah's mask will no longer disappear from her inventory under mysterious circumstances;<br/></li><li> Noble Sword damage bonus no longer applies for hits with other weapons and abilities;<br/></li><li> Temporary Wounds from Camaraderie Badge are now capped correctly at described values;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">UI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Expose Weakness ability description was inconsistent with its effect - fixed, the description has been updated to reflect the ability behaviour correctly;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you could close the party setup selection window without selecting the party members mandatory for the specific quest, which could cause some companion quests to lock;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Localisation</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of typos across the game;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with missing Japanese and Chinese localization for some strings in the DLC/mod manager window;<br/></li><li> Some text was missing in the character generation window for Japanese localization - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Visual</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added some rats to the Freight Line to make it even more atmospheric;<br/></li><li> We have added the representatives of the Adeptus Mechanicus to the train cutscene when exploring the Freight Line. No sacred mechanisms should remain without the watchful eye of the Omnissiah!<br/></li><li> Kibellah's model now reflects the described scars;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Audio</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed inconsistencies of Pasqal's voice lines with the dialogue text while talking with him on the Voidship Bridge.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 4.0 - New Content for Operations!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4538031058666780902</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">​Hi Space Marines!</div><br/>The latest Patch is here! It brings NEW CONTENT along with various tweaks and improvements!<br/>Make sure you read the full note here:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW CONTENT</b></div><br/>💥 <b>New Operation - Termination. </b><br/><br/>This new Operation takes place on planet Kadaku. New dreadful foes have arrived. Make good use of the artillery to annihilate them.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/dbf4a81ef007235b08242b50d199d57804144f6e.png"/><br/><br/>💥 <b>Added Lethal difficulty for Operations</b><br/><br/>Major highlights of it:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ammo Crates have limited refills per player.<br/></li><li> Majoris enemies can become enraged and will be more deadly and harder to kill.<br/></li><li> Armour restores from finishers only if you stay close to your battle-brothers.<br/></li><li> Overcoming such a challenge will grant you new cosmetics…</li></ul>💥 <b>Added photo mode in Operations</b> (works only in solo). Also, characters can now follow the camera with their eyes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0987068ebeefc14bd9004c2edbde7945e0fcb9a9.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>GAMEPLAY AND BALANCING TWEAKS</b></div><br/><b>Melee Archetypes</b>: Fencing weapons' perfect parry window will now have the same duration as balanced weapons but it will start from the first frame of parry animation.<br/><br/><b>Melee Perks</b>: Chainsword, Power Fist, Combat Knife charged attacks perks get significant damage increase.<br/><br/><b>Basic Auspex Scan</b>: bonus damage on bosses is reduced by 30%.<br/><br/><b>Melta Charge</b>: damage to bosses is reduced by 70%.<br/><br/><b>​Enemy Spawn Director PvE</b>:<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tweaked idle spawns.<br/></li><li> Enemy variety within waves is now less random while enemy variety between waves is bigger.<br/></li><li> Extremis enemies can now spawn with additional enemies.</li></ul><b>Difficulty:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ruthless: Ammo crates have limited refills per player.<br/></li><li> Ruthless: Player's armour reduced by 15%.</li></ul><i><u>Note from the devs</u>:</i><br/><br/><i>"With Patch 3 we have noticed that Operations mode became noticeably easier, especially Chaos operations. We are happier with what we have right now compared to what we had on release, because before Patch 3 Chaos missions were unpopular. Still, we think that currently Operations mode is a bit too easy.<br/><br/>Overall these changes are going to make Operations mode harder, but it is difficult to measure by how much. We will continue to monitor those changes and will continue to adjust the balance of Operations mode. This is not the last change."</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/77d9a5a41619ea98270373892a36817546f0002e.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>PVP</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased delay between announcer messages in PvP.<br/></li><li> The starting animation of the Grapnel Launcher for the Vanguard is shorter in PvP.<br/></li><li> Fixed Power Fist in PvP dealing too much damage with short charged attacks.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>AI</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enemy Dodges: Globally replaced full invulnerability on dodge moves of enemies with heavy melee damage resistance.<br/></li><li> Rubric Marine with Boltgun: Disengage teleport max distance is slightly reduced.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>CUSTOMISATION</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> More options for colours customisation for Chaos:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tertiary colours: Sotek Green, Night Lords Blue, Death Guard Green, Khorne Red.</li></ul></li><li> Decal colours: Sotek Green, Khorne Red.<br/></li><li> Colours: Added Liberator Gold colour to default for primary and secondary colours palettes.<br/></li><li> Fixed a lot of issues with display of colours, now they should be more lore accurate (Mechanicus Standard Grey, Ushabti Bone, Phoenician Purple, The Fang, Iron Hands Steel, Retributor Armour).<br/></li><li> Decals: Added new Chaos faction decals for the right shoulder.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>LEVELS</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Vox Liberatis - Daemonhost: Disabled respawn until the last altar in the final arena.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>GENERAL FIXES</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the Assault perk "Ascension" could kill its owner.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Sniper perk "Targeted Shot" wasn’t always working in some cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed an unintended animation cancel with the Bulwark by using the block, which resulted in faster attacks.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the Tactical team perk "Close Targeting" not triggering properly.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the Tactical perk "Radiating Impact" not triggering properly.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the Sniper perk "Guardian Protocol" cooldown not working properly.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where sound was lost after switching the speaker configuration.<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues in Trials.<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues that were causing loss of saves.<br/></li><li> The Thunder Hammer perk "Patience Rewarded" description is now accurate with its actual effect (added "When your Health is below 30%” part).<br/></li><li> Lots of minor UI fixes and improvements.<br/></li><li> Lots of minor animation fixes and improvements.<br/></li><li> Localisation fixes.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>TECH</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.<br/></li><li> Fixed several connectivity issues causing disconnects for players.<br/></li><li> Slightly improved performance.<br/></li><li> Fixed issues controllers not working with Steam Input enabled.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>RENDER IMPROVEMENTS</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> General improvements and fixes.</li></ul><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New content is coming! Watch the Post-Launch Trailer now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4538031058670624542</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Space Marines, attention! 🫡📣</div><br/>A whole year of new content awaits you in <i>Space Marine 2</i>. New Operations, new Dark Angel themed cosmetics, new foes to annihilate, and more.<br/><br/>Get ready for the upcoming new Lethal Difficulty and new PvE operation: Termination, where you will face off against the largest threat the Tyranid swarm has to offer, the <b>Hierophant Bio-Titan</b>.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">See What’s Next in the New Post-Launch Overview</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-aTR-9RYPu0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Free and Premium Content Coming Soon</div><br/>The first major update, featuring Termination and the new Lethal Difficulty mode, is coming for free and for all players very, very soon. <br/><br/>This year and throughout 2025, new content will keep coming to <i>Space Marine 2</i>. Free updates include the upcoming Neo-Volkite pistol, and later new PvE operations, PvP maps and modes and a blood-pumping Horde Mode with just one challenge: <b>survive</b>. <br/><br/>Further awesome cosmetics for all your favorite Space Marine chapters are also on the way soon.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/48cbeba86ee7252b6da6a6c181eb6b66f4bd42e5.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Dark Angels join the battle</div><br/>The Season Pass will soon come to life with a Dark Angels theme pack. New weapon styles, armor pieces, and color schemes featuring the Unforgiven, that will expand customisation options to unlock in the Battle Barge, are coming soon as part of the first Season Pass.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39308af705c0b0ffd996813ea1e63517d7240aba.jpg"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available on PC. Join millions of players today!<br/><br/>Season Pass is included in the Gold and Ultra Edition.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For the Emperor! ⚔️</div><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
