<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #50 (1.5.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997843897243443</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/689dcd3eb376d80ca7e8c34c27889316a2f84534.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Welcome to the patch notes for Hotfix #50 (1.5.3). It is now going live on Steam and it will shortly follow on our other platforms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Psyker ‘Kinetic Flayer’ talent incorrectly triggered on non-valid enemies.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Psyker ‘Warp Unbound’ talent did not properly prevent a Perils of the Warp explosion when using Force weapons (e.g. Force staves).</li><li>Fixed an issue where the text in the Sacrifice weapon screen overflowed outside of the UI.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Ceaseless Barrage’ blessing description did not properly display the Damage vs Suppressed Stat.</li><li>Fixed a visual issue on Hadron’s workbench</li><li>Fixed an issue that could cause a client and server crash when a player was stunned without having any weapon equipped.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Discard options could become disabled to input after performing certain actions in the Discard weapons menu</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Empower menu could appear off-screen when using widescreen resolutions</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Edit Loadout Preset menu could appear empty</li><li>Experience will now show correctly on the Masteries screen if a player reached max Mastery on a weapon by using the Sacrifice menu.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when opening the Penances menu in specific situations</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is related to the Penances that got removed in Hotfix #49. (Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) - Patch Notes)<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the name for the Mastery weapon skin for the Pickaxe would appear incorrectly.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Auspex input tooltip during the hacking minigames in the Rolling Steel mission would appear in English also in other languages.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the information in the Sacrifice Weapon screen tooltip displayed an incorrect minimum rarity level.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The correct minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the value for the Mastery Level required to unlock a Mark could fail to be displayed in the Marks Swap screen.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On<ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li>[*[b]]FSR 3.1 Frame Generation does not do anything during excessive fullscreen effects[/b]<ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame Generation excludes the entire screen from generation when there are a lot of fullscreen effects playing that impact all pixels on screen. This will cause frame gen to just copy the previous rendered result which results in the framerate looking like framegen is disabled while frame counters saying that it is running correctly.</li></ul>[/*]<li>Penances Shown As Not Completed<ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares<ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats<ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li>UPDATED: This is now known to not be a visual issue only. Rather, it involves different values being delivered by the backend than expected. This is being investigated.</li></ul></li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 09:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lore Post: Skaven Chronicles part 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4660753243329528757</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/4802c9c37e1bb84c6f1a9f24b89ae1838544cb26.png"/><br/><br/><i>Few things are constant among the Skaven, but their scheming and plotting is one of them. While our Heroes may have foiled Rasknitt, there’s plenty other vermin are eager to hatch their own devious plans. The farsqueaker, a verminous piece of Skryre engineering, allows some of these would-be masterminds to instantly communicate across vast distances with their networks of agents and spies.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Skaven Chronicles: Part 2</div><br/>I am much pleased with your timely report, Skratch, and heartened by the news of your many successes. The minions I placed in your unworthy paws are clearly moderately capable. Use them well, Skratch. Do not think-think you are my only proxy in the Grey Mountains. Just because I plucked you from your runtish litter as a whelp, it will not displease me too greatly to have to devour you should you fail. I will start at the tail end, yes-yes, and work my way up from there.<br/><br/>The situation in Karak Gnol is more chaotic even than that which you left behind. My predecessor (may he lay forever in the boiling stomach juices of the Great Horned Rat) was too stupid to do away with his more competent and ambitious underlings while he still lived. He thought his cronies in Clan Pestilens would shield him, and they did, but more fool-fool them because now he is dead and a dozen rival chieftains scheme to replace him. None yet recognize my rightful claim, so you see the risk I take sending away so many clanrat warriors, even under the leadership of an expendable deputy like you, and why I demand results. <br/><br/>Not in seven months, Skratch, but now. <br/><br/>I had taken to displaying the heads of my would-be assassins before the entrance to my burrow, but I eventually ran out of spikes. There is a lair-wide shortage of them, I am told. So I have begun adding them to the skavenbrew with the rest of the bodies. The slavemasters inform me that the extra meat is gratefully received in the under-warrens, and perhaps this is a blessing in disguise. The skavenslaves could do with some fattening up. The way things are smelling around here, I may soon need the wretches to fight as well as die-die in the mines. <br/><br/>Given the glowing reports of your progress under Helmgart-place, I have decided that you obviously do not need the reinforcements or the extra funds you requested. My warp tokens are not infinite and I have instead spent your overly generous stipend for this moon-cycle on a Rat Ogre bodyguard for my protection. A far wiser allocation of limited resources, I think-think you will agree.<br/>Now stop chasing after low-hanging tails and give me something I can actually show to my enemies! Bring me a head from the so-called ‘Ubersreik Five’ for starters. Their legend is, I am sure, greatly flattered by the gross incompetence of the skaven they have faced so far, but their deaths by my paw will undoubtedly impress the ignorant masses of Karak Gnol. <br/><br/>Oh, and one more thing, Skratch. <br/><br/>This is important, so listen-hear very closely. <br/><br/>The Pestilent Brotherhood may have done more harm to Clan Fester than the Bloodblight or Rasknitt’s vacuous promises, but I need their warriors and their warpstone if I am to become Warlord. They have their own reasons to loathe the Furless Five, so however you choose to be rid of them – make certain-sure that it is suitably dramatic…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 16:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Bomb Rush - Timed Mode 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/6537626672205704293</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks, time for some firewerkz!</b><br/><br/>For this weekend, we've a new Limited Time Event game mode, Bomb Rush, <br/><br/>Bomb Rush is Kill Konvoy with the bomb spawn rate turned up by x4!<br/><br/>This is an extra, optional game mode that sees players constantly racing to reach new bombs and detonating them on the enemy Stompa. It's much a faster paced game mode where defence is much more difficult, but speed and racing provide more of the focus.<br/><br/>This mode will apply to all 8vs.8 Kill Konvoy maps and will end on Monday <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0dac166cfa66c68b706612dc32092b9b9741c65b.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! <br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703537439791435817</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains and all Warhammer enthusiasts!<br/><br/>A great event called <b>Warhammer Day</b> is in full swing at this very moment! The endless war is raging in the grim darkness of the far future. Join the fight against vile enemies of Humanity and bring glory to the Imperium. May the light of the God-Emperor guide you on your way to victory!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/dca8927d0590393de9db5a9d8352c1519fd00505.jpg"/><br/><b>Warhammer Day</b> will take place till October 7, and countless discounts on the games in your favourite Universe are already waiting for you to claim. So let’s not waste any time and take a look at what good deals this grandiose event has to offer:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Unlimited power grants its bearer unimaginable opportunities. Become an all-mighty Rogue Trader and take command of the great von Valancius dynasty by getting the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game <b>at a 40% discount</b>! Forge the future of the Koronus Expanse!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><br/>A vile Genestealer threat, a new romanceable companion, and archetypes are ready for you to discover in the recently released Void Shadows DLC! Get access to this Expansion, as well as the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC by getting Season Pass <b>at a 40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Upgrade your experience with new in-game items and digital add-ons! The unique weapons, pet, new throne, and voidship model, as well as the artbook, soundtrack, and wallpapers pack are longing to be claimed as a part of Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack <b>at a 40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Ultima Founding DLC announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4693404340619804511</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
To celebrate Warhammer Day, we are really excited to share some really important news about <b>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius</b>. <br/><br/>As part of the celebration, all our Warhammer games have joined a special sale. Please check our steam page to see all the details: <br/>https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/Slitherine<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Ultima Founding DLC </div><br/>The Primaris Space Marines will be joining the battle for Gladius Prime on December 10th. <br/>Featuring 8 new units, the Primaris are ready to step in the battle for the God Emperor  and the Holy Throne. <br/><br/>Unit lists:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primaris Intercessor<br/></li><li> Primaris Aggressor<br/></li><li> Primaris Hellblaster<br/></li><li> Primaris Inceptor<br/></li><li> Primaris Invader ATV<br/></li><li> Storm Speeder Thunderstrike<br/></li><li> Primaris Redemptor Dreadnought<br/></li><li> Primaris Repulsor Executioner</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
