<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/3990819972762046425</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/1bda548badba2d50e8d2166b7e288684c0db4145.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>We've just rolled out Hotfix 5.1.3, bringing with it a pretty hefty range of bug fixes and tweaks.<br/><br/>Read on for the full rundown of what's included:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Gameplay:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in some Dwarf siege maps (Custom Battle and Campaign) where attacking units would end up floating in the air in their deployment zone<br/></li><li> Warlock Engineers now have the passive ability "Musk of Fear" in their skill tree<br/></li><li> The "Draftmaster" skill used by Nakai's secondary Lords now increases the global recruitment capacity<br/></li><li> Fixed some inconsistencies with Khorne unit recruitment costs<br/></li><li> Fixed the Exalted Keeper of Secrets gaining the passive ability "Feasting on Fear" twice from their skill tree<br/></li><li> Fixed Oxyotl's Silent Sanctum army abilities not always being enabled in adjacent regions<br/></li><li> The Axe of Khorne and Armour of Khorne magic items can now be equipped by Warriors of Chaos, Daemons of Chaos and Khorne factions<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some Legendary Heroes had upkeep costs<br/></li><li> Playing as Warriors of Chaos, upgrading a Chaos Trolls unit to Bile Trolls now requires the Rusted Branding Iron technology<br/></li><li> Fixed the major Nurgle settlement level 3 building costing 3 population surplus rather than 2<br/></li><li> Aligned the global recruitment durations for secondary Lords under Nakai (when their buildings are maxed out) with the local recruitment durations for Nakai himself<br/></li><li> Yuan Bo now starts the campaign with the technology "Seasoned Trackers" unlocked, as with other Cathayan factions<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some Regiment of Renown units could gain experience during battles and rank up<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of effects not applying to Carnosaur units<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where checks for bankruptcy were being calculated in the wrong way<br/></li><li> Additional adjustments to how attrition is calculated at end of turn<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where bankruptcy prediction for attrition was not considering raid income<br/></li><li> Fixed the Legendary Red Crested Skink Chief Lord not having the Immortality skill<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the mission "A Hero Becomes a Legend" would sometimes update with the wrong number of battles won by Heroes<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in domination mode battles where AI units continued to be issued orders after being ordered to unsummon, overriding that order and preventing the units from successfully being unsummoned<br/></li><li> Fixed issue when playing as Empire, Kislev city walls were not displaying wall improvement effects<br/></li><li> Fixed Autoresolver inaccuracies with how single entities units (Land Ship, Steam Tanks etc.) behave when damaged in the context of the Autoresolver<br/></li><li> Fixed the Empire Captain skill 'Admired Infantryman' applying to Free Company Militia units<br/></li><li> Daemon Prince Lords can now be saved in Campaign in order to be loaded in Skirmish battles<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Malakai Makaisson's long victory condition would not trigger due to a Legendary Battle not being counted towards the total count of battles completed<br/></li><li> The player can no longer lose the Nemesis Crown to rebel armies, losing the crown altogether<br/></li><li> The Nemesis Crown can no longer be picked up by a character leading an army that has been loaned to the player<br/></li><li> Fixed the Infernal Castellan Chieftain missing the Increase Mobility skill<br/></li><li> Fixed Tamurkhan's Long victory condition stating it requires 3 chieftain devoted battles, when it actually requires 6<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Karl Franz was unable to confederate Balthasar Gelt's faction<br/></li><li> Added Siege Attacker to Ice Witches mounted on Frost Wyrms<br/></li><li> The Gunnery School building now unlocks one tier of Acclaim earlier when playing as Markus Wulfhart<br/></li><li> Multiplayer battle lobbies now auto-add the correct number of player slots for the battle type selected, and auto-adding Ais in Skirmish vs. AI<br/></li><li> Fixed the weapon profiles for the mount versions of Scourgerunner Chariots<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where when fighting Thorgrim Grudgebearer's quest battle "The Axe of Grimnir" in the Realm of Chaos campaign would result in the wrong battle type<br/></li><li> The Khorne Unholy Manifestation "Call of Battle" can now be used on armies that are at sea<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where completing a long campaign victory and gaining an effect that increases Lord recruit rank, would not apply when replacing a Lord<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Wood Elf skills intended to give bonuses to Spellsingers mounted on eagles were applying to Spellsingers mounted on unicorns<br/></li><li> The Electoral Machination "Requisition" now fully replenishes the state troop units rather than adding 1 unit, as the pool size can be increased by Karl Franz's unique skill<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in Chokepoint Battle - High Peak Pass - Bretonnian Hills where defending players could deploy vanguard units in the attacker's deployment zone but could not place the same unit in their own<br/><i>To solve this issue the position of the attacker's guerilla deployment exclusion zone had to be inverted. Now both sides can correctly deploy their vanguard units within their respective deployment zones.</i><br/></li><li> Fixed missing hard collision in a Bretonnia river crossing battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed some Ethereal units not being set to the Ethereal ground type<br/></li><li> Fixed Marauder recruitment cost reduction from Norscan Iron resources not applying properly<br/></li><li> Improved the hard collision around the rocks in the Black Ark map (used in quest battles and domination battles)<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where barricades would give units a 10% ammunition replenish each time the unit docked to them<br/></li><li> Fixed Ripperdactyl mount animation and hitbox being misaligned whilst flying</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issues within the Warriors of Chaos red line skills that apply to rank 7 and above units where some Regiment of Renown units were affected twice<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of effects that weren't applying to Giant Slayers<br/></li><li> Fixed various issues with the Steam Tank portholes<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where some UI elements could be dragged outside their intended position<br/></li><li> Fixed the toggle overcast spells button displaying over the channel Winds of Magic UI<br/></li><li> Fixed missing example Lord and Hero portraits in Overlay UI in battle<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where clicking Esc when the Replace Lord menu was open would deselect the character, leaving the window open and making some features of the panel not work<br/></li><li> Fixed hidden missions showing on army banners if the missions target was that character<br/></li><li> Added the correct image to Conquest battle mode under options menu<br/></li><li> Fixed error where Wood Elves 'Recruit Wild Spirits' marker on settlements opened tooltip about Raise the Dead instead<br/></li><li> Fixed quest battle pins showing on top of characters if the character was in the same region as the quest pin<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Forge button would not always unlock for all Dwarf players in a multiplayer campaign<br/></li><li> Fixed travel button for Oxyotl being active when he was recruiting even though he couldn't actually teleport<br/></li><li> Fixed some effects not showing when hovering over the resource bar effect bundle tooltip<br/></li><li> When playing as the Changeling, an icon now shows when an army is visible to enemy armies<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the help pages panel would open behind the Elector Counts panel<br/></li><li> Fixed some characters displaying with unit tiers<br/></li><li> Fixed the help page for Tribal Confederation (Norsca) displaying the same paragraph twice<br/></li><li> The help page button in the Recruit Wild Spirits panel (as Drycha) now correctly opens the Wild Spirits page<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the help pages panel would open behind the Forge of Daith panel<br/></li><li> Added the missing scripted objective in Rakarth's quest battle "Whip of Agony"<br/></li><li> Fixed UI issue where resources required would overlap with building chain name<br/></li><li> Fix auto unlocked skills not using the greyed out text when in the locked state<br/></li><li> Fixed the enemy lord in Kayzk's Chieftain battle not displaying the correct portrait</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Graphics/Animation:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issue where Chaos Lord is holding his axes with open hands while mounted on the Chaos Steed<br/></li><li> Fixing a bug where Chaos Lord of Khorne would rotate 90 degrees while on his Chaos Steed during certain attack animations<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Thorek and Thorgrim, on the Anvil of Doom mount, would stand up in a sitting position when selected on the Campaign map<br/></li><li> Fixing bug where Herald of Nurgle on Palanquin mount has several missing animations<br/></li><li> Fixed several missing animations in Campaign<br/></li><li> Fixed bugs where Waywatchers &amp; Hawkeyes of Drakira (Waywatchers) do not hold swords in their left hand during idle animations<br/></li><li> Fixing a bug where the walk animations of the Forsaken of Tzeentch are not restarting seamlessly<br/></li><li> Fixed various units not displaying stumps when dismembered:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Nasty Skulkers<br/></li><li> Reaper Bolt Thrower<br/></li><li> Amethyst Wizard<br/></li><li> Festering Stooges (Exalted Plaguebearers) RoR<br/></li><li> Chaos/Norsca Charioteers<br/></li><li> Hellforged Host (Exalted Bloodletters) RoR<br/></li><li> Spellweaver<br/></li><li> Night Goblin Warboss</li></ul></li><li> Fixed bug where the Herald of Slaanesh's leg rotates strangely during an idle animation when on a steed<br/></li><li> Fixed some Be'lakor animations where he is holding a whip when he shouldn't<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the two-handed hammer used by the Bretonnia Peasant Mob unit was not fully textured<br/></li><li> Fixed combat ready animation issues on High Elves Spearman<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with jumping attack animations for Goblin variants<br/></li><li> Resolved rendering issues with Sons of Ghorros (Centigor - Great Weapons) unit which would result in different model parts not being visible<br/></li><li> Addressed some skin issues on LODs to ensure proper rendering<br/><i>LOD means "level of detail", and refers to the models and textures used for units depending on their distance from the camera. For example, units in the far distance will use less-defined models than units that are closer to the camera.</i><br/></li><li> Fixed bug where Daemon Prince attack visual effects are played a few meters in front of him<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with Chaos Lord of Nurgle's sword, which had the wrong orientation<br/></li><li> Empire Outriders are no longer missing their rifles on their back in idle and running animations<br/></li><li> Added several missing Plagueridden on Palanquin mount animations<br/></li><li> Fixed bug where Repanse on Suleman was not playing original WH2 idle animations<br/></li><li> Fixed various animation issues with the Ripperdactyl mount<br/></li><li> Morathi's animations on the campaign map now match her unique battle animations, and she now holds her sword when mounted on the campaign map</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Audio:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cathay War Drums will once again be audible on executing their abilities</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Performance/Stability:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that could occur when cancelling unit recruitment in Campaign</li></ul><hr/><br/>As always, we'd like to say a big thank you to everyone who submitted bug reports over in the CA Community. These reports go a long way in helping us shorten the gap between identifying an issue and resolving it, so if you run into any issues after updating to 5.1.3, please be sure to let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>If you caught our "What's Next?" video back in June you'll remember we mentioned smaller pieces of new content coming alongside our regular patching, and we're excited to announce that patch 5.2, which is currently targeting a late August release, will be the first to include some extra bits and pieces. We'll be sharing a blog in the coming weeks from Design Director Mitchell Heastie, who's been heading up this project, to tell you more about what you can expect.<br/><br/>Until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.14.1 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4368013560353831248</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/>The team is currently hard at work. We'll have news about new content soon.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.13.03</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Version 1.14.1 </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Technologies are now displayed in multiple columns when there are more than 6 technologies in a tier.<br/></li><li> Join Discord pop-up now appears once on game start.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Balance</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased Maleceptor hitpoints from 30 to 36.<br/></li><li> Added Witchfire, Psychic Lash and Ignores Cover to Maleceptor's Psychic Overload ability.<br/></li><li> Added Gift of Mutation to Warp Talons.<br/></li><li> Added Adrenal Glands and Regeneration to Maleceptor and Tyrannocyte.<br/></li><li> Spiritseer's Spirit Mark ability now affects Wraithlords.<br/></li><li> Skitarii Marshal's Agression Override and Control Edict abilities cannot affect fortifications anymore.<br/></li><li> Canoness Lead The Righteous ability cannot affect fortifications anymore.<br/></li><li> Removed Wraithlord' Smash trait.<br/></li><li> Added Chaos Lord, Master of Possession and Warpsmith to the list of Chaos Space Marines units benefiting from Gift of Mutation.<br/></li><li> Removed the action consumption for Weirdboy's Warpath ability.<br/></li><li> Replaced Canoness' Combi-bolter by Boltgun.<br/></li><li> Increased the Wraithlord's Ghostglaive damage from 6.5 to 8.<br/></li><li> Increased the Sydonian Dragoon's Taser Lance damage from 4 to 6.<br/></li><li> Added Acid Blood to Maleceptor and Tyrannocyte.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed Teleport Homer description not mentioning that Assault Terminators and Chaplains can benefit from the trait.<br/></li><li> Fixed Pulse Accelerator not affecting Breacher Fire Warriors' Pulse Blasters.<br/></li><li> Fixed Chaos Terminators' power sword not being affected by Conjoined Weaponry research.<br/></li><li> Fixed XV107 RVarna's Electromagnetic Shockwave dealing 10% damage to all adjacent units instead of itself only.<br/></li><li> Fixed Wraithlord research not unlocking the Hammer of Wrath research.<br/></li><li> Maleceptor now has hammer of Wrath instead of Living Battering Ram and is affected by Hammer of Wrath research.<br/></li><li> Minor language fixes.<br/></li><li> Tweaked death sound delays.<br/></li><li> Fixed Cryptek's Mindshackle Scarabs ability that should not target units with Synapse Link and Khaine Awakened.<br/></li><li> Fixed Warpsmith' Mechatendrils not being affected by Forbidden Energies research.<br/></li><li> Fixed Librarian's Shockwave ability not applying Pinned.<br/></li><li> Fixed Cryptek's Minshackle Scarabs description.<br/></li><li> Fixed researched technologies tier setting unlocking disabled DLC units.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darktide 101: Voice Over Recording &amp; Rules - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4353376861549287202</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d80b7dd458cf94bb5edbd29178cdff5015e6a62.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div>Welcome to the next installation of our Darktide 101 dev blog series. We’re interviewing devs working on Darktide to share what it’s like to create the game. <br/><br/>For today’s blog, we’re talking about Voice Over Recording and VO Rules. Have you ever been surprised by a piece of dialogue you’ve never heard before? Have you ever wondered what it’s like in the booth when recording your favourite lines? Today, you’ll get to find out how it works.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Runtime Dialogue System and VO Rules</div>Our first topic is written by our VO Design guru, Ola. Take it away, Ola!<br/><br/>Darktide's VO system was built off of the way VO worked in our two previous ‘Tide titles, with a lot of additional bells and whistles.<br/><br/>This VO system is a context-aware system, where we send queries to see if we can play something and it will return results based on what the current status of the game is.<br/><br/>We track many many different contexts for this purpose. Some examples include:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> How much health and ammo do the players have?<br/></li><li> Are there other players or enemies nearby? If so, how many?<br/></li><li> Is the combat intense?<br/></li><li> What previous dialogue has played and how long ago was it?<br/></li><li> What weapons do you have equipped at the moment?<br/></li><li> Which players are in the game?<br/></li><li> Which mission are you in?<br/></li><li>What trust level* do you have?</li></ul>(* <i>Trust level is based on the player level 1-30.</i>)<br/><br/>Based on all of these contexts, we set up dialogue rules. These are buckets of VO lines, and when the system finds a match, it prioritizes it based on the amount of contexts it has hit. The more specific a line is, the higher priority it has to play.<br/><br/>We currently have around 90,000 voice lines in the game spread across a total of 6,000 rules. (For context, Vermintide 2 has approximately 39,000 voice lines.) Some of these rules are insanely rare. Part of this is by design. But part of it is that with such a large amount of rules requiring different combinations of contexts, some are bound to be very rare.<br/><br/>The idea is that even if you have played the game for a very long time, you should still feel that from time to time you come across lines you've never heard before. Our player character personalities also play a big part in this. Many lines vary from personality to personality. Therefore, some lines will only ever play when both of those personalities are present in a game together. And as we have 21 personalities, this creates many combinations that take time to discover.<br/><br/>Our most common VO rule is a rule that’s activated when Newly Infected assault players.<br/>This rule has been played 70,000,000 times in the last 30 days (at the time of writing this).<br/><br/>It has the following requirements:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>For that specific enemy to not have played their assault rule* in the last 8 seconds.<br/></li><li>For all newly infected to not have played their assault rule* in the last 4 seconds.</li></ul>(* <i>Assault rule refers to a rule that plays a voice line when an enemy is attacking or running toward the player.</i>)<br/><br/>Our most rare rule is a bonding conversation between the female Savant Psyker and the Ogryn Bodyguard, where the Savant complains that the Bodyguard tends to get in the way due to his size.<br/><br/>In comparison, this rule has only been played 19 times in the last 30 days.<br/><br/>It has the following requirements:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Have at least one friend nearby;<br/></li><li> No enemies nearby;<br/></li><li> For the tension to be decaying (meaning combat has just taken place);<br/></li><li> To have the female Savant Psyker present in the game;<br/></li><li> To have the Ogryn Bodyguard in the game;<br/></li><li> For there not to have been a banter conversation within the last 140 seconds; and<br/></li><li> The Savant Psyker to have triggered the “friendly fire” VO on the Ogryn Bodyguard within the last 90 seconds.</li></ul>Now rare rules are okay, but this is close to non-existent. In an effort to make this rule play somewhat more often, I have recently tweaked these requirements to:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Have less than 3 enemies nearby (from 0);<br/></li><li> No banter in the last 100 seconds (from 140); and<br/></li><li> For the female Savant Psyker to have triggered the friendly fire VO on the Ogryn Bodyguard in the last 180 seconds (from 90).</li></ul>From time to time, we do these kinds of tweaks to the dialogue to try to shift what will be heard, tune down the most common conversations and tune up the rarest. All to keep the dialogue feeling like an alive and dynamic experience for all of the players! (Note: I personally get a real kick out of seeing people posting rare conversations on reddit.)<br/><br/>We put together a video with a series of voice lines that can show the specificity with which these voice rules are created, as well as the pure talent from our voice actors. These lines include:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Zealot hears a Horde coming<br/></li><li> Veteran bonding conversation when low on health<br/></li><li> Pskyer finds ammo when a Zealot is low on ammo<br/></li><li> Veteran sees an Ogryn on a killstreak<br/></li><li> Psyker sees someone hogging ammo<br/></li><li> Ogryn finds a health boost while a Veteran is low on health<br/></li><li> Ogryn responds to friendly fire from a Zealot.</li></ul>https://youtu.be/n8Zbzw2DGug <br/>Alright, that’s it for now! If you’re excited to hear more about this topic, we have plenty more to talk about like the sound design of Darktide, implementation and WIPs, collaboration with level design or other disciplines, etc. If you have any specific questions related to voice over rules, or you’d like to hear more on the topic, please let us know.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Recording Voices</div>Our next topic is written by our Sound and VO team member, David. Go for it, David!<br/><br/>For Darktide, we want all of the voice-overs (VO) to sound natural, as if they belong in the world of the game and they come from the character that is speaking.<br/><br/>There are many things to keep in mind to achieve this goal. For example, when recording voices it's therefore important to be consistent when it comes to the mics and how they are positioned relative to the actor/actress. In both of the recording studios, OMUK and Molinare in London, we use the same type of DPA mic that sits on a person’s forehead. This gives the actor/actress the possibility to move and do gestures while talking. <br/><br/>For Darktide, most of our voice-over is either barking during combat, or talking while walking or even running. It's important to capture this sense of movement and effort. We have tried to achieve this by actually letting the actor/actress move during the recording or add pauses and breaths before/after or in between words. Imagine how you would talk while jogging with a friend. That’s what we’re going for during the session.<br/><br/>Before and during the recording session, my role as a game developer/voice designer is to give the voice director and the actor/actress as much context as possible about the game and the specific situations. For example, if the voice-over line is meant to be delivered while someone is being dragged up after being knocked down, it’s important for the actor/actress to convey this through effort and strain in the voice. If I had to pick, the most common comment from me to the voice director or actor/actress, it’d probably be: "Can we have a bit more effort and movement in the voice please?" It's not super fun when you see how sweaty the actors/actresses are, but it's necessary for world-building.<br/><br/>That’s all for the first peek into what it’s like to record voice lines for Darktide. Would you like to hear more on the topic, such as drafting the voice lines, or what lines are the most difficult to get right? Maybe a deeper dive on the enemy voice work? Do you have any questions for our voice actors? Let us know!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>And so ends our second Darktide 101 dev blog. What topic would you like to hear about next time? Do you have any questions for the devs working on Voice Acting and VO for Darktide? Comment below <br/> and we’ll try to get some more dev replies for you!<br/><br/>Until next time!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 11 - Deff Rally 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338739528778408393</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3eb6793ca760a94568f7db337ba3cc589f4f3d7d.png"/><br/><br/>Oi, not long now till you all get racing again.<br/>So, let’s discuss this capture-the-flag inspired game mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/041d5eb1b04863a112682c7d2717f99247f56f9c.gif"/><br/><br/>Deff Rally is the other game mode, alongside KILL KONVOY, launching with Early Access on August 6th. It pits two teams of eight against each other in a race to capture points. The first one there, scores big for their team.  <br/><br/>Getting there first is, on paper, the easy part. You and your team then must hold the capture point as the enemy arrives, and the frenzy of bullets unfurls. Holding the point increases how many points you earn. Control is easy to lose, so keeping the capture point is crucial for victory. <br/><br/>Eventually, the point is secured, and a mad dash to reach and dominate the next point begins.  <br/> <br/>When all Capture points have been fought over, a final high Orktane race to the finish line beings to see who’s the ultimate speedy Ork. Your placement in the final race will decide how many points you earn, so it’s all about getting there faster than your opponents. Death, naturally, will slow you down.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/612062d68d7a35884219a907993bdfcb1b59ba2c.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Each vehicle has unique roles and abilities that come to life in Deff Rally. We can’t wait to see how you play it and evolve the game-mode. Here’s some examples of how vehicles can be played in Deff Rally. <br/><br/><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon –</b> With the Snazzagon being better in mid-close ranges, it excels when on the offense taking back the point or getting into the heart of the enemy team. <br/><br/><b>Defkilla Wartrike –</b> Because the Deffkilla Wartrike will struggle if it sits still on a capture point, you will often see it drive around taking down key enemy targets, such as Rukkatrukk Squigbuggies or long ranged vehicles. <br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta –</b> The Shokkjump Dragsta is fast, so getting to the next objective first, or winning the race is where the Shokkjump Dragsta really shines. <br/><br/><b>Kustom Boosta Blasta –</b> With some of the best mid to long ranges, chipping away at enemies while they’re approaching the capture point is a specialty of this vehicle. Soften them up for your team. <br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon –</b> With heavy damage at long range, one well-placed shot from the Looted Wagon can decide if a push onto the point will succeed or not. <br/><br/><b>Grot Mega Tank –</b> As the heaviest of the bunch, dislodging a Grot Mega Tank from the point after they’ve gotten settled is a struggle. Hold the point while your team is focused on stopping the enemy attack is where the Grot Mega Tank excels. <br/><br/><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy –</b> Don't underestimate the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy because they can quickly get their team back to full health and ready for the next enemy push onto the point. Recovering your teams' health stops them from being krumped and ultimately delayed while respawning. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c603ec0a4576ad8b56527c5b6ea0076f2baf2ddb.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Your feedback this past year has helped us balance and shape Deff Rally into what you will see with August 6th release. <br/><br/>This game mode will continue to evolve with your feedback so don’t hesitate to leave your thoughts over on our feedback and bug reporting board: https://speedfreeks40k.featureupvote.com/ <br/><br/>With four maps available on early access release, and changes to the ones you know we’re excited to get you back in as fast as possible! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cf69ebec1314f26aef699ada21bfa45f7a8651c2.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4326354629820779098</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines!</div><br/>We’re only 41 days away from the release of <i>Space Marine 2</i>; it’s the perfect time for our monthly Community Update!<i> (got it? 41 days? 41st Millenium?😉😉)</i> We can sense the excitement growing as the release gets closer, and even more, since we announced that <br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h1"><i>SPACE MARINE 2</i> IS OFFICIALLY GOLD </div></b><br/>For those unfamiliar with the gaming industry, this means that the game has been approved by Microsoft and Sony and that we’ve been given the green light for the production of our retail boxes. Though we’ll continue to work on polish until the release, this essentially means that the game is ready.<br/><br/>This is a huge milestone for the teams and another major step towards the game’s full release on <b>September 9</b>, so we’re very proud to share the good news with you all.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f2446b3f3ca06c5cdc594355c9f372f2319148cd.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Frequently Asked Questions</b></div><br/>Over the past months, we’ve seen many questions about the precise features of the game. We’ll try to tackle a few here:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Do I need to have played <i>Space Marine 1</i> to go into <i>Space Marine 2</i>? <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Not at all! While there are returning characters, it's a fresh story that can be understood as its own without having played the first game.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Will the game be available on GeForce Now? <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Yes.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Will it be possible to pre-download the game before the release?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> No.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Is there couch co-op?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> No, co-op features will only be available online.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Does the game require to be “always online” to play?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Offline mode is available for the campaign <br/></li><li> PVE can be played offline, but you won't have access to progression if you do not connect to the servers.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> How long does it take to complete the campaign?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> On average, the campaign should take between 10 to 12 hours to complete. This can vary depending on the difficulty and your player profile.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> What are the PC specs?<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> At this moment, we are conducting the final PC specs tests. We’re very aware that it’s one of the most awaited information on the game, and we will come back to you within the next couple of weeks with the recommended and minimum specs.</li></ul></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>What’s next in August?</b></div><br/>We know you’re super thirsty for more content so be assured that you do not need to worry, you can expect more videos to pop up on our YouTube and social media channels (Discord, Twitter, Facebook). <br/>Talking about videos, we’re currently publishing on our secondary channel a series of short videos detailing some aspects of the game: weapons, enemies, environments… <br/><br/>You'll find the complete playlist <b>here</b>.<br/><br/>Amongst the upcoming short videos, there will be more weapons, a rundown of the different PvE classes, and more!<br/><br/>On top of that, you can expect co-op previews to start dropping during August, with content creators starting publishing videos on their side as well. <br/><br/>Next, we’ll detail the post-launch content of Space Marine 2 in a blog article that should be published around mid-August.<br/><br/>Finally, we’re reaching the final stages of our North America Tour, with Chicago (August 16-18) and Toronto (August 22-25) being the final places where you’ll be able to put your hands on Space Marine 2’s demo before the release. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1775b7d9acd2d9d530728b5ab5361daa9a3ab05f.jpg"/><br/><br/>Aaand that’s it for this month! We hope you’re as excited as we are! <br/>We’re really in the final weeks before the launch of Space Marine 2, it truly feels unreal and we can’t wait to see you play the game! <br/><br/>See you next month!<br/><b>The Emperor protects</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
