<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - June Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4225021101189985804</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/>Your growing enthusiasm regarding <i>Space Marine 2</i> has us incredibly motivated. Last week, you discovered our <b>detailed Gameplay Overview Trailer</b>: a 6-minute in-depth look into the game modes. It features creative director Oliver Hollis-Leick, who dissects the 3 different game modes: Campaign, Operations and Eternal War!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In <b>Campaign mode</b>, lasting approximately 12 hours, you embody Lieutenant Titus, right after the events of the first opus. Titus fights alongside his Battle-Brothers Chairon and Gadriel against swarms of Tyranids and Chaos. <br/></li><li> In <b>Operations mode</b>, you can either play with 2 mates or solo in endlessly replayable PvE action. Face swarms of Tyranids on 6 different maps to defend the Imperium.<br/></li><li> Last but not least, in <b>Eternal War</b>, fight in heated 6v6 matches in 3 different classic game modes: Annihilation, Seize Ground and Capture &amp; Control).</li></ul> → Annihilation is Team Deathmatch mode: two teams compete against each other. Each take down earns your team 1 point. First team to reach 50 points wins the match. <br/><br/>→ Seize Ground is a domination mode: Two teams compete to keep control of one zone that’s moving throughout the match. Keeping control of the zone grants your team points. The winner is the team that reaches the total amount of points given. <br/><br/>→ Capture &amp; Control is a King of the Hill mode: There are 3 specific zones in the arena and each team fights to control them. Gaining and keeping control of a zone grants your team points. Be the first to obtain a certain amount of points to win the match. <br/><br/><b>Watch it here:</b><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5tqDxvpzsKM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3">To go further</div><br/>This month we delivered a featurette focused on <b>Planet Kadaku</b>, showcasing more detailed elements of the game. These videos aim at giving players a more extensive look into small features of the game. You can expect more content like this coming in the following months so stay tuned and follow our socials to make sure you don’t miss them.<br/><br/>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OFh06AnY6Qk<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h3">Dedicated servers</div><br/>We’re happy to confirm that <b><i>Space Marine 2</i> will feature dedicated servers</b>, enhancing your experience in multiplayer. We have prepared a bunch of servers in North America, Europe, Latin America, Asia, and Oceania.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/568f2b3756d303ccde678a02b3debeaef1e1a178.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">About a Beta</div><br/>Over the past few weeks, we have seen incredible excitement around the game, both online and at the shows during the North American tour. Our teams at Focus and Saber have been truly blown away by your passion, and we’ve loved seeing the fan art, reactions and memes that you have shared so far.<br/><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is almost ready. We are now entirely focused on optimization, polish and fixing remaining issues ahead of launch on September 9. This means we will not run a public online beta, as it would take the development teams away from preparing for the full launch, and our priority is to ensure the best possible experience at release.<br/><br/>We know this is disappointing news for some of you. As a thank you to those interested in participating, players who registered via the online signup before June 28, 2024, midnight Paris Time, will receive the limited Bolt Pistol skin below.<br/><br/>We appreciate your understanding and continued support as we work towards delivering the exceptional game you deserve.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3d5982a4a6adac8650fa5f3f6559c18f1f52bd8a.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">We had a blast at GameCon Canada last weekend!</div><br/>Before you can get your hands on the game on September 9 or on September 5 for the Early Unlock, we’re touring in North America to let future players <b>play the demo</b>! Last weekend, we had an awesome time at Game Con Canada and our next stop will be Denver, Colorado from July 4 to 7!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d310e58c5fd691d89647eac299fe004cf6303ddc.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Join us on the official Space Marine 2 Discord server!</div><br/>This month, we also added brand-new <b><i>Space Marine 2</i> emotes</b> to our Discord server, bringing you more ways to express yourself all while honoring the Emperor! Many thanks to the talented SpyderOwO for creating those.<br/><br/>You can become part of the <i>Space Marine 2</i> community and join us, devs, and your fellow Marines, on the official <i>Space Marine 2</i> Discord server.<br/><br/>We will share news there and spend time discussing the game with you each week. Please keep the feedback and requests coming as they’re the grassroot of our community updates here.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6c8ce59e5c46412f231883ba5fffccb2e05ad666.jpg"/><br/><br/>See you next month for more info.<br/><b>The Emperor protects.</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale Now On!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4265553497827561401</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/998aa4acb52a2747d0905a71b5dd5e1d9e2028d6.png"/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">STEAM SUMMER SALE NOW ON!</div><hr/><hr/><br/><b>The Steam Summer Sale is now on until 11th July!</b> Grab big savings on a selection of <i>Total War: WARHAMMER</i> games and DLCs!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/>Whether you're a <i>Total War: WARHAMMER</i> veteran or want to complete your collection of Total War historical titles, this is the perfect opportunity to grab the ones you're missing!<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends Thursday 11th July @ 11AM PT/6PM BST</div></div><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions Twitter Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Sale is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999224210943</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Friends! <br/><br/>Summer holds many pleasant surprises, and Summer Sales are one of them. Let’s dive into the hot offers together!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>The adventure in the Koronus Expanse awaits. Time to venture towards the hidden mysteries of the Warhammer Universe. Get the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader <b>at a 35% discount</b>!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Brighten your playthrough with unique in-game items available in Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Voidfarer Pack <b>at a 35% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>Powerful in-game items, a new ship model, and digital additions - an art book and soundtrack are already waiting for you in Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Deluxe Pack <b>with 35% off</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>If you haven't got Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous yet, now is a good time to act! And <b>a 70% discount</b> will be a pleasant start to your adventure in the lands of the World Wound!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Don't let the end of the game stop your adventure! Complete your journey with three DLC included in the Season Pass, which is available right now <b>with 70% off</b>.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Amazing narrative, new companions, and a huge number of new archetypes. All this can be found in 3 DLCs which are a part of the Season Pass 2. Get it right now <b>with a 40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/81aab3294c21608233e3528dc7ff4e226ae9e98c.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Devblog 7 - Boomdakka Snazzwagon 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4178858570767002619</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0116ec05eff55017e6235593c103d50dbd2c39d.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e9b4a53073b276c2f1263407dc173fba002b775d.png"/><br/>The Boomdakka Snazzwagon makes up for its lack of armor with unbridled quantities of searing bullets thrown at its enemies. For enemies, first come the bullets, then comes the smoke - then the embrace of fiery death.<br/><br/>Race around in a haze of heat as you unleash an onslaught of bullets from your Mek Speshul, ignite enemies with your burna bottles and drown them in exhaust smoke to shroud your escape. <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b3d74b9e58b39c193c1c5f2ff1851a3f0ddae11b.png"/><br/>As far as speed goes, the Boomdakka Snazzwagon falls in the middle of the pack, faster than the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy and the same speed as the Kustom Boosta Blasta. However, with no special movement ability, mastering the Dash ability that all buggies have is key to keeping up with your mob.<br/><br/>The Dash is a powerful acceleration tool that is essential for the Snazzwagon to close the gap and make use of its deadly but inaccurate main gun. It can also be used to change direction quickly: combine it with the handbrake to whip the vehicle around and point your weapons in the right direction. <br/><br/>In Speedfreeks the Snazzwagon is best used up close and personal, quickly injecting yourself in and out of battle in a flurry of bullets, or supporting your Mob into ferocious battle, dealing sneaky damage while they absorb some hits. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/750639e301d93a4b3cda0a04bddd867c817351db.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/506ad1bc98bdf2138d0cd5c39dfa352f0c3bb02e.png"/> <br/><b>Souped-up Speshul</b><br/>Unleash a roaring wave of dakka. Extremely high fire rate but with extremely poor accuracy.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/737b871295b207db83ea9aeb8eb41ad8377312ce.png"/> <br/><b>Burna Bottle</b><br/>Toss a Burna Bottle that sets enemies on fire and sends them running in fear.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2688261a06df7218a0db4d8a9477d4c849e0bb5e.png"/> <br/><b>Billowing Fumes</b><br/>Flood the engine to spew a trail of blinding smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/10f81d44f5ff8313ee330da0d2389ace04f7e7fa.png"/> <br/><b>Dash</b><br/>The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming for determines where the vehicle will go.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/da5ab02b8ff4d8f0d742083e1925b16b4f5645c2.png"/><br/><br/><b>Pro tip:</b> You can only shoot enemies within 180 degrees in front of you, so try to stay near teammates and maneuver in and out of battle.  Use your Burna Bottle as frequently as possible, but save your Billowing Fumes ability for a murky escape when someone decides to heavily target you. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Team-Ups:</div><b>Grot Mega Tank</b> – Since the Snazzwagon’s armor isn’t the best, using a Grot Mega Tank as mobile cover can be a good strategy, with it also helping you drown nearby enemies in dakka.<br/><br/><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b> – Use your Billowing Fumes ability to shroud any Squigbuggies in need of hiding or an escape, and be sure to spray dakka and smash some Burna Bottles in the vicinity for extra damage to enemies in the smoke.<br/><br/><b>Kustom Boosta Blasta</b> – The Snazzwagon and Boosta-Blasta are a potent combo, with both vehicles having escape and/or disorientation abilities in Billowing Smoke and the Stikkbomb. This duo can be frustrating for the opposition – and fun for those driving them. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/fcc35b4582383744332d965a528bfba0c7eff5ff.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Good Against</div><b>Looted Wagon</b> – If caught alone, a Looted Wagon can be circled in smoke then blasted with bullets and fire in a short time.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/85701898b54d4cc00c1e84e862f9a8d14e044922.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weak Against</div><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b> – With a Squigbuggy generally hiding behind the front-line repairing enemies, it’s hard to penetrate and get close to them compared to other vehicles with a movement ability.<br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b> – With the speed of the Shokkjump Dragsta they will weave in and out of combat with you, and try to get around you to shoot you from the back. Stay near allies to help deal with them.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/30a18781f38c1e7e16b3fd95d9c72345b856c4e3.gif"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localization Tool for Our Community</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4248664999224147275</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain!<br/><br/>We sometimes receive requests from players interested in creating a fan localization of Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader into languages ​​that are not represented in the game. We are very happy with such enthusiasm and would like to help our fans in such a glorious deed!<br/><br/>We want to share with you a localization tool that you can use to create your own translation:<br/><br/>https://github.com/OwlcatGames/LocalizationTool<br/><br/>This is an open repository that contains the Localization Tool. You can use it for both Rogue Trader and Wrath of the Righteous fan translation/mod-making (you can even utilize it for your own projects).<br/><br/>To start the fan translation process, you should feed the tool with the game strings. As for Rogue Trader, you can find them inside a mod template archive that is stored on your computer (the game should be installed on your device). The example path for Steam - Steam\steamapps\common\Warhammer 40,000 Rogue Trader\Modding\WhRtModificationTemplate.tar  <br/><br/>The text lines in the tool are divided into columns for ease of searching and translation. You can quickly find the needed line or term in it.<br/><br/>In addition, this tool allows you to conveniently edit any in-game text, for example, correct existing dialogue lines or descriptions. This may be of particular interest to mod creators.<br/><br/>We will be thrilled if this helps you in your endeavors!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/09819f66e266f3d5811513eca204534340e37c96.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
