<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Trygon Update releases on April 15!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500569576639038937</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Save the date, Space Marines!</div><br/>The Trygon Update of Space Marine 2 releases on <b>April 15</b>! 📆<br/> <br/>Face the Trygon on the Exfiltration Map, gear up with the Inferno Pistol and enjoy the new Space Wolves Chapter Pack &amp; Imperial Fists Champion Pack.<br/> <br/>Here's a sneek peak. 😁<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c2364b35ee62f3edc854c73b083bad72aa1ad2bb.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/25e8da513c4b6f446dd875a47ff80ea145205a22.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/33468439454839669c5da543c35d6b18cb3eca9c.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a23bd933bf6de3953f589ab4321607a22b467a93.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Stay tuned!</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #65 (1.7.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835774959060146</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5dc8aaa9878970678f709250f40243982714fe3e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Hotfix #65 is currently rolling its way out across our platforms. While that’s happening, here are the notes!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>General Fixes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed the “Backend Error / Error Signing In” issue some players experienced upon game startup.</li><li>Fixed a crash that could happen when a player joined an ongoing session caused by the 'Bruiser' Ogryn talent.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could occur while suspending the game during active gameplay.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen during the Dark Communion mission end event.</li><li>Fixed a crash caused by a Zealot leaving the game while using the Relic Blade special.</li><li>Fixed a crash when trying to discard weapons while inventory was loading.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players could become unable to swap weapons or Blitz during a mission after opening the Tactical Overlay.</li><li>Fixed issues where Mortis Trials assets were loaded during all game modes contributing to memory problems on Xbox Series S.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Ogryn's Penance 'Onslaught' didn't increment properly.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the 'Falter' Blessing for Shock Mauls listed inverted values for the stagger bonuses. - Thanks to PancakeCultist on the Forums for finding this!</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>Internally this bonus reduces stagger resistance on the target, but it's presented as a direct bonus. It's already presented correctly on Infantry and Helbore Lasguns, as well as on Vigilant Autoguns.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Havoc rewards were not immediately granted upon receiving the weekly cache.</li><li>Fixed a rare issue where Havoc missions could crash due to an error in enemy spawning.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #64.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where players would be unable to counteract the Heinous Rituals due to the Ritual spawning while players are in transitional areas (elevators).</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #64.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Encroaching Garden would affect the progression bar of the Heinous Rituals.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #63.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Mortis Trials Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where certain enemies were not correctly outlined at the end of a wave.</li><li>Fixed a crash caused by the Psyker's Telekine Shield spawned from a Mortis Trials Indulgence Majoris when a player joined an ongoing session.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when a player joined mid-session and had to select multiple Indulgences at the same time.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Capture Objective” floor outline was not visible for players that joined while the objective was ongoing.</li><li>Updated the mission time shown at the end of round to now show the time used for the Fleeting Memories penance.</li><li>Fixed several places where players could either avoid melee combat or get out of bounds.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>Cosmetic and Animation Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Scab Captain would attack without any animations playing.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to Havoc - Derank - Comms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835774959060130</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f127c3bedc657be87151c262bd3b80a8dcf14d05.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>As promised, I’m here to give some details about Havoc and the derank system. <br/><br/>In Nightmares &amp; Visions, we changed how derank worked in Havoc. Previously, only the owner of an Assignment would lose a charge if they lost with a team. After the update, we made it so everyone faced the same risk. <br/><br/>We read the feedback and how this feels punishing, especially how it prevents players from wanting to assist others or accept randoms into their parties. <br/><br/>Here is what we decided to do. <br/><br/>Players will only be eligible to derank if they stand to gain something from it. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A player of higher rank will not lose a charge upon being a participant in a lower ranked mission that failed.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We want to promote higher ranked players helping out in the lower ranks. </i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rank 40 players will not be able to lose a charge through gameplay means at all.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The only way a 40 player will be susceptible to charge loss is thus by manually using the demote button, rank decay, or during a Campaign reset. We want players to be able to experiment with things without the fear of punishment. </i><br/><br/>If a player is helping a player with a lower Assignment, they have nothing to gain from it. Therefore, that player will not lose a charge if they fail the attempt.<br/><br/>For those at Rank 40, they do not stand to gain anything by attempting their assignment again. Therefore, we’ve made it so they can continue to try different builds and challenges to keep it interesting. <br/><br/>We want to ensure we keep the stakes and tension of climbing the ranks in Havoc, meaning all other aspects of ranking and deranking will remain.<br/><br/>These changes are currently being worked on. While we have the backend sorted, we’re working on some UI tweaks to make sure they’re aligned. Pending how these fixes go, we should be on track to implement the changes with our hotfix next week™️ (Hotfix #66). <br/><br/>— The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497191876916412703</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0a12149d6eaeebe1fcde157bf71eb19ef88931ba.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/> <br/>We’re back with Hotfix 6.1.2, bringing a host of fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III. This update includes various improvements and adjustments, with notable faction balance tweaks for Kislev following Patch 6.1.<br/> <br/>With that, let’s get into it.<br/><br/>— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Orc Choreographer<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">HIGHLIGHTS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Kislev</b> - Based on your feedback and reviews by our Design team, we've made adjustments to balance, building, tiering, and tech for Kislev to improve your overall gameplay experience.<br/></li><li> <b>Tzeentch</b> - Kairos Fateweaver has received a number of skill fixes and adjustments.<br/></li><li> <b>Balancing &amp; Bugs</b> - a fresh batch of bug fixes and additional balance adjustments, including fixes targeting recent performance issues e.g. stuttering. As always, please report any other issues you encounter through our bug reporting sub-forum.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">STILL COOKING</div>Here’s a short list of some issues that we couldn’t quite squeeze into this hotfix, but we see them and we’re working on them:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Mod manager/launcher performance issues.<br/></li><li> Issues surrounding the display of enemy movement range previews in campaign.<br/></li><li> Court &amp; Orthodoxy becomes significantly more difficult to balance after confederating your opponent.<br/></li><li> Reports of support stuck at 100/100 and not receiving boons.<br/></li><li> Matriarchal power achievement not unlockable using the new invocations.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue causing potential frame stuttering on certain machines, as well as occasional video frame skipping in the main menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed a possible crash on the end battle screen.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that was occurring when loading the game.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that would occur when completing the Ritual of Rebirth in the Gryphon Wood during a Wood Elven Co-op campaign.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash when accessing the Ice Court.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash caused by loading a save containing the tier 3 church building from pre-Kislev rework. Any instances of the tier 3 church will be replaced by the middle option in the new building tree for the churches.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><br/><b>Kislev Balance Tweaks:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Devotion adjustments: Lowered the requirement for using Invocations to 25+ devotion. (It still costs 50 devotion to perform an invocation).</li></ul><b>Kislev Building and Tiering Adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Ice Guard recruitment building has been collapsed into one single building (found at tier 4), providing access to both Ice Guard variants and capacity for Frost Maidens.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>If you had either building constructed in an existing save, they will convert to the new combined building.</li></ul></li><li>Kislevite Cultural Capital defense buildings have been combined:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Watch patrol building chain has been removed.<br/></li><li>All the benefits associated with it have been moved to the City Defences chain, which combines siege benefits with garrisons and devotion.</li></ul></li><li>Kislev’s Wall buildings now also generate a small amount of Devotion:</li></ul><b>Ataman Experience Adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly increased experience granted by defence buildings for Atamans:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Major settlement walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>33 – 66 – 100 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300</li></ul></li><li>Minor settlement walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>40 - 80 -&gt; 100 – 200</li></ul></li><li>Kislev Cultural capital walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 – 100 – 150 – 200 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300 – 400 – 500</li></ul></li><li>Doubled the Experience granted by Resource buildings for Atamans.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 – 100 - 150 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300</li></ul></li></ul></li><li>Ataman’s Estate:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>XP per turn: 800 -&gt; 1000<br/></li><li>Income modifier: -100% -&gt; -50%<br/></li><li>Additionally, no longer completely disables income<br/></li><li>Starting Supplies for sieges: 300 -&gt; 1000</li></ul></li></ul><b>Ogre Tiering Adjustments</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gnoblar Flingers<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Barracks tier 2 -&gt; 1</li></ul></li><li>Gnoblar Pigback Riders<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Barracks tier 1 -&gt; 2</li></ul></li></ul><b>Other:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bugs where Atamans (Atamen?) were lost forever if they were injured in battle or you lost or traded the city that they were based in. They can now be correctly re-recruited.<br/></li><li>Gnoblar Flingers no longer start at 10% health in garrisons on turn 1 of campaigns. (They were just out of breath!)<br/></li><li> The "Royal Ice Guardians" technology for Kislev now correctly provides upkeep reduction for armies lead by Ice Witches instead of Frost Maidens.<br/></li><li> While Yuri's journey certainly is a struggle, we didn't mean to cut his tech tree down to just the "Struggling" category. The rest of the missing prologue tech tree has been restored.<br/></li><li> Kislev will no longer generate several outdated missions related to the supporter race and the old devotion system.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug in Post Battle screen where mass visual artifacting would occur subsequently filled with black space covering the area.<br/></li><li> Added a cost element on tooltips for provincial devotion rituals.<br/></li><li> The ritual buttons in Kislev's Province Invocations UI are now correctly disabled when Devotion is spent for a Force Invocation and falls below the required threshold.<br/></li><li> Kairos' "Gaze To The Past" skill now correctly applies to the 4 lores aligned with his past head.<br/></li><li> Minor adjustments to Kairos' skill tree:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> added -25% cooldown reduction for all spells to "Prescient Cant" <br/></li><li> added "Fires of Change" lore passive to "Dwell in the Present"</li></ul></li><li> The "Court Agent" trait for Ice Witches and Frost Maidens now gives +2 ice court support per turn.<br/></li><li> Kislev will no longer randomly gain and lose access to Invocations in Gates, Forts and Bastions (these settlements do not have Public Order or Devotion.)<br/></li><li> The Kislev technology "Common Cause" is now correctly limited to units that are between rank 0 and rank 3. (Sorry Regiments of Renown, you're way out of this league.)</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI // UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a scrollbar to the available Atamans list in the Atamans Overlay so that it displays persistently and not only on mouse hover.<br/></li><li> Fixed Victory Conditions strings in the Victory Conditions panel that were missing localisation.<br/></li><li> Fire resistance and Fire Weakness now follow the new visual pattern we implemented in 6.1 with positive values appearing green and negative values appearing red when looking at the tooltip for a unit.<br/></li><li> Fix issue on the Unit Info panel where the Hero Details toggle button did not align correctly with the frame.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><b>Kislev Unit integration adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added some more technology support for Akshina Ambushers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Troll County Pathfinder now provides +10% range for Akshina Ambushers.<br/></li><li> Akshina Ambushers now benefit from Praag Veterans for +2 base missile damage</li></ul></li><li> The 'Leather Treatment' technology now also applies to Gryphon Legion units.<br/></li><li> The ‘Dwarfen Anvil’ technology now also applies to Horse Archers.<br/></li><li> The ‘Breechloaders’ technology now also grants +10% range for affected united.<br/></li><li> Common steel Orthodoxy Boon<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Recruit rank bonus 5 -&gt; 3<br/></li><li> Added Kislevite Warriors to affected units</li></ul></li></ul><b>Other:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The past and Future Kairos in the "Staff Of Tomorrow" quest battle now have spellcasting again. (Past Kairos and Future Kairos both now also only use spells associated with the past or future head!)<br/></li><li> Knights of the Brazen throne have now been issued their extra beefy Skullcrushers, changing their mass 1500 -&gt; 1800 to match the 6.1 Balance Patch Notes that accidentally contained this change before it was made.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where units with the Fire Whilist Moving ability could engage units outside their range if the unit was moving backwards or towards them.<br/></li><li> Gorbad Ironclaw no longer takes penalties for being in a forest while on foot. (He's large and in charge, but not that large).<br/></li><li> Lore of Hags is now affected by spell intensity modifiers (Omen of Spirits is exempted, to prevent it recursively increasing its own intensity).<br/></li><li> Several minor adjustments to RoR units that were not in parity with their regular version:<br/>Sisters of the Singing Doom (Witch Elves) // Melee attack +1<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bightscab's Plaguepack (Plague Monk Censer Bearers) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> Pit Fighters of Hell's Deep (Rat Ogres) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Frozen Heart of Winter (Elemental Bear) // Leadership +10<br/></li><li> The Mordheim Balewolves (The Things in the Woods) // Melee attack +4 // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> The Holy Wardens of La Maisontaal (Battle Pilgrims) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Siren of Red Ruin (Bloodwrack Medusamelee) // Defence +1<br/></li><li> Da Big Un (Rogue Idol) // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> The Fireborn (Dragon Princes) // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> Heralds of Khorne's Fury (Bloodcrushers of Khorne) // Leadership +5<br/></li><li> Maws of Savagery (Skin Wolves - Armoured) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Tithe (Zombies) // Leadership +5</li></ul></li></ul> <br/><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues after updating to 6.1.2, please let us know over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earn the Protector of Tertium Cosmetics</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835774959059229</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Rejects!<br/><br/>Earn the Protector of Tertium Psyker cosmetics by watching eligible Twitch streams! Make your stay in Tertium a stylish, if deadly, fight for survival.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ea32c3f59c243051d00ed44ace577b5cb32df1e3.png"/><br/><br/><b>We're rebroadcasting a collection of Fatshark streams starting this Friday (April 4) at 17 CEST from our Twitch channel. The stream will be running all through the evening, so tune in at any time to start earning the rewards.<br/><br/>You can also watch any of these Twitch streamers while they're live up until April 22 to earn the rewards.</b><br/><br/>Sequens<br/>DaveeBoy<br/>Deepnausea<br/>ImJustJun<br/>Daemoniic<br/>TheAmatorium<br/>Combine03<br/>GAMEHUBLER<br/>Azenev<br/>FuPlaayz<br/>Ferlinna<br/>chocob64bit<br/>NewTypeBTW<br/>KanakoVT<br/>SkavenDan<br/>TaigaTigerVT<br/>Altair<br/>mazzeexx_<br/>NerdrageFred<br/>‍<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Click here, sign up (or log in) and follow the instructions to unlock the cosmetics!</b></div>‍<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>‍<br/><br/><i><b>For a short period of time the automatic confirmation email to join our newsletter was paused. If you signed up on the Atoma Site in the past two weeks you'll likely have a prompt to check your inbox for a confirmation mail (example below), but you won't have it because of the interruption - follow these steps to get a new confirmation email:<br/><br/>Login and go to the Account Dashboard<br/>Click edit<br/>Remove a letter (e.g. "m" in "com")<br/>Save<br/>Now click edit again and change it back to the correct email address and save again</b><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/831e07a22cceff606ad05300de13078f0e7068af.jpg"/></i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
