<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Lovecraftian Days 2025 Sale begins!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/592894082264597614</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lovecraftian Days 2025 sale begins today! <br/><br/>Obtain your own Warrant of Trade and explore the Koronus Expanse, becoming one of the most privileged individuals in the Imperium - A Rogue Trader.<br/><br/>Claim Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and additional content for the game with up to 45% discount!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/48cc5efac26281d3ec02f482f7c3618da9008915.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PTS for Patch 7.0 will close tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/533221307576221865</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines,</div><br/>As the Trygon Update is just about to be released, we're closing the Public Test Server. 🔒<br/>The PTS will close on April 15 at 09:00 am UTC.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">But worry not!</div>The PTS will <b>not disappear</b> from your library. Instead, when you will try to launch the PTS, you will get an error message saying that it's closed. And, we will <b>reopen</b> it when we need feedback.<br/><br/>We wanted to warmly thank all the players who have participated in this first session of the PTS. You're actively helping us do better!<br/><br/>We can't wait to see you for the next session.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For the Emperor ✨</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving AI in Campaign - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/527591808042008726</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/bcdccc31dce1c9277de102a15a62e7e283534c91.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>The time has come for us to talk a little more about Campaign AI, what we’ve been working on in the wake of the first Beta, and how we’ve used your feedback to help steer this big oft-unwieldy ship in the right direction.<br/><br/>We’re pleased to reveal that tomorrow (Thursday 10th April) we’ll be launching our next Campaign AI Beta on Steam, once again giving you the chance to test out our next stage of tweaks and adjustments and provide us with your immensely valuable feedback. If you took part in our last Beta, we’d love to get your thoughts on this latest round of changes, and if you missed out last time, this is the perfect chance to see what we’ve been working on and have your voice heard. You’ll find instructions on how to access the Beta at the bottom if this blog when it goes live tomorrow, so check back when you see us confirm it’s live.<br/><br/>As ever, you’ll be able to discuss these changes and provide feedback in our dedicated Campaign AI Beta forum in the CA Community, as well as via a survey that we’ll be running alongside the Beta. These links will appear here tomorrow, and you’ll also find a link to the survey in-game, on the News Feed when you’re playing the Beta itself.<br/><br/>Before we get into the nitty-gritty of what Rado and the team have been up to, we’d also like to share that this project will henceforth be inducted into our rekindled Proving Grounds initiative. Some of you may recall this initiative from the WH2 days, but for those who don’t, let me give you a brief introduction to what the Proving Grounds are:<br/><br/>The Proving Grounds first debuted back in 2020 and gave our devs the opportunity to explore radical solutions and test systemic changes to core gameplay features, while giving you the opportunity to try out these changes and provide feedback on them.<br/><br/>Of course, there’s no guarantee that these tested changes make it into the main game, but it allows our devs to think outside the box a little and allows you to have your voices heard on what can be some pretty sweeping changes to core parts of the game.<br/><br/>Basically, it’s a chance for us all to work together on improving WH3 for the greater good. The Greater Good.<br/><br/>With this current phase of Proving Grounds, we're quietly confident that these Campaign AI changes are moving in the right direction. These new changes we're now testing for will help to show us what further refinements we need to make before we consider bringing them into the main game, and how that might impact the difficulty of our player experience.<br/><br/>Looking beyond this Proving Ground, we have a team internally starting to explore changes that we think we can make to Sieges, and are hoping to bring you more on that in the summer.<br/><br/>With that admin out of the way, it’s once again time to hand over to the almighty Radoslav. Be sure to check back tomorrow for all the details on how to access this new Campaign AI Beta!<br/><br/>— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Apprentice (Proving-)Groundskeeper<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ THE FULL BLOG 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trygon Update releases on April 15!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500569576639038937</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Save the date, Space Marines!</div><br/>The Trygon Update of Space Marine 2 releases on <b>April 15</b>! 📆<br/> <br/>Face the Trygon on the Exfiltration Map, gear up with the Inferno Pistol and enjoy the new Space Wolves Chapter Pack &amp; Imperial Fists Champion Pack.<br/> <br/>Here's a sneek peak. 😁<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c2364b35ee62f3edc854c73b083bad72aa1ad2bb.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/25e8da513c4b6f446dd875a47ff80ea145205a22.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/33468439454839669c5da543c35d6b18cb3eca9c.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a23bd933bf6de3953f589ab4321607a22b467a93.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Stay tuned!</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #65 (1.7.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835774959060146</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5dc8aaa9878970678f709250f40243982714fe3e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Hotfix #65 is currently rolling its way out across our platforms. While that’s happening, here are the notes!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>General Fixes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed the “Backend Error / Error Signing In” issue some players experienced upon game startup.</li><li>Fixed a crash that could happen when a player joined an ongoing session caused by the 'Bruiser' Ogryn talent.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could occur while suspending the game during active gameplay.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen during the Dark Communion mission end event.</li><li>Fixed a crash caused by a Zealot leaving the game while using the Relic Blade special.</li><li>Fixed a crash when trying to discard weapons while inventory was loading.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players could become unable to swap weapons or Blitz during a mission after opening the Tactical Overlay.</li><li>Fixed issues where Mortis Trials assets were loaded during all game modes contributing to memory problems on Xbox Series S.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Ogryn's Penance 'Onslaught' didn't increment properly.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the 'Falter' Blessing for Shock Mauls listed inverted values for the stagger bonuses. - Thanks to PancakeCultist on the Forums for finding this!</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>Internally this bonus reduces stagger resistance on the target, but it's presented as a direct bonus. It's already presented correctly on Infantry and Helbore Lasguns, as well as on Vigilant Autoguns.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Havoc rewards were not immediately granted upon receiving the weekly cache.</li><li>Fixed a rare issue where Havoc missions could crash due to an error in enemy spawning.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #64.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where players would be unable to counteract the Heinous Rituals due to the Ritual spawning while players are in transitional areas (elevators).</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #64.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Encroaching Garden would affect the progression bar of the Heinous Rituals.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This was a missed patch note from Hotfix #63.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Mortis Trials Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where certain enemies were not correctly outlined at the end of a wave.</li><li>Fixed a crash caused by the Psyker's Telekine Shield spawned from a Mortis Trials Indulgence Majoris when a player joined an ongoing session.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when a player joined mid-session and had to select multiple Indulgences at the same time.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Capture Objective” floor outline was not visible for players that joined while the objective was ongoing.</li><li>Updated the mission time shown at the end of round to now show the time used for the Fleeting Memories penance.</li><li>Fixed several places where players could either avoid melee combat or get out of bounds.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>Cosmetic and Animation Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Scab Captain would attack without any animations playing.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
