<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>DEFFKOPTA GOES BRRRRRRRR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/542244996316659850</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deff is comin' from above</b> on <b>ORKTOBER 23rd</b>!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Deffkopta is by far the most unique vehicle in the game now - it's <i>really</i> different, and awesome to fly. We've been having a proppa time zipping around the maps and using it in the much improved <b>Creation Mode</b>, which is also coming later this month.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We can't wait to get the vehicle into your hands so you can do the same.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Today we reward you patient gits with some teasers of the Deffkopta in action</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aa060504adc1f5408379761f8359379dd94e9bfd.gif"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph">BRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">BTW, only one person guessed correctly when we asked what you thought the next vehicle would be, and that's <b>ML_Paladin888</b> 🧠⚡</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Congrats, you get a free Soundtrakk, ya git!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll be disclosing the Deffkopta's weapons/abilities when it launches with the update in a few weeks ːsteamthumbsupː</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Flyboyz among you will rejoice</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, another GIF?</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3d00d6013eb6ec4e6ccf44adcbb2c1bd5a3e6f5b.gif"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph">We love this lil' guy.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">ORKTOBER IZ 'ERE 🔥</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We're not done showing things off to you lot. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As we've said before, the Orktober 23rd update will be the biggest the game has ever seen, and our next post we'll be revealing the new <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> in Creation Mode</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some testers have already been creating wild race courses that we never thought we'd see in the game, so we're really pumped to find out how the broader community uses these tools. It's a literal game-changer with how creative you can get.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">More details coming soon, but here's a little teaser of a race level made by community member "Only//" with the game's level editor 💪</p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7e4bc8fed084a851365bfafe4533a48d2687491f.jpg"/></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0da4102c5d72896f02525f05662d2f3aea9836b6.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The ORKTOBER celebration continuez next week, so be sure to keep yer peepers on dis page ya?</p><div class="bb_h3">This update will be massive </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, feel free to chat in the comments below or join our Discord to jump ingame with other gits<br/>https://discord.com/invite/speedfreeks40k</p><div class="bb_h1"></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 10.3 is live</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/507342099205586984</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Dear players,</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Patch 10.3 has just been deployed. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that this update simply brings technical compatibility with the upcoming Demo starting October 16. 😌</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h2">Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">added compatibility with the Demo version (to be released 16/10)</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 09:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #79 - 1.9.3 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499459531596630319</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8adc8b2f787c92985d2046fbca56a1846780bafe.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hotfix #79 (1.9.3)</b> is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below. <i>As a heads up, this hotfix will be somewhat heavier than previous ones due to various changes to sound files (~3.3 GB)</i></p><div class="bb_h2">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Scab Plasma Gunner</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New charge sound</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">New “Scope” VFX and “Scope” SFX</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">These should make dodging more consistent</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shot cooldown lowered from 2.4 to 2.0</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lowered dodge window from 0.7 to 0.6</p></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a rare crash that could occur in Havoc when spawning enemies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with subtitles displaying over menus.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug that could cause multiple voicelines to play at the same time in the Mourningstar.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Veteran “Rangefinder Goggles” headgear cosmetics would cause a small patch of balding.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some timing issues with the Plasma Gunner’s sound effects.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Force Staves would fail to shoot the projectile that triggered the Perils of the Warp state.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Veteran's Infiltrate would not end when damaging an enemy in the first 0.5s of entering stealth.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Psyker's Soulblaze from Perilous Combustion and Venting Shriek could be applied to un-aggroed Daemonhosts, waking them up.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Relic Blade</b> - Fixed an issue where it was not always possible to immediately chain an attack after performing a Special activate/de-activate action while sprinting.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note:</b> <i>thanks to players arkanian1210, aroth68 and CobaltNinja (among others) for bringing this to our attention!</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash caused by the visual effects of Rotten Armour enemies.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note:</b> <i>we thought we had fixed the same crash in our previous hotfix, but it was only a partial fix. This should solve all occurrences of the issue.</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where players could path upwards from specific nodes in the Veteran talent tree.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re aware of increased disconnects and server instability since the 1.9.0 update. Hotfixes have provided some improvements and we’re monitoring closely; restoring full stability will take additional time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some players might experience a rare crash occurring when trying to equip items to a character. This is affecting players with old loadout preset data. For players experiencing this issue, creating a new loadout preset should bypass the crash. A fix will be deployed soon to address the crash, which will in some instance delete the character loadouts.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your patience and your understanding!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 09:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Update on Unit Recruitment Issues</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/519725729918748466</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>UPDATE \[OCTOBER 10TH]:</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We have shared some community questions with the team regarding Beastmen, who are known to us as having similar issues with Idle Behaviour. The fixes we currently have in testing aren't showing any direct improvement to Beastmen, so it's evident to us from our tests that we'll need to conduct a similar investigation with them and see if we can include any improvements as a part of this Hotfix. We've started that work already, and will keep you updated.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Meanwhile we're seeing plenty of positives with Lizardmen and Tomb Kings in our testing. TK are still showing a low survival rate beyond turn 25, meanwhile LM are thriving, but most importantly they're both recruiting and correctly engaging with Campaigns.</i></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Hi all,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve been investigating the issues affecting Campaign AI since the release of 6.3.1 and are working hard to restore it back to a better standard. I want to give you an update on why these issues have occurred, and where we are with our progress on fixing them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A Hotfix is in development, currently its singular focus is on Campaign AI Unit Cap Recruitment fixes and the bad AI behavior that stems from this issue. Hotfix 6.3.2 is presently scheduled for release next week. It entered the first phases of our testing earlier today and is showing positive signs of providing an improved experience to the game. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Over the last few weeks when responding to questions on this topic, we had originally planned to publish the fix as part of 7.0. Now that the investigations have been completed and we are almost there with a fix, it makes sense to decouple it from 7.0 to get it out as quickly as we can. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The issues with Campaign AI are unfortunately complex to resolve. We haven't been able to deliver an immediate fix as we needed to conduct some very thorough investigations into the root causes, but we are working as quickly as the complexity allows. We’ll go into that complexity below for those who want the detail, but if you’re just looking for the headline: we’re on it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix 6.3.2 aims to address the recent problem that we’ve seen where factions aren’t recruiting units into their Armies, and the idle behavior that’s stemmed from that. This issue with recruitment has been a highly visible problem since the release of Update 6.3, but this issue wasn’t caused by 6.3 itself. We’ve discovered that this issue has been present in the game prior to this update and affects factions where the AI is tasked with managing Unit Caps. We have found that the AI was building lists of units to recruit without taking caps into consideration, resulting in recruitment failing to occur and stalling the AI decision making process. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">These issues have been compounded by changes that we made to the different resources that are required to recruit units by the Lizardmen and Tomb Kings, and why you may have also seen issues like this happen with factions that use pooled resources (like Spawning Sequence, Meat, Oathgold, or Skulls) to recruit. Lizardmen and Tomb Kings will still face an uphill struggle in their campaigns when managed by the AI (they have challenging starting locations which regularly sees them defeated fairly early on) but they shouldn’t be fighting with both hands tied behind their back. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For a deeper look at what causes these issues, here’s Lead Technical Designer, Radoslav Borisov with detail about how our AI is currently behaving.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The way our AI handles unit recruitment occurs over several distinct steps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">One of those steps is selecting a list of units to recruit into a specific force, with the goal of acquiring the necessary strength to perform a task.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">When the AI is mapping out its shopping list of units that it wants to recruit, unit caps are not currently taken into consideration in a proper fashion. This results in the recruitment action failing as soon as a unit's cap is exceeded.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Recruitment action failure then occurs. Should the AI decide that its next task should be to attack a settlement, it’s generating a recruitment action and then expecting an increase in force strength to a level where it feels the settlement garrison that it's targeted for attack can be defeated. Without the unit recruitment task’s successful resolution, it holds up the subsequent task and leaves the AI in a paralyzed state. It’s a cascade of failures that result in certain factions failing to complete any aggressive actions whatsoever. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">In order to be efficient in how resources are allocated and spent, the AI relies heavily on several beliefs around the current state of the game world.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some examples of these assumptions are things like:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cheapest unit that can be recruited anywhere in the faction</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Strongest unit that can be recruited anywhere</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Most cost-efficient unit (best cost to strength ratio)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Estimated number of turns to reach the recruitment location of the strongest/cheaper unit</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Any mistakes when constructing these assumptions has been found to lead to a catastrophic failure in many of our AI systems.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">If the AI believes a unit is free and provides any meaningful strength increase it will not allocate any resources to buy units – it wrongly believes it can fill its armies with powerful units for free and so will pursue that option and trigger a failure cascade.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">If the cost of a unit is not properly evaluated, the AI finds itself in situations where it has budgeted some money that ultimately ends up being insufficient, causing overspending and running them into an irrecoverable, or very slow to pay off debt.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is where pooled resources come into play – the AI’s ability to understand, plan and budget pooled resources is not ideal.  Lately, AI has not been factoring in pooled resource to its costs properly, leading to incorrect beliefs about what it can and cannot afford, resulting in action failure.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">These past weeks of investigation have shown to us that the majority of our internal systems were unprepared for actions that ostensibly could not fail, to fail. The cascading effect led to all sorts of problems – the AI couldn’t change stances properly, attacking on the campaign failed, recruitment failed, laying siege failed, and so on.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve identified and resolved the leading causes for such failures, but it’s very likely there are other cases we are not yet aware of just yet. Resolving the immediately known causes of this problem is helping us to remove any denser levels of fog that may be obscuring other possible causes, and as they become known to us, we’ll resolve those too.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">As it stands today, there are around 200 different pooled resources in the game and they are used in a large variety of ways. For us to be absolutely certain that everything is properly accounted for is a daunting task, but we will continue working on identifying and resolving any issues in the future, and will not deploy this Hotfix without careful monitoring of the effect it has, and will continue to stay committed to bringing more improvements as necessary.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Radoslav Borisov // Lead Technical Designer</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">News on Tides of Torment will take a back seat until we’ve resolved this issue. We’re looking forward to giving you your first complete look at this next DLC, but fixing this comes first.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">In closing, please accept our apologies for the experience that you’re currently having with the game. I’ll be active across our different community spaces helping to keep you informed on our progress as we move towards the release of Hotfix 6.3.2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Freeman // Head of Community</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praise the Omnissiah – Mechanicus II Demo Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/528732929177683327</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">//\[STATUS: DEMO DEPLOYED]...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">//\[ACCESS: PUBLIC]...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">//\[OBJECTIVE: TACTICAL ASSESSMENT]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The demo of Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II has just finished exloading into the Steam-sphere, and is available right now!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is your chance to command both factions in tactical skirmish combat as you uncover the origins of a new and epic planetary conflict between the techno-religious acolytes of the Adeptus Mechanicus and the ancient, deathless Necron legions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Download, engage and test your tactical logic against the alien threat.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Don’t forget to join our Discord to share feedback, meet the community, and get the latest updates!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
