<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>New In-Game Event: Light the fuse!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/668340807104725674</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Light the fuse!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Things are getting explosive on the streets of Tertium. Wyrmwood agents report an unusually high presence of explosive ordnance in the drop zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0188db98ed9b99cc84a6492b4a4410104c4abaf2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Explosive Uprising condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will <b>start on Thursday, August 21.</b> The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.</b> Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6b52012cfdbee0700f9e9978dc94faea8180c82c.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0f18727b59622f0cfa9f1f0949f4e0c355c2d20a.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060644</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>An absent-minded man of mysteries, Franz Lohner relies on his bulging journal to keep track of occurrences, intrigues and arguments around Taal's Horn Keep. Sometimes his notes are even useful, believe it or not. The Franz Lohner Chronicles are extracts from that journal.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>Franz Lohner’s Chronicle - Unexpected Guests</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">I can’t tell you what a relief it is to have this chronicle back in my hands. It’s been missing so long, I couldn’t even tell you when I’d lost it. Turned the keep up and down, I have, and took every scoundrel in the place to task into the bargain. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Sienna insisted Saltzpyre had nobbled it to ascertain as to whether or not I’d been scribbling down heretical musings. Heretical! Me! And this from the man who set us all looking for the Citadel of Eternity! Anyhow, when I’d had a good rummage through Saltzpyre’s chamber without success - some of the things I found there are better left uncommitted to the written page, I can tell you - Kerillian blamed Bardin, Bardin blamed Kruber, and Kruber just gave me that long, patient look I’ve been seeing a lot lately, and ushered me back downstairs with a stiff drink and a pat on the back. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Where, naturally, I found this wretched book in a pile of unsorted stock for the Emporium of Wonders. Where’d I left it in the first place, most likely. Still, I don’t feel entirely unvindicated. There’s been a lot of little notes left in the margins in at least three different styles of handwriting. It’s a damned liberty is what it is, but I suppose under the circumstances I’d be better off not making more of a fuss. They’re all halfway to thinking that I’m just a foolish old man already,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Anyway, I’ve more troubling things to think on.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve got guests. And not more of those “we took a wrong turn on the mountainside, and are powerfully averse to getting gored by beastmen” sort of guests. Dwarfs, in point of fact, and not any old dwarfs at that. This is no less a personage than one Cousin Okri, and a good grumble of longbeards. I’m pretty sure that a “grumble” is the collective noun for longbeards. If it isn’t, it should be, because so far as I can tell that’s all they do apart from fight endless bouts of practice combat and drink honest men out of their meagre stocks of ale.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">What brings Cousin Okri – who I have to say is shorter than I expected, which is a strange thing to say about a dwarf – to my door? It’s a matter of honour, because of course it is. Turns out, that the title of “drengbarazi” is a weightier one than I’d realised, and Okri’s not best pleased to hear that Bardin’s chosen to bestow it on the other four-fifths of the Ubersreik Five. He’s insisting that their right to bear it be proven in suitable fashion, and forthwith – which I don’t mind saying is awful hasty for a dwarf. In the meantime, Okri and his grumble have set up camp part way down the mountainside, and the nights have been full of drunken singing and the clash of gromril axes ever since. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">I tell you, I can’t wait for the Five to return so we can get this matter sorted out. I’m not getting any younger and I need my beauty sleep.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">And besides, I’m sure whatever Okri has in mind won’t trouble my merry band too much.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Almost </i>sure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.3 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/825966793744974705</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/144e2169665d770754abf1fca495ff21314d0a86.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re expecting to publish the full release notes for Patch 6.3 this Friday, followed by the Update itself next week, but if you can’t wait that long join us tomorrow on Rally Point where we’ll be playing and discussing Patch 6.3 live on stream. In Patch 6.3, look forward to updates and improvements to the Tomb Kings and Lizardmen races, audio updates including the death and rebirth of Alberic le Generic, new unusual locations, new free units, some streamlining on how to claim FLC for WH3 as well as a little extra blood splatter for everyone that likes to stick their noses right into the thick of it during battle.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This week, we have Senior QA Live Technician Liam Newman covering the changes and improvements coming to the Tomb Kings and Lizardmen, Principal Designer Mitch with the sports and weather on Unusual Locations and more, Sam, John and Chris for an update from the audio department and Game Director Todor Nikolov with a quick breakdown of WH3 FLC and how we’ve simplified how to get it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With that, I strongly urge you to click the link below to read the full blog. Enjoy!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">PATCH 6.3 DEV BLOG</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Pixel Daddy™   </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #73 (1.8.5)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/668340807104725672</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #73 (1.8.5) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes and Updates</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a toggle in the Mission Terminal Options to turn off quickplaying into the Battle for Tertium campaign missions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the server to crash when players would step in specific locations in several missions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue related to gas clouds that could cause a crash.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where not all active buffs icons would be displayed in the HUD, but only a part of them.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was preventing equipped items from being shown in the inventory.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the "Executor" blessing was not stacking correctly.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the “Hot Shot” blessing was scaling incorrectly over the tiers, while also remaining active while the secondary weapon was not wielded.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i><b>Dev Note:</b> The blessing will now scale its value 20/30/40/50% over tiers 1 to 4 as intended, instead of the incorrect and reverse scaling 80/70/60/50%.</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the "All or Nothing" blessing was not stacking correctly on Atrox Tactical Axes and Munitorum Sapper Shovels.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Scab Flamers would fail to play their voicelines.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue in the Barber-Chirurgeon where adjusting height only wasn't allowing players to confirm the changes to their character.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Mastery card in the End of Round screen now shows the correct weapon max level exp instead of showing it as level 0 with 0 exp.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added additional error message codes for network errors and server disconnections.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic and Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some clipping issues on the scarf of the Veteran “Bakkan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest” upperbody cosmetic.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where parts of facial hair would disappear while using the Veteran “Family Heirloom Flak Helmet” headgear cosmetic. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the same name was used for multiple cosmetic reward frames.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b><i>Dev Note:</i></b><i> The previously named “Purge the Unclean” frame from the Rotten Armour event is now “Disgustingly Resilient”.</i> </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the “Obtained From” text was not displayed properly for the Rotten Armour event reward frame.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the preview image of the “Brass Crucis” weapon trinket was not displayed correctly.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the following Zealot cosmetic upperbodies could look fractured:  </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Armour of the House of the Begloried Redemptor.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Pious Warrior's Armour.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the purity seal on the Ogryn “Bestest Trophy Pack” accessory cosmetic would float slightly away from the pack. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an instance of metal plates clipping through the gloves of the Veteran “Vostroyan Flak Coat” upperbody cosmetic while inspecting weapons. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues where the anchor on the Ogryn “Field Issue Haversack (XXXXL)” accessory cosmetic would rapidly move around while running.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Zealot “Witchhunter's Hat” headgear cosmetic would incorrectly remove small parts of some hair styles.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the “Intra-Cranial Implant” headgear cosmetic would not connect properly in the neck.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues with backpacks partially clipping into the Veteran “Bakkan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest” and Zealot “Preacher's Bakkan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest” upperbody cosmetics.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Arbites Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the following talents could fail to trigger correctly: Execution Order, Efficient Killer, Malocator, No Lenience, Keeping Protocol and Writ of Execution<i>.</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved the DLC validation process for the Arbites Class add-on.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that could cause the game to crash when using Execution Order.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Arbites Cyber-Mastiff would not disappear with the players during the Outro win cutscene in Mortis Trials.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff smoke effects would not show in the inventory views.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the icon for the Arbites Shock Maul wasn't correctly aligned in the Mastery screen.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feast of Grimnir - Teaser Trailer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/515218419125060119</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><i>It's a time for quaffing and settling old grudges — The Feast of Grimnir approaches, Heroes.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://youtu.be/iQtJlHxZ6Lg</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
