<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 12 - Kustomize ‘Ya ride 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338739528793079279</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Get ready Speed Freeks, the finish line is in sight! </div>Cross it in style, by using ‘ya battle loot to look Snazzy <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2fb2aec78e6ce309bdfbf419582bc020cad5854a.gif"/><br/><br/><b>Scrap </b>and <b>Teef</b> are the two resources that you can use to unlock cosmetics in Speed Freeks. <br/><br/><b>Scrap</b> is collected by fighting and finishing matches. It drives your progression through the WAAAGH! PATH while unlocking plenty of items along the way.  <br/><br/><b>Teef</b> are purchased with real money and can be spent in the Mek Shop to buy cosmetics. <br/><br/>Purchasing the Loot Pass with Teef allows you to earn a ton of extra items in the WAAAGH! PATH. It also lets you skip the latest vehicle's unlock challenge. Please consider purchasing the Loot Pass to unlock a lot of cool cosmetics as well as early access to the latest vehicle!<br/><br/>It’s important to note that all vehicles featured in the WAAAGH! PATH can also be unlocked simply by playing matches and there are also no time limited cosmetics.<br/><br/><b>There are no pay-to-win features in Speed Freeks</b>. Cosmetics (and Scrap Boosts) are the only thing you can buy with real money, whether that's buying the Loot Pass to unlock more items as you play or by buying them directly from the Mek Shop.<br/><br/>Scrap Boosts on the other hand, are progression boosters that allow you to unlock cosmetics faster and have no effect on gameplay.<br/><br/><b>Right now, customization in Speed Freeks is cosmetic only</b>. In the future, we might explore other types of customization options, but we will never lock those options behind a paywall, and we are committed to respecting the time of our non-paying players. <br/><br/>Read on for a walkthrough of the myriads of options available to you to truly express your WAAAGH!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3cb6b08e8b1cc515a13ee1b70db5ce4a314c3d3f.png"/><br/>The Kustomize screen allows you to piece together wild creations, paint them in whatever colors you choose and then take them onto the battlefield to flaunt your spoils of war. <br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Let's put the snazz into our snazzwagon.</b></div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 1: The most important part of customization is the kit</div>A kit is a modified version of the vehicle's default chassis. These can range from small adjustments to full-scale reworks. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e4fd7cbbe05c588ac68920ca3235a5fdae254ca7.png"/><br/>Let’s go with the Spikey Wagon kit. We want this thing to look mean, while sticking to the classic look of the Snazzwagon. You can also buy this kit with Teef as part of the Boomdakka Snazzwagon Pack in the Mek Shop. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 2: Next, the paintjob</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5afbbc00b48b46c374232aaa2a26784b51a38449.png"/><br/>We'll start with the Goff clan paintjob as a base. You can unlock all the clan paintjobs by completing vehicle challenges. For the Goff paintjobs, it's all about racking up kills and assists, because Goffs love getting stuck in!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/874fb2a73bb78a46cb911ef6fb816ae7c61c7c2f.png"/><br/>Let’s now click on the wrench icon to customize the colors. Nothing crazy, we'll just swap the red highlights for some green and yellow. Green, we all know, is best, and yellow because it’s the color of dakka. Of course, this wagon packs a whole lotta dakka.  <br/><br/>Those players who took part in our alpha and beta playtests will notice a lot more paint colors in the above screenshot! <b>There are currently 153 to choose from, including metallics! </b><br/><br/>While the Ork adage goes <b>'red wunz go fasta'</b>, this belief is not yet true at Early Access launch for Speed Freeks because the color of paint you choose won't affect your vehicle's stats. We don't want players to feel restricted in how they paint their vehicles to receive a certain buff. However, we will keep our eye on community feedback about this, so drop us a comment on our Feature Upvote page [link] if you have suggestions about our Ork color theory.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 3: Now it's time for the rims</div>These ones are nice and spiky. If you buy our Loot Pass, they’re unlocked right at the start of the WAAAGH! PATH. But remember, there is no time limit, you can complete the WAAAGH! PATH at your own pace, and at any time!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8fa1978bf0fe954d79f30612fca6d610d34f276b.png"/><br/>Selecting the gear icon again, we can mess with the rim's colors to make them better match the rest of the vehicle. Every good model painter knows how important the details are! If you want to learn more about how we referenced real painted models to define the art style of this game, check out Dev Blog 06!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b5812babd1a2941ed8299b66027f2647a79f56e7.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 4: The tires are already good and spiky</div>...so we’ll move right on to the Gubbinz.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bd9c87ae9c245ced977ab726b329cffd0f984342.png"/><br/><br/>Let's stick the Dakka glyph on there, which is unlocked for all vehicles by completing a Boomdakka Snazzwagon challenge and paint it yellow.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Step 5: Here, we'll choose the Squig Pole</div>It's fully animated, so to really appreciate it gnawing the life out of that metal bar you'll have to check it out in game.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e50a1d483f2706e6e774197609eb6dacdb72cfd5.png"/><br/>The Squig Pole is available in the Supporter's Pack within the Mek Shop. Buying this pack also gets you a loyal Grot companion to go with you in your Krumped Kam taunt screen and several other menu screens. If you want to support this game, please consider picking up the Supporter's Pack!<br/> <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Et Voilà, as Orks don’t say.</div>Compared to the default look, here on the right is our finished vehicle! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aeb97ab24ecd493ad258cbc3ce39c0db08ef23c8.png"/><br/>We hope that the customization features in Speed Freeks will bring more joy to your inner Mek! <br/><br/>Personalization is a huge part of the hobby, and the kit-bashing culture constantly leaves us in awe. For those of us without bits boxes and workshops, please enjoy this Orky digital sandbox. While a videogame could never match the creative spirit that has fuelled the Warhammer 40000 community for decades, these options are our closest digital approximation of that hobby feeling <br/><br/>We can’t wait to see the manic machines you’ll bash together in Speed Freeks. Join our Discord and its dedicated customization showcase channel, #da-snazzlounge, to post your creations. We also want to see them in all our other social spaces: <br/>X/Twitter<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/28cfb7a3e2161a12b6d6b2c156e458adde567bde.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/>  <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>X/Twitter<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 News - Twitch Drops 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162775980702</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8ad5db286be549fbdfaa5679a41085167a8207e6.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8fa4aca9d240a46f428052afefea63b3b1e9a7a4.png"/><br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks! </b><br/>Tuesday we unleashed da WAAAGH! and we couldn’t be more pleased with the rain of dakka spewed across our varied game modes and levels. <br/><br/><b>To celebrate, we’re offering you more free loot to snazz up ‘ya wagon with. </b><br/><br/>Between now and Monday September 2nd, you’ll be able to unlock up to 3 cosmetic items depending on how long you watch a stream, with <b>drops enabled</b>, in the Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks category on Twitch.  Those items are: <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">SHREDDA RIM</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/88d95b9bab5a8a9e33fa1418e2190f29600b9943.png"/><br/>- 20 minutes watch time<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">ZOG GUBBINZ</div> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d14afd4650eec3d46dbac129dea61f6f60b7c9ea.png"/><br/>- 1 hour watch time<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">MANGLA RIM</div> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f9b03140af80ccd063fd884c09911801b0006cad.png"/><br/>- 2 hours watch time<br/><br/>For you to receive these items ingame, you need to link your Speed Freeks Pros Account to Twitch. Go to your Pros account then “Settings” in the top right &gt; Connections &gt; Twitch. <br/><br/><b>Simple. </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/735fde9d06f985f4dd91fd604f9021d935664399.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Not a fan of Twitch? Fear not, these items are not exclusive and can be unlocked individually through purchase in the Mek Store.  <br/><br/>Thanks again for all your support and racing antics. We hope to bring you more rewards like this in future. <br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump into our extended multiplayer gameplay trailer!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4326355898839555163</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello, Space Marines!</div><br/>This is it: <b>one month to go until the release of Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2!</b><br/>In the meantime, as we know you're eager to discover more about the game and its multiplayer mode... <b>Dive into our new extended gameplay trailer!</b> <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/moaWKtTq1zc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Slay your enemies!</div><br/>Whether you play in Operations (PvE) or Eternal War (PvP) mode, choose one of <b>six playable classes </b> (Tactical, Assault, Vanguard, Bulwark, Sniper, and Heavy) and earn Armoury Data and Requisition Points to spend on your Space Marine’s appearance thanks to the game’s <b>deep customization system</b>. You can either unlock the game’s many Chapter presets, or create your own custom Chapters by piecing together individual cosmetic items, be it armour or weapon skins! <b>The more you play, the more cosmetics you will earn! </b> ⭐<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a52fb9bb939884e854a211c37021a4b5b07ee02.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Free content updates after release</div><br/>Space Marine 2 doesn't stop at the release: we will add more content, starting with <b>new “Operations” missions, PvP maps, new enemies, and new weapons</b> through <b>regular free updates</b> available to all. In addition to this free content, if you own a Season Pass, you will be granted additional cosmetics and Chapter heraldry through seasonal, themed DLC that will celebrate the many fan-favorite factions of the Warhammer 40,000 universe! <br/><br/>But we don’t want to tease too much yet… More details will be shared very soon. <br/>👀<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5a38f252d0da44239da71e3d4cb0c937ce08fe35.jpg"/><br/><br/>Thank you all for your incredible support since the reveal of the game, we can’t wait to finally give it to you. <br/><br/>Get ready, Space Marines, for it’s only starting! 💥]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Hit Registration and Cheating ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797812386918</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We've been seeing many reports about hit registration issues and rest assured, this is our top priority to fix.<br/><br/>We've also seen reports of "cheating" associated with the hit registration issue, but those people are not cheating, it's just something going on with the net code.<br/><br/>We have however seen a few reports of confirmed cheaters and we're already taking steps against them.<br/><br/>Apologies for the issues so far! We're just two days into launch now and with the game live and being consistently played by thousands of players, new issues are popping up that we hadn't seen before, we're doing our best to address them. <br/><br/>Thanks for your patience and support.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Server Disconnect Compensation 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797809444568</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Thanks for jumping in Speed Freeks Day 1 of Early Access. We had some server issues at release which caused some of you to be disconnected from matches. This has been fixed by the team with a new server roll out earlier today. <br/><br/>As a thank you for your support and to honor the playtime you lost due to server instability we will be sending out a 1 Day Scrap Boost through our email system, the same one we send our newsletter out with.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9fbb1b9ad50530626b697dac1fcc681be427c2a.png"/><br/> <br/>If you’ve already signed up for the newsletter you will be sent the Scrap Boost automatically. If you haven’t signed up yet fear not, it’s easy to opt in and you will also get the cute little Squig Gubbinz cosmetic topper when you follow. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2623f614a356cf931a23e04980689799fc1db4e8.png"/><br/><br/>To sign up for the newsletter simply log into your Speed Freeks account and click the follow button.<br/>https://prismray.io/games/speedfreeks <br/><br/>To redeem the Scrap Boost click the Redeem Code button in your profile and enter the code that was provided in the email. <br/>https://support.prismray.io/hc/en-us/articles/22351440941073-How-to-Redeem-a-Code<br/><br/> <br/>Sincere thanks for your feedback and support, and welcome to the WAAAGH!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
