<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #67 (1.7.5) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/645814564414293241</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b155602cdb6aca32012467979075997e07b2782b.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Hotfix #67 (1.7.5) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes &amp; Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> If a player is part of a Strike Team when they enter the Mourningstar, the text chat will automatically default to the Strike Team channel instead of the Mourningstar channel. <br/></li><li> When using a controller, it is now possible to hold the button to scroll the Talents/Indulgences list in the Tactical Overlay instead of having to tap it.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that could happen when rapidly pressing the Continue button in the End of Round screen. This only occurred on the Xbox and MS Store platforms.<br/></li><li> Consignment Yard HL-17-36 Mission: The area around the Medicae before the mid-event has received an update to its visuals and layout.<br/></li><li> Level 30 rejects will no longer talk about ratlings.<br/></li><li> Banter is more likely to play in Heresy and above difficulties.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with Ogryn Pickaxes, Cleavers and Latrine Shovels where the weapon could become stuck in the windup animation of a Heavy attack if the Special input was performed during the windup.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Havoc Changes &amp; Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where an incorrect amount of Havoc assignment charges could be displayed in the End of Round screen and in the Havoc menu's reward/punishment animation. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Havoc Campaign - Mission Pool and Mutator Rotation</div>Every third week during a Havoc Campaign, we are rotating the mission pool and mutator pool. One or two missions and mutators will swap out during this time. The next rotation will be on May 26, 2025.<br/><br/><b>Mission Pool</b><br/><i>Incoming</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Silo Cluster<br/></li><li>Smelter Complex</li></ul><i>Outgoing</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Chasm Station<br/></li><li> Chasm Logistratum</li></ul><b>Mutators</b><br/><i>Incoming</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cranial Corruption</li></ul><i>Outgoing</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Blight Spreads</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some clipping issues on the Veteran “Dutiful Privateer Garb” lowerbody cosmetic.<br/></li><li> Fixed physics on Veteran "Truskan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)" upperbody cosmetic to move more lifelike.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Zealot “Opulent Diadem” headgear cosmetic would remove facial hair.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/527594979204268428</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/7a1811257dd96b973695fcedd6b1b2b8a035d3ac.png"/><br/><br/>​Greetings everyone!<br/><br/>Today, we’re releasing Hotfix 6.1.4, bringing new fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III. We are bringing to you a variety of improvements including fixes to AI army movement range not displaying correctly, Ogre Camp spawn locations, and some misbehaving skills and traits.<br/><br/>Without further ado, let’s get into it.<br/><br/>— Anastasija Dolgošejeva // Senior Community Manager // Your friendly neighbourhood penguin<br/><br/>👉 Check out full Hotfix 6.1.4 notes here 👈<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Skulls - Tune in for news and to celebrate Warhammer!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/812447750630146186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>It’s that time of the year when blood is in the air and skulls are waiting to be lopped off. The Warhammer Skulls event returns on <b>May 22nd</b>, alongside our <b>in-game Skulls for the Skull Throne event!</b> <i>But could there be something else coming…?</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/ba3f1a5ac36c110931940789b30042ea630bbf4b.png"/><br/><br/>Every year, the Warhammer Community celebrates the digital world of Warhammer with this event where we showcase existing and upcoming games in the Warhammer universe, and we’ll be there!<br/><br/>On Thursday May 22nd, make sure to tune into the official Warhammer Skulls stream at <b>6 PM CEST / 9 AM US Pacific time</b> to catch the event. There’ll be announcements for <b>Warhammer: Vermintide 2</b> as well as<b> Warhammer 40K: Darktide</b>.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wEonJHkA9ZU?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed Freeks 1.0 Launches on May 22nd</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/541105873081074235</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI LADZ, WE’Z BACK!<br/><br/>Hey all you freeks that love speed, here’s the big news we were talking about…<br/><br/>SPEED FREEKS is leaving early access and <b>launching version 1.0 next week on May 22nd</b>, the same day of the <b>Warhammer SKULLS</b> showcase.<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/845eabe737acbb6705f39c2d0e3c2ae015a32278.png"/><br/><br/><br/>This 1.0 launch signifies a few major things, one being that we’ve got a new publisher, <b>Wired Productions</b>.  Why does this matter to you?  Well, with this publishing switch-up comes big changes to the way the game currently works, meaning <b>it’s no longer Free-to-Play</b> (which had most of its content behind a paywall), and instead is <b>now a low-priced game</b> that comes with the majority of its content included.<br/>---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/>An important note for those of you who played the early access version of the game: you will be getting the launch version for <b>free</b>!  It’s already in your library and will update to 1.0 on May 22nd.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>Us moving away from F2P also means that we can do things like:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Have <b>player-hosted matches</b> with custom settings, including creating bots-only games if desired<br/></li><li>Have <b>private games</b> functionality<br/></li><li>Add a <b>new Free-Roam mode</b> to explore any map and create <b>custom races</b> - an awesome feature that helps illustrate how much more agency players have over the game<br/></li><li><b>Remove the 3rd party PROS account</b> that was previously mandatory</li></ul>Plenty more things to reveal, including <b>new content</b> as well, but you'll have to wait until launch day!<br/><br/>Now, to finalize the conversion of moving the game away from F2P, we’ll need to take it offline for a couple days, so <b>SPEED FREEKS WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE TO PLAY from Tuesday May 20th until Thursday the 22nd, when the game launches version 1.0</b>. We apologize for the inconvenience, but this is a necessary step towards launching with the new changes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/><br/>In the meantime, we hope you have a wonderful weekend, and we’ll say that we’re very excited to see how everyone likes the revamped and improved full launch of Speed Freeks!<br/><br/>---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/>Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks will be available May 22nd at a <b>special discounted price of just $15.99, 15.99€ and £12.99</b>.<br/><br/>Prepare to GET STUCK IN!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/45e28095664ec8f8352612f4ff3fe3b58e7e3b76.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big News Incoming Tomorrow + Temporary Downtime</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/541105873081073854</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI LADZ!  Quick one here...<br/><br/>We needed to drop a heads up about some <i><b>very</b></i> exciting SPEED FREEKS news we'll be sharing tomorrow, May 16th!<br/><br/>Unfortunately, as a byproduct of the exciting changes, the game is going to be unavailable to download for new players for a period of time while we re-tool some things on the backend. Existing players will be unable to connect to matchmaking and play during this period.<br/><br/>This downtime was something we expected to occur tomorrow afternoon, but ended up taking effect 12 hours earlier than anticipated - so we apologize for the inconvenience. But we expect that our players will be quite happy with what we are going to reveal once we do.<br/><br/>We'll share additional information ASAP as to when players can can get back to racin' n' krumpin', plus drop the exciting news about the future of the Speed Freeks tomorrow.  We're eager to share...<br/><br/>SEE YOU'Z THEN!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
