<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.190 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732839</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We don't want to keep you waiting, so another hotfix for some of the most commonly reported issues is up!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Beware of possible spoilers below:<br/><br/>Patch notes:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In some circumstances, the Lord Captain would never get their original form back after the Feudal World of Thassera, resulting in a narrative inconsistency and a loss of access to inventory and levelling - fixed;<br/></li><li> The third combat on Commorragh arena sometimes never ended after all the enemies were defeated - fixed;</li></ul><br/>Note that because we wanted to deploy these fixes as early as possible, these two changes <b>will not be retroactive</b>, which means you will need to reload an earlier save if you want to continue playing right now. <b>Existing saves with this problem will be repaired a bit later, with one of the following updates.</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.188</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732802</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The first hotfix for the new expansion is live, dealing with some of the reported issues over the last night.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Beware of possible spoilers below:<br/><br/><b>Patch notes:</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Abelard could become missing in Commorragh if the Lex Imperialis expansion was activated in Act III. Fixed, let's not have the dear senechal suffer even more!<br/></li><li> If the first Abelard's quest was failed or skipped, it was impossible to start the expansion content from a save in Act 4 due to the lack of the quest NPC - fixed;<br/></li><li> For the first arena of Commorragh, it was possible to get 3 companions if Solomorne, Abelard and Argenta were in the party - fixed, Abelard will come after the first arena in this case;</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Imperialis Twitch Drops!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523094550774809104</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
To supplement the launch of the Lex Imperialis, we're launching a new Twitch Drops campaign! <br/><br/>Starting right now and up until July 15, watch your favourite streamers play the new expansion and have a lot of fun discussing your impressions while you earn exclusive in-game items!<br/><br/>https://roguetrader.owlcat.games/drops<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/5600c899165155b4c24ede0780323323dd16aeef.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abelard, announce that the Lex Imperialis expansion is out!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523094550774809098</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Abelard, announce that the Lex Imperialis expansion for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader is out! <br/><br/>Unravel the dark secrets of the von Valancius dynasty as you navigate a perilous web of justice, duty, and betrayal over 15 hours of thrilling narrative-driven gameplay integrated into the main campaign. Meet the Adeptus Arbites, the unyielding guardians of Imperial Law, and join forces with the new companion hailing from their ranks – the grim and relentless Solomorne Anthar and his loyal cyber-mastiff Glaito.<br/><br/>Become an Arbitrator yourself with the new origin, employ cybernetic familiars with the new Overseer archetype, and expand your tactics with the new available type of combat equipment – shields!<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3622820/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Lex_Imperialis/<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dh9lu23PCiA?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abelard, introduce the large update 1.4.0!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523094550774809094</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Abelard, introduce the 1.4.0 update that supplements the launch of the Lex Imperialis Expansion!<br/><br/>This update focuses on cleaning up and polishing many aspects of the game, including mechanics, visuals, audio and co-op experience. Please note that while this update is big, <u>this is not yet the major update we talked about earlier</u> - we decided that Lex Imperialis deserves its own large version number. The previously mentioned update will be referred to as <b>1.5 </b>from now on.<br/><br/>PLEASE DON'T FORGET TO UPDATE YOUR MODS!<br/><br/><b>Highlights:</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shields and associated talents have been added to the game for all players;<br/></li><li> Rykad Minoris was updated with the presence of the Adeptus Arbites faction for all players;<br/></li><li> All shotguns now cost baseline 1 AP to shoot;<br/></li><li> Area effect from Arc Rifles now works correctly;<br/></li><li> Fixed a lot of desync issues in co-op;<br/></li><li> It is now possible to turn off action camera in void combat;<br/></li><li> Improvements to many cutscenes;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing on many locations;<br/></li><li> Various bugfixes for items, abilities and narrative;<br/></li><li> Many visual fixes to locations, characters, objects and animations;<br/></li><li> A lot of audio fixes: corrections to VO, new and updated sounds;</li></ul><br/><b><u>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</u></b><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">System and stability</div><br/><b>Crashes and softlocks</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash occurring during loading to the introductory cutscene with the Death Cult on consoles;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases where skipping a cutscene could break the game;<br/></li><li> Fixed Abelard sometimes becoming stuck beyond the edges of the map after skipping the cutscene with the pillar in the Prologue;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where cutscene animations that were turned off when the combat began were re-enabled if you loaded a save in combat, leading to AI skipping turns;<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple cases where animations didn't stop correctly when cutscene ended, causing possible visual and mechanical bugs;<br/></li><li> Game could end up in a black screen when trying to skip the Electrodynamic Cenobium reactor blow-up cutscene - fixed;<br/></li><li> Skipping cutscenes no longer causes some NPCs to T-pose;<br/></li><li> Skipping a cutscene with the Patriarch no longer causes a black screen;<br/></li><li> Fixed a combat softlock caused by Iconoclast Conviction ability Transcend the Potential which sometimes grayed out all buttons;</li></ul><br/><b>Lag and freezing</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a problem that appeared in many battles across the game, where if the combat started from a cutscene, random units could sometimes get stuck for 30-60 seconds doing nothing;<br/></li><li> Fixed some cases of lag when using burst attacks;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Narrative</div><br/><b>General</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After sending Cassia off your voidship (you monster!), her servant now disappears with her;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Vincent Gaprak and Hetka Sauerback had no interaction on the voidship bridge;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with conditions that sometimes caused the Three Sorrowful Phalanges quest to be impossible to complete;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with a certain set of decisions that could cause the Bloodspun Web Temple to become empty, blocking the playthrough;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases where dialogues with only the Rogue Trader present were using the stats of other party members for skill checks;<br/></li><li> Heinrix no longer comments on the blood bath event if he's not on the voidship;<br/></li><li> In the final romance event with Marazhai, the Rogue Trader now remembers how they already tried to kiss him;<br/></li><li> Killing Zacchary Weisz now ends the quests associated with him;<br/></li><li> Nomos no longer reappears in Act IV if the Rogue Trader denied or ignored their presence;<br/></li><li> One of the dialogue options at the Inquisition Shipwreck softlocked the game - fixed;<br/></li><li> The name for planet Jessevon from the Three Sorrowful Plalanges wasn't displayed on the maps, and players struggled finding it. The name is now displayed and it should be easier to track the planet;<br/></li><li> Updated the animations in the cutscene with Abelard in the Blood Ties quest to better match the text description;<br/></li><li> Updated the dialogue with the wounded Drukhari in Marazhai's quest;</li></ul><br/><b>Act I</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rykad Minoris has seen some changes related to the introduction of the Adeptus Arbites. The first encounter with them will be available even for the players without the DLC;<br/></li><li> The malfunctioning cogitator at the Electrodynamic Cenobium now correctly reacts to the skill check;</li></ul><br/><b>Act II</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where after saving Achilleas during the siege of the von Valancius palace, he could disappear after the cutscene;<br/></li><li> Fixed an incorrect speaker during the ascension ceremony, where Governor Urbend Drivestem should be talking, not Brasswhisper;<br/></li><li> Jae no longer randomly changes her outfit during her first personal quest;<br/></li><li> Denying Yrliet's assistance and servitorising the rebel in the residence at the same time could leave the player with no options for discovering the rebel base, locking the game - fixed;</li></ul><br/><b>Act III</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Achilleas is no longer displayed as Error Speaker in one of the dialogues in Act III;<br/></li><li> Improved the scene with removing augmentations from a wounded gladiator in Commorragh. You can now see the descriptive text, and the option to remove the augmentation only disappears after successfully doing it, rather than after the first attempt;<br/></li><li> You can now attack Malice after the arena without any further discussion;</li></ul><br/><b>Act IV</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Jae will now approach the Rogue Trader much closer in the cutscene during the conversation about her second quest;<br/></li><li> After Jae's party in the Adeptus Amasecus, Rogue Trader now properly wakes up undressed;<br/></li><li> Getting rid of Falco in Jae's quest counted as failed even if she killed him - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed an incorrect speaker case during the war council before Eufrates-II;<br/></li><li> Fixed an incorrect speaker in the Blood Ties quest when talking to Drivestem family;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Blood Ties quest where it could become impossible to order any execution;<br/></li><li> Fixed Error Speaker cases at Salis Prime;<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple cases of incorrect speaker in the dialogue with the Aeldari at Quetza Temer;<br/></li><li> Heinrix no longer inserts himself into the war council before Eufrates-II when he's not on the voidship;<br/></li><li> It is no longer possible to begin Death Has Whispered Your Name quest without Kibellah in your party;<br/></li><li> The dialogue in Jae's second quest no longer begins in the middle of combat;<br/></li><li> The event with Falco sometimes didn't trigger for Jae - fixed;<br/></li><li> You can no longer inquire Argenta about Salis Prime if the quest has already been completed or failed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mechanics</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shields, talents and ability updates associated with them have been added to the game;<br/></li><li> Bladedancer's abilities that cost wounds no longer spend more wounds because of the effects that increase the Bladedancer's direct damage;<br/></li><li> Chorda's Pyromancer will no longer burn allies with Inflame, they became a lot more careful;<br/></li><li> Damage over Time effects no longer scale with difficulty;<br/></li><li> Difficulty settings no longer influence skill checks made for using items or abilities;<br/></li><li> Executioner's Exsanguination ability used on the caster now correctly provides additional MP;<br/></li><li> Experience is now always correctly awarded for Ulfar's quest;<br/></li><li> Experience is now correctly awarded for puzzles in the Voidship Shrine;<br/></li><li> Extermination no longer works with DoT effects, in accordance to its description;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where after killing Kibellah she disappeared with all her inventory;<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare bug where an invisible negative effect was doing constant damage to the party after Salis Prime;<br/></li><li> Fixed the debuff given to Ulfar and RT as a part of the Lone Wolf quest;<br/></li><li> Force Swords' Psychic Force attack now correctly increases Veil Degradation by 3, as all other Major Psychic Powers;<br/></li><li> Movement abilities (like Dash or Charge) now correctly reset the Bead of Concentration bonus;<br/></li><li> Plaguebearers and similar units now only use Second Wind once per combat as described;<br/></li><li> Press the Advantage's damage bonus no longer applies to incorrect damage instances;<br/></li><li> Slightly increased allied Electro-Priests' MP at Electrodynamic Cenobium. They will also now use Impact damage attack against fellow Electro-Priests instead of Shock attack (which used to heal the enemy);<br/></li><li> The negative effect of using Desperate Measures version of Daring Breach is now visible to player;<br/></li><li> The smelly buff from Footfall now displays the actual malus to Fellowship (-30);<br/></li><li> Using Slash ability no longer removes Defensive Stance bonus, as described;<br/></li><li> Vanguard could pick a wrong route to the target during their Heroic Act Unyielding Guard, which could cause a failure in reaching the target due to the lack of MP - fixed;<br/></li><li> Vanguard Heroic Act/Desperate Measures were improved. Vanguard will move to the target to perform melee attack if possible or use a ranged weapon overwise. Also fixed the weapon sometimes visually disappearing during the animation of the ability;<br/></li><li> You can no longer change your weapon loadout during the activation of long abilities such as Blade Dance;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All shotguns and shotgun pistols now cost 1 AP to shoot;<br/></li><li> Arc rifles weren't doing damage with their chain hits - fixed;<br/></li><li> Multiple items in Commorragh were not in the loot tables by mistake - they will all now drop normally!<br/></li><li> Made a consistency a consistency pass on all shotgun descriptions;<br/></li><li> Consistency pass on Las weapons' descriptions and their inventory interaction sounds;<br/></li><li> [Kiava Gamma Pattern] Omnissian Axe was missing the Sweep ability - fixed;<br/></li><li> [Mars-Pattern] Chainaxe was missing its usage restrictions - fixed;<br/></li><li> [Mezoa-Pattern] Bolt Pistol was not able to burst-fire in melee - fixed;<br/></li><li> Ancient Force Sword's armour penetration bonus was not stacking from DoT effects - fixed;<br/></li><li> Blade Runner Bodyglove worked even if the wielder had less than 50 AGI or above 50% health - fixed, it now works according to its description;<br/></li><li> Blasters are now correctly identified as Xeno Cargo;<br/></li><li> Changed Chainsword damage from 8-10 to 7-9;<br/></li><li> Cloak Of Hatred now displays correctly when equipped on Chorda;<br/></li><li> Crimson Rage now works in all cases according to its description;<br/></li><li> Cultist Hood now only works once per turn. No more infinite Ignite during Finest Hour, sorry!<br/></li><li> Description for the Gloves of Self Sacrifice now includes the duration of the bonus;<br/></li><li> Drained Farseer in the Secret Wing of the Laboratory in Act III now has new loot - The Staff of Krudarach;<br/></li><li> Edge of the Irrevocable had incorrect prerequisites - fixed;<br/></li><li> Edge of the Irrevocable is now a two-handed sword;<br/></li><li> Effects of Force Swords now correctly scale if psy rating of the wielder changed after equipping the sword;<br/></li><li> Elixir of Warp Neutrality will now work correctly when the user deals warp damage to themselves;<br/></li><li> Fixed heretically incorrect interaction between Tainted Phylactery and Know No Heresy;<br/></li><li> Ghost Sword now has correct Aeldari visuals;<br/></li><li> Gladiator's Healing Kit now works correctly for characters with Know No Heresy talent;<br/></li><li> Increased the Omnissian Axe damage to 10-14;<br/></li><li> Mercy's Gift did not provide +15 Fellowship bonus when there were no enemies in a 4-tile radius of the wearer - fixed;<br/></li><li> Parrying with any swords with Fencing Boots equipped did not trigger a counterattack - fixed;<br/></li><li> Shots from certain Foehammers were considered Bursts instead of AoE attacks. Also, returned missing flavor text to them;<br/></li><li> Some Solid-projectile sniper rifles were missing +50% overpenetration bonus - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some Stimulators had different colors in the inventory and on the ability panel - fixed;<br/></li><li> Temporary Wounds provided by Warp Conductor Gloves no longer stack;<br/></li><li> Tervantias the Archmachinator now correctly sells Craftworld Power Sword. Turns out it was behind that box of spleens;<br/></li><li> Tervantias the Archmachinator now drops Warp-Focusing Staff. Better not ask where he stored it;<br/></li><li> The Peripheral Visor Goggles are no longer attached to the character's eye movement, which caused creepy movement and blinking;<br/></li><li> Triumph of Retribution's effect now correctly only triggers on kills made with it;<br/></li><li> Unholy Shard will now correctly trigger only for toxic damage;<br/></li><li> Updated Daredevil Pistol description with its unique ability;<br/></li><li> Warp Horrors immunity from Denial of Nightmares was incorrectly lost in some cases - fixed. This update also removes Warp Horrors effect incorrectly applied while wearing this item;<br/></li><li> Webber was incorrectly available for purchase from the Explorators for players that didn't purchase the Void Shadows DLC - fixed. This update won't take away the item from players that have already got it. Finders keepers!<br/></li><li> Dark Lance was returned to Kasballica vendor. It's available at reputation level 6 for 64 Profit Factor.<br/></li><li> Staff for Trevor Cassini was changed to Yu'Vath Glass Staff. Players that have already killed him will receive the staff automatically.<br/></li><li> Woebringer's special attack wasn't getting the damage bonus - fixed;<br/></li><li> Wolf Tooth Necklace now correctly drops from Doomscream. It was stuck in his teeth, but we got it out;<br/></li><li> You can no longer put Cranial Implant into cargo;<br/></li><li> You can now correctly use Tyrant needle pistol in melee range;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Locations</div><br/><b>General</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A lot of minor updates to clickable interaction icons text and placement across the game;<br/></li><li> Added proper skybox to the Rogue Trader palace at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> At the Voidship Shrine from the Void Shadows expansion, background NPCs on the balconies will now be dissolved correctly when turning the camera;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases where the Fog of War was revealed incorrectly before the player actually visited that part of the zone;<br/></li><li> Fixed an incorrect placement for the interaction marker at the secret room in Dargonus palace;<br/></li><li> Fixed some Iconoclast decorations at Dargonus to prevent NPCs clipping through them during second Kibellah's quest;<br/></li><li> Fixed the incorrect movement of an elevator at the Astropathic Chapel on the voidship;<br/></li><li> Improved lighting in the Warrant Chamber;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing at Footfall;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing at Phton-IV;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing at the Chartist vessel;<br/></li><li> Improved the camera angles and timing in the cutscene where Jae argues with Clementia;<br/></li><li> Improved the pathing at Footfall Sewers;<br/></li><li> NPC in the von Valancius palace that talks about the painting is now standing near the painting;<br/></li><li> Removed some excessive NPC icons from the minimap at Footfall;<br/></li><li> Nobles in the von Valancius Palace no longer stand inside the candles during the Blood Ties quest;<br/></li><li> The NPC commoner carrying a crate no longer constantly gets stuck on Footfall;</li></ul><br/><b>Prologue and Act I</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed visible edges of the map on Rykad Minoris;<br/></li><li> Minor improvements to the Navigator Chamber in the Prologue;<br/></li><li> One of the buildings at Rykad Minoris wasn't dissolving correctly, causing annoyance with the camera - fixed;<br/></li><li> Removed an incorrect pathable tile hanging in mid-air at Eurac V near Cassia's statue;<br/></li><li> Removed the odd pause before soldier deaths at the interrogation cutscene on Eurac V;<br/></li><li> Some floating objects at the Star Port on Rykad Minoris are now again affected by gravity;<br/></li><li> You can no longer trigger Heinrix's appearance cutscene mid-combat at the Electrodynamic Cenobium;</li></ul><br/><b>Act II</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added additional cover elements to the von Valancius palace siege at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Fixed pathing issues on the Gutted Voidship;<br/></li><li> Fixed the Distress Signal Source location not having a name on the minimap;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing at the station during the encounter with Achilleas before Act III;</li></ul><br/><b>Act III</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cursor no longer targets hidden walls in the Drukhari ambush before Act III;<br/></li><li> Fixed a visual issue where revisiting the location caused the gates to the Anatomical Opera in Act III to appear closed even if they were already open earlier;<br/></li><li> Improved the cutscene of releasing Heinrix in Commorragh;<br/></li><li> Removed some invisible walls in the ambush encounter before the Act III;<br/></li><li> Some objects didn't provide cover as expected in the Anver fight on Footfall - fixed;<br/></li><li> Tervantias the Archmachinator and Ulfar are now marked on the minimap as important characters in Commorragh;</li></ul><br/><b>Act IV</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the positioning of an unreachable loot container at the Smuggler Hideout, and added missing difficulty of a skill check on the same location;<br/></li><li> Drukhari Camp in Marazhai's quest now correctly displays the location name;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of bugs with Drukhari animations at the Drukhari camp;<br/></li><li> Added minimap tooltip and location exit marker for the Drukhari camp;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing, fixed missing loot, added traps and improved cutscenes at the Drukhari camp in Marazhai's quest;<br/></li><li> Improved the starting camera angle and party placement for the Drukhari camp;</li></ul><br/><b>Act V</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After failing a Lore (Xenos) check for one of the Necron obelisks on the Epitaph, it was incorrectly displayed to be repeatable with a multikey - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed Marazhai's positioning during the gathering before landing on the Epitaph;<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple cases with floating corpses on the Epitaph;<br/></li><li> Improved pathing at the Epitaph;<br/></li><li> Made minor improvements to the final cutscene with Nomos;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Visual</div><br/><b>General</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Loading the game no longer resets the color of character outfits;<br/></li><li> Added a cutscene for the decision to end the life of the old servant at Janus;<br/></li><li> Added drinking horns to the scene where Ulfar and Rogue Trader cheer for the fallen warriors;<br/></li><li> Camera no longer wanders off from Kibellah during her intro dialogue;<br/></li><li> Emelina in Heinrix's quest no longer remains standing if she is dead;<br/></li><li> Female Lord Captains will now keep their heads slightly above the water when at the pool in their quarters. No more drowning!<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with units sometimes getting stuck in running animation if Charge ability was used when combat ended;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few cases where the Lord Captain was sitting in mid-air near the throne or chair;<br/></li><li> Fixed a minor lighting issue at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of cases with T-posing corpses;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of clipping issues with helmets and character ears;<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare major lighting bug at the end of Act I;<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping on one of the selectable beards;<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect camera in one of the Blood Ties quest cutscenes;<br/></li><li> Fixed some minor geometry issues on Heinrix's neck;<br/></li><li> Fixed some pipes and wires clipping through the carpet on the Iconoclast bridge;<br/></li><li> Fixed the camera position in one of Cassia's romance cutscenes;<br/></li><li> Fixed twitching after death for the Patriarch;<br/></li><li> Fixed Yrliet's sitting animation so that she no longer hovers above the object she's sitting on;<br/></li><li> Grounded a levitating astropath in the Astropathic chapel;<br/></li><li> Improved the placement of various items on the character model in the character screen to reduce clipping;<br/></li><li> Improved the cutscene at Electrodynamic Cenobium;<br/></li><li> Improved the visuals of Nocturne of Oblivion appearing and disappearing;<br/></li><li> Kibellah no longer becomes bald when wearing certain helmets;<br/></li><li> Minor improvements to Kibellah's face;<br/></li><li> Numerous minor visual bug fixes for objects on locations;<br/></li><li> One of Enforcer helmets used incorrect geometry - fixed;<br/></li><li> Target line and path preview in combat were not visible in some cases for units bigger than 1 cell - fixed;<br/></li><li> The dead Gaprak house member in the Blood Ties quest no longer breathes;<br/></li><li> Turning off helmet no longer turns off all the visuals of the Dragonscale Power Armour;<br/></li><li> Cultists of Nurgle will no longer T-pose when attacking with their swords;</li></ul><br/><b>Animations</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added visual effects and improved animations for Nocturne of Oblivion;<br/></li><li> Fixed some broken kneeling animations;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with some Navigators of the House Orsellio being present at the court in prone animation after the battle at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Fixed some issues with cloak animations;<br/></li><li> Fixed minor issues with Ulfar animations at the character screen;<br/></li><li> Fixed the lack of animation and effects for Electropriest attacks;<br/></li><li> Fixed the twitching of animation during AoE attacks with chainsaws;<br/></li><li> Governor Vyatt no longer walks sideways after cutscenes - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some weapons such as Autocannons now correctly shoot from the weapon barrel, not the character's feet;<br/></li><li> Toxic damage caused incorrect death animations - fixed;<br/></li><li> Visual effects<br/></li><li> Veil degradation visual effects sometimes persisted after combat - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">User Interface</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A roll result of 100 caused the message to take two lines in the combat log - fixed;<br/></li><li> Added a scrollbar to the party selection window for cases when the player has a lot of companions (for example, mercenaries);<br/></li><li> Added formula calculators to items with simple [stat] (or [stat bonus]) formulas;<br/></li><li> Added minimap marker for Nomos in Act IV;<br/></li><li> Added multiple sounds to the voidship interface;<br/></li><li> Added some missing icons for abilities and talents;<br/></li><li> Added some missing icons for items.<br/></li><li> Added the Formation button to the UI on console;<br/></li><li> Colonisation window couldn't be closed during dialogue - fixed;<br/></li><li> Debuffs above the characters are now hidden while the character has a speech bubble over them, making it easier to read the speech;<br/></li><li> Empty party UI is no longer present on top of the screen during respec;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case where some UI windows could sometimes open behind other windows;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that sometimes caused the party bar on the top of the screen to disappear;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the tattoo page at the character creation screen could become stuck unless you chose a tattoo;<br/></li><li> Fixed discrepancies in color between different colony projects;<br/></li><li> Fixed some talents not being displayed in appropriate categories on the level-up screen;<br/></li><li> Long names no longer go beyond the boundaries of the dialogue window;<br/></li><li> Minor UI improvements to the quest journal screen;<br/></li><li> Numerous missing icons were added and incorrect icons were fixed for various objects and items in the game;<br/></li><li> On console, having the character selection menu open at the moment a dialogue was triggered could cause that menu to become stuck on the screen - fixed;<br/></li><li> On the Koronus Expanse map, the button to reduce the difficulty of a route sometimes twitched and blinked excessively - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some space combat encounters didn't display the XP gained - fixed;<br/></li><li> Tervantias' portrait in the initiative tracker was using the full body portrait instead of the face - fixed;<br/></li><li> Tooltip for the mirror in the captain's quarters no longer disappears after the first use;<br/></li><li> Tooltips no longer cover important UI elements on console during space exploration;<br/></li><li> Voidship Officer posts will no longer disappear;<br/></li><li> When selecting stat upgrades for multiple levels in a row, the stat changes are now displayed instantly, not after all the levels are selected;<br/></li><li> Widescreen monitors were displaying the background in the custom portrait menu distorted - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Audio</div><br/><b>Sound</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Numerous corrections of existing VO - mismatch with the text, pronunciation, etc.;<br/></li><li> Added a battlecry to the Drukhari ambush on the ladder at Santiel's Pride;<br/></li><li> Added a few panicked voices from the crowd at the Star Port on Rykad Minoris;<br/></li><li> Added a missing explosion sound to a dialogue at the Star Port on Rykad Minoris;<br/></li><li> Added a sound for throwing a coin into the fountain;<br/></li><li> Added a sound reaction to the tech priest in the encounter with the Explorator fleet;<br/></li><li> Added a sound to the sliders in the settings menu;<br/></li><li> Added a voidship level up sound;<br/></li><li> Added angry battlecries to Vladaym supporters before the battle with Chorda;<br/></li><li>  Added atmospheric sounds during the encounter with Marazhai before the entrance to Act III;<br/></li><li> Added background battle sounds at Kiava Gamma;<br/></li><li> Added crowd sounds to the Parade scene at Upperway;<br/></li><li> Added door opening sound when saving Ulfar;<br/></li><li> Added drink interaction sound at Outer Spire Halls:<br/></li><li> Added new sounds to party formation window;<br/></li><li> Added sound interaction for the clock in the captain's quarters;<br/></li><li> Added sound to console-specific inventory item change;<br/></li><li> Added sound to the small elevator at Rykad Minoris Star Port;<br/></li><li> Added sound to the weapon set selection buttons on the ability bar;<br/></li><li> Added sound when hovering over skills on the character creation screen;<br/></li><li> Added sounds for the charge stations at the Upperway;<br/></li><li> Added sounds for the huge transformator at the Upperway;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to angry nobles at the von Valancius palace during second Abelard's quest;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to the custom portrait menu in the character generation window;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to the dying mutants at Kiava Gamma manufactorum;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to the torture of Abel at the Electrodynamic Cenobium;<br/></li><li> Added the sound of parasite infestation in Commorragh;<br/></li><li> Added the sounds of pain to Abelard at Commorragh. Sorry, dear senechal!<br/></li><li> Added unique sound to the trade cargo for faction experience button;<br/></li><li> Added ventilation sounds at the Drifting Voidship;<br/></li><li> Added vox noises to the dialogue with Vigdis at the Voidship Bridge;<br/></li><li> Added vox sounds at Footfall Atrium;<br/></li><li> Added vox sounds on Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Autocannons incorrectly used the sound effects from autoguns, and should now sound more menacing;<br/></li><li> Chaos Space Marines at Kiava Gamma now have battle cries;<br/></li><li> Fixed a lot of cases with NPCs using incorrect faction for the battlecries (chaos cultists using genestealer voice set etc.);<br/></li><li> Toned down an annoying siren sound on Abandoned Landing Site;<br/></li><li> Fixed Eldritch Storm sound effects persisting after ability use;<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect VO for some Death Cultists;<br/></li><li> Fixed random hover and click sounds on the character creation screen;<br/></li><li> Fixed some lacking ambient sounds at Commorragh;<br/></li><li> Fixed the sounds of blood being spilled at Commorragh;<br/></li><li> Improved death sounds of some creatures;<br/></li><li> Improved sounds for the scene with fire and Theodora's ghost;<br/></li><li> Made Servitor footsteps quieter during dialogues;<br/></li><li> Marazhai didn't scream when using the Taunting Scream ability - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed some incorrect inventory sounds for items;<br/></li><li> Removed the distant explosion sounds when the RT arrives to the Star Port on Rykad Minoris for a second time;<br/></li><li> Replaced the sound of Necron doors, made it heavier;<br/></li><li> Sinistoria incorrectly had a male voice - fixed;<br/></li><li> Smoke grenade used incorrect sound effects - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some Drusian NPCs incorrectly used Chaos Cultist voiceover - fixed;<br/></li><li> Sound will no longer get stuck after quickly hovering over multiple buttons in the main menu;<br/></li><li> The Pain Engine at Commorragh arena now has proper sounds in the introduction cutscene;<br/></li><li> The ship crew will no longer cheer when an allied ship is damaged or destroyed in void combat;<br/></li><li> Updated sound for the opening bridge at the prison planetoid;<br/></li><li> You can no longer hear the heretical chants after killing all the cultists in Electrodynamic Cenobium;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Music</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added more tense music during the rally on the lower decks during Abelard's first quest;<br/></li><li> Added appropriate music to a book event in the Chasm;<br/></li><li> Fixed minor issues with music in Kibellah romance;<br/></li><li> Improved Chorda Introduction - added music to the cutscene and dialogue;<br/></li><li> Music will no longer randomly stop and resume during the trial in Commorragh;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Space</div><br/><b>Global Map and Rumours</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Beholding the Truth rumour didn't complete correctly - fixed;</li></ul><br/><b>Star System Exploration</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In a few rare cases the promised loot during colonisation and exploration events was never actually awarded - fixed;<br/></li><li> Star systems Adermat II and Aviorus didn't display the list of planets and resources - fixed;</li></ul><br/><b>Colony Management</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The dialogue option related to Marazhai in the Methods of the Inquisition colony event no longer appears if Marazhai is not in your retinue;<br/></li><li> Fixed the requirements and rewards descriptions for the Humiliating Visit event;<br/></li><li> Players didn't receive the reward for the part 4 of Vheabos chronicles - fixed;<br/></li><li> Visions and Revelations event now correctly displays the resources lost for the first dialogue option;</li></ul><br/><b>Space Combat and Voidship Management</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It is now possible to turn off action camera in voidship combat;<br/></li><li> Alternating between multiple cannon types and torpedoes/bombers/fighters no longer resets their cooldown;<br/></li><li> It's no longer possible to select a cell the ship, fighter or torpedo can't move into, which could cause odd clipping issues;<br/></li><li> You can now switch from fighters or bombers to torpedoes and back, regardless of cooldown on any of them;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Co-op</div><br/><b>Desyncs</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed desyncs caused by multiple Operative abilities;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs in the battle with Theobald Orsellio;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs occuring when trying to cast any damaging ability targeting genestealers;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs related to Momentum change;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs related to Veil Thickness change;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs related to skipping turn after hovering the cursor over consumables;</li></ul><br/><b>Co-op UI</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the issue where in co-op non-host players couldn't leave the character selection window after the host disconnected;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Localization</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of typos and minor formatting issues across all languages;<br/></li><li> Fixed an incorrect translation of the force weapon for Russian localization during the first encounter with Heinrix;<br/></li><li> Fixed some missing text in Chinese language;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of formatting errors in the Chinese localization;<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping and formatting issues for Chinese text;<br/></li><li> Fixed some formatting issues on the character creation screen on all languages;<br/></li><li> Fixed the formatting issues on the Scorpion Sting weapon description;<br/></li><li> Some debuff descriptions had formatting issues in German and Turkish - fixed;<br/></li><li> Some world skill checks in Commorragh didn't have descriptions - fixed;<br/></li><li> Unified the formatting for Ring descriptions on all languages;<br/></li><li> Fixed problems with text size and Turkish localisation in the console version of coop menu - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Miscellaneous</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> There is now an autosave during the preparation round before the final battle on the Epitaph;<br/></li><li> Fixed the tutorial for Bladedancer which incorrectly indicated INT as the primary stat;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
