<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.6</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4656249009455105640</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/2333528b1825f6b2be97bd29739697751fcebb32.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/> <br/>We're releasing another hotfix today to address a couple of emergent issues:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved a potential crash that could occur at the end of a turn after updating to 5.2.5.<br/></li><li> Removed references to older, unreleased content from our game files.</li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><b>DEV NOTE:</b><br/><br/>The act of removing these references in today's Hotfix will also require us to revise our active cache of rollback builds, which will temporarily remove the option to roll back to an earlier release. With this release, the available rollback builds will be set to 0, and today’s build will go on to serve as the oldest rollback version as we release new updates to the game over the coming months.<br/><br/>We apologise to all our players who currently make regular use of our rollback releases, we know how beneficial this feature has become for many of you, and the responsibility for that falls entirely on us.<br/><br/>As mentioned during the launch of version 5.2, we aim to maintain one rollback build for each category: update, patch, hotfix, and release, for a total of 4 rollback builds. This supports players running heavily modified campaigns, helping to minimize delays while their mods are updated. Each subsequent build following today’s 5.2.6 Hotfix will remain available as a rollback option until we have one build in each category - 4 in total - at which point the oldest will be replaced by a newer one.</blockquote> <br/>As always, thank you all for your feedback and bug reports. If you experience any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.2.6 please be sure to report them over in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #48 (1.5.1) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209644504997</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6c662319b9afaf3bdc458118e8ce0d010c8854ea.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Our latest hotfix #48 (1.5.1) is out now on Steam and it will shortly launch on our other platforms. <br/><br/><b>Miscellaneous Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash occurring when enabling FSR 3.1 frame generation without upscaling.</li><li>Fixed a crash occurring when applying the ‘Pierce’ Blessing to the Ogryn Kickback and Rumbler.</li><li>Fixed a crash occurring when using a controller during discard and ending up having no pre-selected weapon when going back on the screen.</li><li>The max potential stats preview will now display correctly on all weapons.</li><li>The help functionality in the Blessings screen of the Mastery menu will no longer keep the screen dim once it gets removed from the screen.</li><li>Fixed a series of typos where Strength was incorrectly showing as Power in Blessing descriptions.</li><li>Fixed a typo in the description of the “Showstopper” Blessing.</li></ul><b>Party Finder Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash that could happen while in the Party Finder menu when failing to retrieve details from joining players.</li><li>Removed hidden keyboard keybindings for starting and canceling party advertisements.</li><li>Players will now automatically get back to the Mourningstar after joining a new party while having the menu open.</li><li>Crash fix that could occur in the Party Finder menu when multiple people request to join your party.</li><li>Fixed an issue where parts of the UI in the Party Finder could fail to be correctly updated when new players joined the Strike Team.</li><li>Removed access to the Party Finder while playing the Prologue with a new character.</li></ul><b>Cosmetic Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the arms of the Veteran “Militarum Tox-Field Trench Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic would look differently sized at certain angles</li><li>Fixed an issue on the Veteran “Militarum Tox-Field Trench Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic where the sleeping bag would deform on certain body types</li><li>Removed a small black patch from the collar of the Zealot “Militarum Tox-Field Chaplain’s Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic</li><li>Fixed an issue where the cylinder on the back of the Zealot “Field-Repaired Acheron-Pattern Rebreather” headgear cosmetic would occasionally deform</li><li>Fixed an issue where the gloves on the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic would occasionally deform</li><li>Fixed an issue where a leather belt on the back of the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic clips with the jacket</li><li>Fixed an issue where the following cosmetic headgears was clipping with certain high-collared upper bodies<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Veteran “Steel Legion Flak Helmet (Parade Polish)”</li><li>Zealot “Votarist’s Pot Helm with Rebreather”</li><li>Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)”</li></ul></li><li>Fixed some clipping issues with the Ogryn “Mk IVc Pot Helm with Gas Mask (XXXXL)” headgear cosmetic</li><li>Fixed some issues with lack of movement on parts of the cosmetic backpacks “Reliquary Array” and “Artillery Carriage Spare”</li><li>Multiple fixes to the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic</li></ul><b>Known Issues</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li><b>Mastery Level Value is Missing in The Marks Swap Screen</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>When in the Marks swap screen, the Mastery level value required to obtain locked Marks may fail to be correctly displayed.</li><li>The issue is only visual, and the locked Marks will be correctly available upon reaching the required Mastery level in the weapon family.</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Information in the Sacrifice Weapon Screen Tooltip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The tooltip in Sacrifice Weapon screen incorrectly states that only Anointed (blue) rarity weapons (or higher) are able to be sacrificed.</li><li>The issue is only in the tooltip text, as the minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Visual Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li>This is only a visual rounding issue, as the actual stats total will always effectively be 380 for every weapon.</li></ul></li><li><b>Auspex Tooltip in Rolling Steel Localization Issue</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The “Move” text in the HUD tooltip when using an Auspex for the new hacking minigame in the Rolling Steel will appear localised in English but is missing in other languages.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances: Stand By For Action and Rapid Response</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>These penances were accidentally included in this release and was not supposed to be included, we will remove them in 1.5.2.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Flash used to be the working name for Operations and this two penances are two old test penances that flew under the radar, we’re sorry for any confusion stemming from this.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - Patch 3.0 (26/09/24)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696781406109497749</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Greetings Marines,</b><br/><br/>The newest patch for <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is now live, packed with new features. And YES, it brings <b>ultrawide support</b>! 😉 And YES, it adds <b>private lobbies</b> in Operations mode! 😌<br/><br/>But that's not all: there's <b>a new Sparring Arena in the Battle Barge</b>! Available while in Operations or Eternal War mode, this brand new area is accessible directly from the Launch Bay. Once there, you'll be given your weapons and grenades as if you were in a PvP match and allowed to spar it out with your Battle-Brothers ahead of your next missions. ⚔️<br/> <br/>We've also introduced the option to <b>reset custom armor and color presets</b> by replacing them with default ones instantly. You can find the complete list of improvements and changes below!<br/><br/>We truly appreciate your reports and feedback, thank you! If you have any, head over to our platform Focus Together, which  features an entire forum dedicated to Space Marine 2 as well as an "Ideas" section that is reviewed by the <i>Space Marine 2</i> teams.<br/><br/>We hope you'll enjoy the improvements brought by this update. <br/><br/>The Emperor protects! ⚔️🛡️<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><b><div class="bb_h3">New features</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>The Hub Sparring Arena</b>, a new special arena on the Battlebarge available in Operations &amp; Eternal War Game mode where players can compete in friendly PvP with the players in their squad.<br/></li><li> Ultrawide support for PC<br/></li><li> Private mode for Operation mode that gives players ability to play operation alone with bots or alongside one friend without being matchmaked with random players during the mission.<br/></li><li> Added What's New &amp; Message of the Day<br/></li><li> Added option to reset custom colour presets<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f63b315c61b276f667464e6435df0cec96b7c1b6.gif"/></li></ul><b><div class="bb_h3">Gameplay and balancing tweaks</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><b></b><li> The marking tool has been updated:</li></ul>[/b]<br/> - Improved responsiveness and comfort of Social Wheel control with a mouse <br/> - Disabled unnecessary objects that do not require highlighting and worked poorly with it <br/> - Several minor bug fixes<br/><br/><li> <b>Power Fist:</b> Damage for fully charged attacks has been greatly increased<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Heavy Plasma:</b> <br/> - Base ammo increased by 5. Blast damage radious increased. <br/> - Overheat per shoot drastically decreased from 50 to 30 for charged shoots and from 20 to 15 for base shooting. <br/> - Base damage slightly increased by 10%.<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Med Stims</b> restore contested health in addition to actual healing <br/><br/></li><li> <b>Aux grenade launcher ammo</b> now can be refilled only with the Ammo Boxes and can not be refilled from the infinite Ammo Cache</li>[/list]<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Campaign</div><u><b>Difficulty:</b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enemy aggressiveness on Veteran Difficulty in Campaign decreased for better singleplayer experience. <br/></li><li> Player's health on Veteran Difficulty in Campaign is slightly reduced to compensate for AI aggressiveness and armor management updates</li></ul><u><b>Bots:</b></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Various inhibiting restrictions were lifted, allowing bots to be more helpful and effective, while still not beating the game for the player <br/></li><li> Bots will now help focus-firing zoanthropes when the player attacks them. <br/></li><li> Heavily eased restrictions on bots finishing of enemies instead of leaving them for the player, to reduce annoyance. <br/></li><li> Bots are now allowed to help with Gargoyle objectives <br/></li><li> Fixed a variety of bugs related to bots getting stuck <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where bots can run out of ammo on weapons without a magazine</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Operations Mode</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tweaked AI Director and spawn rules of Chaos enemies in Operations mode: <br/> - Max number of Tzaangors With Shield on the arena at the same time reduced from 10 to 4 <br/> - Max number of Cultists Snipers on the arena at the same time reduced from 10 to 3<br/> - Max number of Tzaangors on the arena at the same time reduced from 30 to 20 <br/> - Max number of Rubric Marines with Boltguns on the arena at the same time reduced from 8 to 5 <br/> - Max number of Rubric Marines with Warpflamers on the arena at the same time reduced from 4 to 3<br/><br/></li><li> Perfect parry has been updated, now restores armour for killing minoris, not only for countering their special attacks<br/></li><li> Regarding Block and Fencing Weapons, a bug has been fixed in perfect parry window for fencing weapons. Now it has 20 frames window for perfect parry and 10 frames of vulnerability at the end of animation, instead of 30 frames of perfect parry for full animation as it was intended originally.<br/></li><li> Assault Class: Base groundpound damage increased by 30%<br/></li><li> Armor boost drops from destructible crates are now less common (cooldown raised from 30 secs to 60 secs)</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">PVP</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved player spawn system. It should make spawn killing more difficult<br/></li><li> Reworked Vanguard's Grapnel Launcher in PVP. Instead of full stun it will now stagger enemy and will slow him down drastically.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">AI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced ability to stunlock enemies with ranged attacks across all AI characters<br/></li><li> Accuracy of ranged enemies is reduced when attacking from off-screen and accuracy of ranged enemies is reduced when attacking melee-engaged players<br/></li><li> Regarding <b>Hormagaunts</b> and <b>Tzaangors:</b> Melee damage now deals specific amount damage instead of removing 1 complete armour segment per attack<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Zoanthrope:</b> <br/>- Increased psychic scream damage sparsing time from 0.5s to 2s to prevent one shot damage <br/>- Psychic scream damage reduced from 11 to 8 <br/>- Psychic scream effective range reduced from 50 to 40m <br/>- Psychic scream cast range is reduced by 10m<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Termagant: </b><br/> - Fleshborer spray attack damage reduced from 1 to 0.5 <br/> - Flashborer spray attack damage reduced from 0.3 to 0.1<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Tyranid Warrior with Devourer:</b> Projectile damage reduced from 0.9 to 0.6 per projectile<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Rubric Marine With Warpflamer: </b><br/>- Icon of flame damage reduced from 9 to 6 <br/>- Flamer burst damage reduced from 6 to 4 per shoot <br/>- Flamer shooting damage reduced from 6 to 4 per projectile <br/>-Health reduced by 10%<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Rubric Marine with Boltgun:</b> <br/>- Spray attack damage reduced from 1.5 to 1 <br/>- Precise shot attack (with red indicator) damage reduced from 4 to 2 per projectile <br/>- Reduced frequency of teleports used to disengage players to make them less annoying to fight Health reduced by 10%<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Tzaangor With Shield:</b> HP greatly reduced<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Carnifex: </b><br/>- Rage phase updated, carnifex becomes faster and more aggressive <br/>- Taunt frequency reduced <br/>- Fixed a bug where his cone of thorns attack wouldn't fire projectiles<br/><br/></li><li> <b>Hive Tyrant:</b> <br/>- Health slightly increased. <br/>- Resistance to explosives and melta weapons increased by 20%.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Customization </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed icon colour for the Administratum Grey, Auric Armour Gold and Celestra Grey colours<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues with default colors being wrong on some chapters (i.e. Iron Warriors)<br/></li><li> Vanguard Relic Right Greave part now requires 29 victories instead of 36<br/></li><li> Added a Colour pattern called "Greaves Pattern" allowing the player to customize bottom and top half of the leg separately</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f76463bf7443bfb7386339de132add9e691d7449.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Maps</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several issues that were preventing players from progressing within some levels<br/></li><li> Fixed a lot of minor collision issues<br/></li><li> Tweaked dust storm density and duration in Ballistic Engine operation<br/></li><li> Tweaked Heldrake fire timings on the bridge in Reliquary operation<br/></li><li> Trials can be now accessed via Hypnomat in Armoury</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">General fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where changing loadout mid operation would restore your health<br/></li><li> Improved Jump Pack Ability responsiveness<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues in Trials<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where in some rare cases controls would stop working after performing a finisher<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where player does not receive armor data from Hellbrute spawned from chaos portal<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that caused Vanguard's "Adrenaline Rush" perk description to show 1% instead of actual 10%<br/></li><li> Fixed Announcer spam in Eternal War mode<br/></li><li> Fixed multiple ways of duplicating ammo in Operations mode<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Grapnel Launcher would get canceled if overlapped by small geometry<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Tactical perk EMPEROR'S VENGEANCE did not work with Plasma Incinerator.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where several weapons could restore more than actual contested health (i.e. Meltas, AoE weapons etc)<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues that were causing loss of saves<br/></li><li> Fixed an unidentified voice at the end of the story that was assigned to the wrong character.<br/></li><li> Lots of minor UI fixes and improvements<br/></li><li> Lots of minor animation fixes and improvements<br/></li><li> Localization fixes</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event - Unrelenting Hordes- NOW LIVE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209644089925</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/54024acb9c3fca41ee18c923a532a348dadec919.jpg"/><br/><br/>A platoon of Moebian 21st soldiers has been infected by the Blight. Their armour will make them harder to deal with than the usual hordes you encounter. <br/><br/>Rannick's sure there is something afoot. Keep your eyes peeled for any clues as to what the Cult are doing.<br/><br/>Play missions with a set of new Special Conditions, “Infected Moebian 21st”, and as a team collect Grimoires or Scriptures to earn rewards.* This condition will only be available during the event and will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals.<br/><br/>*Similar to past events, the progress will be shared across all members of the strike team. <br/> <br/>This event will start on Thursday, September 26, 2024 and it will end on Thursday, October 10, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/>Note: Players will need to collect the grims on missions with the condition. It won't count if it's from any other mission. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/de41172185b98501b3f8fa68f120d15c8ff73893.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 08:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update on Maintenance for Unlocked and Loaded</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209641366647</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b1aabf58ac8086f06ba6bdef51aeffdd37373329.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>We put this message in the patch notes, but it’s been missed by some so we’re dedicating a post to it, as well. <br/><br/>As you might imagine, transferring over all the weapons and blessings in the game for our existing players –  from the old system to our new system – is a huge task. <br/><br/>There are two important things to note.<br/><br/><b>First</b>, we have disabled certain Mastery and Shrine of the Omnissiah features, as well as the Armory Exchange and Melk’s Requisitorium while the update is continuing to roll out. <br/><br/>This means if you’re checking things right now, you will not see any progress or mastery. <i>However, it does not mean you lost it. </i><br/><br/>While this is happening, we’ve received reports that some players have not been granted the Mastery or Blessings they’re owed. It is likely due to logging in after the above maintenance had started. We’ll let players know when they can log in and check their Mastery progression.<br/><br/><b>Second</b>, some players are experiencing crashes. If players are running the game with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation enabled, and they are tabbing between the exclusive full screen and windows, they may crash. Further, if players run FSR 3.1 Frame Generation, but without any upscaling enabled (such as FSR 3.1, DLSS or XESS), they will crash upon entering the Mourningstar. <br/><br/>The current workaround is to:<br/><ol><li> Use borderless fullscreen;<br/></li><li> If they’re running the game with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation: Enable one of the Upscaling alternatives (FSR 3.1, DLSS or XESS).</li></ol>Alternatively:<br/><ol><li> Disable FSR 3.1 Frame Generation</li></ol>^ <i>We are working on a fix for this to be included in a hot fix. </i><br/>Thank you for your patience today as we work to get everyone up and running again soon. <br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
