<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment arrives on 4th December</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535302985</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/ac94b5045e13b8a8fbd6b97e27ff31baec418906.png"/><br/><br/>​The time has come to reveal that our next Total War: WARHAMMER III DLC, Tides of Torment, arrives on December 4th! This pack includes a terrifying trio of Legendary Lords for the High Elves, Slaanesh and Norsca, and it will be released alongside Update 7.0, which introduces new battle units, campaign features and narrative, free content, and tweaks and fixes for all owners of the game.<br/><br/>You’ll be able to purchase the Tides of Torment as a complete bundle or as individual Legendary Lord content packs, allowing you to decide how you purchase this DLC.<br/><br/>And now, it’s time to see the Tides of Torment trailer:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rhJ1ps1n65k?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ FULL BLOG HERE 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.3.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/567015514185924975</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/92a3cce381835885f02feb4863e9427bfd632a37.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just rolled out Hotfix 6.3.4 for Total War: WARHAMMER III. This time round, we focused on four key areas of improvement; fixes for idle AI, Chaos Dwarfs not recruiting enough high-tier units, Golgfag Maneater idle issues, and improvements to how the Ogre Kingdoms AI uses Camps. Additional fixes across battle and campaign are also being implemented in this hotfix, and you can read the full list of everything included in the release notes linked below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">👉 READ THE FULL HOTFIX 6.3.4 NOTES HERE 👈</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Our teams will now switch their focus to readying 7.0 for it's release on December 4th, alongside the release of Tides of Torment. We have reserved ample patching time to follow up on any issues we want to address following 7.0's release and before we break for the Holidays, but Campaign AI will return as a focus for us in the new year. Whilst we've been able to address many of the impactful issues highlighted in recent months, there's more that we want to do, and we'll be looking to return to this topic as soon as we're able.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll share more details on what’s coming up after this when we can, and in the meantime, thank you for your patience while we work on maintaining and improving WH3.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Until then, see you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— Steve // Senior Community Manager</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash Hotfix</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/574898633352151229</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">We noticed a nasty crash slipped through the cracks, so that's been fixed now ːsteamthumbsupː</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Other notes:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We're also aware that there's issues with a couple vehicle kits going invisible due to the new code around proximity fading when the camera is close to it. We're looking into why this is happening. In the meantime if you could please use a different kit temporarily, would be great.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Steam Deck</b> still has pretty bad performance issues that we're looking into. They seemingly popped up in one of the summertime patches, so we're narrowing down which change could have caused it. Apologies for the issue, we're on top of it though</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We are also looking into server host performance, as hosting a full server can be pretty heavy on a player's PC. Hopefully improving performance here will help with any server desync issues as well</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">We're working on fixing other things as well, plus finishing up the <b>Creation Mode</b> <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> + <b>Workshop</b> for release later this month.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Stay tuned for more news on that</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix for silly things + Deffkopta Rokkits</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/686362177252099430</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Quick one ladz. We needz ta fix sumfin' we'z dun mess'd up ːsteamfacepalmː</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A hotfix patch has just been pushed with:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Deffkopta falling over drunk in various menu screens</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Stompa desync in Kill Konvoy - Scrap In Da Yard</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with wheeled vehicles getting squished/warped when switching to them from Deffkopta. Yes, you read that right</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with Squigbuggy Tires kit being <span class="bb_strike">purple</span> invisible</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with some rims not using proximity fade like other items</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with accessories not being properly attached to Deffkopta</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed Deffkopta <b>drop</b> rokkits to have same proximity fuse and impact radius as the default rokkits</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Fanks fer playin', ya gits!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash Fixes! + Deffkopta Changes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/686362177252098883</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">OI YOU'Z GITS!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This isn't the spookiest of Halloween updates, but it's certainly an Orky one - Or is it? We're fixing things, not breaking them...</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><div class="bb_h3">Alright, some big <b>stability</b> updates first:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with <b>vehicle explosions</b> causing crazy forces and lagging the entire server</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved overall stability and fixed <b>crashing</b> associated with some maps. Hopefully this helps disband the <i>fatal error gang</i> for good ːsteamthumbsupː</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash for systems using an <b>Intel Arc GPU</b></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some performance improvements to various maps</p></li></ul><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some extra things in this update:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a <b>fade</b> function to vehicles so when the camera gets close to it, they don't block the entire view. This is mostly a change to help players aim at <b>Deffkoptas</b> flying around/above them</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added updated main menu buttons in preparation for the HUGE upcoming <b>level editor</b> update</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with Stompa desyncing in <i>Scrap In Da Yard</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deffkopta kits now show in the UI even if not unlocked yet</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Hid some unused Ork animations in Kustomize</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some audio optimizations</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Steam Deck</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">We're still figuring out what went wrong here that's causing extreme performance issues, but we think we have a lead on what's happening and can pinpoint the game update that started the issues. Hoping to have a fix soon, apologies for the wait.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>DEFFKOPTA 🚁</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Most people have been loving piloting this little guy and wreaking havoc from the skies - but some of you gits haven't enjoyed being on the receiving end of the Deffkopta's aerial wrath. Thank you everyone for all the feedback and meta discussion, it's been very fun to read!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've made some changes that we hope will be received well, with the Deffkopta still being a formidable opponent, but less frustrating to fight against:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Deffkopta now has two primary weapon options: <b>Kopta Rokkits</b> and <b>Kopta Drop Rokkits</b>. The Drop Rokkits are the ability you've already experienced.</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>To sum up the difference, the Kopta Rokkits are a shorter range, easier to hit weapon that has a bit of bonus damage when used at the limit of its range. The Drop Rokkits can be fired much further, but are more difficult to hit and don't have access to the bonus damage.</i></p></blockquote></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Drop Rokkit damage reduced to 11 (from 14)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkits (the new default weapon) deal 9 damage in close range, and 14 damage when hitting targets over 50m away. Missile and trail VFX change to show rokkit instability (meaning higher damage) after flying 50 meters.</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>14 damage is the original missile damage value, which you now only have access to at a distance. We found that Deffkoptas hovering directly over your head was not that fun to fight, so we've added an incentive to adopt more of a hit and run playstyle: use your bomb and melee coooldowns, and then retreat to a short distance away to get max damage from your rokkits.</i></p></blockquote></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkit explodes after 100m (compared to Drop Rokkit 200m)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta Rokkit impact radius is 8 (compared to Drop Rokkit 6), and proximity fuse radius is 6 compared to Drop Rokkit 4)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Projectile spread/inaccuracy removed from all Deffkopta Rokkits.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased hit box size slightly, extended it downwards to help with vehicle-on-vehicle body blocking (ie. bomb defense)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Spinning Blades ability now has less ability to change momentum when turning</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Spinning Blades cooldown increased to 7 seconds (from 5)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shows the correct health value in the help screen (100, not 110)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Kopta weight reduced to 4k (from 5k)</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>This makes the Deffkopta take more knockback from weapons, and jump higher from its own bomb knockback.</i></p></blockquote></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>OTHER VEHICLES</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Scrapjet Combat Rokkit damage reverted to 25 (from 30)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">So yeah, this is the first round of DK changes after reading everyone's initial feedback. Our goal is to keep what makes the Deffkopta fun while also improving the experience of fighting against it, and also to simplify things overall but add a bit of complexity for those who want it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since you've played the Deffkopta a certain way already, it will feel a bit different at first. Please give these changes a bit of time to sink in, and we look forward to reading everyone's thoughts and opinions on the update.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3720867577dc70f8d92cdb3f88e031c027cddfed.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>WOT'Z COMIN'</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">A reminder that the next big update includes the <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> (with online workshop support) and a ton of wacky custom maps ready to play.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">It will be the biggest, most game-changing update the game has ever seen and we are very excited to watch the community adopt the tools and have a ton of fun making their own maps.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">WORKSHOP</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The <b>WORKSHOP</b> will have a rating system and we'll highlight player creations in the main menu of the game, too.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Some players will be able to access the level editor ahead of launch to put their creations on the workshop in advance - more details on this in a future post.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Really pumped for this, it's a huge feature for the game and we don't think our players truly understand yet how much it elevates the game :)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/> </p><div class="bb_h3">Thanks for playin' our Orky game</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, we appreciate our players and their dedication to Speed Freeks. We're actively trying to get new players in as it's more fun with other gits. Hope to see you ingame!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
