<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Sale 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4453592738017837701</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains and Crusaders!<br/><br/>The grand event of this fall has come — the Steam Autumn Sale is in full swing! Celebrate the arrival of winter in your favorite games and universes. Don’t miss this long-awaited event and explore the sales on Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous.<br/><br/>There’s no time to linger — the Steam Autumn Sale and the Steam Awards nominations will last only till December 4th! Learn about the awesome sales and nominate the games for the Award right now.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Just yesterday you were nothing, but fate ordered otherwise. Now you are the chosen one of the Emperor Himself, an explorer of the dark space, the ruler of an entire trade empire. You are a Rogue Trader. Choose the path you will take and lead your subjects and get Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader with a <b>40% discount</b>! Become a paragon of Humanity, a merciful leader, or bring chaos to the galaxy.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>The adventures in the Koronus Expanse don't have to end, because Your Lord or Ladyship still has much to do! Pay attention to what’s happening on your flagship, word in the compartments is something very dangerous is dwelling inside. Meet a new companion, try new archetypes, and eradicate the infection in the Void Shadows DLC, by getting the Season Pass at <b>40% off</b>. Moreover, you’ll get access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Your Rogue Trader deserves it. An alternative throne, Cherubim pet, a Firestorm-class frigate model, an epic weapon set, and digital add-ons (artbook, wallpaper set, game soundtrack) are waiting for you in the Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack with a <b>40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>Lead a new crusade against demons and protect the country of Mendev! Ten unique mythic paths, ten companions, twenty-five classes, and one hundred sixty archetypes are already waiting for you in the game. Get Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Enhanced Edition with a <b>70% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Get Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Game of the Year Edition with a <b>10% discount</b> and get the base game with all six premium expansions and four free DLCs available after the game's original release!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/sub/1171676/<br/><br/>Three major DLCs — Inevitable Excess, Through the Ashes, and The Treasure of the Midnight Isles are waiting for you in the Season Pass 1, which you can purchase with <b>70% off</b>! Continue your adventures in the lands of the World Wound!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Yet another three exciting DLCs are available as a part of the Season Pass 2 with a <b>50% discount</b>. The Last Sarkorians, The Lord of Nothing, and A Dance of Masks will completely change your game experience!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide in "Labor of Love" Category</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737316601</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/dc1031436ce4eba20e6fd78fc5e1e0b980d6c549.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominate Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader for Outstanding Story-Rich Game!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4453592738017837094</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
THIS IS NOT A DRILL<br/><br/>In the grim darkness of the far future, there is only Steam Awards 2024. The nominations are already open, and the Imperium needs you to join this fight.<br/><br/>Brothers and sisters, we kindly ask you to support us and nominate Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader for <b>Outstanding Story-Rich Game</b>!<br/><br/>The nomination voting is open until the end of the Autumn Sale.<br/><br/>Сommand headquarters expresses its gratitude to all our players. Your love and support burns brighter than the Astronomican. <br/><br/>Thank you for being with us.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/996f04d42894b2511080beafd6b1500a1ee2157f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Awards 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4464851103138185238</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Brothers and Sisters of the Imperium</div><br/>The time has come to make your voice heard! <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is contending for <b>“Game of the Year”</b> at the Steam Awards, and we need your support to claim this honor.<br/><br/>We believe <i>Space Marine 2</i> shows our dedication to the <b>Warhammer 40k universe</b>, it’s also a testament to the essence of gaming: epic stories, exhilarating combat, and unforgettable moments with your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8d256e7a6b8cf622a2ec52c07aa7435456603885.jpg"/><br/><br/>If you felt the thunder of a bolter, the weight of a chainsword, and the call of the Emperor, show your devotion by nominating us for <i>Game of the Year</i>. Together, we march to victory!<br/><br/><i>- The Space Marine 2 Team</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction Trailer Soundtrack Giveaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647304814</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Greetings Total War fans and music lovers!<br/><br/>Today we're giving away the Omens of Destruction trailer soundtrack for you to listen to whenever you like! 🎼<br/><br/>Claim it now in the Rewards section of the CA Community  👇👀<br/><br/>🔗 https://community.totalwar.com/rewards<br/><br/><br/>Enjoy!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/544391b73e1cf6128b3e629c5ac08b97841fe4d8.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
