<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Rebalance in the Koronus Expanse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4185613970223713932</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c3be0fd9f2bee2f3b6a9e12110a198fc77d1c812.jpg"/><br/><br/>Greetings, Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Rogue Trader has already been out for some time, and our team has not been sitting idle. <br/><br/>While working on fixes and improvements for the game (a <b>massive</b> 2,500+ changes are coming very soon in patch 1.2), we’ve also accumulated a lot of important data concerning character progression and player’s reception of the game’s various systems thanks to both your feedback and extensive internal analysis.<br/><br/>Having already dealt with most of the critical bugs, we felt that the upcoming patch would be a great time to revisit game balance. With these balance changes, we are aiming to provide a better challenge, offer more interesting gameplay, and expand the variety of viable builds, especially on higher difficulties.<br/><br/>To do this, we identified the list of key problems that we felt had the biggest negative impact on player experience. These were split into four major categories:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Excess of additional turns<br/></li><li> Overscaling in the late game<br/></li><li> Sanctioned psykers and pyromancy<br/></li><li> Arch-militant overtuning</li></ul>Let’s talk about each of them in detail.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Excess of Additional Turns</div>While the original design felt engaging, it appears that, in the end, we went too far with the abundance of out-of-sequence turns and attacks. Stacking additional turns gives such a dominating advantage that players who utilize it can entirely trivialize combat, sometimes to the point where the enemy doesn’t even get to take a single turn!<br/><br/>Tuning things like this has to be done carefully and in batches in order to prevent overnerfing, so we began with tweaks to the Officer in patch 1.1. In 1.2, we’re going a step further and implementing major changes to a whole set of abilities that provide additional turns and AP. We want them to stay true to their spirit but do something entirely different than before.<br/><br/>For example, <b>Seize the Initiative</b> no longer provides an additional turn to the Officer, instead allowing the Officer and allies under the effect of the Officer's <b>Voice of Command</b> to deal additional damage to enemies that have not yet acted in combat.<br/><br/><b>In the Hero’s Footsteps</b> now provides a stacking +5 Fellowship bonus when an ally uses a Heroic act and a +5 Toughness bonus when using Desperate measures instead of providing an additional turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/aa2e889596e44a47bb64918f6c876e61bc7b700d.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Overscaling in the Late Game</div><br/>Our players are very quick at finding the most effective combinations, but let’s be honest, those single shots for 1.5 million damage that we’ve seen on some player videos were somewhat… beyond our expectations.<br/><br/>Some of these crazy numbers were indeed caused by bugs, but putting those aside, there were still a handful of items and abilities in the game with multiplicative scaling that did silly things when stacked. While seeing 8-digit damage values is fun to an extent, the sheer amount and availability of such options removed the element of challenge, which we believe is not healthy for the overall game experience.<br/><br/>To address this, we’ve updated a lot of abilities, items, and talents across the game that provided multiplicative bonuses (such as 3 x <b>Intelligence bonus</b>) to give flat bonuses instead (for example, 10 + <b>Intelligence bonus</b>), tweaked some percentage based bonuses to be stronger in the early game but less devastating in late game (such as the Operative’s <b>Offensive Pattern Prediction</b>, the Navigator’s <b>Reveal the Light</b> or the Exemplar’s <b>Deadeye Shot</b>), and fixed a handful of bugs with incorrect scaling such as <b>Confident Approach</b>.<br/><br/><b>Killing Edge </b>was also tuned down, being one of the main offenders that caused skyrocketing numbers.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e00914b7e51e1b702d6ef37dd8901044f539d205.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Sanctioned Psykers and Pyromancy</div><br/>Looking at sanctioned psykers prior to this update, we felt that they were always at a significant disadvantage compared to Idira and her higher psy rating.<br/><br/>We have now made it so that sanctioned psykers can take psy rating-increasing talents earlier (at levels 4/14/24/34 instead of 10/20/30/40). This will not only reduce the eventual difference in psy rating when compared to unsanctioned psykers, but it will also allow sanctioned psykers to take advanced psychic powers earlier. <br/><br/>Unsanctioned psykers can now also take those talents a bit earlier (at levels 9/19/29/39), mostly so that different archetypes have similar access to advanced psychic powers.<br/><br/>With these changes, we hope to achieve a certain parity, where the sanctioned psykers will still have a somewhat lower psy rating but will be able to take higher-level psychic powers earlier in order to compensate. <br/><br/>This wasn't our only change to psykers. For a while, we were concerned that the pyromancer, who was always supposed to be a dedicated damage dealer among psykers, had a weaker damage potential than a telepath (and we received a lot of player feedback about it, as well). In this patch we’re significantly boosting damage numbers for most of the pyromancy psychic powers, starting with <b>Ignite</b> — it now deals vastly increased damage, and pyromancers no longer need to rely on conventional weapons for the first half of the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c4e987d48bea8a7f66b3c60ab329478e6b74d4e2.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Arch-Militant Overtuning</div><br/>According to our observations and community surveys, the Arch-Militant remains the most effective archetype, with a damage potential so high that skilled players could stack bonuses from versatility extremely quickly, gaining a significant advantage. We’ve slightly reduced versatility generation and scaling from it to put the Arch-Militant more in line with the rest of the archetypes. In particular, we’ve made changes to <b>Confident Approach</b>, <b>Reckless Rush</b>, and <b>Wildfire</b>. Note that we don’t intend to nerf the Arch-Militant into the ground — it will still be very effective, but the numbers will be a bit more reasonable.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9ac1ef8e0c22acc6843ccc1324a6e85e5ad3e162.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Plans for the Future</div><br/>Our work on combat balance is far from over. However, after this batch of changes and considering the massive wave of bug fixes that are coming with 1.2, we would like to spend some time assessing the performance of the updated archetypes and analysing the feedback from our players. Although we understand that some of you may end up frustrated with losing your archetype power fantasy, many of these changes are necessary for the game to deliver the experience we envision. Let us know what you think — we need to be sure that we’re going in the right direction!<br/><br/>Later, we intend to go over all encounters that are either known to be difficulty spikes or feel too easy for their level and tune them accordingly.<br/><br/>Lastly, although a bit unrelated, you may have seen in our roadmap and known issues thread on Steam that we recognized the limited availability of conviction points. We’ve received a lot of feedback that their distribution is uneven and scarce, forcing players to make certain decisions in fear of being locked out of conviction levels. We’re working to address this, but unfortunately, we are not yet ready to ship it with 1.2. We expect it to come a bit later, in one of the following updates.<br/><br/>Thank you for taking the time to read this. See you very soon in 1.2, where you will be able to see all the changes yourself, and looking forward to hearing your feedback!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - 5.1.0 Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4208126895057497131</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/08deb2d7f95c4d664f3481b7022224525f6aac36.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks!<br/><br/>Patch 5.1 is finally upon us, arriving Tuesday 25th June, and with it comes the baddest good boy there ever was - Karanak, the three-headed Hound of Vengeance - as a FREE Legendendary Hero!<br/><br/>In anticipation of tomorrow's release, you can now check out the full list of changes coming in Patch 5.1.0 in our comprehensive Patch Notes.<br/><br/>Read Patch Notes 5.1.0<br/><br/>Following the release of Update 5.1 tomorrow (we're expecting to release this at 11AM BST, Tuesday 25th June), look forward to us returning to you this Wednesday with a look at What's Next in Total War: WARHAMMER III. We're excited to share with you all more news about our next Update, and to give some more detail around the additions we're making to Khorne, Ogres, and Greenskins.<br/><br/>Until then, we'll see you on the battlefield! (Karanak says woof woof woof)<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog: Clandestium Gloriana Level Design</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068449174202</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hello, everyone! <br/><br/>We’re excited to talk about the newest mission coming to Darktide: Clandestium Gloriana (AKA Atelium Foundryplex Omega V). For this, we interviewed Lead Level Designer, Fredric Grapensparr and Narrative Lead, Michael Knight, both of whom were part of the team responsible for crafting this new zone for players. <br/><br/>When reviewing feedback from the players around the last mission we designed (The Carnival), we saw the strong response from players regarding the lore and narrative woven into the level. This is something we enjoy doing more of, and that was a key starting point for the design of Clandestium Gloriana.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G6Ca9f6xTn4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><b>Setting the Scene</b><br/><br/>From a narrative perspective, our goal was to create a temple-like facility in the Void between zones. We landed on the idea of lost facilities peppered deep within the bowels of the Hive. These fabled facilities, Machinaria Gloriana, are long-forgotten wonders constructed to support Saint Messalina's crusade through the Moebian Domain. Each is rumoured to house some technological marvel that significantly aided the war effort. Unfortunately these have fallen out of service and become lost through the centuries. (It didn’t help that record keeping was never a strong point for the Adeptus Administratum.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/2b6b7fff0d5d65bd4b65ba01f7ea182169d24936.jpg"/><br/><br/>The machine in this particular Foundryplex was centuries old, and it generated a lot of heat when it was running. This required massive cooling systems. And while the forges have been quiet for 1000s of years…no one seemed to remember to turn off the coolant system. This is the setting of our newest mission: the grandeur and prosperity of the past, contrasted with the decay and neglect of the present. This contrast is then further highlighted by the snow and ice which covers the level as a result of the forgotten coolant system. It’s visually different from anything we’ve delivered before. This setting also allowed us to introduce new gameplay mechanics and objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fbacd2de36cf344d0400d764ec77d8a5601f496c.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Introducing Swagger</b><br/>As a vehicle to further deliver narrative to this mission, the team landed on the new NPC, Swagger. <br/><br/>Swagger is an enigmatic character whose origins remain unknown. He is more capable than players might credit him based on his manner and appearance alone. For example, how did he have the codes to the Mourningstar Vox Network? How does no one seem to know where he is from?<br/><br/>Swagger is the mission giver and unlike our regular NPCs, Swagger will actually be present in the level directing the strike team from the ground. This added an additional technical aspect in terms of audio that we’re pretty excited to share with players.<br/><br/>We can also confirm this is not the last interaction players will be having with Swagger. He will be sticking around.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d5bec8bc98a5455f1e1a523e9cfcd4aba2a67c98.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Navigating the Mission</b><br/>In this mission, players are tasked with meeting Swagger, who has provided the location of this Foundryplex rumored to hold the secrets of true Moebian steel. The objective is to get the facility running, obtain samples and fulfill Hadron’s motivations (whatever they may be). The mission objectives and the end event itself will depend on the players’ capabilities more than past events. If players are a coordinated team, they’ll be able to clear the objectives more quickly and efficiently.<br/><br/>The mission starts with a sense of claustrophobia in order to foster a sense of danger and tension for players. As they progress, the environment opens up to allow for more freedom of movement and good ole’ hack and slash. This is an intentional design choice to make the initial stages more challenging, before providing players with a sense of relief and progression as they move further into the mission. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5f011fc860ee765c321bef642d75919f944e92da.jpg"/><br/><br/>We don’t want to say too much more without letting players be able to experience it for themselves. But we can say we’re particularly excited for players to reach the end event. (Jesper Kyd is a genius.)<br/><br/>Please stay tuned for more updates and dev blogs for Secrets of the Machine God! We look forward to seeing the reactions to this new level.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Update on Itemization</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068448979176</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The release of <b>Secrets of the Machine God</b> is just around the corner, and while we are excited to have you get your hands on it, we also suspect many of you might be expecting itemization to be part of this update. <b>Unfortunately, this will not be the case</b>.<br/><br/>After internal and external testing, we’ve decided the itemization rework isn’t where we want it to be for release this month. We’ve been reading your threads and taking the feedback on. The consensus being this rework should not be rushed. And we agree. <br/><br/>Now, <b>itemization is slated to release after summer</b>. We are making progress. During this time, we’re also looking at expanding the feedback loop on this rework, and will be including more players outside our core-testers. <br/><br/>To get more details, <b>we are working on a dev blog on itemization</b> to give you more insights into the work we’ve carried out so far. <br/><br/>We look forward to sharing more information about itemization and will keep working with the community to shape the upcoming itemization rework. <br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the in-depth Gameplay Overview Trailer now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4161970072170925874</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines! 💥</div><br/>We're incredibly excited to unveil a new detailed Gameplay Trailer!<br/>Narrated by the game’s Creative Director, Oliver Hollis-Leick, this 6-minute Gameplay Overview Trailer dives deeper into <i>Space Marine 2</i>’s main story campaign, its multiplayer modes, and its progression mechanics. <br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> releases on September 9. <br/>Pre-order the Gold and Ultra Editions today and play <b>up to 4 days before release.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch our Gameplay Overview Trailer now!</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5tqDxvpzsKM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">More Missions, Enemies, and Weapons to Release Through Free Updates.</div> <br/>Following the release on September 9, <i>Space Marine 2</i> players will receive new “Operations” missions and PvP maps, new enemies, and new weapons to fight them with, through regular free updates for all players. Additional cosmetics and Chapter heraldry will release as part of the Season Pass with no microtransactions or in-game cash shop involving premium currency.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/382b5355937beabb415b818b0648f9feb5638fc0.jpg"/><br/><br/>Heed the call of battle when <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> launches September 9, 2024, on PC. Pre-order the Standard, Gold, Ultra, and Collector’s Edition now! Sign up as a Focus member to get exclusive news and upcoming special offers for <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> and the whole Focus catalog.<br/><br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
