<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>More fixes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515211349279640979</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hey all, here's a list of some more changes to the game with this new patch<br/><br/>Please <b>restart Steam</b> and remember that most patches are not compatible with older ones, so you will not see games from the previous build in the game browser.  <b>It will take a little while for new ones to start up</b> - or feel free to create a game!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed issue with some challenges not progressing<br/></li><li>Fixed crash bug at the end of match rewards screen<br/></li><li>Fixed bug where hosts were not able to use their customized vehicles<br/></li><li>Fixed bug when selecting alternate abilities in the Kustomize screen<br/></li><li>Improved race waypoint sync for Free Roam mode<br/></li><li>Fixed issue with full games showing as 15/16 in game browser<br/></li><li>Swapped Konstruct skin reward on existing challenge to scrap boost, as it was causing issues<br/></li><li>Added new challenge to both Looted Wagon and Grot Mega Tank that reward players with the Konstruct skin<br/></li><li>Added daily Rukkatrukk challenge, 6 kills + assists<br/></li><li>Added daily Trukk challenge, 3 kills<br/></li><li>Attempted to improve performance on Da Dust Up and Da Gorge<br/></li><li>Fixed some minor collision and visual issues in some maps<br/></li><li>Removed "Mob Up!" achievement for the time being, as parties are not currently in the game<br/></li><li>Disabled daily party challenge since playing in a party is no longer possible.<br/></li><li>Fix for showing player level at Kill Kam and MVP screens</li></ul>We've been pretty on top of issues and still are working on the bigger ones like hit reg and host migration. We'll let everyone know when there's news on that or other high priority items ːsteamthumbsupː<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/147b1768aae9ac663c50a5fec47f3ba790647d05.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Quick Fixes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515211349279639544</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI, just a quick one with some fixes below that we felt necessary to patch<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed crash related to player states<br/></li><li>Fixed issue with game browser not updating<br/></li><li>Fixed accessories issue in the Kustomize menu<br/></li><li>Fixed players not getting scrap from solo matches<br/></li><li>All maps autoselect now when creating a new game<br/></li><li>Bots are enabled by default when creating a new game<br/></li><li>Added number of players in public lobbies to the bottom of the Game Browser<br/></li><li>votekick response window changed to 20 seconds<br/><br/>Have a good weekend ladz ːsteamthumbsupː</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skulls Event extended until June 8th!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546736546679621632</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><br/>We've decided to extend the duration of the <i>Skulls for the Skull Throne</i> in-game event for another weekend! You'll have time to collect <i>more skulls</i> and take advantage of the <i>double XP</i> multiplier until <b>June 8th</b>!<br/><br/>Read more about the event in the original announcement here:<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/812447750630147816]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Balancing + Some Fixes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515211349279638505</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Just dropped a small patch before the weekend. Please be sure to restart Steam to make sure you've got it!<br/><br/><b>NOTE</b>: You may see less games in the game browser until more people download the update, as there will still be some people playing in the previous build.  Those games won't show up in the latest build and vise versa<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>Here's whats up:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>improved skill calculation (and thus team balancing)<br/></li><li>Players can now switch to the losing team at any point in the match as long as the losing team has equal players or less<br/></li><li>Prevention of players to be able to join games that are in their ending phase to avoid issues.  Games in ending phase now show up greyed out in the game browser,<br/></li><li>Game browser now dynamically updates,<br/></li><li>Prevented votekick being able to kick host<br/></li><li>Crash bug fix relating to player challenges<br/></li><li>Longer challenges now show HUD popups more frequently (every 10% instead of 25%),<br/></li><li> Rukkatrukk Blood Axes kit gets hidden since its not supposed to be unlockable until later<br/></li><li>Fix for Trukk skulls kit texture issue,<br/></li><li>Fix for PLAY GAME screen explainer not accepting keyboard/gamepad inputs (Steam Deck suffered from this),<br/></li><li>Da Gorge map has expanded boundaries now, lighter nighttime version<br/></li><li>networking clean-up, more solidity,<br/></li><li> Progression data storage improvements,</li></ul>Major things up next:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Host "migration" so that if a host leaves or gets disconnected for any reason, the lobby of players is not disbanded, but instead is put in a game together with the same settings with a new host<br/></li><li>Hit reg improvements<br/></li><li>Warbands system (clans/clubs).  This was meant to go into the launch version but just had some UI still left to do on it</li></ul>Happy krumpin!<br/>Some of us devs should be playing over the weekend a bit so looking forward to SMASHIN' SUM GITS togetherːsteamthumbsupː<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/880573fa3ef539bb061dfaa37ec62a776389e521.gif"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500574015912412461</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/>Let’s review what happened in May, and what’s coming next!<br/>Shall we start off with what everyone’s waiting for?…<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SIEGE MODE TEASER TRAILER 🩸</div><br/>Revealed during the Skulls Festival of Video Games, the Siege Mode will arrive on June 26. This first teaser trailer gives you a first taste of the upcoming battle, watch it if you haven’t already!<br/><br/>Tear through unending waves of Tyranid and Chaos assaults and fight to survive as long as you can.<br/><br/><b>Give them no ground.</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NDScTIUHlnc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3">Let’s recap what we know about it already:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The action takes place on Kadaku.<br/></li><li> Up to 3 players (either with friends or with 2 bots, just like in regular PvE).<br/></li><li> You will get to fight waves of both Tyranids and Chaos.<br/></li><li> Difficulty will increase for each wave defeated.</li></ul>Your class, and weapon progressions are shared between Operations and Siege Mode<br/>The Siege Mode isn’t a DLC, it’s a <b>free update</b>!<br/><br/>Prepare to hold your ground and survive as long as you can against endless enemies, as <b>only in death does duty end</b>.<br/><br/>​Siege Mode will be playable on the Public Test Server (Steam) starting June 4.<br/>Here’s a tutorial on how to access it.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How it will work ⚙️</div><br/>You will earn points for each completed wave. Points are distributed among each player (e.g. if the wave grants you 600 points, and there’s three of you: then, each person will get 200 points).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/55c25416184d4c71523316b925500b3312e4bfa0.png"/><br/>Spend your points at the Requisition Terminals to buy equipment or reinforcements such as Cadians and Marines (Each player can summon 1 AI Space Marine at a time. Choose their class without restrictions!). The strongest and most expensive being the Dreadnought, which joins the battlefield to help you for 3 minutes. Buy equipment and reinforcements to make the fight easier (or less unbearable 😁).<br/><br/>Every 5 waves, you’ll take the elevator to change sectors and therefore field of battle. Completing each Sector will grant your more rewards (requisition points, armoury data, etc.)<br/><br/>And most importantly, your mission is to ​<b>give them no ground</b>.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Are you ready? See you June 26! ⚔️</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a6e531e31a5a74b4a50ffd3fef3ebda28f84c081.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch 8.0 - SIEGE UPDATE</div><br/>You’ll be able to get a first taste of the new content, via the PTS, which will reopen on June 4. Apart from Siege Mode, other features, free and DLC Content are coming with Patch 8.0 in June. <br/><br/>Here’s a tutorial on how to access the PTS. Contrary to our first PTS: base Game owners can't equip the new customization packs on the PTS, but Season Pass holders can!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Let’s break it down together:</div><br/>Coming along with the Siege Mode : The White Scars and Blood Angels enter the fray.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">⚪ THE WHITE SCARS CHAPTER PACK</div><br/>The White Scars Chapter Pack will include a new Champion skin for the Assault class and three exclusive White Scars–inspired weapon skins for <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Occulus Bolt Carbine<br/></li><li> The Stalker Bolt Rifle<br/></li><li> The Combat Knife</li></ul><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c0fc4a0e132d08919324e6e27654fe15b3958f0a.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0254e5bfaa406e0d3d52e12db225d7cd3bd87237.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f0a261a65d0e9e65f99d2e59ec33868f81f85c4.jpg"/></div></div></div>Also, a host of cosmetic options and heraldry markings for their Successor Chapters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b066256ea388e1db5bd6cd8e09d0c10107cd25eb.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b4c834898fa174b67debd3bf94cb8ed02cab7f98.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6db692fa5ef96c40a3454b8eafdfcf58f7d9b219.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b73fa5f9b8a36fa2e713d59c294a66e6f6151489.jpg"/></div></div></div>The White Scars Successor Chapters are the:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dark Hunters<br/></li><li> Solar Hawks<br/></li><li> Storm Reapers<br/></li><li> Mantis Warriors<br/></li><li> Destroyers<br/></li><li> Marauders<br/></li><li> Storm Lords<br/></li><li> Rampagers</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">🔴 THE BLOOD ANGELS COSMETIC PACK</div><br/>The Blood Angels Cosmetic Pack will provide a number of new armour pieces to be equipped on any of the game’s playable classes, in addition to heraldry markings celebrating eight of the Blood Angels’ Successor Chapters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e9b00e197758eebd0757f8b7881c56347bd9766e.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2fb39e0f5017cf83ce924c48783bd696c67ac436.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/46d0d37e4263b8b2ba15f7bd6d5127e61871dc7b.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6b8123edd3debacc0b18ab3e0d9d99dd7d4347a5.jpg"/></div></div></div>The Blood Angels Successor Chapters are the:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Atlantian Spears<br/></li><li> Blood Dragons<br/></li><li> Flesh Eaters<br/></li><li> Blood Scythes<br/></li><li> Lamenters<br/></li><li> Angels Penitent<br/></li><li> Angels Sanguine<br/></li><li> Flesh Tearers</li></ul>We can’t reveal more for the moment. 😉<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SNEAK PEEK</div><br/>Many sneak peeks are coming with the June and July Community Updates. We’ll talk about the update that comes after 8.0, what we are planning to do after the one year anniversary, and more. 🤫<br/><br/>Stay tuned!!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FOCUS TOGETHER</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">🧑‍🎨 Fan Art Contest on Focus Together</div><br/>You, players, never miss an opportunity to impress us with your art skills. We keep seeing screenshots, painted mini and fan arts everywhere, to our great delight. This time we wanted to host a contest!<br/><br/>Our favorite fan art inspired by the campaign mode of Space Marine 2 will be granted with 2 keys of Space Marine 2 (any platform) to offer to fellow Astartes eager to join the fight.<br/><br/>Rules: Submit your creation in the #Fan-Creations channel of Focus Together to participate! The piece can be digital or traditional and must follow the said-theme! One entry per person.<br/><br/>The winner will be contacted via their DMs. The contest starts on May 30 and ends on June 25!<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">✏️ A word from Focus and Saber</div><br/>We wanted to acknowledge the fact that quality-of-life bugs matter too (such as typos, clipping props of the armour etc…), and we want to fix them. But right now, the major content updates promised in our roadmap are taking up a significant portion of our time. That means some of the smaller fixes will take longer to roll out.<br/><br/>Our current focus is on resolving high-impact issues like crashes and connectivity problems, which can significantly affect gameplay. Every patch aims to bring improvements on that front.<br/><br/>At the top of our priority list right now is improving the connectivity issues that arose after the 7.0 update: We’re mainly talking about infinite “Joining Server” loops and such issues preventing players from joining sessions. We made some improvements with the 7.1 and 7.2 hotfixes, but we’ll keep working on it for the 8.0 update.<br/><br/><b>Thank you</b> for your patience and understanding as we continue to improve the game. Your support and feedback help guide our work. 🖤<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH</div><br/>As usual, let’s keep in touch on Discord and Focus Together. You can also follow us on our socials: Instagram, X, Facebook, Threads and Bluesky.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield, Space Marines.<br/><br/><i>The Focus and Saber Teams. 🦾</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
