<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 4.5 is available!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4472730495692571054</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!</div><br/>The 4.5 update for Space Marine 2 is now live! In addition to bringing a <b>new Secondary Weapon</b> to all players, Patch 4.5 provides <b>buffs to a handful of Primary Weapons</b> and <b>addresses a number of bugs and connection issues</b>. <br/><br/>Read the patch notes below for the complete details:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>PATCH NOTES</b></div><br/><div class="bb_h3"><u>New Weapon: the Neo-Volkite Pistol</u></div><br/>The Neo-Volkite Pistol, a powerful thermal ray weapon, is now available for the <b>Assault, Vanguard, and Bulwark classes!</b><br/><br/>Unlike other weapons, the Neo-Volkite Pistol blasts a heat ray onto your enemies, dealing accumulative thermal damage. Focusing on one enemy will ramp up the damage—until it generates a localised explosion for huge damage to your target and all nearby enemies.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qaab-S4yd9w?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<i>Please note that the Neo-Volkite Pistol will only be available in Operations mode for now as we continue to experiment with balancing in PvP. It will be added to Eternal War mode in our next major update alongside a new Operations map, a new enemy, and the Dark Angels cosmetics. Until then though, you’ll be able to try it out against your friends in the Battle Barge’s Sparring Arena!</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><u>BALANCING TWEAKS</u></div><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Weapons (Operations mode only)</b></div><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/84f550f14cfe00572761dd775acd648593469ae1.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3"><i>PLASMA INCINERATOR</i></div></div></div></div>👉 Slightly <b>reduced amount of heat</b> generated by normal and charged shots for versions: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Master-Crafted - Alpha <br/></li><li> Salvation of Bakka - Alpha <br/></li><li> Gathalamor Crusade - Alpha</li></ul> 👉 Fixed a bug that would cause several versions not producing heat at all.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/309e0758b515fa6cbb9be52748b092104df4ef8f.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3"><i>BOLT SNIPER RIFLE</i></div></div></div></div>👉 <b>Fire rate</b> increased from 50 to 60 rounds per minute.<br/>👉 <b>Headshot bonus</b> increased from x2 to x2.5.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7ec93687e823d425a68f730a4154d09a6e246df6.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3"><i>OCCULUS BOLT CARABINE</i></div></div></div></div>👉 <b>Scope</b> added<br/>👉 <b>Headshot bonus</b> increased from x1 to x1.33<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/84f9b7a9849c5eb642ea690a8cffb7d20893da12.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3"><i>BOLT CARABINE (SMG)</i></div></div></div></div>👉 <b>Adjusted damage falloff curve</b>: Base damage increased by 50% for the first 10 meters, after that, the damage drops to the original pre-patch value.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3d269cd2f727ae47995b2e1673ab8a34aafd4ea7.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><div class="bb_h3"><i>AUTO BOLT RIFLE</i></div></div></div></div>👉<b> Max ammo increased</b> by 1 magazine for each version.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>GENERAL FIXES</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug causing unlocked DLC cosmetic items to get locked again after a restart<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug causing the Sniper perk "Targeted Shot" to not work after swapping weapons.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug causing the Sniper invisibility not getting removed after a shot in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug preventing players from muting the others in PvP.<br/></li><li> Fixed several perks not triggering correctly from enemy kills.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that prevented certain weapon perks from triggering correctly when reaching a specific HP threshold.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>TECH IMPROVEMENTS</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.<br/></li><li> Fixed server disconnects with unstable user connection.<br/></li><li> General connectivity improvements.</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 10:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.2.1.26 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4453590835015975297</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! We are deploying a minor update to address some Void Shadows quest issues and give the players a bit more time to catch their breath after Act III before triggering the Void Shadows Act IV content. <br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Watch out for the possible spoilers below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In rare circumstances, it was possible to get Kibellah’s second quest in Act II rather than Act IV. It was fixed, but the fix will only be retroactive if you haven’t yet talked with Kibellah about the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>death of the officer</span></span>. Otherwise you’ll need to load a game before this conversation for the quest to trigger properly in Act IV instead.<br/></li><li> Multiple quests and dialogues had a minor chance to break if a warp event popped up while they were active - fixed;<br/></li><li> The <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Genestealer attack</span></span> event from the Void Shadows DLC now begins later in Act IV, to let the player catch their breath and level up a bit after returning from <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Commorragh</span></span>.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 09:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Live Event - The Grandfather's Gifts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456968534728114295</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ead25e5ec3cded2fb3a62df4d2c45f7a8714f1ae.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: The Grandfather’s Gifts</div>The Lord of Decay has blessed his most beloved followers with hideous tentacles. So imbued are they with his foul pestilence that they explode when shot.<br/><br/>Dispatch them at close quarters to avoid this.<br/><br/><b>Complete missions featuring the blessed enemies to progress and collect rewards.</b> This condition will only be available during the event and it will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals. Look out for missions with the “Mutated Horrors” condition.<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, November 7, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a new Portrait Frame. (<b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Be aware the frame might not show up immediately in players’ inventories after receiving the notification. Players may need to re-log, or at least leave and re-enter the Mourningstar.</i>)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/550190a3d4d84a5cbf154d0f9f8777ebbf41c08c.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 13:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 03 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4556046454947315881</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speedfreeks!,</b><br/>With your continued feedback we further add to, tweak and improve the game.<br/><br/>Today, we are now live with:<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b391dceab12c8150b09629e8508f65a1ef90842f.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added <b>new Kill Konvoy map</b> "Big Eruptor" based on the Deff Rally map Burna Valley<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5a5e34b7a82b21ed4d54c075441ba3fbeb8c4d2d.png"/><br/></li><li> <b>New alternate lighting variations</b> for Rok Rush (dark nebula) <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b4ba5c33403ef4451756ecc3aabb4f7450298eba.png"/>and Frozen Dakka (night-time) <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5c576d02ecf2c59611ab950159ce05df8708ae15.png"/><br/></li><li> <b>Improved terrain and collision</b> in Kill Konvoy maps Frozen Dakka and Ded 'Ard Desert<br/></li><li> Death volumes added underneath all the maps to respawn people automatically in case they accidentally clip through the terrain<br/></li><li> Added map names to top right of starting screen and end of match team score screen</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/24852a660b47cb1afe7a59773fb3145ba6a76e95.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Burna Bottle now does 10 direct hit damage and its splash damage radius has been reduced by 25%<br/></li><li> Grot Rigging heal increased to 50 from 30<br/></li><li> Scrapjet missile range reduced to 100m<br/></li><li> Scrapjet drill now does impact damage based on velocity.  Damage over time removed due to inconsistency<br/></li><li> Kustom Boosta Blasta Jump ability no longer does damage and knockback to nearby enemies<br/></li><li> Shokkjump Dragsta Shokk Rifle now has enough projectile speed to be functionally hitscan<br/><br/></li><li> There is now an option to <b>dash in the steering direction</b> rather than camera direction<br/></li><li> All HUD reticles now have shadows for easier visibility on bright surfaces<br/></li><li> New colourized ability icons shown on the HUD<br/></li><li> Customization presets can now be switched ingame via the vehicle selection screen<br/></li><li> Presets button now more prominently shown in the UI</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f26deda61208f1c88b36ebf9f023868ecbc0b145.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Parties can now matchmake</b> against other parties by using the same game name and matchmaking at the same time. Other players are able to backfill (matchmake) normally into this game once it's created.  Note that matchmaking using party vs. party may take longer to match than usual, as it is waiting to create a new game with the other party</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/58adbcd6e3b1aacbdb4916eeb8e0d24330deb806.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Matchmaking region selection is now available</b>, as to provide players more control over where they would like to play</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5a62466284ed47bf19e710a9ce02ab154360bb12.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Players can switch teams</b> regardless of skill level as long as their team is winning by 200 points and the losing team has the same or fewer players, or their team is up by 300 points and the losing team has 1 more player or less</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/525bbc93b070fee41947e8acffa76c958e8235a8.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Leader board stats have now been reset</b><br/></li><li> Players can now opt out of the Leader boards via an option at the top of the Leader boards screen<br/></li><li> For match stats to count towards the Leader boards, there must be 12 human players in the match. Stats acquired in limited time events don’t count<br/></li><li> Scrap Loota board no longer counts Scrap Boosts or daily challenge rewards<br/></li><li> Gork’s chosen board now measures kills + assists instead of kills – deaths<br/></li><li> Sawbonez board now tracks raw healing stats</li></ul>NOTE: Leaderboards will keep getting reset through early access, but will not be reset ever again once the game launches v1.0<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d49d959cd6d1c5026f08714c468d18bdc7014e1f.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Switch team function now available for all players on the winning team, if they would like to help balance the match.  Switching team is only available if the winning team is leading by a decent amount and the losing team doesn't have 2 more players than the winning team already<br/></li><li> Deff Rally point bonus for getting a kill while holding the point has been increased back to 5 from 2. This only applies to the losing team<br/></li><li> Reduced height of bomb spawn scrap piles in Kill Konvoy<br/></li><li> Communication pings on the HUD no longer appear on enemies with hidden nametags due to stealth abilities<br/></li><li> Quick comms messages can now be seen during respawn screen and end of match screen<br/></li><li> Anonymous player names option added for those wanting to stream the game and not worry about offensive player names<br/></li><li> When pinging an ally ("PROTECT DAT GIT"), their name now appears next to the message<br/></li><li> Kill assist duration window increased to 10 seconds (from 7)<br/></li><li> Air-time no longer included in MVP screen stats<br/></li><li> Fixed total scrap calculation for player stats<br/></li><li> Windowed mode now available (has issues, to be used at player's discretion)<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash happening at the settings screen</li></ul><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/>  <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.3.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458094434636005403</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8819ade8a9ce45de2046736c42ad35755f2ad1b3.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks! <br/><br/>Thanks for your feedback in the wake of Patch 5.3's release. We've been keeping a close eye on your comments regarding Magic Items in particular, and today we've rolled out Hotfix 5.3.1 which includes, alongside a number of bug fixes, some rebalancing for some of these items. We'll continue to monitor your feedback regarding these, so do keep letting us know your thoughts once you've got your hands on the changes.<br/><br/>We expect our next release to be 6.0, and though our teams will of course be monitoring for any unexpected errors that require an additional hotfix, our heads are now down for the final stretch on the road to the release of Update 6.0 and the next DLC! In case you missed it, you can watch our latest dev chat video for some more details on what's coming.<br/><br/>Without further ado, let's look at today's changelog:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">MAGIC ITEMS BALANCING</div><br/>We’ve received a lot of feedback on our newly released Magic Items and will continue to monitor it. For now, we’ve made the following changes:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Idol of Zak-Alooog</div>This item was more punishing than necessary, and the positives didn’t fully warrant the burden of the negatives. In particular, the fatigue penalty was quite harsh, so we’ve made the following adjustments:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced the movement range penalty from -50% to -20%.<br/></li><li> Removed the fatigue penalty effect.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Helm of Draesca</div>This item was always intended to have a strong tradeoff that aligns with its lore. However, we agree with the feedback we've received that the item was skewed too negatively, particularly providing little reason to keep it equipped. We’ve made the following addition to the item:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a 2% chance per end turn for the helm to grant a powerful unique trait, ‘Power of Draesca.’ <br/></li><li> ‘Power of Draesca’: +20% HP, +20% character experience, +10% ward save, +10% research rate.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Deathsinger/Doomsinger</div>One of the smaller ideas we didn’t manage to include in patch 5.3 was the concept that these sister swords would provide an extra benefit when they are together. We’ve now implemented this and added the following to the swords:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a 5% chance per end turn for characters with these swords equipped to gain a unique trait when both are in the same region. <br/></li><li> Sister Swords: +10 melee attack, +10 melee defence, charge reflect attribute.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when attempting to exchange units with a camp that was being abandoned during the campaign. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred while loading a battle with AI Control selected and Control Large Army toggled off in siege battles with large garrison armies.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a rare end-turn prompt for an idle character when that character already has a destination. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players using the Orcs &amp; Goblins faction could enter Tunnelling Stance when the army's movement points were below 100% while the Waaagh! Army View was selected.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SETTLEMENTS/BUILDINGS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where the Daemon Prince could not properly access the Harbour port building when occupying Erengrad. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Orcs &amp; Goblins campaign where players were unable to target discovered Skaven settlements for a Waaagh! unless their capital was also revealed. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Waaagh's target settlement model would disappear after being razed. The model now remains visible without the need for a save reload.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TECHNOLOGY TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Added 'Fire While Moving' for Gyrocopters and Gyrobombers to the 'Improved Gyrocopter Engines' technology on the Dwarf tech tree. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SKILL TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in Drycha's skill tree where the ‘Indoctrinator’ skill displayed an excessive number of character unit card variants. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ANCILLARIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where certain effects that increased recruit rank for Nurgle units would not work when playing as the Daemon Prince. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">BOUNTIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Adjusted how the monetary reward for Bounties is calculated. Previously, the amount was based on the issuer's Treasury, which could fluctuate significantly regardless of their strength and had no relevance to the selected target. The new calculation considers the player's distance to the target, with higher rewards for immortal targets or province capitals. Additionally, distance is now measured from the nearest settlement owned by the player rather than just the faction leader's army. This change should generally result in Bounty targets being closer to the player.<br/></li><li> Adjusted the Bounty rewards system to ensure a balanced distribution of additional rewards. Players will now receive a consistent cycle through meat, camp growth, and rare ancillaries, reducing randomness and enhancing reward variety.<br/></li><li> Players can now decline a Bounty, triggering a new one to be issued on the following turn.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ZHAO MING'S MERCENARIES</div>​ We've fixed an issue causing Zhao Ming's Ogre Mercenary benefits to not apply to the new Mercenaries added in 5.3. Additionally, we've made the following changes to help take Zhao's mercenary play to the next level.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Faction Trait</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added +10 Melee Attack and Defense to all Ogre Mercenaries.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Skill Tree</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Removed -25% recruitment cost for Ogre Mercenaries.<br/></li><li> Added Guardian for all Ogre Mercenaries faction-wide.<br/></li><li> Added +20% Weapon and Missile Damage for all Ogre Mercenaries faction-wide.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed a bug where hovering over the Ogre Bounties panel link in the help pages while the Bounties were open would cause the panel to flash extremely brightly.<br/></li><li> Improved the visual quality of the Worldroots Forest Health numbers when playing as the Wood Elves. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where lords, including Legendary Lords, would lose their last names in the UI when they were wounded. This issue affected both player-controlled and AI-controlled lords.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where defeating the Nemesis Crown-wielder, Knobber da Bossy Git, did not properly complete the quest objectives, preventing the battle from ending as intended.  </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div>​<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue where the Empire's Steam Tank would fail to fire its main cannon after engaging in melee combat. Now, after exiting melee, the cannon will resume firing as intended, aligning with expected gameplay.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Grave Guard Halberds mistakenly had Expert Charge Defence instead of Charge Defence vs. Large, reinforcing their role as dedicated monster hunters rather than generalist frontline defenders.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where ranged units were sometimes assigned targets just outside of their range, causing them to sit idle instead of firing.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ABILITIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the "Howl of The Great Beast" ability incorrectly triggered a jumping animation for enemy Marauders.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ANIMATION</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed a bug where the Zombie Pirate Deckhands Mob was missing an animation.<br/></li><li> Resolved a visual issue where Skeleton Archers would snap to different positions and move back and forth excessively during the ‘shoot ready’ and combat idle animations.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the weapon of Eternal Guards would disappear while under ranged fire.<br/></li><li> Resolved an issue with the twisted left arm of Blessed Kroxigors during their running animation.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Skarsnik was missing his death animation in the post-battle screen.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ENVIRONMENT</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Prologue's first Land Battle map had a ludicrous parallax setting on a single decal. The parallax setting has since been adjusted for a more pleasing viewing experience.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue in multiplayer campaigns where the Ogre Kingdoms could receive bounties that targeted their teammates.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/><br/>And that's all for today! Thanks again for your ongoing feedback and suggestions. As always, if you run into any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.3.1 please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum. If you'd like to chat about this update (and all other things Total War related!) then be sure to join the official Total War Discord server, or head over to our CA Community forums to join the discussion there.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
