<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Metal Rogue Trader Song is released by Jonathan Young &amp; RichaadEB!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040876103</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Today we proudly present you a heavy metal surprise by Jonathan Young and RichaadEB, made in collaboration with Owlcat Games — the epic Rogue Trader song! <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/69iLUVInUuM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Enough said: LET'S GO!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on Norsca and Tides of Torment Design - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497196316182447143</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/d47668c82cf861f59900db54b8540ae93b417bce.png"/><br/><br/>What’s Next is back, revealing the next faction for our upcoming DLC, Total War: WARHAMMER III – Tides of Torment, releasing later this Summer. This episode gives full focus to our next faction, Norsca, and its newest Legendary Lord: Sayl The Faithless.<br/><br/>Creative Director Todor Nikolov, Lead Designer Vasil Nikolov, and Art Director Stoyan Stoyanov sit down with myself, subbing in for KingGobbo who recently welcomed two baby Mangler Squigs to his family and will be spending some well-earned time off whilst we keep the wheels turning. Congratulations to the Colemans from all of us across Total War!<br/><br/>Watch this full episode of What’s Next right here on the Total War YouTube Channel 👇👀<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-wN0zM9gp-s?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>We were thrilled to reveal Sayl alongside our friends across gaming at yesterday's Skulls Showcase, which if you missed you can check it out here.<br/><br/>Unlike past Skulls events, this year we haven’t released a free legendary lord as we’ve shifted our priorities over the past year to introduce more free content through our game updates, but we didn’t want you to think we’d forgotten about you all the same. 6.2 is not too far beyond the horizon, bringing with it some new units:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Blood Knights (Sword &amp; Shield)<br/></li><li> Hobgoblin Bolt Throwa</li></ul>You’ll find an early preview of additional content coming to 6.2 in this episode of What’s Next, and we’ll be back in the next few weeks with more information about our next title update.<br/><br/>And What’s Next will return at the end of June with a look at our third and final faction for Tides of Torment. We’ll have more behind the scenes looks to show and share with you in the mean-time, and until then, let us know what you’ve loved hearing about today, we always enjoy reading through your feedback!<br/><br/>See you on the battlefields,<br/><br/>— Freeman // Head of Community<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARHAMMER SKULLS 2025 Festival Sale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497194413504594133</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3fb9554a5e78e8d16be6ccc4da0a9cfb8caaa900.png"/><br/><br/>The WARHAMMER SKULLS 2025 Festival Sale is now on! From today until May 29th, grab up to 75% off the Total War: WARHAMMER franchise!<br/> <br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/> <br/>Are you ready to conquer your demons…or become one?<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/> <br/> <br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 29th May @ 9AM PDT/5PM BST</div></div> <br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/> <br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.


X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Launch Day Update from Caged Element &amp; Wired Productions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689831535</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello everyone - Since this post there has been an update in news - a new build, and further information about network issues and working round them. Please visit the pinned discussion post for the most recent updates</div><br/>https://steamcommunity.com/app/2078450/discussions/0/591772149598943899/<br/><br/><br/><br/>--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/279b1bfeef8269e1ab24fcb3f2bc68f2b5baa623.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks. <br/><br/>Today we officially launched Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks on Steam, and whilst the game is now officially out of Early Access, we know the transition has not gone smoothly for many of you. <br/><br/>Connectivity problems caused by our shift from dedicated servers to a player-hosted system have made it difficult for players to find and join matches consistently. We deployed an update shortly after launch today in an attempt to address some of these issues, but unfortunately it did not resolve the core problems. <br/><br/>The development team is working through the night to bring the game back to full online functionality as soon as possible and fully focused on identifying and implementing a reliable fix. <br/><br/>We’re hugely grateful to the community for your patience, feedback, and support. Every bug report and shared log is helping us move faster towards a solution. <br/> <br/>We’ll continue to provide regular updates as work progresses. Please do continue to report bugs, issues and any hiccups you have had so far &amp; we'll continue to answer questions in the discussions as we see them.<br/><br/>Thank for your your patience.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTFIX for Connection Issues</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689831518</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello everyone - Since this post there has been an update in news - a new build, and further information about network issues and working round them. Please visit the pinned discussion post for the most recent updates</div><br/>https://steamcommunity.com/app/2078450/discussions/0/591772149598943899/<br/><br/><br/><br/>--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>This latest patch should fix <b>some </b>network/connectivity issues in the launch build, as well as the game trying to join full matches when it should not.<br/><br/>There's <b>still an issue with seeing games in other regions than your own</b>, but if there's a game up in your region with space to join, you should be able to join it<br/><br/>If you can't seem to join a game in your region that is showing in the browser, please <b>restart the game</b>.  This should only be necessary to do once, after loading the new update for the first time<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/>We are still looking into fixing the issue with <b>not being able to see/join games that are outside of your region</b><br/><br/>Apologies for the issues and we hope everyone's been having a great time, regardless ːsteamfacepalmː <br/><br/>We'll update again once we've done something more with it.  Thanks for playing and sticking with the game!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
