<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>HOT FIX for Host Disconnections, Achievements, Game Names</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515213885413786267</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">OI, quick one 'ere</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with hosts being disconnected for seemingly no reason</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with certain achievements not popping (Roamin' Ded Far, Da Best Krumpa, etc)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stopped showing a user's PC name as default game name if they didn't change it</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with a capture point race not showing properly in Burna Valley</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some networking improvements</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">K, back ta krumpin'</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1b8870bcfba7a27794da6d2dc19290e48cb6530c.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.195 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762733065</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Our tech-priests worked day and night to prepare another hotfix, Lord Captain!<br/><br/>Praise the Omnissiah, more errors were eliminated.<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Saves with the issues described in the hotfix 1.4.0.190 (arena in Commorragh and the Lord Captain remaining in a different form after Thassera) are now retroactively fixed;<br/></li><li> The game could crash when entering Plundered Void Station if you already visited it before the DLC2 patch - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of visual issues with Chinese fonts;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs in co-op related to the hologram of the familiar in combat;<br/></li><li> Sometimes characters could move beyond the boundaries of the map on the Feudal World, walking through a wall - fixed;<br/></li><li> Improved the elevator cutscene on the Feudal World;<br/></li><li> Improved effect for the wall explosion on the Feudal World;<br/></li><li> White color scheme was added for the Cyber-Eagle familiar;<br/></li><li> A few broken dialogue options in Lex Imperialis were fixed and will now work correctly;<br/></li><li> Cyber-Eagle abilities could remain after a respec when another familiar was chosen;<br/></li><li> The Cyber-Eagle is now consistently returning to soaring above the battlefield at the end of its Overseer's turn;<br/></li><li> Rite of Solar Nourishment now correctly grants +5 Agility to the Psyber-Raven;<br/></li><li> The Psyber-Raven's Warp Buffer talent now works as intended, reallocating the Perils of Warp to the enemies. Behold the Unsanctioned Psyker!<br/></li><li> The Psyber-Raven's Psy-Resonator talent now correctly regenerates +1 AP to the Overseer;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull swarm Symbiosis  talent now correctly regenerates +1 AP to the Overseer;<br/></li><li> Fixed non-responsive controller buttons on the character screen;<br/></li><li> Polishing updates to some portraits;<br/></li><li> Sister Argenta can finally receive her Adepta Sororitas helmet that was seen in the trailers, but was lost during the original game release:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e6a40c841dad60698e7a9d065f2c4c853ee2c63f.png"/><br/><br/></li><li> Beautiful flame effects were added to the Martyr shield and Last Stand shield:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e42682e2b53d411d24ead7e1cf1e37da9969c092.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/22f64716c183f0130b8e3b2e04be8f1e6c3b4b49.gif"/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Sale is live! Get the game and its additional content with up to 50% off!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732991</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
It's Summer Sale time! <br/><br/>Whether you are an experienced Lord Captain that wishes to expand their trade protectorate with new worlds and engage in new adventures in the Koronus Expanse, or you are only yet to receive your own Warrant of Trade and inherit the most sacred title of a Rogue Trader of von Valancius Dynasty, this is a good time to consider one or more of the following options!<br/><br/>1. Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration:<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>2. Gain access to two major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis, and expand your campaign with two new companions, exciting new storylines and new interesting mechanics, receiving over 30 hours of content at an additional discount:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/>3. For Rogue Traders whose ambition is beyond measure! Get the base game, Season Pass 1, Digital Artbook, Digital OST, Wallpaper Pack and a selection of in-game items for the ultimate experience:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/36542/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Edition/<br/>4. More is on the horizon for Rogue Trader! Get Season Pass 2 to instantly gain access to new character customization options, and a future access to two more upcoming expansions, both of which offer 15 hours of gameplay: In DLC III - The Infinite Museion, you will delve into a secret vault curated by Trazyn the Infinite himself, and in DLC IV - Processional of the Damned, you will venture into the Processional — a massive, otherworldly graveyard of ships lost to the void:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3650060/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass_2/<br/>5. Get two massive CRPGs by Owlcat Games - Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous at once, and explore both of these amazing worlds in huge, branched stories that last for hundreds of hours:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/41660/Owlcat_Games_CRPG_Bundle/<br/><br/>These are just some examples of the available content for the game - check its page to find out about more options!<br/><br/>Your crew awaits your command, Lord Captain!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/594570/view/499451286721135136</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/28300675/b086637fdc2a1474628b168d24ea29c547d008a4.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>The Steam Summer Sale is so hot right now! From today until 10th of July, grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 10th July @ 10AM PDT/6PM BST</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/364360/view/517465685228519850</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/8548992/b086637fdc2a1474628b168d24ea29c547d008a4.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>The Steam Summer Sale is so hot right now! From today until 10th of July, grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 10th July @ 10AM PDT/6PM BST</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
