<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Public Test Server opens once again!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500574650502221838</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hi Space Marines! ⭐ </div><br/>The Public Test Server opens once more today! Check out this quick FAQ to help you get started and ready before launch.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s a Public Test Server?</div><br/>Space Marine 2’s Public Test Server works as a separate version of the game featuring WIP content and features. Share your feedback to help us refine the patch before its official release. Your input provides an important perspective that will be reviewed by the developer team and have an impact on further game updates.<br/><br/><b>Since this is a test environment, expect the unfinished content and possible bugs. As you will access it through a different game version, your progression will not be tracked.</b> For each PTS update, you will land on the game with levels maxed out and all weapons unlocked.<br/><br/>Please note that the DLCs won’t be available, regardless of whether you own them.<br/>‎ <br/>Since the PTS is "Public", you are free to create content based on it. No NDA will be included.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Which platforms can access the PTS?</div><br/>The PTS is only available on PC via Steam. It is not accessible on consoles (PlayStation/Xbox) or through the Epic Games Store.<br/><br/>Now, let’s see how to install it 👇<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">📝 <u>Tutorial on how to access PTS via Steam:</u></div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Just follow these simple steps:</div><ol><li> Open the Steam client.<br/></li><li> Log in with the account that owns Space Marine 2.<br/></li><li> Go to your Steam Library.<br/></li><li> Look for “<b>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 - Public Test Server</b>” under your Space Marine 2 entry.<br/></li><li> (Optional) Right-click on your Library entry and go to Properties. In the “General” tab, set the game’s default Language to “English”. <i>Translations may still be work-in-progress when you try the new content out on the PTS. <b>As a result, we recommend setting the game to English</b>.</i><br/></li><li> Once you’ve clicked on this entry, install the Public Test Server content. This install instance is not related to the base game, your files will remain in separate directories and all future updates will also be distinct, meaning that your current progression will not be affected by the time you spend on the PTS.</li></ol><b>When the install is complete, the Public Test Server is ready to launch!</b><br/><br/>Click “Play” like you would with any other game!<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Can I try every single feature that will be implemented with the next Patch?</div>Most upcoming content will be available to you. However, we won’t share content that is too buggy or hasn’t undergone the necessary approvals on our side at the time of the PTS release. Also, some content might be present on the PTS, but not accessible to the players. For instance, you may see new Champions in the Armouring Hall but won’t be able to try them unless you own the Season Pass.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How long will the PTS be active?</div><br/>The PTS will run until Patch 8.0 officially launches.<br/><br/>After that, it will go dormant until the next major PTS update.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Will my progress be saved?</div><br/>No, because the PTS runs as a completely separate game version. It does not carry over your previous progress in the game; instead, it provides all players with a default maxed-out level and weapons. This ensures that you won’t have to spend time to unlock all the features, especially the Prestige Ranks.<br/><br/>It will also not save your progress nor transfer it to the official game version afterwards.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Is multiplayer available on the PTS?</div><br/>Yes, even private PvP lobbies will work so you can invite your Brothers and Sisters to play!<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Do mods work with the PTS?</div><br/>Mods won't work with the PTS. <b>Enabling them will cause the PTS to crash at launch. Please, make sure to disable them beforehand.</b><br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How can I give feedback?</div><br/>We need your feedback!<br/><br/>As mentioned in previous Community Updates, the primary purpose of the Public Test Server is to gather your feedback on new content, changes, and balancing tweaks we plan to implement in the game.<br/><br/><b>Our main focus will be on PvE Siege Mode and Absolute Difficulty balancing.</b><br/><br/>We’ve set up dedicated forum threads on Focus Together to let you voice your opinion, which you can find here.<br/><br/>Thank you for helping us make Space Marine 2 the best it can be!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: The Cyber-Mastiff - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520840848816998435</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<i>A cybernetically-enhanced attack hound never far from your side. Send your kill-dog to disable<br/>priority targets, maul enemies, and provide vital support to your strike team.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello everyone!</div><br/>This is the first of several developer blogs centered around different aspects of the recently<br/>announced upcoming class, the Arbites! This dev blog will focus on a key aspect of the Arbites’<br/>gameplay: His loyal pet and companion, the vicious Cyber-Mastiff! This deadly enhanced<br/>canine darts through the battlefield, mauling criminals and pinning them down so that<br/>Judgement may be passed upon them.<br/><br/>We’ve interviewed Game Designer Gunnar, Gameplay Programmer Diego, Animator Olliver,<br/>and Sound Designers Jonas &amp; David, to find out more about what the dog is like and how it was developed.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What is a Cyber-Mastiff?</div><br/>The Cyber-Mastiff is a massive, deadly robotic Imperial hunting dog, bred, trained and enhanced to track and catch their master’s prey. How much of a Cyber-Mastiff’s body remains organic and how much has been replaced with mechanical enhancements depends on each hound. Many have been entirely servitorised but they’re all ruthless killing machines.<br/><br/>The Adeptus Arbites routinely deploys agents with a loyal Cyber-Mastiff companion, and our<br/>Arbites class is no different: The Cyber-Mastiff is core to the Arbites’ gameplay.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ac97c37d9f5143ad5ffecfeaaae13a8be2b738d6.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Design and Gameplay</div><br/><b>What was the process when designing the Cyber-Mastiff?</b><br/>When we were thinking about which class we could do, what direction we could go in and what<br/>was feasible for a class, the Arbites was on the table, and we were never going to do the Arbites and not do the Cyber-Mastiff. The dog is a core theme of what makes Arbites different from the other classes, so as soon as we decided on the Arbites as a class, we had decided on doing the Cyber-Mastiff.<br/><br/>We looked at different games that had done companions as a mechanic, dogs or not. There<br/>were all different sorts of avenues of what makes a good companion and how it needs to differ in our game due to our unique combat loop. From that initial idea, we developed the design and set these directives:<br/>● The dog should always act how the player expects it to<br/>● The dog should always be in the player’s field of view<br/>● The dog should never be in the way.<br/><br/>That was the gist of it; an initial idea, set goals, and then start developing it from there.<br/><br/><b>How does the Cyber-Mastiff work, gameplay-wise?</b><br/>From the very beginning, we wanted the Cyber-Mastiff to be a full companion, to accompany the player through every step of the mission. That was our end goal. In case that proved too difficult, we were prepared to fall back on a more simple implementation that would have it be a temporary ally. Maybe you summon it to attack and pin down an enemy, or it’d only stick around for a limited time on a cooldown, that sort of thing.<br/><br/>But we never wanted this as a solution if we could avoid it, so we’re very pleased with how it’s<br/>turned out. From starting the game and loading into the Mourning Star, to the end of a<br/>mission you’re gonna have a companion, the Cyber-Mastiff. It will follow its master<br/>throughout the mission, always staying in sight when out of combat. Usually it’ll be to the sides, but if the area is more cramped or filled with obstacles it can instead opt to be in the front.<br/><br/>In combat, the Cyber-Mastiff will mostly act on its own, picking out enemies to harass and<br/>attack, <b>but you can command it to attack specific enemies like Elites or Specials by<br/>pinging said enemy twice.</b><br/><br/>Like the Pox Hound on the players, it will pounce and lock down human-sized enemies. On the<br/>Ogryns it will do a heavy stagger and some damage, but it’s not gonna lock them down<br/>permanently. On Monsters, it will attack and it will bite. It’s not gonna do much on the stagger<br/>front but it’s definitely gonna pack a punch.<br/><br/><i>“And then of course you can command the dog to attack something else, like if it’s attacking a<br/>Berserker on the ground and you want it to chase down a sniper, you can do that.” ~ Gunnar</i><br/><br/>When not following an order from the Arbites player, the Cyber-Mastiff will move independently on the battlefield, picking out what it thinks is the best target and chasing it down on its own. <b>It can even rescue its master when disabled by a Pox Hound or a Mutant.</b><br/><br/>While it will often find itself in the thick of danger, the Cyber-Mastiff is very good at taking care of itself. <b>In-game, it cannot be shot or take any damage</b>, and enemies will instead opt to focus on you and the rest of your strike team as it darts around the battlefield. Darktide is a fast-paced game and we did not want players to have to worry about their loyal companion instead focusing on directing it towards high-priority targets while laying down fire on the remainder of the enemies.<br/><br/>Through the talent tree, you can further improve the Cyber-Mastiff’s capabilities with certain<br/>nodes. How many nodes you dedicate to the dog and how many you dedicate to improving your own personal arsenal will drastically change how your Arbites ends up!<br/><br/><b>You can also opt out of the Mastiff if you want to</b>; there’s a talent in the tree that removes<br/>the dog if you’re going for a different playstyle or player fantasy, and you’ll get some pretty<br/>decent bonuses to make up for the lack of a companion.<br/><br/><b>What were the challenges when designing and developing the Cyber-Mastiff?</b><br/>We had to be very careful about the Mastiff’s power. In Darktide, if you’re sufficiently skilled, a<br/>player can achieve some amazing feats on their own and overcome some really tough<br/>situations by yourself. Adding the Cyber-Mastiff on top of that had the potential to create some very overpowered scenarios.<br/><br/>So while it can lock down elites and rescue you from certain situations, you can’t just run around blocking and hope to finish the level letting the Mastiff kill everything.<br/><br/>Mainly, though, since Darktide didn’t have any systems for something like an AI companion, we<br/>had to develop everything from scratch, especially how we were going to make it move. The<br/>work done on Vermintide 2’s Necromancer class wasn’t suitable for this use case (although<br/>many lessons were learned from that implementation), the Cyber-Mastiff’s behaviour and<br/>gameplay was just too different.<br/><br/>Making the dog navigate the levels smoothly, while always being in your field of view but also<br/>not being a bother or in the way was the most difficult part. The pathfinding had to be solid and consistent throughout the level as the Cyber-Mastiff accompanies its master.<br/><br/><i>“Since the dog is a part of you, we couldn’t just make the game go ‘Oh, the dog is in a bad<br/>position, we just despawn it and bye bye’. […] We want it to always fall in a good position.” ~Diego</i><br/>We also went through several iterations of how we handled the player issuing commands to the dog. We couldn’t just add a whole new input and use that, we had to work with the inputs and commands that we already have in-game. We toyed with having it as a Blitz, or as a Combat Ability, but in the end we opted for relying on the tagging system, by double tagging.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Animations</div><br/>While we had a solid base to start with thanks to the Pox Hound, a lot of work had to be done to make the animation set for the Cyber-Mastiff. This involved a rework of the locomotion system and a suite of brand new animations.<br/><br/><i>“For references, I’ve been looking at A LOT of dog videos, and we’ve been quite lucky to have several dogs in the office that I have been recording for reference data. Sadly I haven’t done any mocap for the dog, but they’ve been good actors for videos, hehe.” ~ Olliver</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/893e0f9b6036c723891853b1398562327b89169b.jpg"/><br/><i>Molly hard at work!</i><br/>When making new animations, the process involved a lot of iteration. The basic workflow<br/>involved getting references, making a rough blockout animation to test in-game, then either<br/>re-do or commit to it with a more polished animation that would fit the final product.<br/><br/>A guiding principle while making the animations was to properly convey that the Cyber-Mastiff is not a cute dog. It’s primarily a lethal killing machine, and it is also a cyborg! The animations<br/>need to be ruthless and cold, as well as robotic and stiff in some places, rather than fluid and<br/>playful; all while still properly acting like a dog.<br/><br/>At the same time, however, we wanted the player to be able to engage with the companion in<br/>fun ways. In the Mourning Star, where things are more relaxed, you can do things like give<br/>casual orders to the dog, such as telling it to bark or sit. You can then reward the Mastiff with<br/>food or by petting it!<br/><br/>These kinds of animations were the most fun to implement, but they also proved a challenge in design, as the interactions had to be implemented without going against that guiding principle (mentioned above).<br/><br/><i>“Overall, working with a quadruped is difficult. […] I do like animating, like, monsters and<br/>creatures and stuff. But in my previous works they’ve mostly been enemies, so they had very<br/>stiff behaviour. And the challenges with the dog were that we realized as we went that ‘Oh, we<br/>need this. Oh, we need that’.” ~ Olliver</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Sound Design</div><br/>Almost from the very beginning, the process for designing the Cyber-Mastiff’s sounds was split into two areas:<br/>● The voice, which covers things like barks, growls, breathing sounds and so on ● And<br/>the sound effects, which covers every other sound involved, like footsteps, bites,<br/>mechanical gear and the like.<br/><br/><b>Voice</b><br/>The very first step was finding a base for the voice of the Cyber-Mastiff. Looking through various sound libraries, our Sound Designers searched for dog sounds that sounded big and imposing to fit the aura of the Arbites’ Mastiff. Barks, whines, attack sounds, and especially breathing sounds.<br/><br/><i>“[…] we finally got it into the game with help from coders and then we got instructions that it was a bit too much like a normal dog. […] they wanted more aggressive sounds mixed into the voice. That’s when David took over and took a shot at making it more monstrous.” ~ Jonas<br/><br/>“[…] I then went through and found all kinds of other growls and barks, from bears, tigers and<br/>lions, and pretty much surgically fit them to match the dog sounds Jonas made. […] So it had a<br/>lot more aggressiveness, basically. A deeper voice, and louder as well.” ~ David</i><br/><br/>Making the Mastiff sound menacing enough wasn’t the only challenge! Due to the cyborg<br/>enhancements, a Cyber-Mastiff can sound more or less robotic, and this depends on what<br/>cosmetics the player equips on their dog. This led to the Sound Design team making three<br/>separate ‘voices’ for the Cyber-Mastiff: a fully ‘natural’ voice, a fully robotic one, and one in<br/>between.<br/><br/>This has also been the hardest part of the Cyber-Mastiff’s sound design: Having a ‘cyber’ voice<br/>that sounds cool while still sounding like a dog and making sense. It wouldn’t do to just have<br/>any robot voice, after all.<br/><br/><i>“It needs to be a cool 40K dog. […] That’s why we want it to sound cool, especially when it’s<br/>more cyber-dog as well. ‘Cause we want to set some kind of staple, like ‘This is how Cyber<br/>Dogs sound in Darktide’. That’s why it’s so important to nail it.” ~Jonas</i><br/><br/><b>Sound Effects and Foley</b><br/>Depending on what Cyber-Mastiff cosmetics the player has equipped, it can affect which of the<br/>Cyber-Mastiff’s legs are made of metal and which aren’t. This led to us needing proper sounds<br/>for different combinations, so that the dog would make the correct sounds when moving around depending on your set up.<br/><br/>This was also an opportunity for our designers to make their own sounds from scratch rather<br/>wherever possible. A metal cycle pump, for instance, was a perfect base for the metal footsteps, and sound recordings of it in different locations and on different surfaces gave plenty of material. Or using a glove with paperclips at the tips to make the normal paw sounds!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c583e70d23dc58ece7ca835cbdc2bf764d16bcd7.jpg"/><br/><i>When you hear the Cyber-Mastiff move, you’ll probably be hearing one of these!</i><br/><br/>Playtesting led to a lot of fine tuning and iteration on the volume levels of the different sounds, the footsteps, the barks and so on. The player should be able to hear those sounds without it being annoying, which was a particular challenge with the metal footsteps. At the same time, the sound of combat should drown out some of the sounds but you should still be able to hear the voice of your own dog.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Bonus questions</div><br/><b>Will the Cyber-Mastiff have cosmetics?</b>Yes! You’ll be able to customize their loyal companion by giving it a name and picking its fur<br/>colour and pattern!<br/><br/>Players will also be able to further customize their loyal companion with various cosmetics,<br/>obtained either from the class penances and through the Commodore’s Vestures.<br/><br/><b>Can you pet the Cyber-Mastiff?</b>Yes! Only in the Mourning Star, but there’s various interactions you can have with your<br/>companion in the hub, including giving it a quick pet for being a loyal companion.<br/><br/><b>Is the Cyber-Mastiff a good dog?</b><br/><i>“I mean… It’s a good dog… to its owner. It’s a terrifying killing machine to everything else.” ~<br/>Gunnar<br/><br/>“I want to give a shoutout to Molly here at the office, which is the Art Director’s dog. She is such a well-trained dog […] and she’s been a great source of inspiration for me, haha.” ~ Olliver</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7fc02b73322a49bc439a1876925168e8b86561a7.jpg"/><br/><i>Good job, Molly!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>That’s all we have for today, but stay tuned! More Dev Blogs about the Arbites will be released<br/>soon!<br/><br/><b>This is the Will of the Lex.</b><br/>We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.<br/><br/>Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/<br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497196316182447186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3b7cbbccde3c3a8d79d2423f6924e81f046aae12.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings everyone!<br/><br/>Today, we’re releasing Hotfix 6.1.5, bringing new fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III including various fixes to maneater psychology, quest battles and how Wood Elves rumble in the jungle.<br/><br/>Without further ado, let’s get into it.<br/><br/>— Anastasija Dolgošejeva // Senior Community Manager // Your friendly neighbourhood penguin<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Campaign</div><div class="bb_h2">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash to desktop after manually winning Vilitch’s Quest Battle Vessel of Chaos and waiting for the loading back to the campaign map.<br/></li><li> Fixed bug where Ogre Camps would move after every battle and every game load.<br/></li><li> Marching stance movement extents now should be again shown correctly while the military force is in default stance.<br/></li><li> The Rite of Awakening event video now correctly plays rather than the 2D image.<br/></li><li> When the user opens and immediately close the UI panel for The Skull Throne the script will be canceled to prevent scripted tour pop-ups. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the the campaign camera went under the terrain in some cases..<br/></li><li> Chaos Dwarfs when occupying the Galleon's Graveyard now have a garrison.<br/></li><li> Jungles now function as forests when applying Wood Elf "during forest battles" effects like the skill for Waystalkers, "The Endless Hunters".</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Skills</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Exalted Lord of Change Skill "Impossible Egotist" now correctly give heroes in their army "Silenced".<br/></li><li> Snow Leopards are now affected by the Hag Witch's skill "Wildkeeper".</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">UI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fix getting "Under-City Discovered!" messages for settlements belonging to other factions.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash when trying to open technology tree from Gorbads Tactics menu on non players turn.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">Battle</div><div class="bb_h2">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Issue fixed where multiple RoR Gyrobombers attacking in fast forward are causing game crashes.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Ulrika Maldova would always be staggered by powerful attacks when mounted on a horse.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with one of Arbaal’s quest battles so that Vampire Coast armies are no longer visible before the reinforcements to prevent the pop-up message about hidden foes to appear.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where one of Skulltaker's quest battles could be won without fighting the entire enemy army.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Overtyrant’s Crown quest battle where one of the waves will attack the player armies right after they leave the reinforcement location. <br/></li><li> Golgfag &amp; the Eshin Maneater now have Immune to Psychology attribute like other meaneaters.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Battle Maps</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some floating vegetation on The Dragon Isles battle map.<br/></li><li> Mopped up invisible shallow water on the Road to Talabheim battle map.</li></ul>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 10:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More fixes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515211349279640979</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hey all, here's a list of some more changes to the game with this new patch<br/><br/>Please <b>restart Steam</b> and remember that most patches are not compatible with older ones, so you will not see games from the previous build in the game browser.  <b>It will take a little while for new ones to start up</b> - or feel free to create a game!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed issue with some challenges not progressing<br/></li><li>Fixed crash bug at the end of match rewards screen<br/></li><li>Fixed bug where hosts were not able to use their customized vehicles<br/></li><li>Fixed bug when selecting alternate abilities in the Kustomize screen<br/></li><li>Improved race waypoint sync for Free Roam mode<br/></li><li>Fixed issue with full games showing as 15/16 in game browser<br/></li><li>Swapped Konstruct skin reward on existing challenge to scrap boost, as it was causing issues<br/></li><li>Added new challenge to both Looted Wagon and Grot Mega Tank that reward players with the Konstruct skin<br/></li><li>Added daily Rukkatrukk challenge, 6 kills + assists<br/></li><li>Added daily Trukk challenge, 3 kills<br/></li><li>Attempted to improve performance on Da Dust Up and Da Gorge<br/></li><li>Fixed some minor collision and visual issues in some maps<br/></li><li>Removed "Mob Up!" achievement for the time being, as parties are not currently in the game<br/></li><li>Disabled daily party challenge since playing in a party is no longer possible.<br/></li><li>Fix for showing player level at Kill Kam and MVP screens</li></ul>We've been pretty on top of issues and still are working on the bigger ones like hit reg and host migration. We'll let everyone know when there's news on that or other high priority items ːsteamthumbsupː<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/147b1768aae9ac663c50a5fec47f3ba790647d05.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Quick Fixes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515211349279639544</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI, just a quick one with some fixes below that we felt necessary to patch<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed crash related to player states<br/></li><li>Fixed issue with game browser not updating<br/></li><li>Fixed accessories issue in the Kustomize menu<br/></li><li>Fixed players not getting scrap from solo matches<br/></li><li>All maps autoselect now when creating a new game<br/></li><li>Bots are enabled by default when creating a new game<br/></li><li>Added number of players in public lobbies to the bottom of the Game Browser<br/></li><li>votekick response window changed to 20 seconds<br/><br/>Have a good weekend ladz ːsteamthumbsupː</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
