<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Havoc Q&amp;A - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456969803786092919</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1203d0447080a2a770ff3e7bf219d31282777589.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div> <br/><br/>A couple of weeks ago, we released an Introduction to Havoc dev blog. Similar to when we released the Introduction to Itemization dev blog over the summer, we’ve received a lot of comments and questions. <br/><br/>For Itemization, we answered these in the form of a couple of Q&amp;A posts, and we thought it would be a great format to use for discussing Havoc, as well. <br/><br/>We’ll compile the most common remaining questions after this post and we’ll answer them in the patch notes when it is released on 3 December.<br/><br/>Something that has changed since the last dev blog is the nomenclature used in this game mode. From now on we will be calling what was previously known as a Havoc Order a Havoc Assignment (aka the current mission a player is assigned), and what was previously known as your Havoc Rank will now be known as your Havoc Clearance Level (the highest Havoc Assignment you’ve cleared - whether it’s your own or through the party finder).<br/><br/>We’d also like to say these are the answers we have NOW. Our plan is to evaluate further after release and read player feedback to the game mode. From there, we can see if anything needs to be adjusted or changed by working with the community. We see this as the start of a long journey and will keep tweaking it just like any other system in the game.<br/><br/>Thank you for your passion for Darktide and we hope we can answer the most burning questions we’ve seen. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Are FS concerned about people alt-F4ing this? For the Auric titles it was just the title but this is an entire game mode.<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>“Alt+F4:ing” to circumvent the system is something we’ve taken into account, there are two solutions to this issue, one which is bespoke to Havoc and the other a general solution. If a Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) owner leaves mid-mission <b>without reconnecting</b> it will automatically count as a loss regardless of the result of the mission for that player. It will also mean that the player receives no rewards for the attempt, and it will use up one of the three attempts for that specific Havoc Assignment level.<br/><br/>However, players who remain in the Mission will still be able to complete the mission; if they do, it will count as a win for the remaining players.<br/><br/>ALT+F4:ing to circumvent being “downed” to complete harder penances has been an issue with the Auric penance, and to this end, we’ve introduced more checks when players reconnect.** Players will now respawn back with the health count they had upon leaving, instead of being spawned with a minimal % of hp, and players who ALT+F4 to get around being downed will now spawn back hogtied.<br/><br/>**This is a game wide change coming with Grim Protocols, it is not exclusive to Havoc.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do we select the 1-5 difficulty level when playing Havoc or are these missions working on a completely different system, where difficulty is fixed?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc has its own difficulty structure that is loosely based on the normal difficulties. The way players can choose difficulty is by either starting their Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) by gathering some friends or by starting a group through the party finder. Likewise if you fancy another mission configuration you can look through the party finder and join one there.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>If I complete my Havoc Assignment (Havoc Order) as soon as it’s available, do I have to wait a week before I’m given a new one?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You can complete as many Havoc Assignments in a row as you like. The only thing that is on a weekly cadence is the weekly reward which is based on the highest Havoc Assignment you were able to complete during the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I’m confused about how the decay system works for Havoc.<b><br/><br/>Answer</b><br/>Yes, let’s clarify the fluid ranking system using the new nomenclature written in the intro of this dev blog. It has changed a bit since the last dev blog after reading feedback.<br/><br/>A player’s Havoc Clearance Level will update on a weekly basis based on the highest Havoc Assignment they completed the previous week (whether it was their own Assignment or played through the Party Finder). <br/><br/>As long as a player is active within the Havoc system during any given week they will not automatically decay at the end of the week. We will however keep an eye on how this system plays out in reality and adjust the rules accordingly. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Can you replay your completed Havoc Assignment levels? Like if I was at level 20 but wanted to bust down to 5, could I do that on my own? Or would I need to find someone with a level 5 Assignment to join?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You cannot replay depleted / completed missions since the missions are uniquely generated. If you’d like to take a break and play a lower-rank Assignment you can instead find a compatible team on the party finder with the Assignment you like. The same goes for the opposite: if you want to try your hands on an Assignment that is higher than the one you currently own, you can find a team that is playing a higher one and ask to join them.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Is Havoc level character locked like Melk contracts (well trust level is, so…) so we’ll have to level our 4 characters at the same time each week?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc is not locked to a specific character, “ergo” Havoc is account-wide. With Havoc our intent is for players to adapt to the Havoc Assignment at hand by selecting the correct character, talents, weapons, blessing and curios to best take on the challenge. However, your character still needs to be level 30 to be able to join a Havoc mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Will new garb be also character locked then? (Level up operative to gain access to new Moebian cosmetics for that class).<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The cosmetics from Havoc are account-wide. (The same as any other cosmetic in the game.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>What determines the max difficulty that I can currently play?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>As long as a player is level 30 and can find a group that is willing to take them along, a player could in theory play any Assignment level at any time. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do I get access to a difficulty, based on my current highest completed? Can I access all difficulties &lt;= my current max, or only 1 diff at a time?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>At all times you have access to your own Assignment. If you feel like playing a lower Assignment level the way to do so would be to find a party with a lower Assignment level in the party finder and vice versa if you are looking for a higher Assignment level than what you currently own.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does my max available mission difficulty get reset every week?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Your maximum available mission difficulty will move forward with you into the next week. Each week players will get a new Havoc Assignment based on the highest Assignment they completed the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Do i need to play from diff 1-40 within a single week in order to get to rank 40, unless i just join someone else's high diff mission?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>No, you will continue the next week at the same level that you left off the previous week. The only thing that is weekly dependent is the weekly reward that is based on the highest-ranked mission you completed during the week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>What happens when my rank drops? Do I lose access to the higher difficulty missions?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will always be able to play any Assignment Level that you want to play and are able to find a group that will play with you. Your own Havoc Assignment only dictates which mission you can start yourself. But if you can find a group that is playing a higher-ranked mission that you can join you will be able to do so. Your weekly reward will be based on the highest-ranked mission you have completed. Next week your Havoc Assignment will be set to the highest mission you have completed the previous week.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>To clarify, I’m pretty sure the modifiers at levels 1-40 are fixed for all players (possibly forever?). The only thing different for each player at the same level is the mission and mutators?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Havoc Assignment’s difficulty is composed of two components, one is the static negative modifiers we apply per Level basis and are additive so each Assignment will include everything from the previous one, the other part is generated per Assignment basis and includes the Mission, Theme, and mutators. <br/><br/>Over time we’ll continue adding more mutators into the pool, but more on that at a later time…<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I don’t understand how matchmaking is going to work with this. There is no quickplay, but you can just queue into it? What does that mean for matchmaking? will it try to find 3 other players who are close to your ‘level’?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Due to the vast amount of permutations in the mode, there will not be any matchmaking in this game mode. Also the difficulty is so significant that you will want to tailor the group more specifically than a matchmaking service could do effectively. This is one of the reasons we created the Group Finder, which we hope will see a significant increase in use with the release of this feature.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does this mean that it will take at least 40 weeks for the first players to reach Hacoc Clearence Level 40?<br/><br/>Assuming the answer to the previous question is no, (ie, that when you gain or lose an Assigment Level you can immediately attempt your new Assignment Level), if you are demoted from Clearance Level 20 to 19, but then beat Level 19 and move back up to Level 20, will your new Havoc Assignemnt 20 still be the same as it was the first time?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will be able to reach Havoc Clearance Level 40 as fast as you and your team can complete the Assignments required to do so. There is no time gating happening when it comes to the number of assignments possible to complete in a given week. When you complete a Havoc Assignment, a new one will be designated to you by Darinda Duakane as soon as you report back to her. The new Assignment will not be the same as the previous one if you go up or down in Assignment level.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>I would like to ask what happens to a player’s Havoc rating if they quit before the match completes?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>Leaving before a Havoc mission ends will result in a loss for the player. It will also lock you out of starting another Havoc (only Havoc mission) until the mission has ended. If you are the Assignment holder, you will lose one of the attempts at the Havoc Assignment level. <br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="width=624,height=29"/>https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdoZbRX-cWzyCOZVGm0HA7aXYhRTHwCSnWS65GCU3lJziMFiKYWK2f-zBsLcIVWUzBwW_rtxlhaOPlE_NV7-XXy2XHS_ssiNhTV7F4pjZ2Sjnre3eJXNe5XmHI4nZKnk_ojRnPMPqwMOxUk1R_6LHwSRlmF?key=m0osxNPqksATxB0XbddLg6p3<br/><b>Question</b><br/>Does this mean your Havoc Clearance Level (“Rank”) will never go down, but that your access to Havoc Assignments will?<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>The Havoc Rank will display the highest Clearance Level a player has completed and is not directly linked to the current level of that player's Havoc Assignment. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Question</b><br/>Will there be a way to see what the current havoc rank of a player is? With rewards on the line for mission completion, I just get the feeling that people not ready for the latter half of havoc ranks will just try and join as many high ranking parties they can, looking to get carried through it.<br/><br/><b>Answer</b><br/>You will be able to see the Clearance Levels of all prospective applicants to your group to be able to make the best informed decision.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>OK, that is our Q&amp;A! Thank you to everyone who wrote questions on our previous dev blog. As mentioned above, we’ll compile any of the common remaining questions after this post and we’ll include them in the patch notes for Grim Protocols on 3 December. <br/><br/>Thank you for your passion and we look forward to everyone getting their hands on Havoc and the rest of the update. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Kruber &amp; Ratling Gunner + Hotfix 6.0.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490746800993468496</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>second</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div>But first, congratulations is in order! The first week's spotlight, Kerillian VS Gutter Runner, was a smash hit! The target for the Community Challenge was surpassed in no time, reaching a whopping 270,000 out of 40,000 by the time the event had ended, and was just shy of a million before the reset today! That's a lot of Heroes slain, you devilish Pactsworn!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a91509932b0c354b2376df02549dd83f6bd1332f.png"/><br/><br/>For everyone who played during the last spotlight, you've earned this Kerillian Hero Pose and this portrait frame (provided you accumulated enough playtime!):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/c688fb003f164b523d0f5554d50eac8cfe945716.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly through the Kill-Counter and personal rewards to unlock through a small ‘win-track’. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Kruber &amp; Ratling Gunner Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between November 21 - November 24.</b> All rewards will be granted the following week. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock an <b>exclusive skin for the Ratling Gunner.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Spotlight-track</div>Meanwhile, the win-track rewards will be unlocked depending on how much time you spend in Vermintide 2. Don’t worry, it won’t be too difficult, we promise. You can play Adventure, Chaos Wastes, Weaves, or Versus to unlock the rewards*. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/8de201cdceef319a43210aca4b34665957a53850.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Playing for at least half an hour earns you 60 shillings.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least an hour earns you another 60 shillings as well as 30 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least two hours additionally earns you a brand new Portrait frame and 70 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.<br/></li><li> Playing for at least three hours additionally earns you a Hero Pose for Kruber!</li></ul><i>This playtime is tracked across all game modes, but is only tracked while in an actual match.</i><br/><br/><i>*You cannot actively check on your track progression. All rewards will be granted the following week</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Kruber</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/aeb5353b2fbeeea8c3ced31be7947db1490b9c5f.png"/><br/>Although still world-weary and marked by his experiences, Kruber has found purpose in the aftermath of Ubersreik. As a soldier first, last and always, he understands that some battles have to be fought, no matter the cost. And who better to fight them than Markus Kruber?<br/><br/><b>Learn more about Kruber here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Ratling Gunner</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/84ce6edc1a9b95f76f5c01e1e8fa190cc8a148a6.png"/><br/>The Ratling Gun is a six-barreled monstrosity of unparalleled fire-rate, powered by warp steam and operated with a hand crank. This fearsome weapon is normally operated by a Clan Skryre weapons team, but lighter, experimental versions have been sighted in the Reikland. These variants require only a single ratman to act as crew, with little apparent trade-off.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Ratling Gunner here!</b><br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.0.4 - 20th of November							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Tweaked the power of items received from crafting:</b> Each Hero level past level 30 increases the minimum power of crafted items by 1. This means that at sufficiently high levels, crafted items are guaranteed to be 300 item power. Only the level from the highest level character is considered.<br/></li><li>	(Versus) <b>Tweaked the Helmgart Sellsword Marks received from playing matches:</b> Players now receive 5 coins for playing a match, plus another 5 if they won.<br/></li><li>	Tweaked the rarity of some of the Skaven skins.								<br/> </li><li>	Added the ability to equip Hero Poses on the Deprecated UI.								<br/> </li><li>	Removed fade to black when exiting the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Increased the window where players will count as having assisted or caused an enemy player kill based on how long it's been since you've last dealt damage to them.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Various quality of life improvements to the Custom Game lobby:								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Added the option to create private versus custom lobbies.</b> Private games can be joined by friend joining through Steam or the in-game friend UI.<br/></li><li>	Added more sound effects to various actions in the lobby.							<br/> </li><li>	Added the option to make the level random.							<br/> </li><li>	Added gamepad support for the custom game menu and lobby.							<br/> </li><li>	Changed so your team is always blue and the enemy team is red.							<br/> </li><li>	Added Steam avatars in custom game lobbies.							<br/> </li><li>	Changed the position of the leave button so it is harder to misclick.	<br/> </li><li>	Added an message for when a player-hosted VS lobby cannot be started (eg. everyone is on the same team).</li></ul></li><li>	(Versus) Made improvements to how versus lobbies are displayed in the lobby browser.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Slightly reduced the XP gained from winning matches, completing matches, and eliminating heroes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Added another ladder back up on the first bridge to more easily revive downed Heroes								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Pactsworn can no longer hear key pickup on Against the Grain.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue where the Pactsworn keybind prompts would overlap with the subtitles.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a missing sound when clicking the 'continue' button on the end screen.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue where the text would overlap in the end screen in some languages.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a bug where destroying all 9 chains in Screaming Bell would progress the related challenge by 10 instead.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where some cosmetics on Lohner's Emporium would say "Equippable by all Heroes and Careers" when they weren't.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed various issues in Righteous Stand, including a spot where players could get stuck, a potion that was hard to pick up, some visual bugs, and more.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed the rumbling sound effect not stopping if you die while shooting as a Warpfire Thrower.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the Mission Select tutorial showing up in non-Adventure keeps.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed DLC rewards and handbook popups showing on top of each other.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a visual glitch on the pagination buttons in the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug that made it impossible to open the handbook with controller in the pause menu.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where you couldn't scroll the text on handbook popups using a gamepad.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where the talents where half transparent in the tab menu.								<br/> </li><li>	Made bots in Versus always use default loadouts in both Dedicated Servers and player hosted games, avoiding various crashes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Custom Game) Fixed gamepad input description being incorrect.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Custom Game) Fixed confirm input not being confirmed when selecting a map.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the reward tooltips in difficulty select showing the best earned chest instead of the chest the player would earn at their level.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed crash that could happen when a player left while in a loading screen.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Added a lever to open the Ruins in Engines of War to avoid the mission being soft-locked.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue with Bile trolls portrait frames not showing the correct description								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a visual glitch on the next/prev page arrows in the handbook when using a controller								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed strings not being uppercased in a locale-dependant way (eg. `Botín de guerra` was `BOTíN DE GUERRA`).								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Fixed a bug where Skaven players can get soft-locked when they Q to Heroes that are AFK in the safe zone								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Added a fix to prevent Skaven players from entering the Hero safe zone before the round starts								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Added a fix to prevent Hero players from leaving the safe zone before the round starts								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Engines of War) Climb point improvements								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where allies that left the game early would be shown in the enemy team's scoreboard.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed bug where pact sworn climb points blocked interactions for heroes.								<br/> </li><li>	(Chaos Wastes) Fixed a crash caused by the damage sharing curse.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash caused by joining a match and trying to sync things that the joining player hadn't loaded yet.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where "Player eliminated" badge showed to the Sienna player when Sienna dies from overheating. As hilarious as it was.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed an issue where the cannon balls can get stuck in the elevator								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed an issue where players can not pass the destroyed Ram gate easily on both sides								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) (Fort Brachsenbrücke) Fixed some areas where players can get stuck or end up inside geometry								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Versus lobbies now show the difficulty as 'Versus' in the browser.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue that could cause player-hosted VS lobby level selection to sometimes fail saving.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash when trying to reserve a spot in a custom versus game before joining.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash that could happen when closing the handbook.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed kill and knockdown confirmation badge in Versus not properly showing when players are credited eliminations but are not dealing the final blow.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash when spawning as a DLC career if purchasing it while the game is running. Purchasing a dlc career no longer prompts the user to restart.								<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed victory and defeat sound stingers being muffled at the end of a match</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Status update for the players who lost progression during the update:					</div> <br/>		Hey all,<br/><br/>Apologies for the wait on an update to this issue. We hear your frustrations and concerns, understandably.<br/>We are still working with our backend service provider in an attempt to restore missing player data. A list of all affected player accounts has been provided to our backend service provider, and they are working to provide a snapshot of the lost player data before the issue occurred (which would be the fastest resolution); with which we can merge this back into your post update-6.0.0 account progression.<br/><br/>However, to be fully transparent, we have been informed that this is not guaranteed. It will take a little more time to know for sure. We appreciate this is concerning to hear, and we want to reassure affected players that <b>we have a plan B should it be needed.</b><br/>Our second option, involves using other existing logs and data we have, to create a ""backup"" that can bring your account data as close as possible to what is was prior to update 6.0.0, and then merge this with your post update-6.0.0 account progression. This is an extensive task and will take longer to deploy - so we are hoping it won't come to this.<br/><br/>In the meantime, this hotfix includes a part-fix to unlock Cataclysm again for any players who previously had it unlocked.<br/>We'll continue to provide updates and share more information as soon as we can. Thank you for your continued patience.		<br/><br/>You can follow our progress on this issue through this thread on our forums. <br/><div class="bb_h3">Known Issues</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Selecting a map in Custom Game and then switching to Random Map will crash the host.<br/></li><li> Players joining a Custom Game that is in the Hero selection phase will crash.</li></ul>We’re hoping to get those issues fixed as soon as possible.</blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.14.3 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4465977003046076524</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/>The team is currently hard at work. We'll have news about new content soon.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.14.1</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Version 1.14.3 </div><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed crash when melee attackers kill an Umbra.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 13:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Grim Protocols - Free Update Releasing 3 December</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456969803786092611</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<a class="bb_link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oC1HRacColU" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a25fdadf548b5b8376ce415c30d9a118ac81444b.jpg"/></a><br/><br/>(Note: due to a technical issue stemming from formatting, we are reposting the announcement for Grim Protocols - click the cover above to watch our Narrative Trailer🙏)<br/><br/>Hey Everyone, <br/><br/>We’ve been cooking for you. We’re ready to announce our next major update, Grim Protocols. It will be released on 3 December on all platforms. <br/><br/>This update will include: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> New Game Mode - Havoc: Think you’ve mastered the threat over Tertium? Think again. Havoc is a new end-game experience that will test the resolve of the most seasoned operative. Be ready to face daunting challenges and earn new cosmetic rewards. We’ve posted an initial dev blog about this, and we’re working on finishing the Q&amp;A post to follow.<br/></li><li> New Mission - Dark Communion:  Return to the Carnival and explore its darkest corners. Steel yourself as you face hordes of cultists who will stop at nothing to achieve their Dark Communion. We are working on a dev blog for this. <br/></li><li> Three New Weapon Families: Tear through waves of enemies by wielding the destructive might of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords, and the Ogryn Heavy Stubber. We are working on a dev blog for this…but here is a sneak peek: </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Two-Handed Power Sword (2 Marks) - Zealot:</b> A massive, high-damage melee weapon with wide, sweeping attacks.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade<br/></li><li> Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade</li></ul><br/><i>Two-Handed Power Sword - Unique Features</i>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Heat Activation Mechanic</b>: Generates a heat gauge, building over time. Reaching the limit locks activation briefly (overheat mechanic).<br/></li><li> <b>Special Attack</b>: Sprinting Heavy stab attack for unique engagement tactics.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Two-Handed Force Sword (2 Marks) - Psyker</b>: A finesse-oriented weapon combining melee and psychic powers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Covenant Mk VI Blaze Force Greatsword<br/></li><li> Covenant Mk VIII Blaze Force Greatsword</li></ul><br/><i>Two-Handed Force Sword - Unique Features</i>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Force Cleave</b>: Special attack releases a psychic cleave with scaling based on charge power (three stages).<br/></li><li><b> Smooth Flow</b>: Psyker’s psi-assisted techniques make the weapon feel lighter and more agile.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><b>Heavy Stubber (3 Marks) - Ogryn</b>: A heavy, precision-support firearm for Ogryns, blending suppressive fire with marksman capabilities that will keep the darkness at bay. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Krourk Mk IIa Heavy Stubber<br/></li><li> Gorgonum Mk IIIa Heavy Stubber<br/></li><li> Achlys Mk II Heavy Stubber</li></ul><br/><i>Heavy Stubber - Unique Features</i>:<br/>Primary Fire: Heavy, slow automatic fire for suppressive roles.<br/>Alt Fire: A more precise, single-shot mode for longer-range accuracy.<br/>Flashlight: Included to assist in low-light environments.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Anniversary Special Event:</b> To celebrate the second anniversary of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, the game will host an event that will reward players with a unique weapon trinket. <br/></li><li> <b>And more:</b> Including the expansion of the Penance progression track with new challenges and rewards, as well as quality of life improvements such as an extension of the Party Finder feature and idle animations to Stances. </li></ul><br/>Here are some complementary screenshots of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords as well as a glimpse into Dark Communion. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3778d4edc53be9a890ea84b736621f6d1b5798b3.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b73602cb948ac46648af985c199709508f62b36a.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c669d6c29eabca6e8130daec1cef93f4ecaa6ea5.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0c5f8facbf770ac03247b2abc727f475e2c15a17.jpg"/><br/><br/>We look forward to sharing more about this update with players in the coming few weeks. We’re finishing up dev blogs on the new weapons, the new mission Dark Communion, and more. Stay tuned!<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 17:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mod Support - A Message from the Game Director</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6681747476222836957</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello, Space Marines</div><br/>We’ve seen incredible community engagement since launch, and we’ve noticed that some players have started to create and share mods for Space Marine 2. We wanted to make a game that was moddable from the start (this is why our game pack files are not encrypted, for example). It's always a pleasure for me, as a developer, to see what our community can create. Mods are great, and they will no doubt contribute to this game's longevity.<br/><br/>However, we as developers must also ensure game stability and continuously work towards a smoother experience for all players. Our data shows that a non-negligible amount of recent server stability issues are related to mods, and that instability impacts even those users who don’t have mods installed. We have also received user reports that their save files were corrupted after playing alongside players with mods.<br/><br/>This is why, starting with our next big update in December, mods will be prohibited from public online sessions. That means that you will no longer be able to enter a public game if you have mods installed.<br/><br/>However, we know that mods are a source of fun and creativity, and they will still be allowed in private Operations lobbies. We will continue to provide all necessary server infrastructure so you can play online with your friends with mods. Once we add custom Eternal War lobbies, mods will work for them as well.<br/><br/>We will also be providing an easy entry point to our backend for games with mods installed, so modders won’t have to spend time hacking the game executable after each patch. If we somehow break this pipeline for mods by accident in the future, we’ll fix it. In addition to that, we will be releasing some of our tools to modders so they can develop mods with greater ease.<br/><br/>Thank you for your understanding and cooperation.<br/><br/>The Emperor protects.<br/><br/>—Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 15:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
