<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Extended Arbites Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/610914203288469922</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Aspiring Arbitrators of the Lex Imperialis! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As we promised with the release of the <u>Arbites Gameplay Trailer</u> at the PC Gaming Show, we’re bringing you a 7 minute long video showing gameplay of Arbitrators and their terrifying cybernetically-enhanced companions in their element, dispensing the Emperor’s justice with ruthless efficiency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Give it a watch! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" aq_vdjolpsy?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5b8a0fa6df58683b86cf4c8b5862f60ba2b2cf87.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Regrettably, as this extended gameplay video is not a trailer nor, as it happens, a teaser, we were unable to stir the caption guy from his profoundly deep slumber - so you will have to do without this time around!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Emperor Protects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join us for the Total War 25th anniversary celebrations</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497197576207993840</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/be39422cd27a3116b3ce77f4d8e689be00aaaa91.png"/><br/><br/>Hey Total War fans,<br/><br/>25 years ago, in a small one room office just down the road from where I write this message, Total War was born. The vision was rooted in a love for both history and strategy gaming, with the aim of seamlessly mixing the best parts of grand strategy and real-time tactical battles into a single experience where you truly felt like the commander of a vast empire.<br/><br/>During those early years Total War’s identity formed. The team were focused on authentic recreations of the most pivotal moments in human history from the Age of Antiquity through to the emergence of the great naval empires. As the genre evolved and our teams changed, we expanded into new territory by leaping into the fantastical; meticulously recreating Games Workshop’s iconic Warhammer World as a truly unique strategy experience.<br/><br/>There have been triumphs and tribulations throughout the years, and we’re honoured and humbled to be one of the few video game franchises that get the chance to celebrate such a huge milestone. Without your support this would never have been possible – so a massive thank you from all of us on this special day!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/812d90ece1ee1c37fbff348098652ce711c15ce2.jpg"/><br/><i>[Early 2000's at the old South Water where games from SHOGUN - MEDIEVAL II were developed]</i><br/><br/><br/>Some of you may remember from my update last year that we had plans to celebrate this anniversary in a meaningful way. Our teams are hard at work fine tuning a program of content that not only shines a light on past games but builds the foundation for us to begin revealing what we have planned for the future of Total War. And yes, this means the reveal of new games and content.<br/><br/>25 years of Total War will begin with a look back at our legacy. Taking place from August until the end of November, we’ll journey through each series that has been released since 2000. Expect content like retrospective video interviews, developer livestreams, sales across our entire catalogue, as well as fantasy and historical multiplayer tournaments. We also want to make this a celebration you can get involved in, so we'll be hosting giveaway competitions, inviting you to ask questions of our developers, as well as spotlighting your favourite mods and content creators who have helped make the Total War community what it is today.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b6e5e77e23906595528f385a024b26b119fbd6cc.jpg"/><br/><i>[2013, the launch of Total War: ROME II]</i><br/><br/><br/>Beyond celebrating the past, we plan on welcoming the future of Total War in a big way. Behind the scenes, we’re in the early stages of producing the Total War: 25th Anniversary Showcase, the first video presentation of its kind in our history. Taking place in early December, this show will unveil the new games that you can expect to play in the near and distant future, as well as introduce you to the development teams making them. We’ll have more details to share as we approach the end of the year, but whether you’re a fantasy or history fan, there will be plenty to enjoy!<br/><br/>Alongside all of this will be more WARHAMMER III content. Patch 6.2 arrives next week with a focus on Magical Items, Tides of Torment's third and final faction will be revealed in July, and we'll unveil some long-awaited content at the anniversary showcase. It's incredible to think that this series is now in its ninth year, and we look forward to sharing what we have planned for the future.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/bc0af97b03b074b0aca1cb9053540cac1eca4871.jpg"/><br/><i>[2016, the launch of Total War: WARHAMMER]</i><br/><br/><br/>What’s especially important to me this year is celebrating everyone who has made Total War what it is today. This includes all of you reading this message who have helped create the best community in gaming. Whether you’re playing our games for thousands of hours, watching our trailers, submitting bug feedback, or commenting on our socials, all of this has helped us build a game we all love.<br/><br/>It also takes an army of passionate and talented staff to take our games from concept to completion. Many of them talk about growing up with Total War; how it gave them an interest in history or the deep lore of Warhammer, and how it created a desire for them to work at Creative Assembly. They’re fans making the game they love, and I want to thank each and every one of them, past and present, for their contribution to making this milestone possible.<br/><br/>We hope you’re excited for the future.<br/><br/>Happy anniversary to you all,<br/><br/>— Roger Collum, Vice President of Total War<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/6c60f48ca9e3596a90de8949ddad412389e63e62.jpg"/><br/><i>[2023, pre-launch set created for Total War: PHARAOH]</i><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord Bluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.2 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497197576207993519</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
​​<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8cc53b799d86ba87c47165708323697e50658921.jpg"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>Next week, we’re expecting to publish the full release notes for Update 6.2, as well as the Update itself. Ahead of its release, we thought we’d give you a heads up on what to expect in this update, direct from William Håkestad, Senior Game Designer on Total War: WARHAMMER III.<br/><br/>In Update 6.2, look forward to extensive revisions to Magic Items, an introduction of the AI Improvements tested in the proving grounds, the introduction of a few new Magic Items, and the arrival of two new units: The Hobgoblin Bolt Thrower, and Blood Knights.<br/><br/>Sit tight for the full release notes next week with all of our improvements and fixes, and more on those two new units, but in the mean time here’s William with the Sports and Weather (and plenty of insight on our revisions to Magic Items).<br/><br/><i>Adam Freeman // Head of Community</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 PATCH 6.2 DEV BLOG 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites - Dev Blog: The Voices of the Lex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254834881</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With the introduction of Arbitrators to the Mourningstar and to celebrate the upcoming release of our new DLC we’re going to talk a bit about the voice work. Matthew Ward, Michael Knight and David Wahlund tell us what it’s like working with Darktide’s cast and the process we go through to get the performances just right.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What does the audition procedure look like?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Matthew Ward: </i>The casting process for Darktide never really stops. We’re always adding new characters to the game, which means that we’re always in contact with new talent, either for specific roles or with an ear to getting them involved at some point in the future when something suitable arises. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">As to how we find our actors, it’s always a mix. Some are from blind casting processes where our studio partners source self-taped auditions in line with a casting brief that we provide. Others we approach based on their past work in one medium or another, and more via recommendations from the recording studios or existing cast members. It’s a broad spectrum approach that over the years has given us a great mix of industry veterans, rising stars and the odd member of video game royalty.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In almost every case, the casting process ends with a directed live audition session at one of our studios, where we hone the actor’s interpretation of the character and hopefully hit that sweet spot of what works for them and matches what we’re looking for.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Of course, sometimes we hear something we didn’t <i>know </i>that we were looking for, and that’s really where the magic happens.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Michael Knight</i>: I’m constantly blown away by the talent we manage to draw to our game. I think it speaks to the effort that’s always been put into the voices we feature in the Tide games.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are there many Warhammer: 40,000 fans among the contenders?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It’s not something that we stipulate, but it’s always a bonus when it comes together that way, as the accompanying knowledge and enthusiasm always shows. Greg Jones and Alex Jordan are some examples from our longstanding cast, Michael Geary from our more recent intake. And of course, we have several actors who are familiar with the Warhammer: 40,000 setting from their work on other projects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK:</i> We also often find people who’ve never interacted with the IP being fascinated by its depth (and darkness!)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How specific are the VO directions? I've seen footage of actors holding prop guns and running on the spot to get the right dynamic and exertion sound for the lines. Is there any more like that?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>Some of our actors - and they know who they are - would probably refuse to record if they didn’t have their stand-in weaponry to tote around. I’m almost entirely sure that’s healthy, and I’ll always say that if there’s any chance that they might be listening. Or armed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">But seriously, everyone’s method is different. We record almost exclusively with head-mounted microphones, which allow the talent to roam - or literally throw themselves - around the recording booth if they want. Others get the motion and inflection we’re looking for while standing still or perched on a chair. Whatever gets the results, gets the results.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the weirdest direction that has been given to a VA for this game?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>I don’t know about “weirdest”, but something that always gets good results is directing the actor to shout at the recording engineer. It’s nothing personal (at least I hope not) but that always gets a great result. As far as I know we haven’t yet traumatised an engineer. In fact, most of them tend to end up grinning. People are strange.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>David Wahlund: </i>A maybe unknown and odd part of voice work is the exertions, efforts or grunts. It's the vocals that are not verbalized. In an action game we have a lot of these. When you swing the sword or get hit by a bullet for example. We have 15 different categories. Some efforts or grunts can be used in several different situations. For example a jump grunt can be used when you get pushed etc. These are all quite private sounds. Sometimes, especially when time is short, you might need to give an example yourself. That’s certainly weird the first time you do it. But by doing it yourself you might also take the edge out of the weirdness in the situation for the actor.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How does the performance process for the monstrosities work? How do you decide, or communicate to the actor "that's what we want this thing to sound like"?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>DW: </i>As Matt mentioned earlier, the actor's interpretation is super important. We need to give them as much details and context as possible so that they can be creative<b>. </b>When it comes to creatures or monster-like humans, animations and graphics play a big part. So if you can give as much visual information as possible that will certainly help. What does the mouth look like? How does the creature move? All details matter.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the average length of a recording session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW:</i> Because we ask for a lot of shouting from our actors - “Darktide Conversational Level” has become a bit of a running joke because it’s really not that conversational - most sessions run for an hour, although some of our hardier actors are happy to record for longer sessions. It’s a style of performance that’s very demanding on not only the voice but the whole body.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How many lines on average are recorded in a session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>We plan for around a hundred lines a session. Often that goes higher - when the actor’s in the zone - and sometimes it goes lower, especially when it gets <i>very </i>shouty. It’s always a balance between speed, quality and the actor’s comfort, with the latter being the absolutely most important of the three.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>We’re always adding new voice lines. How often does Fatshark have recording sessions?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It varies depending on what we want to capture. The Arbitrator sessions have been pretty full on (roughly 150 recording hours since the start of the year), but for other updates where we only need to add more NPC lines, it might just take a couple of hours. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We might not invite an actor back into the booth for months (or even years), or sometimes they’ll be in for a couple of hours for several weeks (or months) in a row. It’s all about matching our needs to their availability. Most are very busy individuals, so we try to get our asks in early.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading our dev blog on what goes into the performances and the work behind your new Arbites Class, releasing on <b>June 23, 2025 </b>on all platforms. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll do our best to answer them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites Gameplay Reveal &amp; Deluxe Edition Announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254833683</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">During today’s PC Gaming Show, we gave you a first gameplay glimpse at the Adeptus Arbites and announced the Deluxe Edition. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Check out the gameplay trailer below to see the Arbites unleashing their loyal Cyber-Mastiffs upon lexbreakers, and delivering judgment with extreme prejudice.</p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" ay5tdet0j2c?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We’re not done yet.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the lead-up to launch, we’ll be releasing more reveals. We’ll also be sharing more over the coming days, including a longer gameplay video on June 12. Additional dev blogs on the Arbites' talent tree, weapons, and more, will be published in the weeks prior to release. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>On June 23, you’ll be able to purchase the Arbites Class in two different editions:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Standard Edition: $11.99 / €11.99</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deluxe Edition: $18.99 / €18.99</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cosmetic Upgrade (Upgrade to Deluxe): $7.99 / €7.99</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Deluxe Edition includes the class and cosmetics for your Arbitrator and Cyber-Mastiff:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbites Class</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Unique Class Outfit</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Unique Companion Outfit</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Portrait Frame</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">4 Weapon Skins</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/391adc4a4acb50ff80eeccd7e63e5a69c746b72b.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks for sticking with us through this reveal, we’re beyond excited for you to take control of the Arbites on June 23, 2025! Make sure to wishlist the Arbites Class now so you're ready to restore order on Tertium Day 1.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
