<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog: Clandestium Gloriana Level Design</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068449174202</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hello, everyone! <br/><br/>We’re excited to talk about the newest mission coming to Darktide: Clandestium Gloriana (AKA Atelium Foundryplex Omega V). For this, we interviewed Lead Level Designer, Fredric Grapensparr and Narrative Lead, Michael Knight, both of whom were part of the team responsible for crafting this new zone for players. <br/><br/>When reviewing feedback from the players around the last mission we designed (The Carnival), we saw the strong response from players regarding the lore and narrative woven into the level. This is something we enjoy doing more of, and that was a key starting point for the design of Clandestium Gloriana.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G6Ca9f6xTn4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><b>Setting the Scene</b><br/><br/>From a narrative perspective, our goal was to create a temple-like facility in the Void between zones. We landed on the idea of lost facilities peppered deep within the bowels of the Hive. These fabled facilities, Machinaria Gloriana, are long-forgotten wonders constructed to support Saint Messalina's crusade through the Moebian Domain. Each is rumoured to house some technological marvel that significantly aided the war effort. Unfortunately these have fallen out of service and become lost through the centuries. (It didn’t help that record keeping was never a strong point for the Adeptus Administratum.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/2b6b7fff0d5d65bd4b65ba01f7ea182169d24936.jpg"/><br/><br/>The machine in this particular Foundryplex was centuries old, and it generated a lot of heat when it was running. This required massive cooling systems. And while the forges have been quiet for 1000s of years…no one seemed to remember to turn off the coolant system. This is the setting of our newest mission: the grandeur and prosperity of the past, contrasted with the decay and neglect of the present. This contrast is then further highlighted by the snow and ice which covers the level as a result of the forgotten coolant system. It’s visually different from anything we’ve delivered before. This setting also allowed us to introduce new gameplay mechanics and objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fbacd2de36cf344d0400d764ec77d8a5601f496c.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Introducing Swagger</b><br/>As a vehicle to further deliver narrative to this mission, the team landed on the new NPC, Swagger. <br/><br/>Swagger is an enigmatic character whose origins remain unknown. He is more capable than players might credit him based on his manner and appearance alone. For example, how did he have the codes to the Mourningstar Vox Network? How does no one seem to know where he is from?<br/><br/>Swagger is the mission giver and unlike our regular NPCs, Swagger will actually be present in the level directing the strike team from the ground. This added an additional technical aspect in terms of audio that we’re pretty excited to share with players.<br/><br/>We can also confirm this is not the last interaction players will be having with Swagger. He will be sticking around.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d5bec8bc98a5455f1e1a523e9cfcd4aba2a67c98.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Navigating the Mission</b><br/>In this mission, players are tasked with meeting Swagger, who has provided the location of this Foundryplex rumored to hold the secrets of true Moebian steel. The objective is to get the facility running, obtain samples and fulfill Hadron’s motivations (whatever they may be). The mission objectives and the end event itself will depend on the players’ capabilities more than past events. If players are a coordinated team, they’ll be able to clear the objectives more quickly and efficiently.<br/><br/>The mission starts with a sense of claustrophobia in order to foster a sense of danger and tension for players. As they progress, the environment opens up to allow for more freedom of movement and good ole’ hack and slash. This is an intentional design choice to make the initial stages more challenging, before providing players with a sense of relief and progression as they move further into the mission. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5f011fc860ee765c321bef642d75919f944e92da.jpg"/><br/><br/>We don’t want to say too much more without letting players be able to experience it for themselves. But we can say we’re particularly excited for players to reach the end event. (Jesper Kyd is a genius.)<br/><br/>Please stay tuned for more updates and dev blogs for Secrets of the Machine God! We look forward to seeing the reactions to this new level.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Update on Itemization</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068448979176</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The release of <b>Secrets of the Machine God</b> is just around the corner, and while we are excited to have you get your hands on it, we also suspect many of you might be expecting itemization to be part of this update. <b>Unfortunately, this will not be the case</b>.<br/><br/>After internal and external testing, we’ve decided the itemization rework isn’t where we want it to be for release this month. We’ve been reading your threads and taking the feedback on. The consensus being this rework should not be rushed. And we agree. <br/><br/>Now, <b>itemization is slated to release after summer</b>. We are making progress. During this time, we’re also looking at expanding the feedback loop on this rework, and will be including more players outside our core-testers. <br/><br/>To get more details, <b>we are working on a dev blog on itemization</b> to give you more insights into the work we’ve carried out so far. <br/><br/>We look forward to sharing more information about itemization and will keep working with the community to shape the upcoming itemization rework. <br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the in-depth Gameplay Overview Trailer now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4161970072170925874</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines! 💥</div><br/>We're incredibly excited to unveil a new detailed Gameplay Trailer!<br/>Narrated by the game’s Creative Director, Oliver Hollis-Leick, this 6-minute Gameplay Overview Trailer dives deeper into <i>Space Marine 2</i>’s main story campaign, its multiplayer modes, and its progression mechanics. <br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> releases on September 9. <br/>Pre-order the Gold and Ultra Editions today and play <b>up to 4 days before release.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch our Gameplay Overview Trailer now!</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5tqDxvpzsKM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">More Missions, Enemies, and Weapons to Release Through Free Updates.</div> <br/>Following the release on September 9, <i>Space Marine 2</i> players will receive new “Operations” missions and PvP maps, new enemies, and new weapons to fight them with, through regular free updates for all players. Additional cosmetics and Chapter heraldry will release as part of the Season Pass with no microtransactions or in-game cash shop involving premium currency.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/382b5355937beabb415b818b0648f9feb5638fc0.jpg"/><br/><br/>Heed the call of battle when <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> launches September 9, 2024, on PC. Pre-order the Standard, Gold, Ultra, and Collector’s Edition now! Sign up as a Focus member to get exclusive news and upcoming special offers for <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> and the whole Focus catalog.<br/><br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 6 - Let’s Paint Boomdakka Snazzwagon 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4178858570767112508</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f76a3c78a5c8f7c1ddcab2a60f8dfa6cbb3631dd.png"/><br/><br/>In order to capture the authenticity but also the casual chaotic nature of Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks, we felt capturing the stunning style of the 'Eavy Metal painted miniatures could be a great way to drive the aesthetic of the game. <br/><br/>To do this effectively across the vast quantity of assets for the game, we leveraged the power of Adobe Substance Painter and created a smart material that would do a lot of the 'eavy lifting whilst still allowing us to add hand painted touches to the models. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Research</div>We researched the look of the 'Eavy Metal miniatures. Looked at the painting techniques used by both the 'Eavy Metal painters and hobbyists so we could replicate this process and create a smart material which gives us an authentic painting style. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/ebe4c517ac112d5c57bf03dad04227c08213c06d.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Base Model</div>We take the base model. Bake out mesh maps, Normals, AO, Curvature are our key drivers for the material. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6d43647d91f21372712eded9eb72827a9124d042.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Smart Material</div>Throw on our smart material. This material runs through a multitude of layers which mimic some of the base, shade/washes and highlighting techniques used to paint physical miniatures. We can paint in details in a normal layer which will be computed and given edge highlights/shading. So we can paint in scratches, dents and holes. <br/><br/>When exported as packed textures and imported into our custom Paint Shader in Unreal Engine the Red channel drives our colour ramp, whilst the Green and Blue channels drive dirt and rust respectively. The colour ramp is put through a colour table which has colour gradients set up which reflect the paint colours used on the models. <br/><br/>Where Red is closet to black, the model paint will appear darker, where red is brighter, the paint colours will appear lighter. This gives us the painted shades and edge highlights that are synonymous with 'Eavy Metal's painting style. The Dirt (green) and Rust (blue) are added on top of the paint colours. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8382c3ed967d9678ee2e39b832b3ac3cc34df4fd.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Colour Map ID</div>In order to separate the different painted areas and provide customisation in the game, we utilize an 8 Colour ID map. Here we paint out the areas which will share colours in the game. <br/><br/>We use Red as the primary Asset colour, with Green being secondary and blue being tertiary colours. These will usually be depicted as Gunmetal and Brass/Copper in-game by default. We can also use Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, White and Black to cover any other details that may need to be separated out.<br/><br/>When you change paint colours in the game, it the ID map which dictates which colours go where. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/253a65df6364ecda8b609dcac3004fc5045c9c11.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Snazzy Graphics</div>An Ork vehicle wouldn't be complete without some snazzy paint job graphics. We apply these using a graphics texture. <br/><br/>The smart material has a graphics layer stack where We paint any checks, dags, glyphs either by hand or with stencils in substance. These are then applied over the top of the Paint colours in the shader to apply painted graphics on the vehicle. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/ddbf8d87151d854fdb99bf1fb9a8e850a32d533e.png"/><br/>We are able to change the ID maps and Graphic Maps to provide different patterns and customisation options in the game. <br/><br/>The smart material also provides us additional features for painting in Smoke (for exhausts and gun barrels), Emissive areas for flashy tek gubbinz, as well as other things. Once we are happy we use an export preset to export packed textures and we hook these up in-game. With a few parameter changes to select the paint colours we want, we frequently will reference the official miniatures for this bit, we end up with something like this: <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/178d8c75d658c1b6254be563c44a048ab13bdff0.png"/><br/>As much as this has been about trying to authentically represent the 'Eavy Metal style of the official minis, a core aspect has also been allowing people to paint their vehicles. <br/><br/>It's been great to finally allow players the ability to customise their paint jobs in the Beta and seeing people being able to be creative with it and even replicate their painted mini's in-game has been really rewarding. <br/><br/>Celebrating the creative heart of the hobby as well as the talents of the 'Eavy Metal folks has been something we wanted capture. We hope you think we've done it justice. <br/><br/>Looking forward to seeing you on the battlefield, until then happy gaming!<br/><div class="bb_h3">Joe</div><b>Lead Artist - Caged Element</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e4720e8b9dd905f56b4a553dcad45caf487cfc58.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karanak is coming to WARHAMMER III on June 25th!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/6018578477453270750</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/13b11ff3d2de0390f70fd58f898a3a1ef31852bb.png"/><br/><br/>Karanak picked up the scent! There's no more hiding... 🐕<br/><br/>Our latest free WARHAMMER III Legendary Hero slips his leash (leashes?) on June 25th!<br/><br/>Are you adding Karanak to your roster?<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
