<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497191876916412703</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0a12149d6eaeebe1fcde157bf71eb19ef88931ba.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/> <br/>We’re back with Hotfix 6.1.2, bringing a host of fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III. This update includes various improvements and adjustments, with notable faction balance tweaks for Kislev following Patch 6.1.<br/> <br/>With that, let’s get into it.<br/><br/>— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Orc Choreographer<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">HIGHLIGHTS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Kislev</b> - Based on your feedback and reviews by our Design team, we've made adjustments to balance, building, tiering, and tech for Kislev to improve your overall gameplay experience.<br/></li><li> <b>Tzeentch</b> - Kairos Fateweaver has received a number of skill fixes and adjustments.<br/></li><li> <b>Balancing &amp; Bugs</b> - a fresh batch of bug fixes and additional balance adjustments, including fixes targeting recent performance issues e.g. stuttering. As always, please report any other issues you encounter through our bug reporting sub-forum.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">STILL COOKING</div>Here’s a short list of some issues that we couldn’t quite squeeze into this hotfix, but we see them and we’re working on them:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Mod manager/launcher performance issues.<br/></li><li> Issues surrounding the display of enemy movement range previews in campaign.<br/></li><li> Court &amp; Orthodoxy becomes significantly more difficult to balance after confederating your opponent.<br/></li><li> Reports of support stuck at 100/100 and not receiving boons.<br/></li><li> Matriarchal power achievement not unlockable using the new invocations.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue causing potential frame stuttering on certain machines, as well as occasional video frame skipping in the main menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed a possible crash on the end battle screen.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that was occurring when loading the game.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that would occur when completing the Ritual of Rebirth in the Gryphon Wood during a Wood Elven Co-op campaign.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash when accessing the Ice Court.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash caused by loading a save containing the tier 3 church building from pre-Kislev rework. Any instances of the tier 3 church will be replaced by the middle option in the new building tree for the churches.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><br/><b>Kislev Balance Tweaks:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Devotion adjustments: Lowered the requirement for using Invocations to 25+ devotion. (It still costs 50 devotion to perform an invocation).</li></ul><b>Kislev Building and Tiering Adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Ice Guard recruitment building has been collapsed into one single building (found at tier 4), providing access to both Ice Guard variants and capacity for Frost Maidens.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>If you had either building constructed in an existing save, they will convert to the new combined building.</li></ul></li><li>Kislevite Cultural Capital defense buildings have been combined:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Watch patrol building chain has been removed.<br/></li><li>All the benefits associated with it have been moved to the City Defences chain, which combines siege benefits with garrisons and devotion.</li></ul></li><li>Kislev’s Wall buildings now also generate a small amount of Devotion:</li></ul><b>Ataman Experience Adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly increased experience granted by defence buildings for Atamans:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Major settlement walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>33 – 66 – 100 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300</li></ul></li><li>Minor settlement walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>40 - 80 -&gt; 100 – 200</li></ul></li><li>Kislev Cultural capital walls:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 – 100 – 150 – 200 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300 – 400 – 500</li></ul></li><li>Doubled the Experience granted by Resource buildings for Atamans.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 – 100 - 150 -&gt; 100 – 200 – 300</li></ul></li></ul></li><li>Ataman’s Estate:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>XP per turn: 800 -&gt; 1000<br/></li><li>Income modifier: -100% -&gt; -50%<br/></li><li>Additionally, no longer completely disables income<br/></li><li>Starting Supplies for sieges: 300 -&gt; 1000</li></ul></li></ul><b>Ogre Tiering Adjustments</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gnoblar Flingers<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Barracks tier 2 -&gt; 1</li></ul></li><li>Gnoblar Pigback Riders<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Barracks tier 1 -&gt; 2</li></ul></li></ul><b>Other:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bugs where Atamans (Atamen?) were lost forever if they were injured in battle or you lost or traded the city that they were based in. They can now be correctly re-recruited.<br/></li><li>Gnoblar Flingers no longer start at 10% health in garrisons on turn 1 of campaigns. (They were just out of breath!)<br/></li><li> The "Royal Ice Guardians" technology for Kislev now correctly provides upkeep reduction for armies lead by Ice Witches instead of Frost Maidens.<br/></li><li> While Yuri's journey certainly is a struggle, we didn't mean to cut his tech tree down to just the "Struggling" category. The rest of the missing prologue tech tree has been restored.<br/></li><li> Kislev will no longer generate several outdated missions related to the supporter race and the old devotion system.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug in Post Battle screen where mass visual artifacting would occur subsequently filled with black space covering the area.<br/></li><li> Added a cost element on tooltips for provincial devotion rituals.<br/></li><li> The ritual buttons in Kislev's Province Invocations UI are now correctly disabled when Devotion is spent for a Force Invocation and falls below the required threshold.<br/></li><li> Kairos' "Gaze To The Past" skill now correctly applies to the 4 lores aligned with his past head.<br/></li><li> Minor adjustments to Kairos' skill tree:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> added -25% cooldown reduction for all spells to "Prescient Cant" <br/></li><li> added "Fires of Change" lore passive to "Dwell in the Present"</li></ul></li><li> The "Court Agent" trait for Ice Witches and Frost Maidens now gives +2 ice court support per turn.<br/></li><li> Kislev will no longer randomly gain and lose access to Invocations in Gates, Forts and Bastions (these settlements do not have Public Order or Devotion.)<br/></li><li> The Kislev technology "Common Cause" is now correctly limited to units that are between rank 0 and rank 3. (Sorry Regiments of Renown, you're way out of this league.)</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI // UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a scrollbar to the available Atamans list in the Atamans Overlay so that it displays persistently and not only on mouse hover.<br/></li><li> Fixed Victory Conditions strings in the Victory Conditions panel that were missing localisation.<br/></li><li> Fire resistance and Fire Weakness now follow the new visual pattern we implemented in 6.1 with positive values appearing green and negative values appearing red when looking at the tooltip for a unit.<br/></li><li> Fix issue on the Unit Info panel where the Hero Details toggle button did not align correctly with the frame.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><b>Kislev Unit integration adjustments:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added some more technology support for Akshina Ambushers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Troll County Pathfinder now provides +10% range for Akshina Ambushers.<br/></li><li> Akshina Ambushers now benefit from Praag Veterans for +2 base missile damage</li></ul></li><li> The 'Leather Treatment' technology now also applies to Gryphon Legion units.<br/></li><li> The ‘Dwarfen Anvil’ technology now also applies to Horse Archers.<br/></li><li> The ‘Breechloaders’ technology now also grants +10% range for affected united.<br/></li><li> Common steel Orthodoxy Boon<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Recruit rank bonus 5 -&gt; 3<br/></li><li> Added Kislevite Warriors to affected units</li></ul></li></ul><b>Other:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The past and Future Kairos in the "Staff Of Tomorrow" quest battle now have spellcasting again. (Past Kairos and Future Kairos both now also only use spells associated with the past or future head!)<br/></li><li> Knights of the Brazen throne have now been issued their extra beefy Skullcrushers, changing their mass 1500 -&gt; 1800 to match the 6.1 Balance Patch Notes that accidentally contained this change before it was made.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where units with the Fire Whilist Moving ability could engage units outside their range if the unit was moving backwards or towards them.<br/></li><li> Gorbad Ironclaw no longer takes penalties for being in a forest while on foot. (He's large and in charge, but not that large).<br/></li><li> Lore of Hags is now affected by spell intensity modifiers (Omen of Spirits is exempted, to prevent it recursively increasing its own intensity).<br/></li><li> Several minor adjustments to RoR units that were not in parity with their regular version:<br/>Sisters of the Singing Doom (Witch Elves) // Melee attack +1<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bightscab's Plaguepack (Plague Monk Censer Bearers) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> Pit Fighters of Hell's Deep (Rat Ogres) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Frozen Heart of Winter (Elemental Bear) // Leadership +10<br/></li><li> The Mordheim Balewolves (The Things in the Woods) // Melee attack +4 // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> The Holy Wardens of La Maisontaal (Battle Pilgrims) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Siren of Red Ruin (Bloodwrack Medusamelee) // Defence +1<br/></li><li> Da Big Un (Rogue Idol) // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> The Fireborn (Dragon Princes) // Melee defence +1<br/></li><li> Heralds of Khorne's Fury (Bloodcrushers of Khorne) // Leadership +5<br/></li><li> Maws of Savagery (Skin Wolves - Armoured) // Melee attack +1<br/></li><li> The Tithe (Zombies) // Leadership +5</li></ul></li></ul> <br/><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues after updating to 6.1.2, please let us know over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earn the Protector of Tertium Cosmetics</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835774959059229</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Rejects!<br/><br/>Earn the Protector of Tertium Psyker cosmetics by watching eligible Twitch streams! Make your stay in Tertium a stylish, if deadly, fight for survival.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ea32c3f59c243051d00ed44ace577b5cb32df1e3.png"/><br/><br/><b>We're rebroadcasting a collection of Fatshark streams starting this Friday (April 4) at 17 CEST from our Twitch channel. The stream will be running all through the evening, so tune in at any time to start earning the rewards.<br/><br/>You can also watch any of these Twitch streamers while they're live up until April 22 to earn the rewards.</b><br/><br/>Sequens<br/>DaveeBoy<br/>Deepnausea<br/>ImJustJun<br/>Daemoniic<br/>TheAmatorium<br/>Combine03<br/>GAMEHUBLER<br/>Azenev<br/>FuPlaayz<br/>Ferlinna<br/>chocob64bit<br/>NewTypeBTW<br/>KanakoVT<br/>SkavenDan<br/>TaigaTigerVT<br/>Altair<br/>mazzeexx_<br/>NerdrageFred<br/>‍<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Click here, sign up (or log in) and follow the instructions to unlock the cosmetics!</b></div>‍<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>‍<br/><br/><i><b>For a short period of time the automatic confirmation email to join our newsletter was paused. If you signed up on the Atoma Site in the past two weeks you'll likely have a prompt to check your inbox for a confirmation mail (example below), but you won't have it because of the interruption - follow these steps to get a new confirmation email:<br/><br/>Login and go to the Account Dashboard<br/>Click edit<br/>Remove a letter (e.g. "m" in "com")<br/>Save<br/>Now click edit again and change it back to the correct email address and save again</b><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/831e07a22cceff606ad05300de13078f0e7068af.jpg"/></i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #64 (1.7.2) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520835140699555699</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5d351fcbe9df102fc33d22793582730479a8de80.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>Hotfix #64 (1.7.2) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed instances of small amounts of analogue stick movement taking control over mouse and keyboard.<br/></li><li> Fixed implementation of dead zone threshold on the right gamepad stick. </li></ul> <b>Dev Note (added 2 April):</b> <i>To get the exact same behaviour as pre-Nightmares &amp; Visions patch, playres can set the dead zone threshold to 0.24. This will mirror the dead zone with how it felt at 0 before.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fix for a crash that may occur while presenting the Havoc information at the end of the mission screen.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Assail Shards were not visible when spectating another player.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where aimed Assail shards lost their target after throwing them.<br/></li><li> Available Mastery points are now evaluated against the total amount of points needed to acquire all blessings. The player may still hold more points than needed, but the UI will not acknowledge it and show 0 as the value for the available remaining points in those cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where the equipped weapon was not the first one being selected when opening the weapon selection in the inventory or crafting.<br/></li><li> Fixed Surety of Arms talent giving peril when reloading above the threshold.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Warp Unbound would not prevent players from overloading at the end of Scrier's Gaze.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Mortis Trial Fixes and Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Pacing and difficulty for Mortis Trials</b> - Tweaked enemy compositions to slightly increase difficulty.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased the amount of minions spawned for waves 7/8/9/10/11/12 to make the waves feel more dense.</li><li>Added more minion types for wave 12, increasing the difficulty slightly according to the player power spike.</li><li>Decreasing timer for all waves. It shortened the pacing overall, making waves faster and more intense.</li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>Please let us know how it feels after these changes and we’ll continue to monitor feedback.</i> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a potential crash that could occur during scanning objectives in Mortis Trial.</li><li>The UI for the Mortis trials now behaves as expected if a player joins mid-session.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the wrong objective text was shown during scanning events in Mortis Trial.</li><li>The “Hold Your Ground” objective in Mortis Trials now shows the objective marker towards the area if you are outside of it, regardless of other players already being inside.</li><li>Fixed minor Level Art bugs.</li><li>Awarded Trinkets now display as expected in the notification panels.</li><li>The Mortis receiver machine in the lobby was lit up by default, but it has been fixed so that it only lights up after receiving the Mortis relic.</li><li>Changed out Sefonis' pictures on the cogitators in the lobby as well as in the posters on the levels.</li><li>Fixed issue where players would no longer receive buffs if they were dead and were supposed to select a buff in the Mortis trials.</li><li>Fixed a place in Mortis Trial where players could not  get attacked by melee enemies.</li><li>Fixed a bug where players died while teleporting while bringing back the Relic, which would cause the server to crash.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Cosmetic Fixes </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a black patch on the right arm of the Zealot “Vostroyan Flak Coat with Chainmail” upperbody cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed instances where part of the characters face would appear missing while wearing the following Ogryn headgear cosmetics.  <br/></li><li> Vostroyan Hat with a Chainmail Hood (Tundra Soil, XXXXL)<br/></li><li> Vostroyan Hat with a Chainmail Hood (Rust Patches, XXXXL)<br/></li><li> Vostroyan Chainmail Hood (XXXXL)<br/></li><li> Amended the “Obtain From” text on the “The World’s A Stage…” cosmetic insignia to now show the relevant event.  <br/></li><li> Amended the “Obtain From” text on the “Plasma Canister” weapon trinket to show the correct source of the item. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on an all-new DLC, Patches &amp; Betas - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497191242656908469</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Greetings folks!<br/><br/>Hot on the heels of Patch 6.1, we're back in the recording studio to chat about patches, betas and what's next for WARHAMMER III! 👀<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/avVyfLV6YXI?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500568489646358807</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Brothers and Sisters,</div><br/>Many announcements have taken place throughout March. Let’s rewind a bit, and then let’s dive into the upcoming content! We’ll also tackle the polls taken to make the Absolute Difficulty more to your liking.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">MONTH’S REWIND</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">We’ve made a huge announcement ⭐⭐⭐</div><br/>Mid-March, we announced that <i>Space Marine 3</i> had begun development and we’re excited to see your enthusiasm, although we hear those of you who fear for <i>Space Marine 2</i> and its future support.<br/><br/>So let us set the record straight: <b><i>Space Marine 3</i> does not mean the end of <i>Space Marine 2</i>'s development. ​Far from it.</b> No teams are shifting over, no one is abandoning the game, and our plans to bring more awesome content to <i>Space Marine 2</i> remain. We are working on much more content and surprises for the months to come, such as a new class, more operations, melee weapons, and more! Trust us, there are surprises even dataminers haven’t found out about :) <br/><br/>This announcement simply marks the genesis of a new project, <b>years away from release</b>. We’ve made a decision and have just started the process.<br/><br/>Many of you were very excited for this project and this makes us incredibly happy and motivated. Thank you for the unwavering support.<br/><br/><br/>That being said, we still have a lot to offer to the players with <i>Space Marine 2</i>. <br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">We launched the PTS on March 13!</div><br/>The Public Test Server was made available mid-march and you’ve been very dedicated and serious about it!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5ec61352a7be0277f5d94254c2a9496f54626c7b.png"/><br/><br/>We’ve opened a forum on Focus Together to let you voice your opinion on the content featured in the PTS. Even if we might not have enough time on our hands to reply to every thread, we’re collecting your thoughts and making adjustments on our side. So, thank you!<br/><br/>We already started to compile your feedback, and we’ll implement some of them directly on a PTS update that will come early April. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Regarding your feedback on the PTS features, we want to tackle the most important one here:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Prestige Perks are not gamechanger, they are too weak and not worth the effort.</i></li></ul><i>💬 Prestige Perks have not been conceived as game breaking perks meant to allow you to roll on late game content. Another way to say it is that we don’t want the Prestige Perks to be so strong they become “must-haves” for higher difficulties. We really want to emphasize that you don’t need Prestige Perks to beat Absolute difficulty. This would make grinding for them an obligation when we really want them as minor rewards for those who choose to pursue them. The idea behind Prestige Perks is to provide you with more replayability, so you actually have a purpose farming PvE content (other than purging for the Imperium of course!). We don't want players to feel like they need to base their builds upon prestige perks, otherwise it will feel like a forced grind. </i><br/><br/><b>Don’t forget that there’s a unique cosmetic for each class to unlock once you maxed out a class. </b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Prestige Ranks are resetting the class progression to level 1, it will be tedious and too long to get level 25 again.</i></li></ul><i>💬 In recent updates we've increased the amount of xp players are getting in preparation for the prestige system. We've added extermination bonus, quick match bonus, plus new difficulties grant more xp.</i><br/><br/>On top of that we’ll add an XP bonus to make your post-prestige progression faster.<br/><br/>Again, we are trying to strike the balance between having something to keep playing and not forcing players to grind for a hundred hours.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>The Prestige Perks for the Heavy Class are too centered around melee combat.</i></li></ul><i>💬 We are working on changes regarding the Heavy’s Prestige Perks to better integrate them for Heavy’s builds.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Assault should have access to the Inferno Pistol!</i></li></ul>💬<i> Absolutely, that’s why we’ll include the weapon to Assault’s options starting from the next PTS update.</i><br/><br/>Join the players on Discord if you want to chat about this PTS and the future instances!<br/><br/>‎ <br/><div class="bb_h2">⌛ Patch 7.0 - Trygon Update</div><br/>Patch 7.0 will be released in mid-April on all platforms. Let’s dissect the content together!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">New DLC content</div><br/><b>Space Wolves Chapter Pack 🐺</b><br/>​	​	​<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a23bd933bf6de3953f589ab4321607a22b467a93.jpg"/><br/>​<div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/972f2da5efa33dc0c6bacc52fc146fb8348f5f2e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2e1a4ad9d85767cf862d6613ef3b04279b48434d.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/33ff795584ca36d68ab5654ee1965aec161ca86c.jpg"/></div></div></div>Behold the arsenal tied to this Chapter:​<br/>​<div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6c21fdc88eddf684fe0a0c9a65132520135551f3.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d0028a3208d331da60e019192ada80f7cbe64cb4.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2c67ef5d488f9628dd9249d676cf1ceea17be5f7.jpg"/></div></div></div>The Space Wolf Chapter Pack comes with its Great Companies. See below:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b7292fb19932826f77217c6dc365825a02fe1bf1.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Imperial Fists Champion Pack ✊</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/33468439454839669c5da543c35d6b18cb3eca9c.jpg"/>​<div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3030c804842966e9b08b0c01ac26bd696a5d7611.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9def04cb1b7febe37b749d404b8dcd7cdf7c6b1e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7de3b9e48cfcd4b5aafdcffd5cec24766685feaa.jpg"/></div></div></div>​<br/><div class="bb_h2">New Map for PvE 🏜️</div><br/>The new Exfiltration map is coming with Patch 7.0! As the name of the update hints, you will meet with a terrible new boss: the Trygon.<br/><br/>The Trygon is a giant Tyranid creature that can burrow itself in the ground and carve underground tunnels that can be used by smaller Tyranids to bypass the defense lines and coordinate surprise attacks. <br/><br/>“Exfiltration” takes place on Avarax. Your mission is to exfiltrate a Tech-Priest occupying an Adeptus Mechanicus facility on the planet. However, you’ll have to cross a Trygon territory to reach the facility. You’ll have to deal with the relentless assaults of the creature to complete your mission.<br/>​<div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6d795d2fb87b144f79149b65a205ca8e2dabd001.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/60c6580d8d46bec867e7a665facec922ac347de3.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a7be398f91df64a5ccbb2f96716df3ba4a1fcbf.png"/></div></div></div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d8f554761ea9c6fe1a831eeeeeb6d84084322254.png"/><br/><br/>Speaking of PvE, as discussed before in the PTS section, more features will be tweaked. Prestige Ranks will become unlockable, and weapon class restrictions will be adjusted, allowing classes to access more weapons. Additionally, PvE matchmaking will be improved, reducing the chances of joining a team with the same class.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Regarding PvP ⚔️</div><br/><b>Patch 7.0 will bring Private Lobbies to PvP!</b> Also, we made matchmaking improvements for better team balancing.<br/><br/>Private Lobbies will give you the opportunity to customise your PvP experience, with many adjustable options! You’ll be able to:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> tag with up to 11 other players (6v6 lobbies)<br/></li><li> toggle friendly fire<br/></li><li> change the class limit restriction<br/></li><li> change the score/time limit<br/></li><li> modify the damage multipliers of the weapons<br/></li><li> … and more!</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General additions ➕</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Weapons Perks Rework (details here)<br/></li><li> New Colors available in the Armouring Hall: Volupus Pink and Thousand Sons Blue</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/feb63254040ed3438e8c9d07ed3ceb07bca22e48.jpg"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cloth coloring for Bulwark and hoods (every class).<br/></li><li> Option to color hands separately from arms<br/></li><li> Also, the Inferno Pistol will now be available to Assault, Vanguard, Sniper and Heavy Class players, both in PvP and PvE!</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8a38484141c5c8c7e904c5430a183c351e551b3e.png"/><br/>​	​	​	​<br/><div class="bb_h2">Cannot wait until the release in April? Try it on the PTS ⚙️</div><br/>You can try patch 7.0’s WIP content early if you’re playing on Steam! Only thing you need to do is to install the Public Test Server. Here’s a quick tutorial on how to do it. We promise it’s easy!<br/><br/>You can already read the changelog of Patch 7.0 here.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">🆙 March Community Event</div><br/>From March 24 to 30th, XP rewards for both Operations and Eternal war are increased by 25%.<br/>So head back to the battlefield, it’s time to put in the work.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/94d84317678899aa9c34c28ef5ebcd81d8e82497.png"/><br/>You won’t need PROS for this Event.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">💡 Ideas on Focus Together</div><br/>We see your ideas and are doing our best to give them a status and leave comments when we can. However, they remain extremely numerous so please be patient, and remember that we will mainly tackle ideas that have been upvoted with the most G2G points.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">🔖 Results of the Absolute Difficulty polls</div><br/>First of all, we want to kindly thank you for your input! We’re working hard to improve the game and make it to the players’ liking. The Absolute Difficulty, as expressed in the previous Community Update, was tough to balance, so we’re grateful for your inputs. <br/><br/><b>Let’s see the results!</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You’ve voted for more enemies on Absolute Difficulty. With a total of 74.64% votes for and 25.36% against.<br/><br/></li><li> You’ve voted against augmenting the Ammo refills limitations. With a total of 24.75%  votes for and 75.25% against.<br/><br/></li><li> You’ve voted for more enemy aggressiveness. With a total of 70.47% votes for and 29.53% against.<br/><br/></li><li> You’ve voted against increasing enemy health and damage. With a total of 15.84%  votes for and 84.15% against.</li></ul>Your feedback on both the Absolute Difficulty poll and PTS content is well taken. We are planning to make some careful changes in Patch 8.0.<br/><br/>That’s it for this month! As always, we want to thank you for your dedication and your passion! Seeing your feedback and comments on the game really drives us to deliver more and more content. Space Marine 2 wouldn’t be the game it is now without you, and we’re far from finished with this title! <br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Emperor Protects!</div><br/><i>The Saber &amp; Focus teams</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 15:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
