<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Only in Death Does Duty End</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/6896791183179046870</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/894cc33c71710e8e624f512ff156e24b11ae90a2.jpg"/><br/><br/>The release of Unlocked and Loaded brought a new face to the Mourningstar. Commissar Darinda Dukane has assumed command of the Moebian 53rd regiment - the famed Steelheads. These stalwart troops have been deployed to Tertium at the behest of the Planetary Governor, Lord Margrave, who is disturbed by the perceived lack of progress made by the Inquisition.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">But what is a Commissar of the Astra Militarum?</div>The Commissars of the Officio Prefectus are fearsome, iron-fisted authoritarians who keep the wheels of the Astra Militarum in motion. To the masses of Humanity, most of whom recognise the black greatcoat, peaked cap and polished boots of a Commissar from hab-block propaganda frescoes or grainy recruitment vids, these inflexible men and women are Imperial authority made manifest. Their amorphous remit is to ensure that all do their duty in the Emperor’s name, and the high rank and wide-ranging powers of these Departmento Munitorum agents give them leeway to enforce discipline at all levels. Should discipline and morale falter, should orders fail to be obeyed in anything less than exemplary and immediate fashion, it is these ruthless men and women in black who take whatever steps necessary to restore order –<br/>no matter the cost.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">A Commanding Presence</div>Commissars rarely assume direct command of a regiment and the circumstances by which Commissar Dukane came to head up the 53rd remain shrouded in mystery - or are at least snarled up in the processes of the Imperium’s infamous bureaucracy. However, it is plain that she enjoys the full confidence of the sectors lord militant, and has swiftly moved to assume immediate control of the Atoman warzone, masterminding aggressive deployments by the 53rd and rallying the winnowed survivors of the Moebian 21st - until now, the only official Astra Militarum presence in Tertium.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Uneasy Allies</div>With initial drop zones secured, Dukane has taken station on the Mourningstar and even now casts a suspicious eye over Grendyl’s warband, whose motives and masters she clearly does not trust. Nonetheless, she is too practical not to recognise the necessity of allies and has assigned the finest drill sergeants of the 53rd to tutor the rejects in proper weapons drill. Expendable allies they might be, but every heretic the members of the warband eliminates is one less heretic to stand in her path.<br/><br/>But not everything is going Dukane’s way. Tertium’s insidious cult refuses to let this upstart newcomer foil their long-held plans. Even as the 53rd secures new ground the heretics prepare to strike a humbling blow, presenting Sergeant-Major Morrow with an opportunity to prove the warband’s worth…<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 11:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 1.2.1.17 is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4687775476024437132</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The Omnissiah blessed us with the <b>Patch 1.2.1.17</b>! Our Tech-Priests are humbly presenting nearly one hundred fixes, changes, and improvements that are ready to explore.<br/><br/><i>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</i><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">System and stability</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved performance for the console platforms;<br/></li><li>[Xbox] On a 1+ hour play session, some users encountered various progress-blocking bugs: inability to save the game, hanging loading screens, and critical errors, referencing the fog of war. All these problems were fixed;</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">Narrative</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A female worker on Footfall spoke about herself using incorrect gender — fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the lines of warp ghosts, so they would act in character;<br/></li><li> Minor dialogue fixes;<br/></li><li> You will now have the correct reactivity to your choice during the prologue when meeting with the Death Cult;<br/></li><li> In Hunting Grounds quest, Ulfar's line was presented as if said by Calligos Winterscale — fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the logic in dialogue with Vizsier of the Bloodspun Web, if Kibellah was brought to Freight Line;<br/></li><li> Dreams and Stories quest will be now marked as failed if not completed until the end of Act II;<br/></li><li> During Kibellah's questline, the Journal lacked a reminder of a certain meeting on <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Dargonus</span></span> — fixed;<br/></li><li> Added new dialogue options during the first encounter with the Death Cult;<br/></li><li> Fixed dialogue interruption with Yrliet in the Rogue Trader's chamber;<br/></li><li> Improved some wording in dialogues;<br/></li><li> In some cases, when playing in co-op, Kibellah had missing text in some pop-up dialog lines — fixed;<br/></li><li> The text did not correspond to the success of a Medicine check on a sick person on the Freight Line location — fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed the difficulty of the Lore (Warp) check in A Card Inverted quest, now it is easier to pass it;<br/></li><li> The dialogue in Voidship Shrine occurring after the battle has been made more structured and clearer to understand;<br/></li><li> Vladaym Tocara could mention Kibellah in dialogue, although she was not yet taken into the team — fixed;<br/></li><li> If the player already has a completed romance, it will be impossible to start a romance with Kibellah;<br/></li><li> The player couldn't talk to the administratum clerk in Jae’s personal quest — fixed;<br/></li><li> Now Kibellah will react to the happening events more frequently;<br/></li><li> In Zacchary Weisz's quest about his memories, there was an option to leave the Chapel, thereby blocking further progression of the quest — fixed;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Mechanics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Steel of the Forge talent now correctly protects from the Prone buff;<br/></li><li> The Crossfire ability didn't work correctly for the hostile Genestealers — fixed;<br/></li><li> Praying in Voidship Shrine will now grant buffs to the characters;<br/></li><li> During the battle in the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Crypt Main Hall location</span></span>, the player couldn't place characters in certain tiles of the location – fixed;<br/></li><li> The Bladedancer used to end the Acrobatic Artistry ability in the next tile from the original one if their first movement during the turn was the Death Waltz jump — fixed;<br/></li><li> The Battle Trance ability now correctly removes Stunned effects;<br/></li><li> In the battle in the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Crypt Main Hall location</span></span>, <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Genestealers</span></span> ran out of covers during the preparatory phase — fixed;<br/></li><li> Enemy's extra turn could interrupt the Bladedancer's Death Waltz Heroic Act — fixed;<br/></li><li> Webber's Immobilised effect is now correctly taken into account when interacting with abilities and items;<br/></li><li> Fixed the bug with the Bladedancer allowing jumping over full covers. Now the jump requires the character to see the place where they jump;<br/></li><li> The Bladedancer is no longer able to jump on covers using the Death Waltz Heroic Act in the fight with Aurora in Star Port;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Pair Holster now works as intended, and provides one attack with a pistol that costs 0 AP;<br/></li><li> Ritual Knife no longer enables crits for abilities that use a weapon in the other hand;<br/></li><li> Unquenchable Fury's description has been corrected to match its actual behaviour;<br/></li><li> Heavy Emergency Cutter now correctly triggers only once per melee burst attack (not per each hit);<br/></li><li> Smiter now correctly ignores armour and deflection;<br/></li><li> Missionary Oath now correctly becomes unavailable when using targeted abilities;<br/></li><li> Metal Claw Gloves now modify armour directly, instead of increasing armour penetration of attackers;<br/></li><li> Fixed the incorrect name of the Death Cult armour;<br/></li><li> The loot gained after the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Enforcer Officer's</span></span> death in <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Voidship Shrine</span></span> has been changed;<br/></li><li> Demolition Instructions had incorrect calculation in the description — fixed;<br/></li><li> Partner in Death now deals an attack of opportunity if an ally uses a ranged attack;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Locations</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the navigation path for the characters on the location of Jae's personal quest;<br/></li><li> Some NPCs on the Voidship Bridge were standing too close to each other — fixed;<br/></li><li> A marker for <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Nomos</span></span> has been added to the Voidship Bridge map;<br/></li><li> Some containers at the Gutted Voidship were unlootable — fixed;<br/></li><li> In the Death Has Whispered Your Name quest, officers and aristocrats were standing in the heretical palace decoration texture if the player had the heretical Conviction — fixed;</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">Visual </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enhanced the visuals of several NPCs, improving their outfits and making them more suitable for their roles;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug on Eurac V which caused Cassia's animation to stutter, when she rises from her knees;<br/>Improved the crowd’s animations;<br/></li><li> The Acid in Haemonculus's Laboratory now looks better;<br/></li><li> Added the cutscene of the Rogue Trader sitting on the throne after a boss fight;<br/></li><li> Added character animations to the dialogues from the Void Shadows DLC;<br/></li><li> Improved the environment textures in the Temple of the Bloodspun Web location;<br/></li><li> Improved animations of characters and crowds in the Freight Line location;<br/></li><li> Enemies in the Freight Line location have become more diverse in appearance;<br/></li><li> One of the death cultists was standing inside the NPC on the bridge — fixed;<br/></li><li> Improved crowds and character animations in the Freight Line location;<br/></li><li> Two servitors were standing inside each other on the bridge — fixed;<br/></li><li> The Rogue Trader model could disappear during the romance quest with Yrliet — fixed;<br/></li><li> When loading a game in co-op, the characters' capes were abnormally stretched — fixed;<br/></li><li> Added a cutscene demonstrating how the Freight Line location changes after the player's decisions;<br/></li><li> Kibellah's face was slightly fixed;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">User Interface</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> When playing on a console or with a controller, each portrait in the character generator has its own appearance settings, such as hairstyle, tattoos, etc. While progressing through character creation, these settings would revert to default when entering the corresponding UI section. Now, these settings will remain consistent with the portrait until you change them;<br/></li><li> If a character is immobilised, they will no longer have Movement Points;<br/></li><li> When playing on a console or with a controller, entering the DLC/mods tab during a cutscene could lead to an error — fixed;<br/></li><li> The Enfeeble ability description had the incorrectly calculated value for damage bonus — fixed. This was only a text mismatch actual mechanics were working correctly;<br/></li><li> Added missing formula in Shield of the Emperor ability description;<br/></li><li> Added missing formula in Syphon Life (Desperate and Heroic Acts) ability description;<br/></li><li> Fixed some features/talents not getting new icons;<br/></li><li> Fixed some features/talents not using the formula calculator;<br/></li><li> If the character wears an item that cannot be taken off and the slot in the inventory is locked, you may double-click on the item you want to wear to place it in another available slot;<br/></li><li> On consoles, an empty dialog window could block the view — fixed;<br/></li><li> Changed the question-mark rumour icons on the global map;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Audio</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The sound of shots was absent in the cutscene of the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Genestealers ambush</span></span> — fixed;<br/></li><li> The Valiant Commissar's Skull now has his very own voiceover line;<br/></li><li> Added sounds to some effects in the Freight Line location;<br/></li><li> Added the sound of the coming train in the cutscene in the Freight Line location;<br/></li><li> Lacerax on the bridge was snoring too loud, we had to make it quieter, as it disturbed the whole crew;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Space</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added several new names to planets that had duplicated names;<br/></li><li> The Barrage-Type Flak Shot ability obtained from the Flak Ammo Arsenal could fail to work in space battles — fixed;<br/></li><li> When playing on a console or with a controller, the player could lose the ability to move the voidship in space battles — fixed;</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">Co-op</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several issues that could cause desyncs when playing in co-op;<br/></li><li> It was not possible to continue the game in some situations in co-op because the game required the DLC, although it was disabled in this save — fixed;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Localization</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> When switching the language, not all options were translated into the selected language without restarting the game — fixed;<br/></li><li> The word "user's" has been removed from several formulas related to consumable items in Russian;<br/></li><li> Fixed the attributes translation while inspecting the voidship;<br/></li><li> Fixed a typo in the Russian description of Fighters Deck (Fury Interceptors);<br/></li><li> Some Spanish dialogues were missing translations, text was displayed in English — fixed;<br/></li><li> Some abilities and phenomena present in space battles were not translated into Chinese, Spanish, and Japanese — fixed;</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Kibellah was absent during the Rykad Minoris triumph — we kindly asked her to be there;<br/></li><li> Barks said by the warp ghost disappeared too fast so it was impossible to read them — fixed;<br/></li><li> During the cutscene <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>of the beginning of the battle with ghosts in Astropathic Chapel</span></span> the camera flipped back to the player's party — fixed;<br/></li><li> We asked Yrliet to step away from Kibellah on the bridge — these two didn't get along very well;<br/></li><li> The Limited Outfit DLC was removed from the list of DLCs available for purchase;<br/></li><li> [Xbox] On Xbox you could delete Voidfarer's pack, Deluxe pack, and Limited Outfit via DLC manager window, which could lead to strange game states. The delete option now is no longer available;</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 08:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.7</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4656249643711098807</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/24d54f0940e0101af001412ce67b77000e476e52.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings,<br/><br/>Today we're releasing Hotfix 5.2.7, which includes several bug fixes and adjustments to enhance your gameplay experience.<br/><br/>Check out the full details below:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A cleanup procedure has been implemented to automatically remove crash dump files older than one month from users' machines, helping manage disk space without affecting recent diagnostic data; this process is triggered only when a crash occurs.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Kroxigor Ancients and Red Crested Skink Chief characters had varying combat skills based on the Lizardmen Legendary Lord selected. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where, when the Blue Scribes left an army, the effect granting a random Cataclysm Spell was not removed from the army. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where stealing Magic Items would block the item drop chance for reinforcements. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the code was incorrectly checking for a lord's rebellion after data removal had begun. The rebellion check is now performed earlier, allowing the rest of the code to be skipped if a rebellion occurs. <br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Resolved an issue where technologies requiring active Gifts of Chaos were not consistently providing bonuses for Warriors of Chaos factions, particularly affecting techs like 'Mystical Banner' and 'Temple of Tzeentch' when playing as Vilitch. Bonuses should now correctly apply once the relevant Gifts are active.</span><br/><i>Unfortunately this fix has not made it in to the final release of hotfix 5.2.7, but will be included in our next release. Apologies for the confusion!</i></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where multiple instances of the same Path to Glory event would trigger upon unlocking one. <br/></li><li> Fixed a missing icon when recruiting an Exalted Hero of Tzeentch. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Daemonic Progression panel would not open when accessed through the Character Details panel. <br/></li><li> The Dwarf Ancestor Rune no longer incorrectly states that it grants permanent death immunity to all nearby units. (This was purely a UI issue.) <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Chaos Dwarfs' settlement type icon on the city label would not update after the settlement type was changed. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where several tooltips for contact effects in the Flesh Laboratory were missing text. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where characters with long starting trait names, such as 'Virtue of the Impetuous Knight,' could clip outside the recruitment box. <br/></li><li> Fixed several Tomb King building icons that were using the wrong colour. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where misleading tooltips would pop up after purchasing an upgrade in the Rewards of Dread panel. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Herald of Tzeentch (Metal) was incorrectly treated as a Slaanesh-aligned character when determining the likelihood of army abilities for Daemons of Chaos. <br/></li><li> Fixed the porthole camera angle for the Shadewraith Gunners (Deck Gunners) Regiment of Renown. <br/></li><li> The Blue Scribes can now access the Lore of the Hag in Custom Battle. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the abilities 'Rot or Die,' 'Necrotic Phylactery,' and 'Isha's Rain' did not display their names when hovered over in certain contexts. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where several Legendary Lords were using incorrect unit cards in quest battles.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Emperor Karl Franz's name was duplicated on his unit card in battles fought during a campaign.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a multiplayer campaign desync issue that occurred when a player without ownership of a building in the Nurgle chain upgraded a building to complete the cycle and then recruited all available Forsaken of Nurgle units. </li></ul><hr/><br/><br/>Thank you once again for your feedback and bug reports. If you encounter any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.2.7, please make sure to report them in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - Hotfix 3.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696782040358852369</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines!</div><br/>We just pushed a small hotfix that brings various fixes. Thank you for your support!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Patch Notes</b></div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several crashes<br/></li><li> Fixed heavy stutters on some CPUs<br/></li><li> Fixed launch issue on Linux and Steam Deck<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with dynamic resolution and ultrawide screens<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with upscalers using wrong resolution parameters</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Shadows DLC Full Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703537439805736932</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>It's time to immerse yourself in the ominous and atmospheric music from Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader DLC – Void Shadows! Save the full soundtrack to your playlist, and may the light of the God-Emperor protect you.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/i_gr8Tu5myc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
