<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.0.57 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/786538109548364959</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/>Our tech-priests prepared another small update to apply a few fixes to your voidship.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hunter's Withdraw talent no longer provides infinite dodges against all types of attacks;<br/></li><li> The game could freeze while travelling on the global map - fixed;<br/></li><li> On the first part of the Critical Task quest and the activation point for the fuel lever did not appear - fixed;<br/></li><li>The Warp effect could trigger even if the party was not in battle - fixed;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Update - New playable monster: Rat Ogre! Patch 6.2.0</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/509566731895702858</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div>This update brings a new dangerous toy for the Pactsworn side in Versus: A new playable monster, the Rat Ogre!<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/2dc0740c-942f-4cda-bbc0-b6b44aa8e773/Rat_Ogre_169.png?format=1000w"/><br/>When the time comes for a Monster to spawn in a Versus match, Pactsworn players can choose between the Bile Troll and the Rat Ogre. While both are monsters, their way of assaulting the Hero team is very different, and so it is up to the players to choose the right tool for the job (or just the most fun!)<br/><br/>The Rat Ogre’s specialty is scrambling the Hero team through a frenzied assault. It excels at separating the Heroes and taking advantage of the chaos to chase after stragglers, pummeling away with wild, ferocious attacks that don’t give the defender room to breathe.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How to play the Rat Ogre</div>Similar to the Bile Troll and the Heroes, you’ve got light attacks and heavy attacks. Tapping your attack button (Default Keybind: Left Mouse Click) results in a series of fast but powerful attacks. Holding down the attack button results in a Heavy Attack, a downward slam with both fists that deals massive damage but is tricky to pull off!<br/><br/>Holding the secondary attack button (Default Keybind: Right Mouse Click) allows the Rat Ogre to prepare to Leap! Charge the leap for a short while and then aim. Once charged, you can release the button to launch yourself through the air, knocking any Heroes you land upon away and sending them flying all over. Perfect for making a dramatic entrance and throwing those pesky Heroes into disarray.<br/><br/><i>You can also find this information in the in-game Handbook!</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s next?</div>We’re super excited about the release of Versus, it was a massive milestone for a project that we love and we’re glad that it’s been overall a fun time and well-received by the community!<br/><br/>But what’s next for Versus? Beyond the Rat Ogre, we’re looking to add more little things and tinker a bit more in the coming year! There’s a lot of very valid feedback that you guys have given that we want to address and we hope to be able to do that bit by bit in 2025. There are also small additions planned, such as Custom Settings to player-hosted games.<br/><br/>Other than Versus, we’ll continue working on the rest of the Verminous Dreams campaign maps (hope you’ve been having fun with The Forsaken Temple!), as well as a previously mentioned Weapon Pack which is still in the pipeline. Beyond that, well, we can’t reveal everything, can we?<br/><br/>Barring hotfixes, this will be the last Vermintide 2 update of the year, and what a blast it has been! <br/><br/><i>We hope you enjoy the Holidays and the Gifts of the Wolf Father, and we hope you’ve had as much fun with this game this year as we have! See you next year, drengbarazi. <br/>- The Vermintide 2 Team.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch 6.2.0 patch notes</div>As a heads up, due to a sudden issue with our patch building process, this update will be around a 25 gb download on PC. We apologize once again for the inconvenience, we thought we had seen the last of it. We’ll continue investigating to hopefully avoid more patches like these in the future.<br/><br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Versus) Enabled the Rat Ogre as a Monster option for Pactsworn.												<br/> </li><li>	Hero Poses should no longer be counted as inventory items when calculating inventory space and should allow players that have reached the inventory cap due to poses to once again open chests.												</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed a crash when clicking on future rewards on Gifts of the Wolf Father. Re-enabled the ability to see what's coming next in the Gifts of the Wolf Father calendar.												<br/> </li><li>	The Forsaken Temple fixes:												<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed enemies getting stuck on the wrong side of the chasm of the second Grim path.											<br/> </li><li>	Patched up safe spot hole											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked wonky hang ledge by temple chasm											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked trigger for end event door marker to not show after door is opened											<br/> </li><li>	Made sure 2 barrels always spawn around the plaza											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked terrain around drop into drained lake											<br/> </li><li>	Added collision to stuck spot in end event fake elevator											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue with the end event stairs.											<br/> </li><li>	Patched up spot where a waystone piece could be be lost or cheesed											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed crash when two players interact with an elevator in "The Forsaken Temple" at the exact same time.</li></ul></li><li>	Fixed a rare crash when attempting to preview Pactsworn skins before they've loaded.												<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a Chaos Wastes crash when using a Grenade mid-mission.												<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fort Brachsenbrücke - Prevented cannonballs from getting stuck in the elevator</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">An update regarding the data loss issue:</div>Hey all, just checking in again with a progress update and some further information to share.<br/><br/>Our backend developers have a 3-step plan to restore the missing data:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Stage 1: Gather and collate account data from storages we have, and transfer this to another system which will be used for rebuilding missing account data<br/></li><li> Stage 2: Conduct some wizardry in this system to organise the data (e.g. get the latest/highest/correct value for each statistic for each player) and prep it for being merged back in to our backend data<br/></li><li> Stage 3: Update the backend and merge the rebuilt data into existing account data.</li></ul>Stage 1 is in full swing and data is currently being downloaded and transferred to our system required to rebuild the missing data. This is a tremendous amount of account data, and will take some time to complete. We’re exploring whether we can scale this process up and complete it any faster, but for now an approximate estimate is that this stage will take a few weeks to complete.<br/><br/>Please bear with us, and we’ll continue to provide updates when we have more to share.<br/><br/>A big thank you for your continued patience during this process.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 10:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/641297020996289632</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines,</div><br/>We deployed a hotfix on <i>Space Marine 2</i> that fixes multiple issues that appeared with the 5.0 update. <br/><br/>You'll find the complete patch notes down below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><b>General Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug that caused the Perfect Parry window for <i>Fencing</i> melee weapons to be shorter than intended. We reverted the values to pre-patch levels.<br/></li><li> Fixed a server-related issue that would cause a loss of control on PC.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where one of the Chainsword Artificer version was dealing more damage than intended.<br/></li><li> Fixed: “Iron Hands Steel” emblem colour was red instead of black.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that caused Keyboard mappings to be reset after installing the new patch.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to change controls for the Ability button (you might have to change controls one more time).<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Jump Pack ability would spend more than 1 charge in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug in the Campaign mission “Skyfire” (part 2) where a script would not start properly in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Modified: The new mechanic for Blocking weapons “Adrenaline Surge” now restores 2 armour segments instead of 1 when discharged.<br/></li><li> Locked access to the Research Center until the Adeptus Mechanicus gives its blessings.<br/></li><li> Restored progression for modded version of the game (warning popup will still appear and say otherwise, but progression should be saved nonetheless).<br/></li><li> Several crash fixes.</li></ul><br/>Thanks for your continuous support. Shall you encounter issues with this new update, let us know on Focus Together or on our Discord Server.<br/><br/>The Emperor Protects.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511749</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3d46c256ba2490462ec65b341d5a7d4b64aa3d03.png"/><br/><br/>Hey everyone,<br/><br/>We’ve adjusted our hotfixing plans slightly to prioritise the splash attack issues that have been present since the release of Update 6.0. We have just rolled out Hotfix 6.0.1, which addresses these issues:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reverted various splash attack max target counts to match at least the minimum number of splash zones units have in metadata.<br/><br/><i>Dev note: In 6.0.0 we made a change to the maximum number of targets a splash attack can hit based on a weapon strength ratio, this change was originally intended to apply to single entity units only and inadvertently was applied to monstrous infantry, cavalry and infantry units. This caused a series of issues with how our splash attacks are calculated, we have reverted the changes to these units while maintaining the single entity splash attack changes. After this hotfix you will see monstrous infantry, cavalry and infantry return to their pre-patch 6.0.0 state. There is a chance this may still affect some units, so please do keep reporting any issues you come across so we can investigate further.</i><br/><br/></li><li> Added missing text strings from a small number of tooltips.<br/><br/><i>Dev note:  Whilst we're aware of other issues present in the game at the moment, currently set to be addressed in a further Hotfix releasing later this week, we had the opportunity to include this one as part of today’s fix, and isn't representative of our current prioritisation of certain issues.</i></li></ul><br/>By implementing these necessary changes today, it has also rolled out some additional battle balancing adjustments that we’ve been working on. A full list of these changes will follow later today as an addition to our 6.0 Battle Balance Details thread, so please check back for the full details!<br/><br/>Although today's hotfix does not include any of the items originally disclosed in our known issues post, please rest assured that we will be back later this week with an additional hotfix to address those and more.<br/><br/>As always, thank you for your ongoing feedback and for your patience while we investigate and address these issues. If you encounter any new problems after updating to version 6.0.1, please let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Who is the 100th Legendary Lord?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511318</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Four contenders, each staking their claim for the coveted title of 100th Legendary Lord™.<br/> <br/>Golgfag, Skulltaker, Gorbad, Arbaal. Who will come out on top? There's only one way to find out...<br/> <br/>FIIIIIGHT! ⚔️<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8EqoO8e7PJE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 15:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
