<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Sale is live! Get the game and its additional content with up to 50% off!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732991</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
It's Summer Sale time! <br/><br/>Whether you are an experienced Lord Captain that wishes to expand their trade protectorate with new worlds and engage in new adventures in the Koronus Expanse, or you are only yet to receive your own Warrant of Trade and inherit the most sacred title of a Rogue Trader of von Valancius Dynasty, this is a good time to consider one or more of the following options!<br/><br/>1. Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration:<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>2. Gain access to two major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis, and expand your campaign with two new companions, exciting new storylines and new interesting mechanics, receiving over 30 hours of content at an additional discount:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/>3. For Rogue Traders whose ambition is beyond measure! Get the base game, Season Pass 1, Digital Artbook, Digital OST, Wallpaper Pack and a selection of in-game items for the ultimate experience:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/36542/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Edition/<br/>4. More is on the horizon for Rogue Trader! Get Season Pass 2 to instantly gain access to new character customization options, and a future access to two more upcoming expansions, both of which offer 15 hours of gameplay: In DLC III - The Infinite Museion, you will delve into a secret vault curated by Trazyn the Infinite himself, and in DLC IV - Processional of the Damned, you will venture into the Processional — a massive, otherworldly graveyard of ships lost to the void:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3650060/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass_2/<br/>5. Get two massive CRPGs by Owlcat Games - Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous at once, and explore both of these amazing worlds in huge, branched stories that last for hundreds of hours:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/41660/Owlcat_Games_CRPG_Bundle/<br/><br/>These are just some examples of the available content for the game - check its page to find out about more options!<br/><br/>Your crew awaits your command, Lord Captain!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/594570/view/499451286721135136</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/28300675/b086637fdc2a1474628b168d24ea29c547d008a4.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>The Steam Summer Sale is so hot right now! From today until 10th of July, grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 10th July @ 10AM PDT/6PM BST</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/364360/view/517465685228519850</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/8548992/b086637fdc2a1474628b168d24ea29c547d008a4.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>The Steam Summer Sale is so hot right now! From today until 10th of July, grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 10th July @ 10AM PDT/6PM BST</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Summer Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497199486905352605</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b086637fdc2a1474628b168d24ea29c547d008a4.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>The Steam Summer Sale is so hot right now! From today until 10th of July, grab up to 75% off a selection of Total War titles.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/885970/Total_War_ROME_REMASTERED/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 10th July @ 10AM PDT/6PM BST</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROADMAP, Soundtrack, Supporters Pack, New Patch + More!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515213885413785778</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">The speedin' and freekin' kontinues 💥🏁</div><p class="bb_paragraph">It's been just over one month since Speed Freeks launched, and despite some turbulence out of the starting gate, the game is now the best it's ever been - and we're still making it better.  </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just released another update with some fixes and additions. Full patch notes can be found further down this page.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To celebrate one month of post launch krumpin' as well as the Steam Summer Sale, we're giving everyone <b>double</b> <b>Scrap</b> until the end of the sale. Just play normally ingame and you'll see a scrap bonus show up at the end of a match.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>ROADMAP</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">In addition to this, we're dropping you some quick news about the upcoming roadmap, though we know it's pretty light on details right now. We'll be disclosing more info in the coming weeks, but for now you can see the kind of upcoming content bein' smashed together by da boyz in da mek shop:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cc9f14c7149ee413819af37d80f666a7ebc3310b.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW VEHICLES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">This next one is pretty exciting, because we know this vehicle will be a lot of fun to play with</p><hr/><div class="bb_h3">Comment below saying which vehicle you think is coming next, and <b>those that guessed right will get a free <u>Soundtrack</u> DLC</b>!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">(must comment with your guess before 12:00 am PST on July 1st)</p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>SOUNDTRAKK </b>🎵</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wotz dat? Ya heard us right, Speed Freeks is getting a <b>soundtrack </b>DLC drop, coming next week!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This soundtrack has all the songs from the trailers, the ingame menu theme, and a new piece of music that combines a bunch of them together - along with some exclusive unheard parts in it 🔥</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've seen plenty of people comment that they want the soundtrack.  Well, it's finally here... <b>and it zoggin' BANGS</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>SHARE-ABLE RACES</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Right now in Free Roam mode, players can create custom races. This is cool, but we want people to be able to easily save and share their races with each other so they can spread da Speedwaaagh!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Our goal is Steam Workshop support for this, plus more intuitive tools for creating the races.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We can't wait to see what kind of insane courses players create, then watch others speed and stunt all over the place trying to get the best time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>NEW MAPS</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've got a really cool Kill Konvoy map in the werks that has parts that feel a lot different from the current batch, but also has familiar gameplay core to the mode. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Along with that there's a Deff Rally version of Da Gorge that will have a different lighting/weather setup.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Speaking of weather, we'll be adding stormy versions of some Kill Konvoy maps as well in the future.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>GAME MUTATORS</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We're bringing back Dakka Frenzy, Bomb Rush and Random Vehicle, plus some new mutators that make the modes feel fresh.  Expect something race-y</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/995ffe8e717de04ab7a9f557c54780e617c1da15.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>SUPPORTERS PACK</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">That little git and his squig on a pole are back, along with some snazzy rims and tracks for your favourite vehicles. We really appreciate anyone who grabs this pack to show their support of the game, y'all are stellar gits</p><div class="bb_h3">https://store.steampowered.com/app/3750860/Warhammer_40000_Speed_Freeks__Supporters_Pack/</div><div class="bb_h3"><b>TRADING CARDS, BADGES, BACKGROUNDS &amp; EMOTICONS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Some snazzy gubbinz now available for those kollectorz out there!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0648e391c0f64cd7e95092e949fd630712eae16.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Can see the points shop stuff here: https://store.steampowered.com/points/shop/app/2078450</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>BUNDLES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Wired and <b>Slitherine (Gladius)</b> have teamed up for a Warhammer 40k bundle that scratches your itch for both kunnin' strategy and brutal action. If one of the gits you know doesn't have either game, this is the time to jump on it!</p><div class="bb_h3">https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/55421/Warhammer_40000_Speed_and_Strategy_Bundle/</div><p class="bb_paragraph">You'z might have seen this one already, but Speed Freeks is bundled with developer Caged Element's previous game GRIP, too. The ultimate combat racing bundle 💪</p><div class="bb_h3">https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/54112/Combat_Racing_Bundle/</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>PATCH NOTES</b></div><div class="bb_h3">MISC</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>TUTORIAL MODE</b>There is now a tutorial mode entry in the PLAY GAME screen that eases players into each game mode, focusing on the tips showing in sequence for general knowledge and learning objectives. Every time a tutorial match is played, the same tips will show in sequence, guiding the player.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Double Scrap </b>event is now on until July 10th</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added explainer to Free Roam mode for those who hadn't seen it yet</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Properly localized all text in the game for supported languages</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved performance on Kill Konvoy - Da Gorge</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved jump pad placement/functionality, plus added a few more in Da Gorge</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added Supporters Pack DLC. All items in DLC are framed in yellow in the KUSTOMIZE screen - except for the grot companion. Dat git is obvious 👀</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">VEHICLES</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>KUSTOM BOOSTA-BLASTA</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rivet Kannon damage reduced to 7.5 (from 8.5)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>TRUKK</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Adds back the Trukk's ability to go mach speed while maintaining acceleration. Turbo frogger Trukk is back on da menu boyz!</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Get involved in the community and mob up with other gits!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Our community may be kunnin' n' brutal', but they're also super nice gits.  Jump into one of these places to go full Ork:</p><div class="bb_h3">Discord</div><div class="bb_h3">r/SpeedFreeks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4632f08ea6bbd65d79448452c0b0d37c241b0742.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2078450/" width="850"></iframe>
</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
