<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.7</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4656249643711098807</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/24d54f0940e0101af001412ce67b77000e476e52.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings,<br/><br/>Today we're releasing Hotfix 5.2.7, which includes several bug fixes and adjustments to enhance your gameplay experience.<br/><br/>Check out the full details below:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A cleanup procedure has been implemented to automatically remove crash dump files older than one month from users' machines, helping manage disk space without affecting recent diagnostic data; this process is triggered only when a crash occurs.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Kroxigor Ancients and Red Crested Skink Chief characters had varying combat skills based on the Lizardmen Legendary Lord selected. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where, when the Blue Scribes left an army, the effect granting a random Cataclysm Spell was not removed from the army. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where stealing Magic Items would block the item drop chance for reinforcements. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the code was incorrectly checking for a lord's rebellion after data removal had begun. The rebellion check is now performed earlier, allowing the rest of the code to be skipped if a rebellion occurs. <br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Resolved an issue where technologies requiring active Gifts of Chaos were not consistently providing bonuses for Warriors of Chaos factions, particularly affecting techs like 'Mystical Banner' and 'Temple of Tzeentch' when playing as Vilitch. Bonuses should now correctly apply once the relevant Gifts are active.</span><br/><i>Unfortunately this fix has not made it in to the final release of hotfix 5.2.7, but will be included in our next release. Apologies for the confusion!</i></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where multiple instances of the same Path to Glory event would trigger upon unlocking one. <br/></li><li> Fixed a missing icon when recruiting an Exalted Hero of Tzeentch. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Daemonic Progression panel would not open when accessed through the Character Details panel. <br/></li><li> The Dwarf Ancestor Rune no longer incorrectly states that it grants permanent death immunity to all nearby units. (This was purely a UI issue.) <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Chaos Dwarfs' settlement type icon on the city label would not update after the settlement type was changed. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where several tooltips for contact effects in the Flesh Laboratory were missing text. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where characters with long starting trait names, such as 'Virtue of the Impetuous Knight,' could clip outside the recruitment box. <br/></li><li> Fixed several Tomb King building icons that were using the wrong colour. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where misleading tooltips would pop up after purchasing an upgrade in the Rewards of Dread panel. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Herald of Tzeentch (Metal) was incorrectly treated as a Slaanesh-aligned character when determining the likelihood of army abilities for Daemons of Chaos. <br/></li><li> Fixed the porthole camera angle for the Shadewraith Gunners (Deck Gunners) Regiment of Renown. <br/></li><li> The Blue Scribes can now access the Lore of the Hag in Custom Battle. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the abilities 'Rot or Die,' 'Necrotic Phylactery,' and 'Isha's Rain' did not display their names when hovered over in certain contexts. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where several Legendary Lords were using incorrect unit cards in quest battles.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Emperor Karl Franz's name was duplicated on his unit card in battles fought during a campaign.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a multiplayer campaign desync issue that occurred when a player without ownership of a building in the Nurgle chain upgraded a building to complete the cycle and then recruited all available Forsaken of Nurgle units. </li></ul><hr/><br/><br/>Thank you once again for your feedback and bug reports. If you encounter any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.2.7, please make sure to report them in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - Hotfix 3.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696782040358852369</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines!</div><br/>We just pushed a small hotfix that brings various fixes. Thank you for your support!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Patch Notes</b></div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several crashes<br/></li><li> Fixed heavy stutters on some CPUs<br/></li><li> Fixed launch issue on Linux and Steam Deck<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with dynamic resolution and ultrawide screens<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with upscalers using wrong resolution parameters</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Shadows DLC Full Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703537439805736932</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>It's time to immerse yourself in the ominous and atmospheric music from Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader DLC – Void Shadows! Save the full soundtrack to your playlist, and may the light of the God-Emperor protect you.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/i_gr8Tu5myc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #50 (1.5.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997843897243443</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/689dcd3eb376d80ca7e8c34c27889316a2f84534.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Welcome to the patch notes for Hotfix #50 (1.5.3). It is now going live on Steam and it will shortly follow on our other platforms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Psyker ‘Kinetic Flayer’ talent incorrectly triggered on non-valid enemies.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Psyker ‘Warp Unbound’ talent did not properly prevent a Perils of the Warp explosion when using Force weapons (e.g. Force staves).</li><li>Fixed an issue where the text in the Sacrifice weapon screen overflowed outside of the UI.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Ceaseless Barrage’ blessing description did not properly display the Damage vs Suppressed Stat.</li><li>Fixed a visual issue on Hadron’s workbench</li><li>Fixed an issue that could cause a client and server crash when a player was stunned without having any weapon equipped.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Discard options could become disabled to input after performing certain actions in the Discard weapons menu</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Empower menu could appear off-screen when using widescreen resolutions</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Edit Loadout Preset menu could appear empty</li><li>Experience will now show correctly on the Masteries screen if a player reached max Mastery on a weapon by using the Sacrifice menu.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when opening the Penances menu in specific situations</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is related to the Penances that got removed in Hotfix #49. (Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) - Patch Notes)<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the name for the Mastery weapon skin for the Pickaxe would appear incorrectly.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Auspex input tooltip during the hacking minigames in the Rolling Steel mission would appear in English also in other languages.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the information in the Sacrifice Weapon screen tooltip displayed an incorrect minimum rarity level.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The correct minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the value for the Mastery Level required to unlock a Mark could fail to be displayed in the Marks Swap screen.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On<ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li>[*[b]]FSR 3.1 Frame Generation does not do anything during excessive fullscreen effects[/b]<ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame Generation excludes the entire screen from generation when there are a lot of fullscreen effects playing that impact all pixels on screen. This will cause frame gen to just copy the previous rendered result which results in the framerate looking like framegen is disabled while frame counters saying that it is running correctly.</li></ul>[/*]<li>Penances Shown As Not Completed<ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares<ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats<ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li>UPDATED: This is now known to not be a visual issue only. Rather, it involves different values being delivered by the backend than expected. This is being investigated.</li></ul></li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 09:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lore Post: Skaven Chronicles part 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4660753243329528757</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/4802c9c37e1bb84c6f1a9f24b89ae1838544cb26.png"/><br/><br/><i>Few things are constant among the Skaven, but their scheming and plotting is one of them. While our Heroes may have foiled Rasknitt, there’s plenty other vermin are eager to hatch their own devious plans. The farsqueaker, a verminous piece of Skryre engineering, allows some of these would-be masterminds to instantly communicate across vast distances with their networks of agents and spies.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Skaven Chronicles: Part 2</div><br/>I am much pleased with your timely report, Skratch, and heartened by the news of your many successes. The minions I placed in your unworthy paws are clearly moderately capable. Use them well, Skratch. Do not think-think you are my only proxy in the Grey Mountains. Just because I plucked you from your runtish litter as a whelp, it will not displease me too greatly to have to devour you should you fail. I will start at the tail end, yes-yes, and work my way up from there.<br/><br/>The situation in Karak Gnol is more chaotic even than that which you left behind. My predecessor (may he lay forever in the boiling stomach juices of the Great Horned Rat) was too stupid to do away with his more competent and ambitious underlings while he still lived. He thought his cronies in Clan Pestilens would shield him, and they did, but more fool-fool them because now he is dead and a dozen rival chieftains scheme to replace him. None yet recognize my rightful claim, so you see the risk I take sending away so many clanrat warriors, even under the leadership of an expendable deputy like you, and why I demand results. <br/><br/>Not in seven months, Skratch, but now. <br/><br/>I had taken to displaying the heads of my would-be assassins before the entrance to my burrow, but I eventually ran out of spikes. There is a lair-wide shortage of them, I am told. So I have begun adding them to the skavenbrew with the rest of the bodies. The slavemasters inform me that the extra meat is gratefully received in the under-warrens, and perhaps this is a blessing in disguise. The skavenslaves could do with some fattening up. The way things are smelling around here, I may soon need the wretches to fight as well as die-die in the mines. <br/><br/>Given the glowing reports of your progress under Helmgart-place, I have decided that you obviously do not need the reinforcements or the extra funds you requested. My warp tokens are not infinite and I have instead spent your overly generous stipend for this moon-cycle on a Rat Ogre bodyguard for my protection. A far wiser allocation of limited resources, I think-think you will agree.<br/>Now stop chasing after low-hanging tails and give me something I can actually show to my enemies! Bring me a head from the so-called ‘Ubersreik Five’ for starters. Their legend is, I am sure, greatly flattered by the gross incompetence of the skaven they have faced so far, but their deaths by my paw will undoubtedly impress the ignorant masses of Karak Gnol. <br/><br/>Oh, and one more thing, Skratch. <br/><br/>This is important, so listen-hear very closely. <br/><br/>The Pestilent Brotherhood may have done more harm to Clan Fester than the Bloodblight or Rasknitt’s vacuous promises, but I need their warriors and their warpstone if I am to become Warlord. They have their own reasons to loathe the Furless Five, so however you choose to be rid of them – make certain-sure that it is suitably dramatic…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 16:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
