<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #71 (1.8.3) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520843384949051382</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4090708bc4130993b2a510a1f6e3ea9c7abdd491.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #71 (1.8.3) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To stay consistent with how Arbites cosmetics have been presented to players, we’ve deployed a fix for an issue introduced with Hotfix #70 where precinct decals were incorrectly appearing on them. With Hotfix #71 the intended decal behavior will be the following:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">All progression gear upper bodies will display the selected precinct number. The upper body of the deluxe edition will remain unchanged. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The cape in the Deluxe edition of the Arbites DLC will not display a precinct number.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Earnable in-game cosmetics that include capes will not show a precinct number on capes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Arbitrator Revelatum Plate with Covert Ops Coat (Lucis) in the Commodore's Vestures will not display the precinct number on the right shoulder anymore - to stay consistent with how the cosmetic was presented to players.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Upgraded to the latest version of FSR (3.1.4).  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Basic Training rewards preview images were displayed in an incorrect size.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where backstory choices were randomized at the start of an operation in the Barber-Chirurgeon instead of using the player saved backstory.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with the ‘Chained Deathblow’ Turtolsky Heavy Sword blessing where the critical chance bonus would not scale correctly on all tiers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Additional fixes for a crash that could occur when Auspex devices started playing sounds the same time as the player wielded a weapon.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the server to crash when players would step in specific locations in several missions.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic &amp; Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fix for the Veteran “Regimental Beret” headgear cosmetic causing part of hairline to be hidden.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some headgear cosmetics would cause the hairline of the characters to break.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Arbites Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lowered requirements for some Arbites Penances:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">'Justice Dispensed' from 3500 to 750</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">'Arbites Gunner' from 3500 to 2000</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">'Castigator's Arrest' from 3500 to 2000</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where sound was not playing correctly when the Nuncio Aquila ability expired.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some enemies were getting deformed when pounced on by the Cyber-Mastiff.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Smoke-emitting VFX are now enabled again for Cyber-Mastiff cosmetics displaying said effects.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Remote Detonation' could trigger Ranged Attack bonuses (e.g. the ‘Puncture’ weapon blessing).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where blood effects were not being applied on the Shock Maul and Suppression Shield head.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Prosecution Blow' didn't apply correctly.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the ‘Pinpointing Target’ blessing would not trigger on the Shotpistol and Riot Shield.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Inspiring Recitation now correctly applies the intended 30% damage reduction, as stated in its description.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed ‘Castigator's Stance’ not replenishing Toughness on activation while standing on fire surfaces.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where players couldn't tag enemies in certain cases while using the double tag setting.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where enemies tagged with ‘Execution Order’ would stay tagged even when not relevant to the mission anymore.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korean added to supported languages at launch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/547864982714322547</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We’re very pleased to announce that Team MoDakBul, who provided post-launch Korean localisation for the first game, will be providing their services once again for Mechanicus II.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Big thanks to both Team MoDakBul and our Korean-speaking players for your support. We’re excited to make Mechanicus II more accessible to even more of you on day one!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.4.0.200 is out</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762736041</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>A patch for Warhammer 40000: Rogue Trader has arrived for PC. We’ve addressed the blocking issue that might occur in Act IV for some players with the Arbites origin.<br/><br/><u>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</u><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After speaking with Proctor Adriana Yeager in Act IV, further plot progress could become blocked for the players with the Adeptus Arbites origin in some cases – fixed. If you experienced this bug, speak to Adriana Yeager and then to Clerk Tertius Quart to advance in the quest.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.4.0.199 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762736018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Update 1.4.0.199 is live! The Heartless now becomes available instantly, multiple commonly reported bugs have been fixed, and inactive weapon sets no longer contribute to the character stats!<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Based on player feedback, the Heartless, new escort ship from Lex Imperialis, will now appear instantly rather than after finishing repairs in Act IV. Its stats will be a bit lower while in Act II, to represent its damaged state;<br/></li><li> It is no longer possible to land on Thassera without Solomorne under certain circumstances;<br/></li><li> Solomorne no longer inserts himself into some dialogues when he’s not in the party;<br/></li><li> Fixed cases of incorrect behavior of Precognition ability that would sometimes prevent the player from ending the turn;<br/></li><li> Fixed severe FPS drop caused by unexpected interaction between Relentless Blaze and Will to Live. Also fixed Relentless Blaze not counting Soul Burn as burning;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs caused by saving during the preparation round;<br/></li><li> Inactive weapon sets no longer provide the weapon bonuses to characters in addition to the active set bonuses.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 8.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500577186633222898</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Hello Space Marines,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The 8.1 Hotfix is now live on every platform. It fixes various crashes and connectivity issues, as well as a bug preventing the Helmet reward for Siege Mode to unlock.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several crashes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several issues causing disconnects</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Siege Mode rewards from wave 25+</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of small fixes to Siege Mode map geometry</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed bug that was causing random enemies to get stronger much faster in infinite waves, causing one shot deaths randomly (Note: enemies are still going to get stronger but it will be not random and more consistent)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug in Siege Mode that occurred when a player would join a game in progress, the game would not apply difficulty modifiers correctly.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug in UI that was causing inability to change colour presets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor localization fixes</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 09:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
