<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>A Day At The Theatre!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520834687966380439</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e0f69bd79ef3e7731191219d071e7361c744c6bd.png"/><br/><br/>Sefoni's new training protocols whisk you off to the Theatres of Mortification. Unleash carnage in the Mortis Trials.<br/><br/><b>To make progress in the event, complete 4 consecutive waves in the Mortis Trials. Each set of 4 waves completed grants 1 event progress point. It is possible to earn up to a total of 3 progress points per completed Mortis Trial run.</b><br/>This event will start on Tuesday, March 25. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/94f5cafa928b28b6237b8c9d60e84b9df7b38c23.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.1 Now Available!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497190789924782590</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hey folks,<br/><br/>Patch 6.1 has now arrived in Total War: WARHAMMER III! Highlights include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🏰 Full Kislev overhaul! Sally forth your Atamans, balance support with Court &amp; Orthodoxy and enjoy a refreshed tech tree<br/></li><li> 🔮 Build your own spell lore with reworked Fragments of Sorcery for Kairos Fateweaver<br/></li><li> ⚔️ Two new free units! The Nan-Gau Grenadiers for Cathay and Gnoblar Flingers for Ogre Kingdoms<br/></li><li> 🛠️ A plethora of QoL changes, including an improved unit ability list UI</li></ul>...plus much more!<br/><br/>Read the full Release Notes at the link below:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Patch 6.1 Release Notes</div><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues after updating to Patch 6.1, please let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum so our QA teams can investigate.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield! <br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmares &amp; Visions - OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520834687966380392</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9e6f037279456af5edf1b85ad33625e954fa5f28.png"/><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z_OKJUZKHe8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div> <br/>One of our favourite times of year: releasing a new update for Warhammer 40,000: Darktide…<br/><br/>Nightmares &amp; Visions has already begun to roll out across our platforms. Keep reading to see what’s waiting for you on the Mourningstar.<br/><br/>We are trying something new with patch notes. <br/><br/>From now on, we’ll be listing the patch notes in FULL on our website ONLY. This is because as the game grows, it’s often between 40-50 pages each major update. When trying to format these across three platforms (each with their own formatting)...please think of our poor CM. (Yes, I wrote this. - Straw)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">You can read about the rest of the update on our website.</div><br/><div class="bb_h1">Mortis Trials</div>Sefoni has a new challenge for you, rejects. The Theatres of Mortification contain the Mortis Trials. A fiendish new addition to Sefoni's training regime. Enter the Psykhanium and Sefoni will pit you against waves of enemies, but she'll also provide what she calls Indulgences (ability enhancements well beyond the powers of an average fighter) to help you in your endeavour. You can begin the trials in the usual way, by visiting the Psykhanium, but for a quicker entry, check out the new terminal near the mission board.<br/><br/>There is a lot to unpack in Mortis Trials, but we don’t want to spoil the fun that awaits. You can read our latest dev blog to learn more about it, or dive right into it once you’ve downloaded the update.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d9bc5e2a50d44f265663fd5eb7b73773752656de.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: A Day At The Theatre!</div>Sefoni's new training protocols whisk you off to the Theatres of Mortification. Unleash carnage in the Mortis Trials.<br/><br/><b>To make progress in the event, complete 4 consecutive waves in the Mortis Trials. Each set of 4 waves completed grants 1 event progress point. It is possible to earn up to a total of 3 progress points per completed Mortis Trial run.</b><br/><br/>This event will start on Tuesday, March 25. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/94f5cafa928b28b6237b8c9d60e84b9df7b38c23.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Reminder of Havoc Maintenance Announcement </div><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">With Havoc Campaigns, we’ll be introducing new balancing to the game mode. Ahead of Nightmares &amp; Visions, Havoc has been “off-campaign” and unavailable to play from Sunday, March 23 until today, the day of release on March 25.<br/><br/>During this off-time and to reflect the balance changes made, we’ve reset everyone to their nearest threshold depending on the highest they reached the previous Havoc Campaign period. (Please see the chart below.)</blockquote><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1d361f3998fe57239e7e8839cfedd29dd715fc08.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Updates to Havoc </div>As we previewed in our earlier dev blog on Updates to Havoc, there are some structural changes and more coming to Havoc with this release.<br/><div class="bb_h2">Rank Overhaul</div>Starting with Nightmares &amp; Visions, ranking in Havoc will change. All players who participated in the mission will rank up their order (up to three ranks) depending on eligibility. To be eligible you need to have an order of equal or lower rank.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4ac08cd45ba331c5620247fcbe2a71343b5e8389.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A gap greater than or equal to 10 gives an increase of (3) Clearance Levels.<br/></li><li> A gap between 6 and 9 gives an increase of (2) Clearance Levels.<br/></li><li> A gap of less than or equal to 5 gives an increase of (1) Clearance Levels.</li></ul>Based on feedback received, players' new order next week will no longer be equivalent to the highest played the previous week, rather we’ve opted to roll over the current order rank. <br/><br/><b>Dev note: </b><i>The inactivity decay is still active and it only triggers upon no interaction with the Havoc system.</i><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Havoc Campaigns</div>With this update, we’re introducing Campaigns to Havoc. Our intention is to release a new Campaign with different mutators and a rotating mission pool, alongside our major updates to Darktide. <br/><br/>Havoc Campaigns is what we’ve opted to call the rotation of the mission pool and mutators within Havoc. We want players to be able to learn and adapt to these combinations, while also changing things up over the period of the current Havoc Campaign. We will share more information on our plans for this in a few weeks.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Mission Pool</div>The previous missions from Havoc have been rotated out with the start of this new Campaign. The following missions are a part of this latest Campaign: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enclavum Baross<br/></li><li> Clandestium Gloriana<br/></li><li> Dark Communion<br/></li><li> Vigil Station Oblivium<br/></li><li> Hab Dreyko<br/></li><li> Power Matrix HL-17-36<br/></li><li> Magistrati Oubliette TM8-707<br/></li><li> Ascension Riser 31<br/></li><li> Relay Station TRS-150<br/></li><li> Comms-Plex 154/2f</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">New Mutators</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Heinous Rituals</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reports indicate that the Admonition has begun creating more Daemonhosts in this area, stop these rituals before it's too late.</li><li>Based on the mission length X amount of rituals will spawn. These rituals are composed of 8 Dreg ritualists trying to summon forth a new Daemonhost. Kill them all before time runs out or face the wrath of the newly created Daemonhost.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">The Encroaching Garden</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Marked Enemies, blessed by the Lord of Pestilence, will heal affected allies in proximity. </li><li>If these enemies are not dealt with quickly, they will rapidly regenerate the enemy forces. </li><li>Select enemies will be marked, and while these enemies are alive they will heal allies at a rate of 1200HP/s within a 5 meter radius. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Enraging Elites</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Elite enemies fall into rage when under 50% HP left, increasing their attack speed, damage caused and rendering them immune to crowd control.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Rampaging Enemies</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enemies in this sector are rampaging. They gain increased defence against attacks upon witnessing the death of an ally.</li><li>When an afflicted enemy dies, allied enemies in a 4 meters radius around are buffed up to 5 stacks, each stack providing damage reduction.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Havoc Balance Tweaks </div><div class="bb_h3">Emperor’s Fading Light</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed the increased shooting time from ranged enemies.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This was removed in response to the lack of build diversity where players felt forced to bring abilities like Psyker Telekine Shield or Zealot Chorus of Spiritual Fortitude.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added in Moebian Lieutenants that have a 80% chance to spawn throughout the mission.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Lieutenants are derived from the Twins and based on players' sentiment that they were “stuck” in their special assignment. We felt it fitting to bring out enemies that feel familiar.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Weakened Monstrosities will have a low chance of spawning throughout the mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Horde Pacing</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed horde spawn frequency from being based primarily on distance traveled through the level, to relying on timers. Please note that the amount of hordes allowed is still calculated based on main path traversal.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This change was made as backtracking too far turned off hordes. Also it was changed to combat being able to predict roughly where hordes show up.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3">New Horde Compositions</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>New coordinated horde strike type: “Blockade sandwich”.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i>This strike may happen if the strike team tries to backtrack too far.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3">Roamers</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed density type “none” from Havoc. This change was made to make the mission feel more oppressive with less chances for breaks.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Density type decides on how many roamers we spawn in a given area during regular and Auric missions.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed spawn population of roamers to be more balanced between melee and ranged, instead of being primarily one or the other.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This change will on average lower the spawn amount of gunner-esque enemies by 20%; this change is subject to be introduced during regular and Auric missions depending on the reception.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3">Specials</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased coordinated strike and surge frequency.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased Havoc Challenge rating. </li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>Challenge rating is a rough measure of the "challenge" the players are encountering, this value is part of defining the allowed limits of enemies spawned concurrently.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3">Miscellaneous</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Mission accept/reject popup for Havoc missions will now show chevrons that indicate how many rankups you will gain for your own Havoc order if successful.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/75541088728b4836e8feb4ef95d070ecc5c2a635.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Quality of Life Change for Havoc</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/619ae430c88ae3f6dfb085aa8eef5be9584b1823.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Party Finder Notification Change</div><br/>When the player is in a mission, the party finder invite popups are replaced by notifications that no longer block gameplay.<br/><br/><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We wanted to give a little extra shout out to Badwindt on nexusmods.com for pointing us in the right direction! When we were looking to implement a fix for this, the mod gave us an idea of where to look. </i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Quality of Life Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">DLSS 4 Support Added to Darktide</div><br/>Support for DLSS 4 has been added, featuring Multi Frame Generation for GeForce RTX 50 Series graphics cards. This technology generates up to three times more frames per traditionally rendered frame, significantly boosting FPS. Additionally, DLSS 4 offers faster single Frame Generation with lower memory usage for both RTX 50 and 40 Series. Additionally users can now choose between the CNN model or the new Transformer model for DLSS Super Resolution on all GeForce RTX graphics cards.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"> Class Changes </div><br/><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn Talent Tree Rework</div>Our favorite Abhuman is getting his Talent Tree revamped! We had a few clear goals we wanted to achieve with the rework that all boiled down to one point: Providing more Build opportunities.<br/><br/>We released a dev blog about the Ogryn Talent Tree changes and since then we’ve made a few more tweaks. You can read about them in full on our website.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3f710d204d57ca89203b2436fe7f8d3e78c5fccf.jpg"/><br/><br/>Don’t forget, we partnered with Games Lantern to get the new Ogryn Talent Tree up on their build simulator so players can test out their new builds.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weapon Balance Changes &amp; Tweaks</div><br/>In this update, we are addressing some of the outliers in the Darktide arsenal, whether over or under-performing.<br/><br/>We approached this objective by tweaking values, but also by adding new features and attack chains, or by shifting the power budget of the weapons, with the goal of giving each of them clear strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/>In all cases, we made sure that the fantasy of each weapon was maintained or even reinforced by the changes.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Blessing Description Updates </div><b>Dev Note: </b><i>We have changed the underlying system which is used to present the values used in Weapon Blessings. It will now pull values directly from the data used for the Blessing, instead of these values being hard coded separately.<br/><br/>What this means for you as players is that nothing has changed. But there might be instances of Blessings that look like they have been rebalanced now. In reality, it means that the Blessings will be showing the values that are defined in the game code. This is purely a visual change. </i><br/><br/>Known Issue from Nightmares &amp; Visions<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There is an issue with Psyker’s talent “Mettle” where the game client will crash if the talent reaches 31 stacks of movement speed buff. </li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will be fixed with Hotfix #63 (1.7.1).</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">You can read about the rest of the update on our website. </div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Thank you for reading about our latest update, Nightmares &amp; Visions. We’ve worked hard on this update for our community. It’s exciting to finally be able to share it with all of you. <br/><br/>And this is only the beginning of what we’ve got in store for you this year.<br/><br/>We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction: Mortis Trials - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520834687966380114</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8189710bbc0ebae80f039434fba5e8b741870a45.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone! </div><br/>As promised, we are back this week with another dev blog for the next update for Warhammer 40,000: Darktide - <b>Nightmares &amp; Visions</b>, which <b>releases next week</b> on <b>March 25, 2025. </b><br/><br/>This week, we’re focusing on new content coming to the game in the form of <b>Mortis Trials.</b> This <b>feature </b>has been designed to be a unique, replayable activity whereby players will mash through <b>waves of enemies in visions induced by Sefoni</b>, the Mourningstar’s mysterious Psyker. <br/><br/>With the arrival of Commissar’s Moebian 53rd and the escalation of the Battle for Tertium, Rannick has grudgingly decided that they need to step up the Rejects’ training regime from, well, <i>nothing</i>, to something. <br/><br/>With resources tight and the warband’s operatives more than a little… varied in their approach to combat, he and Morrow have turned the matter over to Sefoni. Which makes sense, given that she’s the creator and maintainer of the <i>Mourningstar’s </i>Meat Grinder - a psychically generated oubliette where Rejects can familiarise themselves with new weaponry. <br/><br/>To make this possible, she’s manifested a new nightmarescape that Morrow calls Sefoni’s Reverie.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What is Mortis Trials?</div><br/><i>Unlocked from Trust Level 13,</i> Mortis Trials is a new activity in Darktide where players can experience something they wouldn’t encounter in normal missions, something with crazy wave compositions and roguelike elements. The fickle nature of these psychic manifestations has ensured that no two trials are alike, and only those who adapt will prevail. By accessing Sefoni’s Reverie on the Mourningstar, players will be transported to the Theatres of Mortification. These are the arenas where players will face the challenges Sefoni has created for them.  <br/><br/>At the end of a successfully completed trial, players will return to Sefoni’s Reverie.<br/><br/><b>Havoc </b>is a <b>game mode </b>with multipliers upon multipliers, and stacked mutators; which has been designed for late-game players to face a challenge. The experience of an <b>activity </b>like <b>Mortis Trials </b>is designed to be chaotic, with easy access for immediate fun. That said, players will face horrors in these theatres, where there is no escape or surrender. Only by standing your ground and fighting with unwavering determination will players emerge with victory. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What will the game play loop look like for Mortis Trials?</div>Unlike some other experiences in Darktide, Mortis Trials offers more modular pacing rather than non-stop action. Pacing is key, with the difficulty increasing over time in a fun and expandable way. <br/><br/>Each trial consists of 12 waves of heretics to clear. These waves will be broken into three waves of three, and then a final set of three heretical-filled waves straight from Sefoni herself. <br/><br/>When launching Mortis Trials, players will first select the difficulty level they wish to try. From there, the players will assemble in a central theatre. <br/><br/>Before facing the initial wave, players will receive a small buff. The buff they receive is based on the “indulgence” that is chosen before this first wave begins. <br/><br/>Each indulgence has a specialization which will define the type of small buffs player will get during the play through. These include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Pyrokinetic</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in dealing fire damage, or improving combat effectiveness while attacking burning targets.</li><li><b>Voltaic</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in dealing electric damage, or improving combat effectiveness while attacking electrocuted targets.</li><li><b>Fulminator</b>: This Indulgence Archetype combines elements from both Pyrokinetic and Voltaic disciplines. It applies both electric and fire effects on enemies and can improve combat effectiveness when fighting electrocuted or burning enemies.</li><li><b>Death Dealer</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in close-quarters shooting and melee. Quick swapping between weapons and quicker reloads.</li><li><b>Colossus</b>: This Indulgence Archetype specialises in survivability, focused on close-quarters melee combat.</li></ul>Based on the archetype selected, the players will receive <b>another </b>small buff for the second wave. Every third wave, the players will be required to move around the arena and complete a designated task. These are the “<b>objective</b>” <b>waves</b>, which happen on the 3rd, 6th and 9th waves.<br/><br/>Upon completing the objective, Rejects are granted a cache of ammunition and supplies to aid in the trials. Further, players will then <b>pick </b>an additional stronger buff. This buff, along with the others, will continue to stack after each wave is successfully cleared. After each objective wave, players will <b>pick </b>an additional stronger buff. (These buffs are often amplifying player abilities, grenades, etc.) Only the most devout and blessed will survive.<br/><br/>After the last objective wave is completed (i.e. wave number 9), Rejects must endure a final set of three waves surging with enemies.  These are the waves where the players are the strongest. We want to give them plenty of time to enjoy their power to the fullest.<br/><br/>After successfully completing one round of the Mortis Trials, players must return the Mortis Relic to Sefoni in her Reverie. The strain of these Trials pushes her to her limit, causing stray thoughts and memories to slip out of her head. Attentive players might glean unintended insights into key members of the Mourningstar crew, so you better pay attention.<br/><br/>Repeated playthroughs of the Mortis Trials promise different play experiences, with new Indulgences to try and new conversations to unlock.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1"> Narrative Focus: Mortis Trials </div><br/>To learn more about Mortis Trials from a narrative perspective we are handing the dev blog over to our Narrative Lead, Michael Knight and our Lead Writer, Matthew Ward.<br/><br/><b>Sefoni’s one of the first characters a new Reject meets, but we don’t know much about her. Is that about to change?</b><br/><b>Michael Knight:</b> Yes and no. Sefoni’s delighted that she’s got new playthings to torment - the Rejects probably treat her better than most of the rest of the warband - but she’s also very secretive. That said, generating the Trials of Mortification places Sefoni under enormous pressure, and fragments of her past have a tendency to manifest without her knowing.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>Not just her past.<br/><br/><b>MK: </b>I’m pretty sure that we’re not supposed to talk about that. Grendyl wouldn’t like it. Safe to say, the Trials of Mortification offer the Rejects the opportunity to learn a lot more than Rannick intends. That probably won’t end well for Sefoni, but again, I doubt she cares.<br/><br/><b>How do the Rejects complete a Trial?</b><br/><b>MK:</b> Each Trial of Mortification is effectively a beefed-up exercise in a section of the Meat Grinder. The Rejects need to defeat the waves of enemies being projected by Sefoni, accomplishing tasks along the way. If they win, they’ll unlock a relic and get one step closer to being initiated into the Mourningstar’s elite cadre of Mortis Operatives. Fail, and… you can guess the rest.  <br/><br/><b>MW: </b>But Sefoni isn’t entirely heartless. The Meat Grinder’s her world. It follows her rules, so she’s prepared to offer the Rejects a series of indulgences (in-game buffs) that will help them meet the challenge.<br/><br/><b>MK:</b> Rannick isn't going to like that.<br/><br/><b>MW:</b> There’s definitely a sense that she’s not answering to Rannick any more, if she ever did.<br/><br/><b>You said something earlier about the Rejects having a chance to learn things that Rannick doesn’t want them to know. Can you tell us a little more about that?</b><br/><b>MK:</b> Well … Sefoni’s a psyker, a pretty rare and formidable one. And she’s been with Grendyl a long time. She’s overheard a lot over the years. Chances are, she knows a lot more about the warband than even Rannick. How far that goes - and how deep it goes - remains to be seen.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>One thing’s for sure… As time goes on, she’s going to get bolder.<br/><br/><b>MK: </b>Unless Rannick catches her.<br/><br/><b>MW: </b>Unless that, yes.<br/><br/>Hmm…there is a lot to be unpacked there. I’ll leave that for the community theory crafters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Thank you for reading our dev blog on Mortis Trials, part of the new content coming alongside the Nightmares &amp; Visions update slotted for release next week on March 25, 2025. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll make sure we answer them in the patch notes. <br/><br/>Remember, the Emperor protects. But He also demands sacrifice. <br/><br/>We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.5.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/606402352818161401</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.5.3 - 17th of March							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Bot Improvements: (note, these changes were missed from patch 6.4.0 patch notes)								<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Bots now avoid healing Zealots.						</li></ul> </li></ul> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed social wheel messages not working in Versus.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Weaves was inaccessible for some players.							</li></ul> </blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
