<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Mechanicus II Releasing Spring 2026</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/529865894144246448</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Mechanicus II is officially set to launch next spring. Since the Next Fest demo in October, we’ve been parsing every data-fragment of feedback, from long-time disciples of the Omnissiah and newly initiated alike. One of the most frequent requests was for the return of lingua technis, the distinctive machine-code language of the Machine God’s faithful that helped create the unique atmosphere of the original title. Given the demand, we’re committed to adding it as an optional setting at launch for anyone who prefers it over standard voiceovers.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re also hard at work on performance optimisations and tightening up the moment-to-moment experience, particularly with regards to the speed of gameplay. Some of you noticed the animation speed-up settings in the demo, some didn’t – either way, it’s staying. On top of that, there’ll be an option for the Move action to be automatically selected when a unit is chosen, helping keep the pace snappy and reducing input overhead. Ultimately, our priority is to ship a version of the game that meets the standards you expect – and the ones we set for ourselves.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, there’s still plenty left to show you before release. A major focus will be systems that weren’t part of the demo, especially leader customisation. The first of five spotlight videos is now live, covering one Adeptus Mechanicus leader and one Necron leader – starting with Tech-Aquisitor Scaevola and the Necron Lord Ominekh.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" snu_juwmvdq?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll also be showcasing our non-leader units through a series of profile cards, beginning with the six units featured in the demo. While not exhaustive, they’ll give you a solid look at the key weapons, skills, traits, and upgrades that shape each unit’s identity. Expect new cards weekly from now through launch across all our social channels, including Discord – feel encouraged to drop in and take a look.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/45031461/74a077513b2c0a2d39b158f02f5809a8e6f680c7.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for your continued support as we advance toward launch. The cog continues to turn.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Fest has begun!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/528734197434548760</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Steam's triannual festival of demos starts today, and Mechanicus II is taking part.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The demo's been out just over a week now, and the response from the community has been really encouraging. Thank you for the support, feedback and bug reports – we’ve been reading it all!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just pushed an updated demo build with the following fixes and improvements:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added controller support.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor optimisation improvements – investigating this has been and continues to be a priority.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issues caused by changing difficulty mid-skirmish.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug causing Skitarii Rangers' faces to disappear.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a soft lock when exiting to the main menu at the exact moment a tutorial triggered.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed font rendering issues in French, Simplified Chinese, Japanese, and Korean.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed UI issues on 16:10 displays.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an error caused by alt-tabbing between windows.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added missing loading-screen quotes in several non-English languages.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">New to the community? Join us on Discord to discuss the game with us and your fellow acolytes of the Machine God, and maybe even take part in our character colouring competition, in which you could win prizes worth over £600!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praise the Omnissiah – Mechanicus II Demo Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/528732929177683327</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">//\[STATUS: DEMO DEPLOYED]...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">//\[ACCESS: PUBLIC]...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">//\[OBJECTIVE: TACTICAL ASSESSMENT]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The demo of Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II has just finished exloading into the Steam-sphere, and is available right now!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is your chance to command both factions in tactical skirmish combat as you uncover the origins of a new and epic planetary conflict between the techno-religious acolytes of the Adeptus Mechanicus and the ancient, deathless Necron legions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Download, engage and test your tactical logic against the alien threat.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Don’t forget to join our Discord to share feedback, meet the community, and get the latest updates!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gameplay Overview for Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/547870056202109075</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">The Omnissiah has blessed us with a glimpse of what to expect from Warhammer 40,000 Mechanicus II. Get a first glimpse of what’s to come in the sequel:</p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xd_nkrcwz0w?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Whether you’re a faithful servant of the Omnissiah or aligned with the ancient dynasties, wishlist today and prepare for the battles to come.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Mechanicus II will be playable at Gamescom!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/501707621168840903</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">The Omnissiah calls, and we’re answering at Gamescom! For the first time ever, Mechanicus II will be playable on the show floor. Step into the next chapter of the critically acclaimed turn-based tactical series and experience the beginning of the war for Hekateus IV first-hand.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is your chance to retake command of the Adeptus Mechanicus forces, and to also get a taste of leading the Necrons of the Sankhotep dynasty against their world’s invaders. We can’t wait to show you what’s in store – see you in Cologne on 20-24th August!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
