<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #58 (1.6.5) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592036258645046</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/465a2dc3a25ffc297e2644fa2f8b52ce9307794e.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>We’ve got our first Hotfix (#58 aka 1.6.5) for the year ready for everyone now. It’s begun to roll out across all of our platforms and it’ll begin to be available shortly. Players might want to relog to access the new servers.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Re: Stalls and disconnects on console. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We are continuing to investigate the increased rate of stalls causing disconnects on console. We’ve seen this happens more frequently in high intensity missions such as higher levels of Havoc and Auric Maelstrom missions. We have some initial ideas on what might help with these disconnects and we have included those fixes in this patch. <br/></li><li>We have additional fixes in the works for the next update as well. As the hotfix rolls out, we’ll continue to monitor player comments to see if there have been improvements, as well as checking data on our end.</li></ul></li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> [Console] Fixed a rare crash which could happen when suspending the game immediately after launching it. <br/></li><li> Fixed an uncommon crash which could happen when a player joined a Strike Team through the Party Finder due to the game failing to retrieve their profile data.<br/></li><li> Small improvements to memory usage for UI code. <br/></li><li> Improved presentation of the Weapons and Curios icons. The icons will now appear smaller, but better aligned and with more of the item visible. <br/></li><li> Fixed UI crash that can happen while showcasing the mastery progression in the end of round. <br/></li><li> Fixed some typos and incorrect translations.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description text of the Special action was overlapping with the UI in the Inspect screen for the Blaze Force Greatsword weapon family.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Quickplay “Select Threat Level” UI element was misplaced in the Mission Board menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where an incorrect image could be displayed when receiving a Party Finder invitation while already participating in a mission.<br/></li><li> Fixed a missing texture issue that sometimes resulted in a crash.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with missing physics and stretching materials on the Veteran “Desert Hood (Dune camo)” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the eyebrow would be removed while wearing the Zealot “Votarist's Pot Helm with Rebreather” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed the scaling of the decal on the side of the Psyker “Krieg Witch Mask (Krieg 143rd, Shadow Ops)” headgear cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the eyebrow would be removed while wearing the Ogryn “Mark XII Brute Model Cranial Implant (Size XXXXL)” headgear cosmetic.  </li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 10:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"DLC of your dreams" community survey - give us your feedback!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503940938959160186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We've asked you about this in Pathfinder, and the time has come to do the same for Rogue Trader. <br/><br/>What would a perfect DLC be for you, should we make more of them?<br/><br/>Let us know by participating in the "DLC of your dreams" survey: <br/><br/>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/3NCWL3B<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/1c5bca97ec02029f65b72f4e34db061a66df2d4f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darktide 101: Creating the Sound of Darktide w/ Jesper Kyd</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592036258644887</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b632ca853074e994ca690566d29d4792228dc0ab.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>This one has been a much requested dev blog. To celebrate the New Year and our latest update–Grim Protocols–we sat down with Jesper Kyd to discuss his work on creating the music we all love so much.<br/><br/>Grab your favourite drink, or snack and dive in for another Darktide 101 blog.<br/><br/><b>Straw Hat: What is your creative process like for Darktide? How is it that you normally approach a track? Do you often have somewhat of a complete idea once we give you a rundown of the level, like with Rolling Steel or Dark Communion?</b><br/><br/>Jesper Kyd: I would say it’s a bit of both. You know, the intuition is certainly there now that I’ve worked on Darktide for a bit. But these last few missions I’ve worked on, the train mission (Rolling Steel) and the cultist one (Dark Communion), certainly are going in a different direction. There’s a lot that still needs to be invented for that, and then added into the Darktide sound.<br/><br/>The usual approach is that I get a video of the level and a playthrough with the audio team and then we discuss ideas. I get to soak up the atmosphere and I start to hear in my head what would be really cool. Sometimes, it’s very instant. Like for Dark Communion. For that map, it was instant. I knew exactly what I wanted to do right away.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9051b87e93bf5ac7d6285db7b6b42aa6fe686f58.png"/><br/><i>Make sure to check out Jesper's latest track on YouTube.</i><br/><br/>The track for that mission came out really quickly. It was this eight minute track that just kept going. It was really fun to make. It was more of a grimdark orchestral style. I wouldn’t say that’s unusual for Darktide, but it does have a lot more orchestral elements than other tracks have had so far, which made it a lot of fun to work on.<br/><br/><b>The players are always so excited when they find out there is a new Jesper track on the way.</b><br/>That’s really great to hear. It’s great to hear players are excited, too. I think you can hear my excitement in the music. You know? I’m just having so much fun working on this music, because it really is a good combination of what I like to do. I like to do something new, something fresh, and then mix it with all my electronics and orchestral elements and melodic things. And Darktide really is perfect for that.<br/><br/><b>How much time do you spend on a track for Darktide?</b><br/>Well, it’s interesting. Because sometimes, I can get a majority of a track done in a day – if I’m just totally in a zone. I know exactly what I want to do. Other times, it can take me up to two weeks.<br/><br/>I think the more clear it is to me what the track should be, and the more clearly the map communicates what the intent is, the faster it goes.<br/><br/>With Dark Communion, I knew exactly what I wanted. So while it’s a longer track, I wrote it much, much quicker.<br/><br/>Something like Rolling Steel, you could go a lot of directions with that. It could’ve taken longer to figure it out. But I knew I wanted the pulses of the train moving, the strange grunting and breathing sounds, and all that kind of stuff in the music. That mission is a bit about stressing you out. But it can’t just be about stressing you out in a stressful way. It has to be in a cool way, too. I had to make sure it’s not going to drive you crazy, right?<br/><br/><b>Exactly, because it’s a shorter mission too, and players will be hearing it more often.</b><br/>Yes, exactly. It’s not just an alarm going off. It has to be something more musical. It needs to still be cool on repeated listenings.<br/><br/>Subtlety is something I work a lot with, too. Even though Darktide’s music is pretty aggressive. It’s not shy music. However there are still a lot of layers. There are a lot of elements you might not pick up on the first few times you hear it, perhaps you only feel it. But after more repeated listens, you might start to notice it.<br/><br/>It is something really interesting about writing music for games. It has to be written in a way that rewards repeated listens. It’s kind of the opposite if you write a pop song. For a pop song, you want everyone right away to say, “Yes, this is it.” Because then the song can chart, right? For games, it’s like the opposite. You’re trying to make it layered, so that the music can grow on you and you can still listen to it time and again.<br/><br/>For Warhammer, it’s such a massive universe. There is so much lore that goes into it. For our game, it feels like you truly did create something to encapsulate the gothic, grim, dark nuances of Darktide. You couldn’t imagine this score in any other game.<br/><br/>It was definitely a part of the brief in the beginning that the team wanted a score that was not typical for the genre, which has more orchestral and choir and maybe guitars.<br/><br/>I think holding on to the choir though was really interesting, and we needed something to make it recognizable as Warhammer. The human voice is so powerful, and mixing that up with this industrial and these rhythms from the tracks creates something fascinating.<br/><br/>Also the organ. Whenever I use the organ, there always seems to be a positive player reaction.<br/><br/><b>I was going to say that is one of my favourite parts, where you’ve mixed those heavy, industrial sounds with the organic, human voices. When the choir and organ come in on some tracks, it’s really powerful.</b><br/><br/>There is something really God-like about those instruments, where the choir gives you this feeling like you’re now dealing with the Emperor. And the organ kind of goes in that same direction. It feels like it would be the Imperium’s kind of instrument.<br/><br/><b>For the latest track for Dark Communion, you said it came to you pretty quickly. Was there anything about this track that stood out to you?</b><br/><br/>The whole idea was based around creating something ritualistic. Something to sound like there is a seance of some sort going on somewhere in the level. No matter how subtle or big the music gets, it is meant to always give you that feeling. There are some subtle visual signs we approach from the distance, the way you see the smoke and colours. As you get closer, the music gets more and more epic. And then once we’re in the church, it’s full on.<br/><br/>It was so much fun to write. It’s not everyday you get asked to do a big ritualistic cue, inspired by the soul leaving the body, etc.<br/><br/><b>Through composing for Darktide, is there anything new you’ve felt like you’ve learned about music or your process while working on it?</b><br/><br/>Oh, absolutely. Darktide was one of those projects that I knew exactly what I wanted to create. And I knew I couldn’t do it. I had to figure out, how do I do it?<br/><br/>It very much had to do with the capacity of the studio. I had some things to solve because of what I wanted to do. I got a whole new Department of my studio running. It’s to do with step sequencing from the 70s. It required these old devices that can play back notes, but it plays it back in a very funky way. You know, it has a lot of swing to the actual notes, so everything sounds more alive. I wanted everything to sound like it was performed.<br/><br/>So all the synthesizers in that score, those 30-40 synthesizers I play, are mostly played live, or they run through these step sequencers. It gives this really organic feeling, like you’re part of a living world, instead of just having the computer perfectly synchronize everything. You know, everything on the beat is perfect, or you’re using software for the synthesizers. I wanted to stay away from all that.<br/><br/>We needed something really organic, that sounded lived in. And a lot of these synths are 40 years old. So, they sound 40 years old. And they sound used; they sound lived in. They sound very different from the day they were released in 1976. It’s a different sound, because the components and the keyboards, they age. I think it just sounds much cooler. I’m not a big fan of anything that sounded brand new. That’s kind of the perspective I took with everything.<br/><br/>I had to find a way to use my sequencer program, Cubase, with these step sequences so I could tempo synchronize everything. And that was really, really difficult. I had to get a custom box built for it, just to make it work, because there was no way you could do it without customizing something.<br/><br/><b>So, you were determined. You were thinking: I know the sound I want.</b><br/><br/>We got this box made, and now I’m able to run it so all my synthesizers are synchronized, and that was something I had to invent for Darktide. Because I knew I wanted that sound, like when you hear the Darktide theme, when that bass line that just comes in and you’re like, it’s supposed to make you pause and say what is this?<br/><br/>And it’s such a weird mixture of styles. And that is the technique on full display. It might just sound like a simple bass line, but to get that thing going, and to get it sounding that loose, and to get it sounding full of anarchy. Because you start underground in Darktide. It was very much designed to support that. Everything is chaos, anarchy, and dirty. You’re a reject.<br/><br/>Then, of course, we mix all that with the choirs and the organs, which is more the Imperium, and that’s the sound of Darktide. Those two opposing elements that really don’t belong together. I try to make them belong together, you know? Because that’s the world of Darktide.<br/><br/>And the last bit was, how do you make something that takes place 40,000 years in the future. We wanted to avoid being stuck with the idea that it had to be futuristic. No. It has to be real. It has to sound lived in. There’s been a war going on for 1000s of years. The Imperium knows war. That’s a sound that has been through the ringer. It’s been through hell and is still running.<br/><br/>The last thing I can say about that is I directly got a quote from the team that they wanted the music to sound like living machines that had been forgotten about. These machines have been running so long that people forgot how they actually work. They only know how to maintain them.<br/><br/>All of this I’ve been talking about, I think it all comes together to fit this organic sound that has become Darktide. And I think it fits the game so precisely. People just get it. You don’t have to explain it.<br/><br/><b>What is the strangest thing you’ve ever mixed into the soundtrack?</b><br/><br/>On the main title track of Darktide, it has “children.” I did a 15 layer children’s choir. But it’s all me. I was able to manipulate it live so that it ended up sounding like children. And I thought, there is this intense bass and industrial stuff mixed in, and then having these children, almost like children of the Emperor, coming in and chanting against all that underground industrial noise.<br/><br/><b>If you did the children’s choir, is it actually you anytime we hear a choir in Darktide?</b><br/><br/>No, we work with the Hungarian Scoring Choir and recorded them live for Darktide. And, man, that was an awesome session. It was just really cool to see them, you know, starting to groove out to the music. All those choirs are manipulated by me to sound a little bit more machine-like and perhaps people don’t even realize it’s live, but they’re all singing.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Alright, that’s all from our interview with Jesper! If you have any other questions for him, let us know in the comments. I’ll share some of them with him and make sure he sees them!<br/><br/>We hope you enjoyed this latest Darktide 101 dev blog. If you have other topics you’d like to see us discuss more, please drop a comment, too. I’ll try to set them up! (- Straw)<br/><br/>Until next time,<br/><br/><i>The Darktide Team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE new map: Devious Delvings is out now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/738127762059952962</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.3.1 - 24th of January							</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Versus) Increased the cooldown for playing sound when pinging frequently.							<br/> </li><li>	Devious Delvings - Damage taken from the water does not interrupt revives anymore.							</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Devious Delvings - Fixed a crash that could occur in the elevator.							<br/> </li><li>	Devious Delvings - Fixed a visual bug where the water splashes in first person wouldn't go away if you died.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash when clicking on a Versus Custom Lobby entry with Custom Settings active while in a non-Versus Keep.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a Dedicated Server Crash when slotting in a barrel in any barrel event.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a rare crash in Versus that would occur when two clients join a lobby at the same time.</li></ul></blockquote>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/78PZItRY4tE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><br/>The second installment in the Verminous Dreams campaign,<i> ‘Devious Delvings’</i>, is out now, free for all owners of Vermintide 2!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Devious Delvings</div>Having infiltrated the Skaven-infested ruins of the mythical Athel Lithri, our Heroes must now investigate the site to find out what it is that the verminous Pactsworn are scheming. The devastation and machinery suggest a massive project, but what are they after in this temple of all places?<br/><br/>Well, either way, better get to the bottom of it and smash every rat that comes your way. And the ones that don’t, too, for good measure (Saltzpyre agrees).<br/><br/>Just like the previous maps, <i>Devious Delvings</i> comes with its own set of Okri’s Challenges and rewards, such as a portrait frame and paintings!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Versus: Custom Game Settings</div>And for the Pactsworn enthusiasts, we’ve got an exciting new addition! When creating a player-hosted custom game, the host now has a suite of adjustable settings to tweak and modify how the match will play out! You can take the opportunity to make things super crazy, or to make your own competitive changes!<br/><br/>Some examples of the settings you can find in Custom Games:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Early Win toggle<br/></li><li> Hero Bots toggle<br/></li><li> Friendly Fire toggle<br/></li><li> Number of Hero Wounds<br/></li><li> Knocked down Hero health<br/></li><li> Horde Ability charge rate<br/></li><li> Pactsworn respawn timer<br/></li><li> Pactsworn Catch up with Hero distance<br/></li><li> Spawn distance from Heroes<br/></li><li> Pactsworn Health<br/></li><li> …And more!</li></ul>On top of those and every other setting being added with this update, we plan on hopefully expanding that list with more and more settings as time goes on! Feel free to give us your own suggestions for settings you’d like to tinker with in Custom Games!<br/><br/>In the lobby browser, games that are playing with rules different from the default ones we use in Quickplay Servers will be flagged as having a modified ruleset.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Developer Stream today  - 17:00 CEST - twitch.tv/fatsharkgames</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/437f23d90815dd6952f4a2f68426bf71f68b3347.jpg"/><br/>We’ll be hosting a stream on our twitch today at 17:00 CEST! Level Design Lead <b>Rickard </b>and Art Director <b>Joseph </b>will be showing off the new mission as well as answering your questions and chatting with the community. Come hang out! twitch.tv/fatsharkgames<br/><br/><br/><i>Without further ado…</i><br/> <div class="bb_h1">	Patch 6.3.0 patch notes						</div> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Added a new map, 'Devious Delvings', as the second mission in the Verminous Dreams campaign.</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Mission comes with its own set of Okri's challenges and rewards as usual, including shillings, a portrait frame and two paintings.	</li></ul></li><li> <b>Added configurable settings for player hosted Custom Versus Games.</b> <br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Made it so Versus Custom Games with changed settings show up differently in the lobby browser.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Added the ability to set a custom name for Versus player hosted lobbies.							<br/> </li><li>	Added more combat banter for our Heroes. Hell yeah.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Removed the ability to respond to other players' world markers.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Opening the communication wheel when looking at one's own world marker no longer displays "Cancel".							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) World markers behind walls are now cancellable.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Removed cooldown of enemy pings in Versus. Ping attempts that don't print chat messages have a significantly higher limit regarding spam prevention.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Removed 'Ping Only Item' and 'Ping Only Enemy' keybinds. 'Tag Only' keybind no longer places world markers. 'Place World Marker' is now bound to middle mouse button by default (It is still possible to place world markers with regular tag 'T').							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Players can now ping enemies when knocked down.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Elite enemies are now pingable.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Pactsworn players can now ping enemies through walls.							<br/> </li><li>	Added a keybind to only open the Weapon Pose wheel.							<br/> </li><li>	Added the ability to rebind the key to switch page in the emote wheel.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed the sanctioned mod 'Neuter Ult Effects' crashing in official realm if mods it depends on fail to load.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Kruber could never thank Kerillian for healing him. Listen, it was embarrassing, okay?							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where players could upgrade weapons to Veteran quality before level 30 in certain menus.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed Weave bots not using cosmetics from the selected bot Loadout.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug with the icons on Versus weapons not resetting when removing applied illusions.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where floating hats appeared in various menus when being in the Versus Keep. I bet that was Olesya trying to lure Kruber somewhere.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a bug where the "Easy Meat - Kill a hoisted hero" challenge was obtainable if the killed player was hoisted at any point during the round, not just if the player is hoisted when killed.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a bug where the "Not so Fast! - Disable a Hero that is Reviving another Hero" challenge was obtainable by simply disabling any hero, regardless if they are reviving or not.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed some mistakes with the German localization.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where hero skins that overwrite hats would still take texture changes from said hat, if applicable (Notably, Slayer head cosmetics changing tattoos and skin)							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the model of a rapier illusion having a gap between the blade and the hilt.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a bug where controller sensitivity would be reset to default after each round.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed wonky UI behaviour after deleting a loadout.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the Huntsman talent "Makin' it look easy" icon not being colored on the HUD.							<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the name of a bundle in Lohner's Emporium spilling out of place.							<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed an issue where the matchmaking UI would show 'N/A' when Quickplaying while in a party.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.1.11 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503940938959159390</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>We are deploying an update to resolve some of the frequently reported desync cases in co-op. <br/><br/>While this update should improve the situation, it does not yet cover all known cases. We are still in the process of investigating and fixing more of them, and will deploy another update as soon as possible.<br/><br/>It will help if you report any desyncs you encounter via the bug report tool! Can be done by pressing ALT+B or pushing both sticks on a controller at once.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Desperate Measures;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Cassia’s Lidless Stare;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few desync issues caused by Grand Strategist’s stratagems;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by hovering the cursor over Apexalium Stimulant in combat;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by opening the inventory in combat;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by quickly clicking through the items in the inventory;<br/></li><li> Fixed desync issues caused by certain sequences of attacks and abilities;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
