<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 03 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4556046454947315881</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speedfreeks!,</b><br/>With your continued feedback we further add to, tweak and improve the game.<br/><br/>Today, we are now live with:<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b391dceab12c8150b09629e8508f65a1ef90842f.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added <b>new Kill Konvoy map</b> "Big Eruptor" based on the Deff Rally map Burna Valley<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5a5e34b7a82b21ed4d54c075441ba3fbeb8c4d2d.png"/><br/></li><li> <b>New alternate lighting variations</b> for Rok Rush (dark nebula) <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b4ba5c33403ef4451756ecc3aabb4f7450298eba.png"/>and Frozen Dakka (night-time) <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5c576d02ecf2c59611ab950159ce05df8708ae15.png"/><br/></li><li> <b>Improved terrain and collision</b> in Kill Konvoy maps Frozen Dakka and Ded 'Ard Desert<br/></li><li> Death volumes added underneath all the maps to respawn people automatically in case they accidentally clip through the terrain<br/></li><li> Added map names to top right of starting screen and end of match team score screen</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/24852a660b47cb1afe7a59773fb3145ba6a76e95.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Burna Bottle now does 10 direct hit damage and its splash damage radius has been reduced by 25%<br/></li><li> Grot Rigging heal increased to 50 from 30<br/></li><li> Scrapjet missile range reduced to 100m<br/></li><li> Scrapjet drill now does impact damage based on velocity.  Damage over time removed due to inconsistency<br/></li><li> Kustom Boosta Blasta Jump ability no longer does damage and knockback to nearby enemies<br/></li><li> Shokkjump Dragsta Shokk Rifle now has enough projectile speed to be functionally hitscan<br/><br/></li><li> There is now an option to <b>dash in the steering direction</b> rather than camera direction<br/></li><li> All HUD reticles now have shadows for easier visibility on bright surfaces<br/></li><li> New colourized ability icons shown on the HUD<br/></li><li> Customization presets can now be switched ingame via the vehicle selection screen<br/></li><li> Presets button now more prominently shown in the UI</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f26deda61208f1c88b36ebf9f023868ecbc0b145.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Parties can now matchmake</b> against other parties by using the same game name and matchmaking at the same time. Other players are able to backfill (matchmake) normally into this game once it's created.  Note that matchmaking using party vs. party may take longer to match than usual, as it is waiting to create a new game with the other party</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/58adbcd6e3b1aacbdb4916eeb8e0d24330deb806.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Matchmaking region selection is now available</b>, as to provide players more control over where they would like to play</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/5a62466284ed47bf19e710a9ce02ab154360bb12.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Players can switch teams</b> regardless of skill level as long as their team is winning by 200 points and the losing team has the same or fewer players, or their team is up by 300 points and the losing team has 1 more player or less</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/525bbc93b070fee41947e8acffa76c958e8235a8.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Leader board stats have now been reset</b><br/></li><li> Players can now opt out of the Leader boards via an option at the top of the Leader boards screen<br/></li><li> For match stats to count towards the Leader boards, there must be 12 human players in the match. Stats acquired in limited time events don’t count<br/></li><li> Scrap Loota board no longer counts Scrap Boosts or daily challenge rewards<br/></li><li> Gork’s chosen board now measures kills + assists instead of kills – deaths<br/></li><li> Sawbonez board now tracks raw healing stats</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d49d959cd6d1c5026f08714c468d18bdc7014e1f.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Deff Rally point bonus for getting a kill while holding the point has been increased back to 5 from 2. This only applies to the losing team<br/></li><li> Reduced height of bomb spawn scrap piles in Kill Konvoy<br/></li><li> Communication pings on the HUD no longer appear on enemies with hidden nametags due to stealth abilities<br/></li><li> Quick comms messages can now be seen during respawn screen and end of match screen<br/></li><li> Anonymous player names option added for those wanting to stream the game and not worry about offensive player names<br/></li><li> When pinging an ally ("PROTECT DAT GIT"), their name now appears next to the message<br/></li><li> Kill assist duration window increased to 10 seconds (from 7)<br/></li><li> Air-time no longer included in MVP screen stats<br/></li><li> Fixed total scrap calculation for player stats<br/></li><li> Windowed mode now available (has issues, to be used at player's discretion)<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash happening at the settings screen</li></ul><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/>  <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.3.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458094434636005403</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8819ade8a9ce45de2046736c42ad35755f2ad1b3.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks! <br/><br/>Thanks for your feedback in the wake of Patch 5.3's release. We've been keeping a close eye on your comments regarding Magic Items in particular, and today we've rolled out Hotfix 5.3.1 which includes, alongside a number of bug fixes, some rebalancing for some of these items. We'll continue to monitor your feedback regarding these, so do keep letting us know your thoughts once you've got your hands on the changes.<br/><br/>We expect our next release to be 6.0, and though our teams will of course be monitoring for any unexpected errors that require an additional hotfix, our heads are now down for the final stretch on the road to the release of Update 6.0 and the next DLC! In case you missed it, you can watch our latest dev chat video for some more details on what's coming.<br/><br/>Without further ado, let's look at today's changelog:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">MAGIC ITEMS BALANCING</div><br/>We’ve received a lot of feedback on our newly released Magic Items and will continue to monitor it. For now, we’ve made the following changes:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Idol of Zak-Alooog</div>This item was more punishing than necessary, and the positives didn’t fully warrant the burden of the negatives. In particular, the fatigue penalty was quite harsh, so we’ve made the following adjustments:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced the movement range penalty from -50% to -20%.<br/></li><li> Removed the fatigue penalty effect.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Helm of Draesca</div>This item was always intended to have a strong tradeoff that aligns with its lore. However, we agree with the feedback we've received that the item was skewed too negatively, particularly providing little reason to keep it equipped. We’ve made the following addition to the item:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a 2% chance per end turn for the helm to grant a powerful unique trait, ‘Power of Draesca.’ <br/></li><li> ‘Power of Draesca’: +20% HP, +20% character experience, +10% ward save, +10% research rate.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Deathsinger/Doomsinger</div>One of the smaller ideas we didn’t manage to include in patch 5.3 was the concept that these sister swords would provide an extra benefit when they are together. We’ve now implemented this and added the following to the swords:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a 5% chance per end turn for characters with these swords equipped to gain a unique trait when both are in the same region. <br/></li><li> Sister Swords: +10 melee attack, +10 melee defence, charge reflect attribute.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when attempting to exchange units with a camp that was being abandoned during the campaign. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred while loading a battle with AI Control selected and Control Large Army toggled off in siege battles with large garrison armies.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a rare end-turn prompt for an idle character when that character already has a destination. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players using the Orcs &amp; Goblins faction could enter Tunnelling Stance when the army's movement points were below 100% while the Waaagh! Army View was selected.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SETTLEMENTS/BUILDINGS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where the Daemon Prince could not properly access the Harbour port building when occupying Erengrad. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in the Orcs &amp; Goblins campaign where players were unable to target discovered Skaven settlements for a Waaagh! unless their capital was also revealed. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Waaagh's target settlement model would disappear after being razed. The model now remains visible without the need for a save reload.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TECHNOLOGY TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Added 'Fire While Moving' for Gyrocopters and Gyrobombers to the 'Improved Gyrocopter Engines' technology on the Dwarf tech tree. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SKILL TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in Drycha's skill tree where the ‘Indoctrinator’ skill displayed an excessive number of character unit card variants. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ANCILLARIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where certain effects that increased recruit rank for Nurgle units would not work when playing as the Daemon Prince. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">BOUNTIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Adjusted how the monetary reward for Bounties is calculated. Previously, the amount was based on the issuer's Treasury, which could fluctuate significantly regardless of their strength and had no relevance to the selected target. The new calculation considers the player's distance to the target, with higher rewards for immortal targets or province capitals. Additionally, distance is now measured from the nearest settlement owned by the player rather than just the faction leader's army. This change should generally result in Bounty targets being closer to the player.<br/></li><li> Adjusted the Bounty rewards system to ensure a balanced distribution of additional rewards. Players will now receive a consistent cycle through meat, camp growth, and rare ancillaries, reducing randomness and enhancing reward variety.<br/></li><li> Players can now decline a Bounty, triggering a new one to be issued on the following turn.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ZHAO MING'S MERCENARIES</div>​ We've fixed an issue causing Zhao Ming's Ogre Mercenary benefits to not apply to the new Mercenaries added in 5.3. Additionally, we've made the following changes to help take Zhao's mercenary play to the next level.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Faction Trait</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added +10 Melee Attack and Defense to all Ogre Mercenaries.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Skill Tree</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Removed -25% recruitment cost for Ogre Mercenaries.<br/></li><li> Added Guardian for all Ogre Mercenaries faction-wide.<br/></li><li> Added +20% Weapon and Missile Damage for all Ogre Mercenaries faction-wide.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed a bug where hovering over the Ogre Bounties panel link in the help pages while the Bounties were open would cause the panel to flash extremely brightly.<br/></li><li> Improved the visual quality of the Worldroots Forest Health numbers when playing as the Wood Elves. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where lords, including Legendary Lords, would lose their last names in the UI when they were wounded. This issue affected both player-controlled and AI-controlled lords.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed an issue where defeating the Nemesis Crown-wielder, Knobber da Bossy Git, did not properly complete the quest objectives, preventing the battle from ending as intended.  </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div>​<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue where the Empire's Steam Tank would fail to fire its main cannon after engaging in melee combat. Now, after exiting melee, the cannon will resume firing as intended, aligning with expected gameplay.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Grave Guard Halberds mistakenly had Expert Charge Defence instead of Charge Defence vs. Large, reinforcing their role as dedicated monster hunters rather than generalist frontline defenders.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where ranged units were sometimes assigned targets just outside of their range, causing them to sit idle instead of firing.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ABILITIES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the "Howl of The Great Beast" ability incorrectly triggered a jumping animation for enemy Marauders.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ANIMATION</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​Fixed a bug where the Zombie Pirate Deckhands Mob was missing an animation.<br/></li><li> Resolved a visual issue where Skeleton Archers would snap to different positions and move back and forth excessively during the ‘shoot ready’ and combat idle animations.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the weapon of Eternal Guards would disappear while under ranged fire.<br/></li><li> Resolved an issue with the twisted left arm of Blessed Kroxigors during their running animation.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Skarsnik was missing his death animation in the post-battle screen.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ENVIRONMENT</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Prologue's first Land Battle map had a ludicrous parallax setting on a single decal. The parallax setting has since been adjusted for a more pleasing viewing experience.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved an issue in multiplayer campaigns where the Ogre Kingdoms could receive bounties that targeted their teammates.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/><br/>And that's all for today! Thanks again for your ongoing feedback and suggestions. As always, if you run into any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.3.1 please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum. If you'd like to chat about this update (and all other things Total War related!) then be sure to join the official Total War Discord server, or head over to our CA Community forums to join the discussion there.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Havoc Game Mode - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4476108195413098968</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone,</div><br/>We’ve long seen the comments from players saying they want more of a challenge from Darktide. Players would like to continually challenge themselves and improve their skills. You want to face the horrors of the tide.<br/><br/>We’re excited to announce the next major game feature we have been working on for Darktide: <b>Havoc</b>.<br/><br/>If you’re a player who relishes overcoming obstacles and seeks to measure and improve your abilities, then Havoc has been crafted specifically for you.<br/><br/>This dev blog is an introduction to Havoc and to answer initial questions. We’re still performing tests for it, and we’ll announce a release date as soon as we are confident! We will be following this dev blog up with another Q&amp;A, similar to what we did with Itemization.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What is Havoc?</div>Commissar Dukane and the Moebian 53rd Steelheads have arrived on Atoma, keen to prove their mettle and quash this uprising. Havoc missions represent Dukane’s influence on the war for Tertium. She believes in firm, swift, decisive action, striking at the heart of the traitor forces and ensuring each mission takes the maximum toll on the enemy.<br/><br/>An uncompromising taskmaster, she demands the best from all her charges, rewarding those she deems worthy with yet more perilous missions, or as she might say, opportunities for greatness.<br/><br/>Let’s break this down further.<br/><br/>Havoc is a new tiered progression system we have been working on for Trust Level 30 players.* This system will consist of different levels, known as Order Levels. There will be 40 Order Levels in total for Havoc.<br/><br/>Each Order Level will incrementally increase in difficulty, with increasing negative modifiers and varying mutators. Players won’t only face increased hordes or enemies, they’ll also encounter 4 brand new mutators, including one the community has recently encountered: the Infected 21st Moebians.<br/><br/>** Only Trust Level 30 players will be able to access Havoc.<br/><br/>A player’s Havoc Rank is the highest level they’ve reached and successfully completed in Havoc.<br/><br/>A Havoc Order is the current mission a player is facing. Each Havoc Order is unique and personal to the player in terms of what mission and what mutators.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Key Features of Havoc</div><div class="bb_h2">1. Tiered Challenges</div><br/>There will be 40 Havoc Order levels for players to progress through for Havoc. With each level missions will become incrementally more difficult, allowing players to gauge their skill progression. To unlock Havoc, players must first complete an Auric or Non-Auric Maelstrom mission.<br/><br/>For each Order level, more negative modifiers are introduced. This increase is additive, meaning the previous modifiers will carry over to the next Havoc Order, plus any new ones on top of it. For example, if an Order level 1 reduces toughness regeneration, then Order level 2 will reduce toughness regeneration and another negative modifier on top of it. So on, and so forth until Order level 40 provides the most challenging content in the game.<br/><br/>A player will need to beat an Order level once in order to progress to the next Order level. A player will have 3 attempts to beat a Havoc Order level before being demoted down one Order level.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">2. Personalised and Dynamic Havoc Orders</div><br/>While the modifiers are pre-defined for each Havoc Order, the mission and mutators applied to each order level will be unique and randomized for each player. This means Order Level 1 for one player will not look the same as a level 1 Order for another player.<br/><br/>If a player fails to complete the Havoc Order after an attempt, the player can continue to attempt the same unique mission and mutator combination. However, the enemies and spawns will appear in different places throughout the mission, which brings a level of variety and unpredictability so no two runs are the same.<br/><br/>As mentioned above, players will have 3 attempts per Order Level before being demoted one level.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">3. Fluid Ranking System</div><br/>Havoc will update a player’s Order Rank on a weekly basis. If a player was unable to complete their Havoc Order before Havoc is updated for the week, they’ll remain at the same Havoc Order. But they’ll have a different mission and mutator combo to attempt.<br/><br/>If a player does not succeed in progressing forward in any Order Levels during the week, they will be decayed 1 Havoc Order the following week.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">4. Cooperative Gameplay</div><br/>Players are not alone in their journey. Havoc encourages inviting friends to help progress through the Havoc Ranks together. While using the Party Finder to form a team, players will choose which friends’ Havoc Order to challenge together. The only requirement is to be at least level 30. If players form a group, it doesn’t matter if one friend is Havoc Rank 1 and the others are Havoc Rank 20. They can all play together.<br/><br/>For example’s sake, let’s say we had a group of four players: Player A (Havoc Rank 20), Player B (Havoc Rank 19), Player C (Havoc Rank 19), Player D (Havoc Rank 1).<br/><br/>If those players formed a group and successfully beat Player A’s specific Havoc Order 21, at the end of the mission, all of the players will have a new Havoc Rank of 21. However, those players’ Havoc Order (aka the personal mission currently available to them in Havoc) will not change until the following week.<br/><br/>The following week, all players will be Havoc Rank 21 and they’ll have a Havoc Order level 22 to complete.<br/><br/>Players will always be promoted the following week based on their highest completed Havoc Order level the week prior. In this example, even though Player D started at Havoc Order 1, they are brought up to Havoc Rank 21 since this is the highest difficulty they completed the previous week .<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">5. Party Finder Integration</div><br/>One of the reasons we wanted to introduce the Party Finder was specifically for Havoc. Because the difficulty is so high, it wouldn’t work to simply Quick Play into a Havoc mission. Because of the varying combinations of mutators and missions, and the increasing difficulty, players will want to prepare their talents and weapons based on the challenge they’re facing. Using Quick Play would not allow players to properly prepare for the challenge.<br/><br/>There will be a separate section in the Party Finder for players to create and join Havoc parties. You can create a party based on your own Havoc Order or join others. If friends are forming a party together, they’ll need to choose which player’s Havoc Order they’d like to attempt together.<br/><br/>Again, anyone can join any party regardless of their own Havoc Rank or the current level of their Havoc Order, so long as they’re Trust Level 30.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Missions, Mutators and Conditions</div>When Havoc is launched, it’ll have 8 missions in the mission pool. These were chosen based on a few criteria, like zone, mission type, win rate in upper difficulties, etc. Operations (like Rolling Steel) are not planned to be a part of this rotating mission pool at this time, due to them being different in nature to our other missions.<br/><br/>Havoc will introduce 4 bespoke mutators which players will only find in Havoc. Havoc Order levels will be able to have up to 2 mutators active at one time. The community has already encountered one of these during the latest event: the Infected 21st Moebians. We think you’ll enjoy the other ones we have planned. We’re going to keep them as a surprise for now and share them closer to release.<br/><br/>Conditions will also be a part of the mix for possible Order levels for players to tackle. However, not every Order level will include a condition. It’ll be more spread out, with a condition being present ~5 Order levels. This includes Lights Out, Ventilation Purge and Tox Gas. (Note: Ogryns soon will no longer be suffering from the dark.)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Future Content and Updates</div>In the future, we’ll rotate the missions that are available for Havoc. Also, any time a new mission is added in an update, it will enter the mission pool. (As mentioned above, Operations are not planned to be a part of this rotation.)<br/><br/>We also plan to add more mutators over time for Havoc. So let us know if you have any ideas that you’d like to see in the future.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Rewards for the Brave</div>You might be wondering, how will players be rewarded? Players will receive materials and Mastery XP. There will also be a cache based on your weekly progress within Havoc, where players can earn extra Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/>Beyond materials, there will also be frames, titles and insignia to be earned throughout the Penance system. We’ll also be adding an all black Moebian 53rd cosmetic set, which will be earnable through playing. (Note: Players will not need to get to Order Rank 40 to earn this cosmetic set, don’t worry.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Ready to Face the Tide?</div>Alright, that’s a wrap on the Introduction to Havoc. We’re working hard on testing and putting together the final touches for this upcoming game mode. Once we’re ready, we’ll be able to share a release date.<br/><br/>Similar to our Introduction to Itemization, we’ll be following this up with a Q&amp;A dev blog to answer any player questions we see! Please stay tuned and join the conversation.<br/><br/>Thank you for your support.<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 17:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on 6.0 Design &amp; Audio - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4487367194477330698</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hey folks!<br/><br/>Back in June we put out our first "What's Next?" video, where you heard some of the WARHAMMER III development team to reveal the first details about our next DLC. You guys seemed to like it, so we went and did another one, and invited Mitch along to talk about our interim patches too. You also seemed to like this, so the question is; are you in the mood to hear even more about the next DLC and update 6.0? <br/><br/>No? Oh okay, fair enough, guess we'll sign off now then...<br/><br/>But wait... if you DID happen to be interested, then you'll be happy to know we have another video for you! This time we are joined once more by a familiar face, Senior Game Director Rich Aldridge, for an update on development, along with Designer Josh King and Project Audio Director Chris Goldsmith, to dive a little deeper into their respective disciplines and what they've been working on for this upcoming DLC and update 6.0. (We're even in a snazzy new studio!)<br/><br/>Come for the DLC news, stay for the gross sound effects and shouty voices...<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jonQ2jNsVos?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>We have a lot more goodness coming your way towards the end of the month, including the first official DLC trailer, some tasty blog content, and a deeper look at the new Legendary Lords in their respective gameplay showcases. We'll also have some giveaways kicking off over on Discord where you'll have multiple chances of winning codes for the DLC on launch!<br/><br/>If you want to keep up to date with all of this, then be sure to join the official Total War Discord server and follow our social channels linked at the bottom of this blog.<br/><br/>Until next time, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— <i>Steve Coleman (KingGobbo) // Senior Community Manager</i><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #52 (1.5.10) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4476108195413098948</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f1202d0d0337e924f373a218d2dcf6a92b601668.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heya Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: The Grandfather’s Gifts</div>The Lord of Decay has blessed his most beloved followers with hideous tentacles. So imbued are they with his foul pestilence that they explode when shot.<br/><br/>Dispatch them at close quarters to avoid this.<br/><br/><b>Complete missions featuring the blessed enemies to progress and collect rewards.</b> This condition will only be available during the event and it will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals. Look out for missions with the “Mutated Horrors” condition.<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, November 7, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a new Portrait Frame. (<b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Be aware the frame might not show up immediately in players’ inventories after receiving the notification. Players may need to re-log, or at least leave and re-enter the Mourningstar.</i>)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/550190a3d4d84a5cbf154d0f9f8777ebbf41c08c.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/919347318793f380732186d8401324039b7b12cc.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bug Fixes and Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Social menu could fail to correctly display the status of other players and also block invitations/join requests.<br/></li><li> Fixed memory leak crashes which could happen when inspecting weapon stats.<br/></li><li> Fixed issues where the max potential for weapon stats could change when empowering a weapon.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Weapon level calculation is now handled in a more reliable manner. Some weapons that had their total stats below 380 at max Empower level will now be at 1 level below max (490 instead of 500) - meaning players will need to go to Hadron’s and empower from 490 to 500.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where FSR 3.1 Frame Gen would appear as disabled when playing excessive fullscreen effects, using lens distortion or showing certain GUI elements (e.g. the screen effect when a Stimms buff is active).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Nvidia DSR/DLDSR would not work in fullscreen display mode.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where weapon penances were unlocked in the Mourningstar and claimed, but were not shown as completed.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the game would sometimes render only in a corner of the screen while in fullscreen display mode but on lower resolution than the monitor.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Windows chime sounds could play when using Alt+Tab to switch between fullscreen and windowed display modes.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the “activated” status of weapon Special actions could be canceled by getting stunned. <i>Partial Fix. (We've received some reports that this fix does not apply properly to the Power Sword or Thunder Hammer. We're investigating this. Thank you!)</i><br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description text for the Armourbane blessing would display incorrectly for Tiers 3 and 4.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some sound effects (e.g. reload sounds) would be played predominantly only on one side.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <span class="bb_strike">Fsr 3.1 Frame Generation Does Not Do Anything During Excessive Fullscreen Effects</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Penances Shown As Not Completed</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <b> Purging Flames Penance is Bugged</b><br/></li><li> <b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
