<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #61 (1.6.8) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/498313608291156600</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/53c700fb2a8a9e21b0cad7edf2c6e6bb2c962c6b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><div class="bb_h2">Return of the Infected Moebian 21st - LIVE EVENT</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/df09123cbd01b20c9924c0148f51a5f9eca3fa5e.jpg"/><br/><br/><i>A platoon of Moebian 21st soldiers has been infected by the Blight. Their armour will make them harder to deal with than the usual hordes you encounter. <br/><br/>We thought we'd stopped this mess after that trouble at the cathedral. Well, you know what to do.<br/><br/>Play missions with a set of Special Conditions, “Infected Moebian 21st”, and as a team collect Grimoires or Scriptures to earn rewards.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> This condition will only be available during the event and will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals.<br/></li><li> Similar to past events, the progress will be shared across all members of the strike team. </li></ul><b> This event will start on Thursday, February 20, 2025.</b> The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><b>Hotfix #61 (1.6.8)</b> is currently rolling out and it’ll be available for everyone across our platforms today. You’ll find the notes below.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hong Kong server region now generally available.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue which caused the Empower weapon crafting operation to occasionally give results that didn’t match the preview.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash which could happen when loading into the Excise Vault Spireside-13 mission. </li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i> Excise Vault Spireside-13 will return to the mission board on Thursday, February 20.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> General crash fixes and stability improvement for console. <br/></li><li> Fixed a clipping issue on the back plate of the “Truskan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)” Veteran cosmetic upperbody.  <br/></li><li> Changed the name of the “Combat Axe (Saint’s Fluke)” weapon skin cosmetic in order for it to more accurately reflect the weapon family it’s compatible with.  </li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/689716592460694095</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/6f32d0409588551b00734755244860ba9f149b97.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/><b>Hotfix 6.0.5</b> has just dropped for Total War: WARHAMMER III, bringing with it a suite of improvements and fixes. Here are some highlights:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Azhag now has access to his missing spells ‘Spirit Leech’ and ‘Aspect of the Dreadknight’<br/></li><li> AI with multiple reinforcements are now less idle in battle, attacking the player rather than waiting for all reinforcements to arrive<br/></li><li> Camera movement is faster and more responsive on the Campaign map (particularly noticeable in late-game scenarios)</li></ul>If you're currently opted-in to the Campaign AI Beta branch on Steam, these changes will arrive tomorrow (19/02) so that you can take advantage of the improvements alongside the Campaign AI changes included in the Beta.<br/><br/>Now let’s jump into the full list…<br/><br/><hr/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a rare VFX-related crash that occurred during battle. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">General/Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Nurgle factions did not receive Infection rewards when sacking or razing a settlement. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Blood Pilgrimage mission was completed when recruiting any unit, instead of only the specified ones.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">Skill Tree</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Azhag didn’t start with access to Spirit Leech and Aspect of the Dreadknight.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enhanced performance when moving the camera on the campaign map, particularly noticeable in late-game scenarios when most of the shroud is uncovered. This improvement ensures smoother and more responsive camera movement, providing a better user experience. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the 'Undo assigned skill points' button remained clickable in the Character Details panel when switching to the Details tab. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the 'Collect income' checkbox in the UI was not displayed properly. <br/></li><li> Stuttering when rapidly hovering over different unit cards in the Campaign and Battle UI should now be reduced.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General/Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where, when repositioning ranged units in a different direction, they clumped together and got stuck. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue causing The Forbidden Fens vegetation VFX to appear red.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">AI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the attacking AI remained stationary for too long during battles with multiple reinforcements, waiting for all of them to arrive instead of attacking the player. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Animations</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Adjusted the maximum number of splash attack victims the Terracotta Sentinel can hit with its attacks.  <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Terracotta Sentinel’s weapon visibly snaps while transitioning between animations. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Ushabti Great Bows would not show the proper equip/unequip animation when switching between ‘turn’ and ‘melee attack’ animations. <br/></li><li> Bonebreaker and Terrorgeist mounts now use their matched combat animations against Cathayan units. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug in Skirmish mode where the AI stats modifier would reset as the player navigated away from the relevant menu.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug that occurred in a multiplayer game with Golgfag, where the Mercenary Contracts mechanic stops working after Save/Load. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">AUDIO</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added missing audio to water features on the Greed Grove battle map and to some corruption pools on the campaign map. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the SFX of the floating pyramid during the Black Pyramid end-game scenario sounded low quality. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with environmental audio on the Thundering Falls subterranean battle map. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the SFX for sinking ships would include human voices for non-human factions.</li></ul> <br/><hr/><br/><br/>If you run into any new issues or bugs after updating to 6.0.5, please be sure to raise them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum so our wonderful QA teams can investigate.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III is 3 Years Old!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/689716592460693628</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Total War: WARHAMMER III is 3 years old today! Thank you to all of you who have been a part of this journey so far, whether you joined on day 1 or day 1095! 🎉<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/49FQJ0pOL_Q?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.2.8 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/796677083608645727</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Update 1.3.2.8 is live, solving the issues with Marazhai’s romance, bringing you fixes for a number of desync issues, localization fixes, and adding Turkish localization on consoles and for Void Shadows DLC.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch notes:</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">System and stability</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Some cutscenes could freeze the game when skipped - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Narrative</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Abel sometimes did not join the Lord Captain in the Let the Cycle Be Discontinued Pasqal’s quest, which could break multiple cutscenes;<br/></li><li> Restored a few missing options in Marazhai’s romance dialogues that mysteriously disappeared after patch 1.3, preventing one of the endings from being reached; </li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mechanics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the description for Bounty Hunter’s Hot on the Trail ability to be consistent with the actual bonus;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Thought Guide’s Will bonus is now correctly reflected in its description;<br/></li><li> Blooddrinking Staff’s Will bonus is now correctly reflected in its description;<br/></li><li> Astartes Chainsword’s description no longer duplicates itself;<br/></li><li> Noble Sword had an incorrect description that didn’t match its actual stats - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Locations</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the hitbox of Occluding Sphere at the Inquisition Shipwreck, which could cause pathing issues;<br/></li><li> Fixed a broken cutscene at Santiel’s pride;<br/></li><li> Fixed a few unreachable overtips at Santiel’s pride;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Co-op</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a number of desyncs caused by Bring it Down ability;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of desyncs caused by Vanguard abilities;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Audio</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Improved sound effects and music in multiple cutscenes;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Localization</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Turkish localization is now available on consoles;<br/></li><li> Void Shadows DLC is now also available in Turkish;<br/></li><li> Fixed font issues with some special characters for multiple languages including Turkish;<br/></li><li> A lot of minor localization fixes in all languages: typos, formatting, incorrect tags, “[draft]” text, term inconsistencies etc.;<br/></li><li> Fixed a lot of missing and incorrect glossary links;<br/></li><li> Some Eurac-V item descriptions didn’t have any translation other than English and Russian - fixed;<br/></li><li> Champion of the Abyss buff had an incorrect description in Russian - fixed;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 10:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/621036612100292637</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hello Space Marines,<br/><br/>We deployed a hotfix on Space Marine 2 that fixes issues that appeared with the 6.0 update, mainly connectivity issues, but also adding the Salamander emblem on the right shoulder pad.<br/><br/>If you encounter issues with this update, let us know by making a bug report here.<br/><br/>You'll find the complete patch notes down below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several crashes<br/></li><li> Fixed various connectivity issues <br/></li><li> Fixed issue with Biovore spawned mines being unkillable in a rare case <br/></li><li> Fixed issue with modded games being locked to offline mode <br/></li><li> Fixed Unyielding Ceramite perk deleting armour gained from Armour Boost <br/></li><li> Fixed Volkite VFX not playing correctly on Biovore <br/></li><li> Fixed music getting stuck in PvP matches <br/></li><li> Added missing Salamanders emblem on right shoulder pad <br/></li><li> Minor localization fixes</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
