<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Communication Breakdown!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520837698904129739</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/50a49917f42f1c39ca7b94d4cc715f943940b6c9.png"/><br/><br/>The Traitorous 6th have disrupted Hive communications with tainted technology.<br/><br/>You must root out these tech-heresies and restore regular Hive communications.<br/><br/><b>To make progress in the event, find Tainted Communications Devices and complete the hacking sequence. Then, finish the mission. Each device will grant you 1 point of progress.</b><br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, April 24. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/66c55cabc88b396f591efc095d3fb644716c0d8f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500571481680379989</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!⚔️</div><br/>A Hotfix has just been released on Space Marine 2. Its main focus is to solve the <b>connectivity issues</b> that are occurring since the release of the 7.0 update last week. We’ll keep working on <b>improving the connectivity over the upcoming days</b>. Let us know if you see improvements with this hotfix, or if you still encounter issues.<br/>On another note, this patch also brings <b>small balancing changes</b> to some weapons, weapon perks, and class perks.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>PATCH NOTES 7.1</b></div><b> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Fixed several crashes.<br/></li><li> Fixed several connectivity issues.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that locked Assault's Relic Regalia as a Prestige 4 reward.</li></ul></b><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Power Sword</b></u></li></ul>Power Rake and Power Whirl damage greatly increased.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Neo-Volkite</u></b></li></ul>Volkite Discharge damage increased by 12.5%.<br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Weapon Perks</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Plasma Incinerator</b></u></li></ul><b>"Perpetual Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Fast Venting"<br/><b>"Adamant Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with “Plasma Collection"<br/><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Common Speed"<br/><b>"Charged Cooling"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Adamant Restoration"<br/><b>"Common Speed 1"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Fast Venting"<br/><b>"Common Speed 2"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Common Cooling"<br/><b>"Perpetual Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Honed Precision"<br/><b>"Fast Venting"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Blast Radius"<br/><b>"Plasma Collection"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Efficient Charge"<br/><b>"Adamant Restoration"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Charged Speed"<br/><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Adamant Velocity"<br/><b>"Charged Speed 1"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Perpetual Velocity"<br/><b>"Charged Speed 2"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Great Might"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Heavy Plasma Incinerator</b></u></li></ul><b>"Elusive Fire"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Brutal Rampage"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Plasma Pistol</u></b></li></ul><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: Switched position in the skill tree with "Efficient Charge"<br/><b>"Efficient Charge"</b>: Switched position in the skill tree with "Blast Radius"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Power Sword</u></b></li></ul><b>"Reeling Blow"</b>: effect increased from 30% to 40%. Duration increased from 4 to 8 seconds. Cooldown increased from 10 to 15 seconds. <br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Perks</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Vanguard Prestige Perk</b></u></li></ul> <b>“Exigency Charge”</b>: Fixed an issue preventing the bonus from activating properly. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Sniper Prestige Perk </b></u></li></ul><b>“Versatile Precision”</b>: Fixed a bug that caused this perk cooldown to be more than 15 seconds<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Heavy Prestige Perk</b></u></li></ul><b>“Auxiliary Reload”</b>: Now properly triggers when killing an Extremis (or higher) enemy.<br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Global Perks QoL</div></b> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All perks that are triggered from perfect parry will now trigger from perfect block as well (even if description doesn’t mention that).<br/><br/></li><li> All perks (class, weapons, prestige) that are triggered by “killing 10 enemies in a rapid succession” changed to “killing 7 enemies in a rapid succession”. Time window between kill to keep the kill streak going is increased from 5 to 6 seconds.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your brief for the April Community Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500570844611739691</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Listen up, Space Marines!</div><br/>Get ready for the new Community Event on Space Marine 2! 🤩<br/> <br/>This time, your mission consists in collectively bringing down 200,000 Trygons to obtain the <b>Mark X Tacticus breastplate</b>. This is the perfect moment to rally and engage side by side in battle.<br/><br/>If you are victorious, this is the prize you'll receive:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f56e27b6ccd91e004e2a8c8bd6da8b0b4d7ddc9.png"/><br/> <br/>The event starts on April 17 and runs until the 27. <br/>It requires a connection to PROS.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e785444e0b43efd977b239ec3397a01a19878e95.png"/><br/><br/>Onward, Space Marines!<br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects. ⭐ </div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 10:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #66 (1.7.4) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520837042930712619</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div> <br/>Hotfix #66 (1.7.4) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>General Fixes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where players could fail to dodge-slide when using weapons with quick but short dodges.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the UI was showing Ogryn emotes with a New marker, but no new emotes were available.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the 'Precognition' Blessing for Duelling Swords and Combat Blades incorrectly showed a duration of 5s instead of 2s.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that could happen at the end of the Vigil Station Oblivium mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Changes &amp; Fixes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where players could join other’s Havoc Assignments while they are still locked in to their own Assignment.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a Havoc mission vote expiring could lead to the initiator being locked in to their Assignment.<br/></li><li> Fixed occasional spurious demotion when cancelling the ongoing Havoc Assignment.<br/></li><li> Fixed end-of-round view displaying a loss after winning a Havoc level 40 Assignment.<br/></li><li> Group Finder request-to-join list will no longer scroll back to top upon getting new requests.<br/></li><li> Increased Horde Strike type “Blockade Sandwich” trigger distance from 20 to 50.<br/></li><li> Dev Note: This strike may happen if the Strike Team tries to backtrack too far.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Campaign - Mission Pool and Mutator Rotation </b></div>Every third week during a Havoc Campaign, we are rotating the mission pool and mutator pool. One or two missions and mutators will swap out during this time. Some may have noticed this already happened this week!<br/><br/><b>Mission Pool</b><br/><i>Outgoing</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Clandestium Gloriana<br/></i></li><li> Dark Communion</li></ul>[/i][/list]<br/><i>Incoming</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Excise Vault Spireside-13<br/></i></li><li> Consignment Yard HL 17-36</li></ul>[/i][/list]<br/><b>Mutators</b><br/><i>Outgoing</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>None.</i></li></ul><i>Incoming</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Moebian 21st</i></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Derank Changes</b></div>The Derank changes to Havoc that we shared in our dev blog earlier this month are going live with this hotfix. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A player of a higher Assignment Rank will not lose a charge upon being a participant in a lower ranked mission that failed.<br/></li><li> Assignment Rank 40 players will not be able to lose a charge through gameplay means at all.<br/></li><li> For those at Assignment Rank 40, they do not stand to gain anything by attempting their assignment again. Therefore, we’ve made it so they can continue to try different builds and challenges to keep it interesting.</li></ul><br/>We had some questions about how Assignment Rank 40 players may change their Assignment:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Play it and win;<br/></li><li> Wait for the weekly reset;<br/></li><li> Play with another Assignment Rank 40 player and beat it;<br/></li><li> Manually derank to Assignment Rank 39, beat it (within 3 charges), get a new assignment. </li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Mortis Trials Fixes &amp; Tweaks</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where players would not get their Indulgences pool initialized, which would make it impossible for them to get Indulgence buff choices after the waves 3, 6 and 9. <br/></li><li> Dev Note: This happened to players that were part of the starting Strike Team but spawned later than the rest due to slow loading.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the server region option was not taken into account when matchmaking for Mortis Trials.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Cosmetic Fixes</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where gaps would appear between the torso and arms while wearing the Psyker “Blind Witch’s Leash Raiment” upperbody cosmetic.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with floating ornaments on the “ ”Plan A” Vostroyan Rippergun “ weapon skin.<br/></li><li> Fixed the ability for blood effects to tint the entire body of the “ ”Last Stand” Vostroyan Lasgun “ weapon skin red when using the bayonet attack.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Havoc Known Issue - Visual Only </b></div>After losing a mission, rejects with a higher Havoc rank helping out rejects with a lower Havoc rank may encounter an animation showing them losing a charge, even though they didn’t. This is purely a visual (animated?) issue. <br/><br/><i>(E.g. player A is rank 30 with 1 charge left and tries to help player B with their rank 10 assignment. After losing, player A gets an animation showing them go from 2 charges to 1. In reality they had 1 charge before the mission, and will still have 1 charge when they get back to the Havoc menu.)</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trygon Update is out!!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500569576639038653</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Brothers and Sisters,</div><br/>It's HERE! The <b>Trygon Update</b> is out!! 🎉<br/><br/>Both Free and Season Pass content is being added to the game, check the trailer for a quick rundown of the new content.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7oAHVCnAXxY?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">👇 Let's see what's new</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">New PvE Mission "Exfiltration" and Trygon boss</div><br/><b>A new PvE mission is available!</b><br/><br/>The Tech-Priest occupying an Adeptus Mechanicus facility on Avarax has refused a withdrawal order. Captain Acheran has authorised Magos Galeo to assist in retrieving her.<br/><br/>Your objective is to reach the Adeptus Mechanicus Facility and assess the status of the Tech-Priest.<br/><br/>Beware of the new Terminus Enemy. It bursts from the ground to unleash devastating assaults with its <br/>scything claws and bio-electric attacks.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c2364b35ee62f3edc854c73b083bad72aa1ad2bb.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/60c6580d8d46bec867e7a665facec922ac347de3.png"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h2">The Inferno Pistol</div><br/>The Inferno Pistol is added both in PvE and PvP. <br/>It's a close-range thermal weapon, available for Assault, Vanguard, Sniper and Heavy.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d94e499da6cb7038dbdcdb8e2d70e20ce20ea561.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Two new skins &amp; DLC Cosmetics</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">🐺 The Space Wolves Chapter Pack</div><br/>Which includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Space Wolves Chapter Champion (Vanguard)<br/></li><li> Space Wolves Chapter Weapon Skins (Bolt Carbine, Chainsword and Thunder Hammer)<br/></li><li> Space Wolves Great Companies Cosmetics (Armour, Heraldry, Company Markings)<br/></li><li> Along with cosmetics for the 12 Great Companies.</li></ul><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a23bd933bf6de3953f589ab4321607a22b467a93.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b7292fb19932826f77217c6dc365825a02fe1bf1.png"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2c67ef5d488f9628dd9249d676cf1ceea17be5f7.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6c21fdc88eddf684fe0a0c9a65132520135551f3.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d0028a3208d331da60e019192ada80f7cbe64cb4.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h3">✊ The Imperial Fists Champion Pack</div><br/>This Champion Pack comes with the Tactical Champion and a Plasma Incinerator skin.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/33468439454839669c5da543c35d6b18cb3eca9c.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2c8969784800b7ffa78b3ef43524fd18c813476b.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h2">New customisation options</div><br/>New paints are available in the Armouring Hall: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Volupus Pink<br/></li><li> Thousand Sons Blue</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/feb63254040ed3438e8c9d07ed3ceb07bca22e48.jpg"/><br/>New elements of customisation are available too such as: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cloth colouring for Bulwark (17 options)<br/></li><li> Hands colouring</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9a5bf7111a7f36c7cc3feddb7243a76cb3296029.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">⚙️ System and balancings</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Prestige Ranks are unlockable in PvE<br/></li><li> PvP now has private lobbies: A custom lobby to invite your fellow Brothers. You can choose the mode and map, and also change the gameplay settings, like score or time limit or even damage modifiers to create your own fun game modes.<br/></li><li> Weapons class restrictions have changed: classes have now access to more weapons<br/></li><li> Bolt weapons buffs<br/></li><li> Weapon Perks update: The Weapon Perks update will not reset each weapon's skill tree. Therefore, you are free to revisit your current weapon perks and reassign your Mastery Point to your convenience, since some perks have changed or have been replaced.<br/></li><li> General Fixes<br/></li><li> And more: for a detailed rundown of the changelog, please check this page. </li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Join us on our platforms! 💬</div>Don't forget to join fellow Space Marines on Discord, or on Focus Together, where players are invited to chat in the forum and drop ideas they have for the game, for the devs to see!<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
