<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 15 - Shokkjump Dragsta 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4603329177923390701</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c9b5eed82519a346c625356f4f595f3a715b2abf.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bb0ae6c76572ad17dddabf99c588693f7c167276.png"/><br/><br/>The Shokkjump Dragsta puts the word Speed into Speed Freeks. It’s a lightning-fast marvel born from Ork innovation. It can punch a warp tunnel through reality, to quickly cross the battlefield, leaving chaos and destruction in its wake.<br/><br/>In Speed Freeks, the Shokkjump Dragsta uses its speed to convince the enemy that it’s everywhere on the battlefield all at once. That, combined with its range, makes it a menace that will always find a way to get a shot in on you. There’s no escape.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/77df52c06c9393d7e41d96e4808649148a26cbb4.png"/><br/>With the the Shokkjump Dragsta, you are fast, and so you can be anywhere you choose. The most important part of playing this vehicle is keeping an open eye for opportunities and using your speed to be where you’re needed. Whether it’s flying to the front lines and helping take out key targets or going back to help your own allies stay alive.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1802e7f25de932e3d2285ded3dcc33a9ffb4bcbf.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><b>Shokk Rifle -</b> The Shokk Rifle delivers accurate, long-range damage thanks to its targeting Squig.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cd5e461a26cfac01250d4cc63ee0db62b9435bdc.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><b>Rokkit Launcha -</b> Fire a burst of explosive Rokkits at the targeted vehicle.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/522c88d555a5ec297bcab5b0806d9a775b25ae5e.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><b>Shokk Tunnel -</b> The Shokkjump Dragsta zooms forward, shrouded by its shokk technology and temporarily invisible to other players.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/10f81d44f5ff8313ee330da0d2389ace04f7e7fa.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><b>Dash -</b> The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming at determines where the vehicle will go.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/27efc4db2f9d3ad7a446fd677a490fa47095699c.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Keeping up your speed is important as the Shokkjump Dragsta, make sure to alternate between using your boost, Shokk Tunnel and Dash to keep the speed up. Your Rokkit Launcha fires homing missiles and can reach people who hide behind corners.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/82dc50357e247821ef99b629fa8b3e018a0a731f.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-Ups</div> <b>Deffkilla Wartrike –</b> Using the range of your Shokk Rifle you can help soften up enemies while your friendly Deffkilla Wartrike goes in for the kill. Sometimes, they will survive with very low health and using your speed there’s no way they can escape.<br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon –</b> Keep an eye on who your Looted Wagon is shooting at. When they get an enemy low on health, they’ll drive away to hide. Using your speed and range you can pick of targets as they try to recover.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c0616ad3070d44f66ccc656e58bc979f7b1482be.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against </div><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon –</b> With the low mobility of the Boomdakka Snazzwagon you can use your speed to get behind them and decide when to fight them and when to get away. It will not be fast enough to chase you, nor the range to hit you.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weak Against </div><br/><b>Deffkilla Wartrike –</b> Be careful of the Deffkilla Wartrike as they can use its Hook to keep up with you or bring you to a stop. As you cannot shoot backwards, having a Deffkilla Wartrike chasing you down can prove fatal without support. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c322f0610c70559ada8b5083dd79ff56d259c764.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn more about the Warhammer 40,000 lore with Titus himself!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4605582245626207826</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!!</div><br/>The grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000 can be daunting to dive into! This is why we're are thrilled to introduce the first episode of the “Titus Talks” a 3-part video series presented by Lieutenant Titus himself, Clive Standen, and dedicated to welcoming newcomers to the rich expanse that is the 41st millennium. ✨<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Watch Episode 1: What is Warhammer 40,000?</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jfuTX-Fz44M?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">Today’s first episode focuses on introducing players to the Warhammer 40,000 universe.</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Who is this Emperor? <br/></li><li> What are the forces at play? <br/></li><li> Who are the Space Marines, and why is this galaxy in a state of constant war? </li></ul>Presented by Clive Standen, who voices Lieutenant Titus in the game, today’s video lecture serves as an introduction to a multi-part series. <br/><br/>An upcoming part two will come later, dedicated to presenting who and what the Space Marines are.<br/>Then, the third and final video will discuss what it all means in the grand setting of the game itself.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3bfb23b45e2559b47c744c9fdf769181b4a8f644.jpg"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available now on PC. Get the Gold or Ultra Editions to secure your Season Pass!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4601078645996370015</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/7217db716931d913bb0af4892e4a858bbeed9dfc.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/> <br/>We're back with a small but important update for Total War: WARHAMMER III. Today, we're rolling out Hotfix 5.2.4 to address a specific issue that has been affecting some of you during your Warriors of Chaos campaigns.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolves a crash to desktop (CTD) that could occur when pressing the 'Choose Path' button in the 'Path to Glory' panel.</li></ul>We know how frustrating crashes can be, especially when you're deep into the chaos of battle, and we appreciate your patience while we worked to get this fix out to you.<br/> <br/>Additionally, we want to provide some clarity regarding a note from Hotfix 5.2.3: "The AI-controlled Lord will no longer withdraw when ambushed if it has a good chance of winning." The change is not specific to Lords. The correct information is that the battle AI will not withdraw when ambushed if its army has at least 75% of the attacker's army strength. Army strength is calculated by the sum of its units' strength. While this unit strength value is not visible to players, it is a key factor in AI decision-making, greatly enhancing its battle strategies in many situations.<br/> <br/>We are also aware of a separate issue, not addressed in this fix, where an army may retreat in battle after already retreating earlier in the same turn, causing the entire army to be wiped out. We are actively investigating this and appreciate your reports and feedback on the matter.<br/> <br/>As always, thank you for your continued support and feedback—it helps us keep improving the game. If you run into any new issues after updating to 5.2.4, please report them in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/> <br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from a Rogue Trader's journey through the Koronus Expanse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4594323246557001114</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captain! <br/><br/>It's been over eight months since the game released. During this time, we've turned to you more than once for advice on how to make your journey more comfortable. The post-release survey was one such occasion. An astounding 15241 people took part in it, which, according to our esteemed Lexmechanics' calculations, took them a collective total of 335302 minutes to complete. <br/><br/>We immensely appreciate the effort you're putting into further improving the game. Based on the survey results, we've already fixed numerous “sore spots” such as the behaviour of the cargo interface in the game's third act, or the miscalculated difficulty levels in skill checks. As a thank you for the work you've done, we're going to share the most interesting community perspectives that were reflected in the survey results. <br/><br/>With a passion for all things precise, as is typical of any servant of the Omnissiah, our Lexmechanics have drawn up a report for you that is rich in intriguing correlations and captivating data tables:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Introductory Notes</div><br/>Worth mentioning first is the fact that by four months after release, more than half of all survey participants had clocked over a hundred hours in the game. That might’ve been surprising if the player base didn't consist overwhelmingly of CRPG fans. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/71c032bea871693540e4ab12f0930349d2586f20.png"/><br/>We knew that releasing a game in the Warhammer 40,000 universe meant submitting it to the scrutiny of demanding critics. A mere 7% had no or only cursory experience with the setting. We enjoy assuming the role of guides on the journey to the dark future, and we are proud to say that players trust us with the job: a whopping 96% of captains had their expectations of the setting's atmosphere met, to the incredible delight of the Warhammer fans among the game's creators. But enough bragging! On to the more fascinating facts, as well as some disconcerting ones.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Interface</div><br/>Regardless of whether a Rogue Trader was a Dogmatic or followed one of the Radical paths, all of them equally disliked loot-related hassles, be it their ship's cargo management or their party's inventory. The organising, the sorting, the tedium of managing a huge number of items, and especially the situations where stolen loot would, upon recovery, return to a bag instead of where it had previously belonged, were things that frustrated our players a great deal. We've fixed some of those problems and are still working on others. <br/><br/>It's worth noting that while most Rogue Traders were torn between Puritanism and Radicalism, 89 among them preferred to altogether skip delving into the value system.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Ground Combat</div><br/>While picking through loot was a mostly unrewarding experience, obtaining it was quite another matter. On average, players gave the ground-combat system 4.3 points out of five, which surpassed the Beta rating for this metric. <br/><br/>57% of participants thought the Lord Captain had been through just the right number of ordeals. Among the rest, opinions were split between those who'd prefer more ordeals and those who envisioned a more peaceful life for the protagonist. Luckily for the Rogue Trader, the well-wishers outnumbered the daredevils nearly two-to-one.<br/><br/>We'd always known that Warrants of Trade were granted only to Humanity's bravest. But this time, they showed themselves to be quite deft as well. Players who opted to skip the character-build part and go straight for the Story mode were satisfied with the challenges they faced. For their part, those who started the game on a higher difficulty level would’ve preferred to challenge yet fiercer foes than the ones they actually encountered. Indeed, the higher the difficulty a player selected, the likelier they were to report a dearth of worthy opponents. Worry not! Our latest major update has made significant changes to the balance of archetypes. Perhaps now the Imperium's enemies will present a serious hurdle in your path.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/f3ec1fdcf4ffa719104351324244b5a755f0880b.png"/><br/>Speaking of archetypes, in the survey, we asked you lots of questions about your characters' combat abilities. These were the results: over 60% of survey participants got a taste of Exemplar, the third tier in a character's career. Other archetypes available earlier in the game saw yet greater use, with the top spots going to Soldier and Officer, which had some form of involvement in the Lord Captain's adventures in over 90% of cases.<br/>Soldier and Officer also topped the list of audience-favourite archetypes. Great Strategist came bottom of that list, their difficult-to-execute stratagems earning many an indignant comment.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/681fea00d72defa0a88da1ee8a2e31115c84892a.png"/><br/>Notably, the special abilities players deemed to be the most powerful (and perhaps overpowered) were Arch-Militant's Wildfire, Soldier's Rapid Fire, and Assassin's Death Whisper. Operative's Intimidation was deemed the weakest.<br/><br/>When it came to key mechanics, Officer shone once again with their ability to grant an extra turn to an ally. You liked both the mechanics and the spirit of this archetype's abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/85b6b3f5bb059a28fe0957e5b1bd02af3da7069c.png"/><br/><br/>However, there'd be no point in any of those skills without someone to use them on, now would there? Who among the Rogue Trader and their retinue's opponents emerged as the most popular one, and who as the most detested? Alas, these questions cannot be answered without spoilers. But if you've conquered the Koronus Expanse before, you could probably make a guess, and it would probably be correct.<br/><br/><span class="bb_spoiler"><span>We don't know what the exact reason was, between the earliness of the encounter, the pesky sniper on the roof, the untiring parries, and the endless attempts to preserve each of the three shuttles, but there's no doubt that Aurora, also known as the Chaos Space Marine, won the hearts of the largest number of Rogue Traders.</span></span><br/><br/><span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Edge of Daybreak and his gang were the next biggest favourite. Forgefiend closes the top three.</span></span><br/><br/>Interestingly, most of the negative combat experiences were caused by encounters that involved no bosses or named characters. Case in point, mid-flight battles.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Character Creation</div><br/>Creating and customising a character is a key aspect of any role-playing game. To make sure no Rogue Trader lacked in individually tailored options, we added over 500 talents to the game! Many players hinted that we might have tried too hard there... Thus 37% of participants would have liked the options to be fewer. The same percentage said the number of options matched their expectations. There were also those who didn't find enough variety, but the former two outnumbered these four to one.<br/><br/>As for the Rogue Trader's Origin, the majority's preference leaned firmly toward Sanctioned Psyker. Voidborn Psyker was therefore the most popular combination, ahead by almost a third of the runner-up, Imperial World Noble.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/6ad55f7d121aec523261ff8ed6a0b98cb4bbae5a.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Companions and NPCs</div><br/>We've asked you before to share your first impressions of the companions, and the poll results were quite unambiguous: Argenta led in every category! Although she's still a favourite, the Lord Captain has by now had the opportunity to form a more comprehensive picture of their retinue's other members.<br/><br/>This time around, we looked at the following criteria in our companions: interesting story, dialogue, and interactions; mechanical efficiency; best romance; and most attractive. Let's go through these in order.<br/><br/>The Rogue Trader's loyal Seneschal emerged as their most interesting companion. This choice surprised us and would probably surprise Abelard himself! He'd most likely be flattered too. <br/>Pasqal's <i>multifaceted</i> personality also got its fair share of attention.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/3c6d75ad410fe2cce9fb7bac414c333d6c38ea4c.png"/><br/>Owing to her unique origin, Cassia came first in combat efficiency.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/5f177bc2ecdb6fcae7831a9dcdf8041853b36e85.png"/><br/>Her heart-stealing efficiency put her in the lead as well. And keep this document far from the Inquisition's eyes, for Yrliet and Marazhai were a very close second and third. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/b90c1e04c86fcc5851336f0431b137a05cf187a5.png"/><br/>Naturally, these statistics would've been incomplete without Argenta taking at least one of the top spots. Her fervour in combat and her zealous smile won over many.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/5501ebd689509354ddc231cb7c73d2aece7bc73e.png"/><br/>Now what about those who can only be observed from the sidelines? We left this as a free-form question so that participants could name whatever non-player character they wanted as their favourite. After meticulously sifting through over 5,000 comments, we had the following top ten: a Koronus Expanse All Stars according to the heir of House von Valancius.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/dbe7791dd4dd34b337bdd73440d6c304f03b850c.png"/><br/>There's a high likelihood that the vote results might have been altered by an organisation we've been unable to trace. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Conclusion</div><br/>As the cogitators hum and the Lexmechanics rhythmically count off the figures, the time to part has crept unnoticed upon us. We truly hope you've found it interesting to see these survey results and to learn more about the way you play. We certainly have. Collecting and reading your responses for this article felt like discussing our favourite game with friends! We found it incredibly interesting to hear what aspects of the game you liked the most, where you spent the most time, and which moments delighted you the most. It was an interesting conversation with a lot of takeaways for us regarding the gameplay, your personal preferences, and ways we might improve the game.<br/><br/>As the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader team, we'd like to say a big thank you to each and every one of you. Your responses, opinions, and ideas are genuinely important to us as we, too, are passionate fans. Seeing your engagement and enthusiasm is what inspires us day to day as we work to bring this universe to life. <br/><br/>That's all for now, but more is on the way: we're already preparing new updates and content which we're sure you're going to like. Follow the news and brace yourselves for more thrilling adventures in the Koronus Expanse. Thanks for being with us, and see you soon, friends!<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - Hotfix 2.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4599952112536314026</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!</div><br/>A small hotfix has just been pushed on PC and consoles. Read the patch notes below for the details:<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><b>Crashes and bug fixes</b> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some rare possible crashes when starting the game<br/></li><li> Fixed a rare possible crash that occured during the first cutscene<br/></li><li> Fixed several other rare crashes<br/></li><li> Fixed several rare bugs that were causing soft locks in the story mode</li></ul><b>PC Only</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Optimized CPU behavior on high end CPUs</li></ul><br/>On top of that first quick fix, we're preparing a bigger patch for later in September. This patch will bring, among other things:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ultrawide support<br/></li><li> Private PvE lobbies<br/></li><li> Sparring Arena in the Battle Barge</li></ul>And more!<br/><br/>Thank you for your support.<br/><br/><b>The Emperor Protects.</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/77d9a5a41619ea98270373892a36817546f0002e.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
