<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hive Scum class - Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/618810005643067450</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>

<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" v-4khjxor00?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' width="850"></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1"></div><div class="bb_h1">Introducing New Class: Hive Scum</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum have finally crashed the party – Darktide’s second Class DLC.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/18a29fdd5e0d952ede7cbd118acdfd9fc1639a57.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Born and raised in Tertium, the Hive Scum are true criminals. The real deal. Each is a high ranking and lethal footsoldier in service to one of the cartels that run the city’s underbelly.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While most don’t have formal military training, a lifetime surviving on these streets have taught them all they need to know to be killing machines, using unconventional weapons, toxins and underhanded tactics. And while some might deem them untrustworthy, they’ve got plenty of reason to use those skills against the Heretics infesting Tertium.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hive Scum comes in hot with a ton of class features. As <b>experts at fast paced, frenzied gameplay</b>, they bring several new and unique things to the table for the forces of the Mourningstar. For the first time in Darktide, we will have <b>true dual-wielding, both in close combat with the twin shivs, and at range in the form of twin-wielded stub and autopistols</b>. But that is not all, as they also come with new makeshift weapons, like <b>crowbars and bonesaws</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There will also be plenty of options to create your unique Hive Scum; <b>new faces, tattoos, hairstyles</b> and even (for the first time) <b>face paints</b> that will let you customize them to your heart's content.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Stimm lab and Cartel Special</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum is more than just a pretty face. All those years in the hive have granted the scum enough chemical know-how to <b>brew their very own Stimms</b>. Upon reaching level 5, you will gain access to the Stimm Lab, a new <b>separate talent tree</b> that lets you customize your Cartel Special, a <b>personalized Stimm</b> for use in the field.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Spending points in the Stimm Lab will add buffs to your Cartel Special (of increasing effectiveness) that activate upon use during missions. Unlike other Stimms, the Cartel Special runs off a cooldown timer, meaning that you will be able to use it multiple times throughout the mission.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The amount of effects you can add is dependent on the Volume of your Stimm, which increases as you level up. As more and more powerful effects are crammed in, your cooldown will begin to climb. There will be a balance here to find for your particular build.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Cycling Stimm use regularly is a core part of playing Hive Scum, but if you prefer to play without it, emptying your Cartel Special will automatically unequip it, letting you use street Stimms in missions as per usual.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cooldown:</b> between 15 to 75 seconds, depending on points used.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/> </p><div class="bb_h2">Talent Tree</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As the scum of the hive, your playstyle is going to work a little bit different to what you might be used to. The Hive Scum is volatile and comparably squishy to its peers, but with great payoffs in damage, toxin spread and customisability. As usual, the talent tree can be viewed as three sections of a whole, shaping your troublemaker to your liking.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">There is a strong emphasis on movement, gap-closing and critical strikes all throughout the Hive Scum tree, but as we dive deeper into specialization we will also find prominent focus on close ranged firepower, relentless melee pummeling, damage-over-time zoning and supportive utility.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Let us go through the more impactful choices you can make in the tree.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Blitzes</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Blinder</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A light, quick-to-use grenade that staggers enemies. Useful for gap-closing or a quick get-away. Every 20th kill replenishes 1 charge. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Charges: 3. (The upgraded version, ‘Blackout’, increases the maximum amount you can carry to 5).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Boom Bringer</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A high power missile launcher that obliterates anything in its path. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Charges: 2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Chem Grenade</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thrown toxin containing grenade. The canister breaks open and the contents spill out across an area for a time when it explodes. Any enemies standing in the tox will gain up to 6 stacks of Chem Toxin, lose 50% of their Hit-mass and violently explode upon death. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Charges: 3.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Combat Abilities</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Desperado</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hive Scum has two Stance based Combat Abilities. The first one, ‘Desperado’, removes any Sprint Cost, grants +20% Sprint Speed, as well as making you immune to ranged attacks for 10 seconds. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, while Desperado is active, reloading your weapon does not reduce your ammo reserve, meaning that the ammo at hand when entering the ability will remain identical when it ends.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The upgraded version, ‘Enhanced Desperado’, also highlights enemies within Close Range (12.5 meters). Killing them will extend the duration of the ability by 1 second. At 20 seconds, the duration will begin to greatly diminish.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Cooldown: 45 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Rampage!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Enter ‘Rampage!’ for 10s. For the duration, gain +50% Melee Strength, +20% Attack Speed and +25% Damage Reduction.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Landing Melee Strikes during the duration will extend it by 0.3 seconds. At 20 seconds, the duration will begin to greatly diminish.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When the duration is over, however, you become Exhausted for 7 seconds, receiving +25% Damage Taken and -75% Stamina Regeneration Speed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Cooldown: 30 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Stimm Supply</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Place a refitted Medical Crate on the ground, bolstering you and your allies. If you have a Stimm equipped (via the Stimm Lab or otherwise), Stimm Supply will consume it, copy its effects and disperse it to any nearby allies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, Operatives breathing the Crate’s gas will also heal up to 40 Corruption over time and become immune to it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Cooldown: 60 seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Auras</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Gunslinger</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When an Ammo Pickup is collected by you or allies in Coherency, you each replenish Ammo equal to 5% of that pickup.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The upgraded version, ‘Gunslinger Improved’, increases the amount to 10%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Ruffian</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You and Allies in Coherency gain additional 10% Melee Damage.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Anarchist</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You and Allies in Coherency gain additional 5% Critical Chance.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Keystones</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Vulture’s Mark</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Killing a Specialist or Elite Enemy with a ranged weapon grants you a stack of Vulture’s Mark for 8 seconds (stacking 3 times).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Each stack grants +5% Ranged Damage, +5% Critical Chance and +5% Movement Speed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">While at max stacks, Specialist and Elite Ranged Kills also restore 15% Toughness to you and Allies in coherency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Adrenaline Junkie</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Melee Hits grants you a stack of Adrenaline. Critical Melee Hits grants 1 additional stack. Not gaining a stack within 2 seconds will remove a stack instead.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">At 30 stacks, you gain Adrenaline Frenzy for 10s, granting you +25% Melee Damage and +10% Attack Speed for the duration.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Reaching Adrenaline Frenzy again during its duration will refresh it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Chemical Dependency</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Using a Stimm (any Stimm) grants you a stack of Dependency for 90 seconds. For each stack, gain +10% Ability Cooldown Reduction. Stacks 3 times, decaying one at a time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/> </p><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/74c58e758999ca7c0dd61e63c94d3454ebaf9c27.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Crowbar</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Wrong man in the right place ah?”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Direct and unsophisticated, the Crowbar is the go-to tool of Hive Scums with a slugger inclination. Its generous Damage, Impact and Stamina values make the Crowbar an easy to use and dependable weapon. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Through its Special action, the grip on the weapon can be altered to swiftly access different moveset types, allowing it to deal with any surprise in the battlefield.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Crowbar also has the newly introduced Charged Swings effect on its Heavy attacks: the more time a Heavy windup is maintained, the more Strength will be added to the following attack (up to +22.5% total Strength generated over 3 steps, with a similar timing as the Thrust Blessing).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Special action switches the grip on the Crowbar between the primary “Blunt” and secondary “Beak” modes, changing the moveset and the properties of the attacks.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In primary mode, attacks have increased Cleave and inflict good Impact also to secondary enemies hit during the swing. In secondary mode, attacks remain stuck deep into the first enemy hit, to be then yanked out for an additional instance of Damage and Impact.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It is possible to cancel the second hit by performing a Dodge while being stuck after the initial hit, but at the cost of some Stamina.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, the first attack chained immediately after a Special grip change (to either side) will have additional power.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For more information on the Crowbar and a breakdown on its moveset, check out the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Shivs</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">From the Senior Chymist notes:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“However cool it may look, refrain from licking a coated blade.”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Metal junk from out-of-order machinery; an array of deadly blades. The difference is subtle, and resides fully in the skill and footwork of the fighter dual-wielding these instruments.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Shivs have strikingly fast attack speed, sporting also great mobility, increased Critical Chance and a Backstab damage bonus, but require high precision from their user as the weapon potential is unlocked through hitting weakspots and delivering devastating critical hits.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">However, the speed and nimbleness are contrasted by low Impact and Cleave capabilities, making these weapons all about the melee dance. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Swiftly throws a spare coated shiv, dealing immediate damage and applying stacks of Chem Toxin on hit. The amount of throwing shivs is limited, but they can be regained when killing enemies  with backstabs or when killing Elite, Specialist or Monstrosity enemies in melee.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This Special attack can be used to quickly deal with lesser enemies outside of the immediate reach of the Shivs, or to contribute additional damage against larger ones.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The damage of the projectile and the amount of Chem Toxin stacks are increased when hitting a weak spot and on a critical hit.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk I Improvised Shivs</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This mark of the Shivs focuses on stabbing, with a suite of Strikedown Heavy attacks and Assassin Lights with great first target effectiveness.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk III Improvised Shivs</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This mark has enhanced Cleave values on its Light and Heavy slices, but the best single-target attacks are gated behind the Push-attack chain.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For more information on the Shivs and a breakdown on their moveset, check out the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/354c5be7a65839ab2fcf204b613c386566f959ec.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bone Saw</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My toxin formula has been concocted in the lowest levels of the Underhive.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>So you know it’s good.”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Bone Saw showcases the craftiness and underhanded tactics of the Hive Scums. Chem coatings are applied to the blade, allowing it to punch above its weight by turning a rusty instrument into a weapon that even Nurgle’s chosen will learn to fear.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A fresh coating will be applied when performing the Special action, alternating between the <i>Chem Toxin</i> and <i>Brittleness</i> on-hit effects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Bone Saw is coated by a chem layer at all times, with the option of switching between the two available coatings through the Special action. While the moveset and the general performance of the weapon remains the same, <b>each coating has its own strengths and peculiarities</b>. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">If performing a Critical Strike, an additional stack of the on-hit effects will be applied. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When using the <i>Chem Toxin</i> coating, the weapon applies a small amount of stacks of the related effect, doing damage over time to affected enemies. This effect is shared with other weapons and abilities of the Hive Scum, allowing the Bone Saw to benefit from and add to already applied stacks of the same Chem Toxin.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The base properties of weapon hits are altered to inflict <b>more damage to “fleshy” armour types</b> (e.g. Unarmoured, Maniac).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When using the <i>Brittleness</i> coating, the weapon applies on-hit a small amount of stacks of an unique Hive Scum Brittleness debuff, granting additional damage from any source against the more hardened armour types. This effect has a limit of 15 stacks (for a total of 37.5% Brittleness), but can be applied in addition to other forms of Brittleness without sharing the same maximum cap.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The base properties of weapon hits are altered to inflict <b>more damage to “armoured” armour types</b> (e.g. Flak, Carapace).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For more information on the Bonesaw and a breakdown on its moveset, check out the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Dual Auto Pistols</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Branx Mk III Autopistols</b> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Introducing Darktide’s first dual ranged weapon. What's better than a high fire rate autopistol? Two high fire rate Autopistols to unleash a storm of bullets upon the heretics.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The weapon goes all in for mobility and offence, fielding a high magazine and ammo reserve for those who are not interested in precision aiming and like to run and shoot in a general direction. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍Very effective at short to mid ranges!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Primary Fire</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Shoot from the hips with both guns simultaneously without sacrificing mobility.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Secondary Fire</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Secondary fire braces both guns for slightly increased accuracy at the cost of movement speed. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Perform a quick push to stop heretic's melee attacks, then proceed to shoot them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For details on the Dual Auto Pistols’ blessings, check the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8e6b9743a591746be01a80bc4ffeb92de31ee789.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Needle Pistol</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Software version 7.0"</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Branx MkII / MkVI Needle Pistol</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Needle Pistol: The Chemist's Weapon of Choice</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This virtually silent pistol fires toxin-coated needles. While the needles themselves inflict a low amount of direct damage, they apply a powerful toxin that deals high damage over time. To quickly dispatch heretics, multiple stacks can be applied. Weakspot and critical hits also inflict a higher amount of toxin.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The weapon features excellent handling, low recoil, and good hip-fire accuracy, becoming pinpoint accurate when aiming down sights. Its main limitations are a small magazine capacity and a restricted ammo reserve. So choose your targets with care.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alternate fire mode. Flip the switch to alter the chemical composition of the toxin, making it highly Volatile and with the following effects:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Needles explode on impact into a toxic cloud, applying stacks of Chem Toxin in a small area</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enemies hit with a direct hit explode upon death</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">MkII explosion deals damage</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">MkVI releases a large gas cloud that applies a small amount of Chem Toxin stacks.</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For details on the Needle Pistol’s blessings, check the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Dual Stub Pistols</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My guns! So anyway…”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Dual Stub Pistols offer high mobility and a fast semi-automatic fire rate. They feature good damage per shot and are reliable close to long-range. Which gives a lot of flexibility of movement for rapid repositioning, evasion, and flanking.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Primary Fire</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alternating shots right to left from hipfire. Decent accuracy without sacrificing mobility.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Secondary Fire</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Goes into braced mode. Slightly improving accuracy at the cost of mobility.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Weapon Special</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Special ability performs Trickshot with precision that grants pinpoint accuracy (for a brief duration) for the following shot, resulting in higher weak spot and critical damage.‍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For details on the Dual Stub Pistols’ blessings, check the </i>full post on our forums.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re so excited to have you guys finally be able to play both the new class and the new mission! Let us know what you think in the comments!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– The Darktide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment - Patch 7.0: Introducing the Free Content and The Masque</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535303002</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/eebe2ffe8e0573f0dbb85339180e34f678942de9.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings commanders! It’s high tide we talked about the free content and overhauls we’ve been working on for some of WARHAMMER III’s existing races and factions. This is one of our heftier updates and it’ll land day-and-date with the Tides of Torment DLC pack. We’re spotlighting the headline changes here, but the update also includes a host of smaller adjustments and discoveries for players to find.<br/><br/>The beneficiaries of these updates are not just the self-same races which are getting new Legendary Lords with Tides of Torment, namely the High Elves, Norsca and Slaanesh, but also the Dark Elves. We’re dropping a major faction overhaul for Norsca, a significant feature-update for the High Elves, and Slaanesh is the recipient of our Free-LC Legendary Lord. Certain Legendary Lords are also getting some much-deserved TLC, bringing them into line with some of the more recent releases.<br/><br/>There’s a bunch to get through here, so we’ll deal with it all race by race.  Let’s start with our FreeLC Legendary Lord: Slaanesh’s all-singing, all-dancing champion, that Daemonette of Daemonettes, The Masque! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ THE FULL BLOG HERE 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Update: No Man’s Land - Out Now! (1.10.0 Patch notes)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/508472441549357793</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xz0g-lybujo?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Our latest free update, <i>No Man’s Land</i>, is now available for all players! <b>Patch 1.10.0 brings a new story campaign, a brand new Operation, and a slew of quality of life changes, balance adjustments and bugfixes.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The No Man’s Land story campaign will be available at 14:00 CET today.<br/>The new DLC class, Hive Scum, will be releasing later this afternoon.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Without further ado, let’s get right into it!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">New Story Campaign: The Road to No Man’s Land</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b530a913b6ecc2d467b2b8680ba96cf50594ea12.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A <b>new story campaign</b> has been added to Darktide! Similar to <i>Battle For Tertium</i>, play through three specific missions in a connected storyline, unlocking new chapters as you go. The first chapter starts with the Moebian 53rd fending off a heretical train hijacking via the <i>Rolling Steel</i> Operation, followed by <i>Excise Vault Spireside-13</i> as the second chapter. The third and final chapter of this mini-campaign is the new Operation: <i>No Man’s Land</i>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alongside it are 3 penances, awarded for completing the campaign on various difficulties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The new story is a <b>permanent addition to the game</b>, meaning that these missions will always be playable at any time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, for anyone who wishes to play the new mission without going through the short story, <b>we will make No Man's Land always available in the mission board for a week</b> after its release. <b>After that, it will be added to the regular mission rotation pool.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With the introduction of this, the “Campaign Playlist” has been renamed to “Special Assignments” and houses both the <i>“Battle for Tertium”</i> and <i>“The Road to No Man’s Land”</i> campaigns. These special assignments will introduce new content in a narrative way expanding Darktide’s living story.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">New Operation: No Man’s Land</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/106cb2363be1776608ecd472ba65cac83a757cae.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Good luck everyone.”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In a city as ancient, war-torn and enormous as Tertium, whole districts can fall into disrepair and be lost to the ravages of time. One such area, Consora’s Folly, has been taken over by the Admonition. Your job is to accompany Knight Commander Dragor and his Leman Russ Battletank, <i>Lionheart</i>, into this ruined zone. Your target: a long-lost fortress from a forgotten conflict, now a major base of operations for the insidious cult.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6459491ab9c55c64a336d71e73837c89f47cd258.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">New Ogryn Personality “The Heavy”</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Big lad, bad attitude.”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alongside the new Hive Scum class, as a special treat to celebrate our 3 year anniversary, we have a new, <b>free</b>, voice profile for the Ogryn. Fan favourite <b>Tim Bentinck</b>, known for his role as <b>Victor Saltzpyre</b> in the Vermintide series, lends his voice to the new “The Heavy” Ogryn personality! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Heavy has spent time amongst the various cartels that run Tertium's underworld. He's loud, aggressive and fond of using rhyming slang, just like the Hive Scum.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Upcoming In-Game Live Event: The Day of Atonement</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The stolen rations were tainted and now the hab blocks teem with infected. Atone for your deeds at the altars of Saint Messelina Gloriana. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This event will start on Thursday, December 4.</b> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>"Disturbing news has reached us from the poorer hab zones in Tertium. The recovered rations that were recently distributed to the unfortunate souls who reside in these districts appear to have been tainted. A great sickness has spread through these areas.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>My masters in the Ecclesiarchy have called for a Day of Atonement. You must beg our dear Saint Messelina Gloriana for her forgiveness and protection for our beloved Tertium.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Pray at her Blessed Altars and scour the hive for any Holy Relics you can find. Only through devotion can we hope to save our city.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>- Sister Hestia Prine"</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, you need to play missions with the Atonement condition, interact with the shrines presented in the missions and defeat the enemies which show up after activation. Along the way you can also gather holy relics for additional event progress. </b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel, Diamantine and a cosmetic insignia.</b> As a special celebration reward, those who complete the last tier of this anniversary event will receive <b>500 Aquilas</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/72e11bca6a81b42bc43725503870dfdd28d51786.png"/> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <b>Pray at the Blessed Shrines and search for holy relics to unlock the following rewards:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>200:</b> 50,000 Ordo Dockets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>600:</b> 3,000 Plasteel</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>1000:</b> 4,000 Diamantine</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>1600:</b> 3,000 Plasteel</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>2500:</b> 100,000 Ordo Dockets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>3600:</b> New Insignia</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>4500:</b> 500 Aquilas</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Regimental Bundle: Athonian Tunnel Rats</div><p class="bb_paragraph">There’s a new rotation in the Commodore’s Vestures, and a new Regimental pack to go with it: the Athonian Tunnel Rats! Make sure to check it out!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><div class="bb_h2">Havoc</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Rampaging Enemies</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the buff did not apply to Dreg Captains</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Rotten Armour</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed damage reduction effect not applying correctly</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note:</b><i> Rotten Armour works as follows: the rotten enemies spawn with a high damage reduction buff that is lowered when they take damage, to ultimately end up giving the player a 25% increase in damage towards that target. This behaviour wasn’t working as intended at all times, thus making the modifier harder than expected.</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the damage reduction only scaled against ranged damage</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev note: </b><i>It was unintentionally only affecting ranged</i> <i>weapons, but the intention is for both ranged &amp; melee weapons to be affected.</i></p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Contaminated Stimms</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blue stimm</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Moved stagger resistance to Red stimm</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lowered damage reduction from 80% to 60%</p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Encroaching Garden</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Healing amount has been changed from a static 1200HP/s to be based on the main armour type of the healed enemy as follows:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Unarmoured</b>: heals 1200 HP/s</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Flak</b>: heals 950 HP/s</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Unyielding</b>: heals 1100 HP/s</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Maniac</b>: heals 950 HP/s</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Carapace</b>: heals 800 HP/s</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Infested</b>: heals 1000 HP/s</p></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">General Tweaks &amp; Quality of Life changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Added functionality to allow the deselection of Blitz, Auras, and Abilities within the Talent Trees</b>, even if nodes below were selected. Leaving the Talent Tree menu in an invalid state will reset the Tree to the layout it had when originally entered.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We have added two Threat level unlocking bonuses for experienced players:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">If you already have unlocked the next Threat level with another operative, you will receive a small bonus for each mission won. The bonus is doubled if you have two other operatives with that Threat level.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You will start receiving a winning streak bonus on your 3rd consecutive win, and maintain the bonus until you face defeat.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Added the following enemies to the Meat Grinder:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Plasma Gunner</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mutated Poxwalker</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Infected Moebian 21st</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The last two have also been added to certain penances as a requirement to unlock them in the Meat Grinder.</i></p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Mission Terminal has received some upgrades as follows:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Quick Play button has been re-done and now lives alongside a Special Assignments button.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Condition text has been moved down alongside the Primary/Secondary objective information in order to give more space to the details of any given mission.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The font has been updated in order to more closely match the visuals.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Special Assignments window has new opening and closing animations.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Campaign debriefs now display an animated waveform when hovering over them.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We have added an <b>Aquila Welcome Offer</b> to the Commodore’s Vestures, a one-time purchase for players to receive an Aquila pack for a <b>heavily discounted price</b>.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This is available in the Purchase Aquilas section of the Commodore’s Vestures.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked the damage efficiency hitmarker indicators:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a new Light Blue hitmarker colour, to be displayed for hits with Reduced damage efficiency:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blue hitmarker: Negated/Heavily Reduced efficiency</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Light Blue hitmarker: Reduced efficiency</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">White hitmarker: High/Full efficiency</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dev note: This is to provide more information about hits that are not completely or almost completely negated, but that still are not delivering their full damage into the target.</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated the HUD iconography to better convey which Strike Team members could be in need of different Pickups:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Weapons not using ammo (i.e. Force Staves) will show a greyed out ammo icon.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Peril based Blitzes (i.e. all Psyker ones) will show a new icon.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blitzes not using Grenade Pickups (e.g. Remote Detonation, Blades of Faith, or Big Friendly Rocks) will show a new icon.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed the Symbol Auspex minigame to no longer generate two targets in the same column for consecutive rows.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The keybinding of the Next Item and Previous Item actions no longer affects scrolling in the Tactical Overlay.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Double-click is now supported to equip weapon cosmetics.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">If a weapon family only has one mark, that mark will be properly displayed in the Marks switching menu.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Lone Wolf</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Blitz replenishment split up into two separate values for the Voltaic Shock Mine and Arbites Grenades, at 90s and 45s respectively</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b><i>Dev Note:</i></b><i> The Voltaic Shock Mine was too powerful to justify getting a free Charge every 60s.</i></p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Veteran Mk III Sapper Shovel</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked the hitboxes and damage windows for several attacks.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased the range of the Heavy 2 attack.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b><i>Dev Note:</i></b><i> thanks to player Uttrik for bringing this to our attention!</i></p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Duelling Sword</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated the description of the Special action in the Inspect screen to mention the Peril cost for Psyker operatives.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The players’ underclothing has now received a new, refined texture.'</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New Events Information View</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Sire Melk has received an upgrade in the form of a new Events informational view. Here you can see information about currently active events, including rewards you can earn and your progress towards them.</p></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes</div><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the “Preview Voice” option on cosmetics headgears would not work for Zealot and Ogryn operatives.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed instances of the Quick Play button disappearing when swapping difficulties in the mission terminal.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbitrator class operatives will now appropriately respond to friendly fire.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Suppression was not always correctly applied to players.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Dev Note: Suppression is a system intended to make sway and spread worse while under heavy enemy fire to simulate flinching from near misses. Generally Precise ranged weapons suffer more, while Close Combat weapons suffer less.</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Some talents and abilities make you or allies immune to Suppression, and the Veteran is always immune (to represent their experience in combat).</i></p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed various talent buffs being presented with missing information in the Tactical Overlay.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed various talent buffs not showing up in the HUD.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some cooldown reduction talents not giving the last second of CDR before the duration ended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash which could happen when two players interacted with the various Auspex minigames at the same time.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed enemies taking cover facing the player instead of the opposite side in the Mortis Trials ‘Theatre of Rectitude’.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Master-Crafted Shroudfield' stated that the duration was increased by 5s (the new total duration) instead of the accurate 2s.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Full Bore' could activate when shooting allies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the 'Unstable Power' description displayed an incorrect value.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Mortis Trials objective to complete Wave 1 wasn’t being displayed in the Theatre of Rectitude.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue in the weapon inventory where scrolling could make the weapon card become fixed on screen until leaving that screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Fixed an issue where players could try and discard an equipped Curio.</i></p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Thunder Hammer</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the description of the “Shock &amp; Awe” weapon blessing was displaying incorrect values.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b><i>Dev Note:</i></b><i> Thanks to player kuli (among others) for bringing this to our attention!</i></p></li></ul></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several cases of misaligned weapons in the inventory icons and Shrine of the Omnissiah.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">When changing weapon Mark, all of the weapon information will now be immediately updated in the weapon inventory once the change takes effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The end of mission screen now waits for all elements to be displayed before closing automatically.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Kinetic Flayer' wouldn't properly activate when at Critical Peril.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Weapon preview in the Marks screen will no longer rotate with player input.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Fury of the Faithful' could lose its guaranteed empowered hit due to other damage instances (e.g. ongoing Bleed damage).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Just a Dream' converted more Peril than intended, and where it didn't trigger effects such as 'Quietude'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing bots to not have the stat bonuses, resulting among other things in not having the correct amount of scaling for the Wounds statistic.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the timer bar in the mission accept popup could have a bigger width than expected.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Cosmetic and Animation Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The cosmetic accessory “MkVIII Field Vox Unit” can now correctly be used on Arbitrator operatives.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed visual issue with the Psyker “Psykana Tunic (Moebian 53rd)” upper body cosmetic  — it no longer appears see-through on the inside.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed clipping issues on the arms with the Ogryn “Brute’s Battle Armour (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed hair clipping issues on the Psyker “Fabian MkIII "Mind-vent" Witch Crown” headgear cosmetic.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The head of betentacled Ogryns should now display properly.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where inspecting a weapon skin reward in the Penance menu would show a broken Ogryn mannequin.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some cosmetic VFX being visible in first person when switching cosmetics in the Meat Grinder.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Known Issues</div><p class="bb_paragraph">There’s a few known bugs that we hope to fix as soon as possible in the next hotfix, please keep them in mind while playing!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The attack audio for Power Weapons (such as the Relic Blade, Power Falchion, Thunder Hammer and Power Sword) is using default audio instead of their empowered sfx.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] Stimm Supply description is missing the duration the crate stays active.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The duration of the ability is 20 seconds.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] The ‘Focused Resolve’ talent is not properly triggering on Specialist kills.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] The ‘Blinder’ Blitz talent’s description does not mention that you can regain charges via close range kill (still works just fine)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] Dual Stub Pistols’ stat "Critical Bonus" does not display any details in the Inspect screen, and is not scaling as intended.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] ‘Rampage’ Combat Ability description:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Missing: Toughness is replenished to full upon use.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">‘Attack Speed’ should be ‘Melee Attack Speed’</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Missing: When Ability ends, Stamina is set to 0.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Hive Scum] Voiceover for Combat Ability uses can interrupt ongoing dialogue.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some Weapon Skins in the Commissary have outdated or otherwise incorrect names.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some of the text in the Psykhanium Tutorial, some Penances, and some Hive Scum talents, are missing translations.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">\[Controller] New ‘Battle for Tertium’ option in the Mission Board is automatically opened when playing on controller.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Play Button disappears when entering and exiting Special Assignments</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mission highlight and difficulty isn't updated when switching difficulty</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Back button fails to function when clicked after invoking the 'BATTLE OF TERTIUM' window in the mission terminal</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Note that it's only when trying to click on the actual "BACK" option in the lower left-hand corner, the button input works.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The countdown when loading into a mission is not visible in the ready up screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The new penances related to No Man’s Land are missing Penance Score rewards.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">De-selecting certain nodes from the talent tree can <i>visually</i> look like you can make illegal trees. <b>This is only a visual bug</b>, the talent tree is not saving with these impossible setups.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The Psyker Upper Body cosmetic "Athonian 98th Witch's Garb" causes the character's hands to disappear.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading the patch notes for this update! Please look forward to the release of Hive Scum later today!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Purchase the Hive Scum here:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– The Darktide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25th Anniversary Showcase Timings</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/364360/view/494961642665148656</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/8548992/4312dd46ebdc286f1d48b45dbaf3253c67e78b48.jpg"/><br/><br/>Total War Community,<br/><br/>An exciting new era is upon us.<br/><br/>Join us on<b> December 4th</b>, <b>4pm GMT</b> for the <b>Total War 25th Anniversary Showcase</b> – a special video presentation celebrating exciting new projects across historical and fantasy Total war.<br/><br/>This showcase will be your front seat to see what we’ve been eagerly building behind the scenes. Across the franchise, we’re working on a variety of projects that span different settings and stages of development and now we finally get to share some of them with you.<br/><br/>Wherever you are in the world, we can’t wait for you to tune in and be part of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/8548992/70de51381aa4dc88a0d9ddc308d88452edaddbfb.jpg"/><br/><br/>You can watch the 25th Anniversary Showcase on our official channels:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Total War Official YouTube Channel<br/></li><li> Total War Official Twitch Channel<br/></li><li> Total War Official BiliBili Channel</li></ul><br/>Or alternatively, tune in for the excitement of live reactions with your favourite creators and media sites who will be co-streaming the event.<br/><br/>25 years of Total War have led to this moment, but this is just the beginning.<br/><br/>Ready your popcorn, and we’ll see you at the showcase.<br/><br/>– The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25th Anniversary Showcase Timings</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/594570/view/527612739964633412</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/28300675/4312dd46ebdc286f1d48b45dbaf3253c67e78b48.jpg"/><br/><br/>Total War Community,<br/><br/>An exciting new era is upon us.<br/><br/>Join us on<b> December 4th</b>, <b>4pm GMT</b> for the <b>Total War 25th Anniversary Showcase</b> – a special video presentation celebrating exciting new projects across historical and fantasy Total war.<br/><br/>This showcase will be your front seat to see what we’ve been eagerly building behind the scenes. Across the franchise, we’re working on a variety of projects that span different settings and stages of development and now we finally get to share some of them with you.<br/><br/>Wherever you are in the world, we can’t wait for you to tune in and be part of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/28300675/70de51381aa4dc88a0d9ddc308d88452edaddbfb.jpg"/><br/><br/>You can watch the 25th Anniversary Showcase on our official channels:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Total War Official YouTube Channel<br/></li><li> Total War Official Twitch Channel<br/></li><li> Total War Official BiliBili Channel</li></ul><br/>Or alternatively, tune in for the excitement of live reactions with your favourite creators and media sites who will be co-streaming the event.<br/><br/>25 years of Total War have led to this moment, but this is just the beginning.<br/><br/>Ready your popcorn, and we’ll see you at the showcase.<br/><br/>– The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
