<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #69 (1.8.1) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961124013</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1a183a007f5e01d15e6915b946678f2c630fd0d9.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #69 (1.8.1) is currently rolling out across our platforms. This hotfix addresses multiple crash issues and gameplay bugs primarily related to the release of the Battle for Tertium Free Update and the Arbites Class.  In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the biggest crash stemming from the Battle for Tertium release: a crash would occur when starting the game and joining servers with a certain combination of skins/trinkets and the Ogryn Pickaxes. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that occurred often when playing missions with Toxic Gas enabled.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that occurred when having the Steam overlay disabled.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash occurring when creating a new character if scrolling too quickly throughout the character creation menus.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that can occur when selecting the Lone Wolf talent while your Cyber-Mastiff is wearing a smoke-emitting cosmetic. As a temporary fix we removed visual FX from the dog cosmetics while we investigate a more permanent fix to be deployed soon.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that would occur when Auspex devices started playing sounds the same time as the player wielded a weapon.</p></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Play button on the Mission Board would temporarily be unavailable if no Campaign mission was active.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The hair of the “Brahms’ Memories” NPC in the Meat Grinder is now properly displayed.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the notification pop-up for unlocking a curio slot would continuously re-appear.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed the Scab Radio Operator variant from the “Traitorous collective” penance.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Note: the same issue in “Elitist” penance will be fixed in the next hotfix.</p></li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">"Modify Cyber-Mastiff Appearance" in the Barber-Chirurgeon screen is now translated to all languages.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Break the Line' wouldn't properly interrupt Weapon Actions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff would stop attacking after its owner had been consumed by a Beast of Nurgle.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff wouldn't jump down from the Valkyrie at the start of 'Rolling Steel'.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff would target the Poxbusters automatically. It should only do so at the order of the Arbitrator from now on.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff would have its Outline enabled even when the related Options setting was set to Off.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff had the wrong attack type towards Daemonhosts spawned through the 'Heinous Ritual' circumstance.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff could have two cosmetics applied during mission cutscenes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Execution Order' would decrease the Damage dealt by Monstrosities attacked by the Cyber-Mastiff.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Break the Line' would force heavy stagger on the Dreg Captains.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the 'Castigator's Stance' description didn't specify that it replenished all Toughness.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the 'Nuncio-Aquila' descriptions didn't specify its Cooldown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where 'Hold the Line' didn't specify the stacks Duration.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff could get stuck in between walls for an extended period of time.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the 'Voltaic Shock Mine' description displayed an incorrect range value.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Note: The actual range for the mine is 3m.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a check that prevents players without the Arbites DLC from purchasing the Arbites Exterminator Shotgun weapon skin in the Commodore's Vestures.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that could occur when a Veteran would activate 'Executioner's Stance' near a Cyber-Mastiff.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was preventing equipped weapon cosmetics from showing up in the Operative menu, Mourningstar or Ready Up screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Various improvements to how cosmetics and rewards are displayed in the inventory.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that could cause a crash when killing an enemy as a Veteran while nearby a Cyber-Mastiff and having the "Target Down!" talent selected.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that could cause the server to crash when a player joined while on an elevator.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.2.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497198852915331570</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/722bba490cfcd504daa0ed7cb8b1d974eb412439.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Greetings everyone!<br/><br/>Today, we’re releasing Hotfix 6.2.1, bringing new fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III including balance changes to Books of Khorne and some new quality of life improvements.<br/><br/>Without further ado, let’s get into it.<br/><br/>— Anastasija Dolgošejeva // Senior Community Manager // Your friendly neighbourhood penguin</p><hr/><div class="bb_h1">Quality of Life Highlights</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Implemented a “Enable Realms of Chaos Frontend Video” (currently “Skip realms of Chaos video”) option into Game settings in the main menu. Enabling this setting will ensure the Realms of Chaos video plays before the frontend. Disabling it will skip the video when launching the game.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/36a3e9b38b355d204dd6f28110b656bfeb1a51fa.png"/></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Single clicking on the icon for a reinforcement point on Domination Maps will no longer pan the camera to that location. Double clicking on the icon for a reinforcement point on Domination Maps will pan the camera to that location.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Campaign</div><div class="bb_h2">Items</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> We had one extra Unique tier item we planned to add that didn’t quite make it into 6.2: The Chalice of Malfleur. The Chalice is an arcane item that offers a huge trade-off to a caster - can you overcome its huge miscast penalties to benefit from its powerful rewards?</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Azhag's Crown of Sorcery no longer says it unlocks Lore of Death spells since Azhag has this innately.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed an issue where the next volumes of the Books of Khorne wouldn't drop for a Khornite faction.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Balance Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> We’ve changed Khorne’s version of the Book of Khorne so that it no longer gives Spell intensity and instead Silence’s everyone in the region. A bit more fitting and useful for a Khorne faction.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> We originally made the decision that the permanent razing effect of the completed Book of Khorne would prevent even Khorne factions from settling ruins through their automatic ruin colonization feature - however on second thought and considering your early feedback we’ve decided to re-enable ruin colonization via this feature for Khorne factions. We’ll continue to monitor feedback on this.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Skills </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Caskets of Souls aren't just for Christmas! They're affected by red line skills like other units :)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Azhag's skill "Insane Visions" now provides factionwide hero recruit rank increase instead of provincewide.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Paint da Beasts now affects Waaagh trophy units.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">UI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Moved "Minor Faction Potential" and "AI Strength &amp; Threat Assessment" checkboxes from endgame settings to general campaign settings (this will not affect current campaigns).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> “Implemented a “Enable Realms of Chaos Frontend Video” option into Game settings in the main menu. Enabling this setting (currently “Skip realms of Chaos video”) will ensure the Realms of Chaos video plays before the frontend. Disabling it will skip the video.”</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> The Black Ark’s Docked effect now uses an icon when in pre-battle screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed not restoring army selection after treasury, objectives or treasure maps panel has been closed.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Volksgrad is a major settlement, the garrison buildings available now correctly reflect that.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> The Altdorf College of Forbidden Magic now correctly shows as a landmark in the building browser.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed a potential crash on AI turns.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed a crash when defeating a Malakai adventure’s Wood Elf Force.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> When occupying Kislev settlements that contain Court or Orthodoxy buildings, those buildings now convert as expected.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Shadow Realm stance no longer shows as a negative effect for Alith Anar.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> The cost of discovery buildings is now in the correct order for Bretonnia, Vampire Coast, Dark Elves, Empire, High Elves, Lizardmen, Norsca, Skaven, Tomb Kings, Vampire Counts, Wood Elves, Warriors of Chaos, Grand Cathay, Daemons of Chaos, Khorne, Kislev, Ogre Kingdoms, Slaanesh and Tzeentch.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Battle</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Fixed a possible crash during battle that may occur on the map "Vampire Forest" and possibly other maps too.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> We've removed the expendable attribute from the Hobgoblin Bolt Thrower because Hobgoblins are not expendable.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Blood Knights &amp; Blood Knights (Lances) now have their own unit caps.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> Hobgoblin Bolt Thrower now has its own unit cap, matching that of other bolt throwers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> The Grudge Settler Quarreller (Great Weapons) now has the correct class (and icon).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"> The Emperor's Wrath (Steam Tank) no longer shows different stats in battle &amp; campaign.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">— The <i>Total War</i> Team</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord Bluesky</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solomorne Anthar, a Champion of the Lex Imperialis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523094550774808943</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Xenos and Chaos minions are not the only things threatening Humanity in the grim darkness of the 41st millennium. Even among humans, there are many who would seek to attack the power of the Imperium from within. But regardless of whether the criminal is driven by personal gain or the heresy of mercy, the outcome is always the same. Justice will not be denied, and any encounter with the Adeptus Arbites is inevitably followed by a quick sentence and swift execution.<br/><br/>The Arbites will not be bribed, intimidated, or swayed by heartfelt pleas. Their lives are spent serving the Lex Imperialis, a holy code of laws tracing back to the Emperor's own decrees. Their prayers are ancient codices, their duty—to collect the tithe that fuels the Imperium’s war machine on countless fronts and any who would dare threaten it. Each member of the Adeptus Arbites has undergone rigorous training at the Schola Progenium and is granted access to first-class weaponry, including powerful shotguns, heavy shields, and deadly cyber-familiars. Their name has become synonymous with the fear of Imperium Law, and their appearance means swift judgement and certain retribution.<br/><br/>Solomorne Anthar embodies this implacable justice, which cannot be swayed or thwarted by wealth or lofty titles. Years of service have purged him of all human qualities, for his duty demands absolute commitment. Only one creature has ever earned the Proctor’s affection: Glaito the Cyber-Mastiff, a living weapon of the Lex Imperialis, and the most loyal of companions.<br/><br/>For Solomorne, the world is simple and clear: everything must conform to the order established by the God-Emperor, and there is no excuse, and no mercy, for any violators of the Lex Imperialis. No sacrifice is too great if it is made to uphold His Law, and only the authority of the holy Warrant can force the Arbitrator to bow his head. But even in the Koronus Expanse, where crime runs rampant and the Adeptus Arbites lack both numbers and resources, Solomorne is determined to follow the letter of the Law until he draws his final breath.<br/><br/>Yet, even the most unbreakable principles may crack under a single fatal flaw. Beset by enemies of Humanity, riven with contradictions, and full of terrible secrets, the Koronus Expanse will become the catalyst for events that will push Solomorne to the brink—and show just how strong his faith in the Lex Imperialis truly is.<br/><br/>Meet him tomorrow in the Lex Imperialis expansion!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/3daca1b1520b2f040c475b1cb9ce0a688c6903ec.jpg"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites Class - Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254835229</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Introducing: Adeptus Arbites</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Adeptus Arbites have arrived – Darktide’s first Class DLC. Get the Arbites Class on all platforms today, you can choose between the Standard Edition and the Deluxe Edition. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink][dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710950/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class_Deluxe_Edition/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d846a0ad5d8dc966d34f07b734659eff2f41325.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/02ae078b9cb1ac80e59c8037b1d7dec0521a25cd.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Adeptus Arbites enforce the Lex Imperialis – the Imperial Law. The institution’s most visible officers, known as Arbitrators, are utterly unforgiving of those who dare transgress the Law. They are swift to unleash brutal punishment upon those guilty of threatening the Imperium’s working, and no one is beyond their long reach.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">They have been present on Tertium for at least as long as Inquisitor Grendyl’s forces, investigating anomalies in the planet’s Tithe offerings.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The situation has grown so grave that Marshall Vortern has decided that the long arm of the Imperial Lex needs to take a firmer grasp of the situation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>It is worth noting that the Arbites’ arrival takes place after the events of the Battle for Tertium,</b> so while you can absolutely play as an Arbites through the new campaign, some of the story scenes will not be addressed to your type of character. For this reason, we suggest playing the Battle for Tertium for the first time with one of the core characters.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Cyber-Mastiff</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Arbitrator's loyal companion and best friend will join you in the slaying of lawbreakers and other scum. After you’re finished with customizing its name and looks, you’ll soon have it fighting alongside you. The Cyber-Mastiff has its own Passive target selection, which it will use to help you against anything that comes too close. You can also command it to attack a specific target, which will override any behaviour of its own. To command your Mastiff, you simply double-tap your Tag Input on any enemy that is eligible to be Tagged.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7f114b1ed9183c8abae5457a9d9e9741eb727749.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When the Cyber-Mastiff attacks a Human-Sized enemy, it will pounce on it, knocking it down and keeping it that way until it kills the enemy, or you order it to attack something else. When attacking any larger enemy the Mastiff will do a jump attack, staggering and dealing damage to the enemy.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Note: You can change the Command from Double-Tap to Single-Tap in your Input Settings. You can also enable and disable Outlines as well as Names, for your and other Arbitrator’s Companions.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d596ac49b151d421e2128f5f12bc112eaaf2f9f6.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Talent Tree</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">As an Arbitrator you have plenty of options when it comes to how you wish to play. Going from left to right in the Tree we will find a few prominent themes. From Elite killing and Cyber-Mastiff handling, to Hybrid Combat and Supportive Utility, and lastly Crowd Control and Melee. While the Cyber-Mastiff is iconic to the Arbites, if you prefer to play without it, take a look at the Lone Wolf Talent!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Let us quickly go through the more impactful choices you can make in the Talent Tree.</p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Blitz Abilities </b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Arbites Grenade</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Your base Blitz is an Impact Grenade that deals high damage and stagger to anything struck by it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Charges: 3</i><br/>The upgraded variant increases the maximum number of grenades you can carry to 4.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Voltaic Shock Mine</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Throw a Voltaic Shock Mine onto the floor that lies dormant until an enemy comes near. Upon activation the Mine shocks enemies within 3m, electrocuting them for up to 15s.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Charges: 2.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Remote Detonation</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Cause an electric Explosion around your Cyber-Mastiff's position. This deals Damage, Electrocutes, and Staggers nearby enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Charges: 3. You replenish one charge every 60s.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Combat Abilities</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Nuncio-Aquila</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Iconic to the Arbites, is the Nuncio-Aquila. Deploy it to create a 7.5m area where allies regenerate 7.5% Toughness per second.  Additionally, Enemies in the area have +15% Damage Taken. Lasts 20s.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>60s Cooldown.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The upgraded variant also grants allies 30% Suppression Dealt, -25% Recoil, 30% Impact, as well as makes them Slowdown Immune, Suppression Immune, and Immune to interruption of Alternate Fire (i.e. Braced attacks and ADS attacks).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Castigator's Stance</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Instantly replenish your Toughness and enter the Castigator's Stance for 10s. During the stance you have +15% Movement Speed, 80% Reduced Damage Taken, 100% Reduced Movement Speed Penalties from Actions (e.g. attacking, bracing, aiming, interacting or charging heavy attacks), but you cannot Sprint.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>45s Cooldown.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Break the Line</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Step forward and Bash, causing high Stagger to enemies in front of you, and gain +25% Damage, +50% Impact, for 6s.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>20s Cooldown.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Auras</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Part of the Squad</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Your Cyber-Mastiff is more than just a pet, it is a crucial member of your Team. Your Cyber-Mastiff now counts towards your Coherency count and acts as its own coherency source, increasing the potential distance of your Auras.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The upgraded variant also reduces the Toughness Damage Taken by any ally in coherency by 7.5%.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Ruthless Efficiency</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You and Allies in Coherency gain additional 7.5% Reload Speed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Breaking  Dissent</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You and Allies in Coherency deal additional +10% Damage vs Staggered Enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Keystones</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Execution Order</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Periodically mark Elites, Specialists, and Bosses for Mercy Sanction. Killing a marked enemy replenishes 15% Toughness. Your Cyber Mastiff gains 150% Damage for 8s after attacking a marked enemy. You gain +15% Damage and +10% Attack Speed for 8s after killing a Marked Enemy.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Terminus Warrant</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Ranged Attacks grant stacks of Melee Justice for each Enemy Hit (max 30). Melee Hits remove 1 stack(s). While you have stacks of Melee Justice, gain +15% Melee Damage and +25% Melee Impact.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Melee Hits grant stacks of Ranged Justice (max 30). Ranged Attacks remove 1 stack(s) for each Enemy Hit. While you have stacks of Ranged Justice, gain +15% Ranged Damage, +50% Ranged Cleave and +50% Suppression.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Forceful</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Staggering Hits and Blocked Attacks grant Stacks of Forceful. Lasting 5s and stacking 10 times. Each stack gives +5% Impact and +2.5% Damage Resistance. Remove one stack on damage taken.</p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Cyber-Mastiff Iconics</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">In addition, there are three Talents that affect the Behaviour of your Cyber-Mastiff.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Unleashed Brutallity</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Your Cyber-Mastiff prioritises Elite and Specialist Enemies, and deals +25% Damage to them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Go Get ‘Em!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Your Cyber-Mastiff prioritises Ranged Enemies, and deals +50% Damage to them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Lone Wolf</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You are no longer accompanied by your Cyber-Mastiff. Gain +15% Toughness Damage Reduction, +10% Attack Speed, +10% Damage, +1 increased Charges on your Blitz Abilities, and you replenish a charge of your Blitz Ability every 60s. <i>This Iconic cannot be taken with any other Cyber-Mastiff related talent.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/706efc9fd9efa22eeb1c05b55020876e090e9911.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8f11954d910991a4873e1e3ce7a42d603aa01085.jpg"/></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">To read more about the Adeptus Arbites Talent Tree, <u>you can read our dev blog on our website</u>.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">You can begin playing around with builds using the <u>Build Simulator on GamesLantern</u>. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">To read more about the Cyber Mastiff, <u>you can read our dev blog on our website</u>. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">To read about the unique weapons coming to Adeptus Arbites, read below!</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>New Weapon Families</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The Arbites Class comes with a unique set of new weapons, exclusive to the Arbites!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Shock Maul and Suppression Shield</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Overview</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The combination of empowered Suppression Shield and Shock Maul gives the Adeptus Arbites unparalleled ability in repressing any kind of uprising, be it disgruntled Lexbreakers from Imperial manufactorums or Chaos-tainted heretics. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">While its mobility is not impressive, the Shield grants this weapon superior defensive and control properties: in addition to great Stamina and Block Cost values, it has top-tier Push range and strength. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Furthermore, the Shield is capable of Blocking ranged fire coming from a frontal angle, but also normally unblockable attacks (like Crusher overhead smashes or Sniper longlas shots). </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Staggering enemies with either the Maul or the Shield will also inflict the Electrocuted status, which can be used to enable additional effects like the ‘High Voltage’ Blessing. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Weapon Special</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The shield's Special action unleashes a powerful shockwave, staggering and suppressing enemies within a wide frontal cone. <i>This action consumes a portion of the Special charge meter, visible diegetically on the inside of the shield.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Special meter regenerates by blocking attacks and slowly over time</b>, with larger enemies granting additional meter. <b>Initiating the Special action requires at least a partial meter.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> Hold the Special input to precisely time the shockwave; block properties are maintained throughout the action for maximum safety. Use this Special to shift the tide of battle, either by attacking disoriented enemies or executing a tactical reposition.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <b>Branx Mk VI Arbites Shock Maul and Suppression Shield</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This mark is especially easy to use, with immediate access to simple Strikedown attack chains but also Relentless and Vanguard strikes, all with high Impact values.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Attacks</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 1:</b> Moderately fast, vertical Strikedown attack with good Damage against all armour types.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 2:</b> Moderately fast, diagonal Vanguard attack with good Cleave.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 3:</b> Fast bash Strikedown attack performed with the shield. This attack can easily interrupt enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 4:</b> Fast poke Strikedown attack, with very good Damage against all armour types.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Push-attack:</b> Horizontal Relentless attack with good Impact and Cleave properties. <i>Chains into Light 2 and Heavy 2.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 1:</b> Slow, horizontal Relentless attack performed with the shield, with great Impact and Cleave. This attack can easily inflict Stagger on enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 2:</b> Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with great Damage, Finesse multiplier and armour penetration.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Horde combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-attack &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt;  Block cancel &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Single Target combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; L1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; H2 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Branx Mk XI Arbites Shock Maul and Suppression Shield</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This mark does not have immediate access to Strikedown attacks, but makes up for it by granting powerful combo chains which can be easily looped. However, the fastest way of reaching the Strikedown strikes requires some Stamina expenditure.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Attacks</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 1:</b> Fast, horizontal Relentless attack with good Impact and Cleave properties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 2:</b> Fast, horizontal Relentless attack with good Impact and Cleave properties. Chains into Light 3 and Heavy 1.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 3:</b> Fast, diagonal uppercut Strikedown attack with good Damage and Finesse multiplier. Chains into Light 4 and Heavy 2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 4:</b> Fast vertical Strikedown attack with very good Damage against all armour types. Useful to complete a quick single target combo.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Push-attack:</b> Fast, diagonal uppercut Strikedown attack with similar properties as Light 3. Chains into Light 4 and Heavy 2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 1:</b> Slow, slightly diagonal Relentless attack with great Impact and Cleave.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 2:</b> Slow bash Strikedown attack performed with the shield, with good Damage and Impact. This attack can easily interrupt enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 3:</b> Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with great Damage, Finesse multiplier and armour penetration. Chains into Light 3 and Heavy 2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Horde combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt;  Block cancel &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Single Target combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-Attack &gt; H2 &gt; H3 &gt; H2 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-Attack &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; H2 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-Attack &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-Attack &gt; H2 &gt; H3 &gt; L3 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-Attack &gt; L4 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Arbites Shock Maul</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“You fool! Now that I have accepted Grandfather’s gifts, I can never die! – </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i><b>Good</b>.”</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Overview</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When an Arbitrator is in need of maximum brutality, no other weapon comes close to the Arbites Shock Maul: this huge plasteel rod crackling with electrical power can dispatch any foe, sometimes in just one hit if they are lucky.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With generous Stamina and high Impact on every swing, it can handle itself in all kinds of engagements.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Staggering enemies will also inflict the Electrocuted status, which can be used to trigger additional effects like the Stun from the Special attacks.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Weapon Special</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Arbites Shock Maul's Special attack is an electrically charged strike capable of controlling and Stunning enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Pressing the Special input will perform the next attack in the Light chain with modified properties:</b> while the base Damage, Speed and Cleave of the attack will be lowered, the Impact value will be increased and the attack will briefly Stun most enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, enemies which are already Electrocuted will be Stunned for multiple seconds, while also receiving significant damage over time.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This damage is particularly effective against enemies clad in Flak or Carapace armour.</b> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Since the Special attack does not require any activation or recharge period, it can be weaved into combos at any opportune time.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <b>Branx Mk III Arbites Shock Maul</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks to its multiple vertical Strikedown attacks, this weapon mark can easily dispatch foes of any size.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The attack chain from Push-attack allows to combo directly in other Relentless strikes, allowing for great crowd control at the cost of some Stamina.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Attacks</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 1 / Light 2:</b> Moderately fast, vertical Strikedown attacks with good Damage against all armour types.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 3:</b> Fast diagonal uppercut Relentless attack with good Impact and Cleave properties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Light 4:</b> Moderately fast diagonal Vanguard attack with good Damage and Cleave properties.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Push-attack:</b> Horizontal Relentless attack with similar properties as Light 3. Chains into Light 3 and a unique Heavy follow-up.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 1:</b> Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with great Damage, Finesse multiplier and armour penetration.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy 2:</b> Slow, horizontal Relentless attack with great Impact and Cleave.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Heavy follow-up from Push-attack:</b> Slow, horizontal Relentless attack with similar properties as Heavy 2. Chains into Light 4 and Heavy 2.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Horde combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-attack &gt; L3 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; ...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-attack &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; Block cancel &gt; ...</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-attack &gt; Hfollow-up &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Push-attack &gt; Hfollow-up &gt; L4 &gt; Block cancel &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>(Light attacks can be swapped out for Special attacks for more control at the cost of Damage and Cleave.)</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Suggested Single Target combos</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; H1 &gt; …</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>(Light attacks can be swapped out for Special attacks for more control at the cost of Damage and Cleave.)</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><div class="bb_h3">Subductor Shotpistol and Riot Shield</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Judgment Mk IV Subductor Shotpistol and Riot Shield</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Overview</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Introducing Darktide’s first ranged weapon with shield. The Arbites Shotpistol combines a heavy, shell-shooting revolver with the protective capabilities of a Riot Shield.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The weapon trades mobility for defense, fielding a large Stamina amount and top-tier Block cost values.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> Very effective at shorter ranges, with a limited 5-shot cylinder magazine and a speedloader reload system.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <u>Primary Fire</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Fire justice-dispensing shells towards anyone that defies the Lex, without sacrificing mobility.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Secondary Fire</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Secondary fire braces the shield for blocking, whilst still allowing the shotpistol to shoot. The Riot Shield can block all kinds of melee and ranged attacks, but mobility will be reduced.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Weapon Special</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The specials on these weapons are both shield related.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Utilize a quick push attack for when enemies get too close by pressing and immediately releasing the Special input.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Alternatively, keep the Special input pressed to strike with a heavy shield swipe and deal significant damage and stagger, lining enemies up for an easy follow up shot.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/183a7360d00292995e3786cabde43ef4fd80b9f4.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Exterminator Shotgun </b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><u>Overview</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A large, powerful Will of the Lex dispensing shotgun!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While its fire rate is not the fastest, each shot packs a punch with exceptional damage and a good amount of cleave.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It’s got quick handling that makes it suitable for close combat, but it remains very competent at medium or even long ranges when in secondary aimed fire mode.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Exaction Mk III Exterminator Shotgun</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Mk III has a dynamic choke: shoot in hipfire mode into large groups with a large horizontal spread or aim for improved precision and tighter group of pellets in secondary braced fire mode.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Exaction Mk VIII Exterminator Shotgun</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While still being a large pump-action shotgun, the Mk VIII comes with an extended barrel and<b> </b>is a standard spread, heavy-hitter variant with good damage into armoured enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The amount of shells that can be loaded is lower compared to the Mk III version, but the tighter spread makes this mark very capable against priority targets also at longer ranges.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The pellet spread becomes even more accurate in secondary braced fire mode.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <u>Weapon Special</u></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With the Arbites shotgun, we are introducing a new type of special ammo.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The design intent for this is for them to be an active choice to use, but to have a larger impact on tough engagements.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The number of special shells are limited and visible on the weapon's top rack, for a maximum of 6 special shells on both marks; only one special shell can be loaded at once. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Special shells are replenished when picking up ammunition.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Both shotgun variants' special shells retain their (high) regular damage output, plus special properties:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk III: </b>Electric Shells - Stun enemies upon impact and give Electrocution debuff with Damage over time. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Mk VIII: </b>Armor-breaking Shells - Gives a significant Brittleness debuff to enemies hit for several seconds, helping both the player and the other teammates to focus fire on impervious threats.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>– The Darktide Team</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live Now: Inferno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520842750961123852</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><b>New In-Game Event: Inferno</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The streets of Tertium are aflame. Whether by heretic plot or over-zealous Imperial enforcement makes no real difference. Missions must still run, so be careful down there. You're literally dropping into a hot zone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, complete missions with the Inferno condition.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This event will start on Monday, June 23. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic portrait frame.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c3a344287451a7676da43e2a3d831053af7c257d.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/48ebf065d7f8058c2c24aaecda294d00b32284fe.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
