<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>April Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500571481680380468</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines!</div><br/>You’re in for a new Community Update, where we’ll discuss what happened throughout April and what’s coming for the next months! Let’s begin.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">RECAP OF THE MONTH</div><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">THE TRYGON UPDATE 🐍</div></u><br/>In April, we released the 7.0 “Trygon” Update. It contained both free and DLC content, including:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A new PvE Map called Exfiltration and a new boss fight against the Trygon<br/></li><li> Two cosmetics DLCs: The Imperial Fists Champion Pack and the Space Wolves Chapter Pack<br/></li><li> The inferno Pistol, for both PvE and PvP (available for Assault, Vanguard, Sniper and Heavy)<br/></li><li> Private Lobbies in PvP<br/></li><li> Expanded Weapon Arsenal for all 6 classes<br/></li><li> New elements of customisation, including: Volupus Pink, Thousand Sons Blue, cloth colouring for Bulwark, hand customisation.<br/></li><li> Weapons perks and Prestige Perks were updated<br/></li><li> Several buffs, and bug fixes</li></ul>Read the details of the patch notes here!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Watch the trailer if you missed it 😉👇</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7oAHVCnAXxY?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Nevertheless, the 7.0 Update brought a bunch of unexpected bugs: for instance, matchmaking became a big issue. Saber Interactive deployed the 7.1 hotfix first to improve matchmaking stability. <br/><br/>Today, we pushed the 7.2 hotfix. It should bring a solution to most connectivity issues, specifically infinite “Joining Server” loops and black screens after completing an Operation.<br/><br/>We’re truly sorry for the inconvenience, we know how much of a bother it’s been for the past weeks.<br/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">“SEISMIC ACTIVITY” COMMUNITY EVENT</div></u><br/>Your mission has just ended. Were you successful?<br/><br/>This time your brief was to collectively bring down 200,000 Trygons between April 17 and 27.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e785444e0b43efd977b239ec3397a01a19878e95.png"/><br/>The least we can say is: you CRUSHED it, Space Marines! It has been tallied that over 800,000 Trygons were obliterated over the course of these ten days.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8668e574b45f477b1f283220facad92da71a07c7.png"/><br/><br/>Your faith holds firm, and the enemy lies in ruin. <br/><br/>As promised, your reward is the<b> Mark X Tacticus Breastplate</b>. Since, the question was raised: yes, you can change the colour of the skulls. <br/><br/>But that’s not all, to reward your commitment in this event, the ​<b>Porphyr Shield Chainsword skin</b> will be available to claim through PROS. The code will be shared to you on May 5th and until the release of the 8.0 Update. So, stay tuned!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d6cc06d71d8d8af11d31de6852581846ce59040b.png"/><br/><br/>The Emperor provides.<br/><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WHAT WE’RE WORKING ON</div><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">CODENAME: HORDE MODE</div></u><br/>With the Trygon update released, our focus has now shifted to Patch 8, and it is getting closer each day! 🤫<br/><br/>Today we would like to tease you a bit more about what it is going to be like. First of all, you will be able to play up to three players (or with 2 bots, just like in regular PvE) and you will get to fight waves of both Tyranids and Chaos. Difficulty will increase for each wave defeated, so you’ll have to prepare yourself accordingly to vaporize as many waves as you can. Also, your class and weapon levels will be based on your PvE levels.<br/><br/><br/>Oh and here’s a sneak peek of the map! 👀As you can see, the action takes place in Kadaku.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39ab253e1770992a8f6bfe33a4a793a907474ca8.png"/><br/>The “Horde Mode” release date and its actual in-game name will be announced at <i>[redacted💀💀]</i>… <br/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">THE NEXT UPDATE</div></u><br/>You will have access to the PTS again to test the 8.0 update before the release. Stay tuned, we will give you more information later.<br/><br/>The 8.0 update will bring more free and DLC content to the game. We cannot unveil everything yet, but here’s a few things you can expect from it:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Blood Angels Cosmetic Pack<br/></li><li> White Scars Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Horde Mode<br/></li><li> Rebalancing of the Absolute difficulty following the community polls</li></ul>Last month, we did a community poll on Focus Together to collect your feedback and see what you were interested to see on the Absolute difficulty to differentiate it more from Lethal. You will see the changes we made as part of the 8.0 update. Expect an even tougher challenge!<br/><br/>And more, stay tuned 🤫<br/><br/>The release date will also be confirmed during the <i>[redacted💀💀]</i><br/><br/><br/><u><div class="bb_h2">FOCUS TOGETHER</div></u><br/>Since the release of Space Marine 2, you were encouraged to share your thoughts on the game and even suggest ideas on Focus Together. To this day, we’ve implemented more than 40 ideas from the community, into the game. We always keep an eye on them.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f8cb15eecd98ee97151f2335fde8cf5eebba2456.png"/><br/>Recently, we’ve added the Trygon, the hand customisation, and released the Inferno Pistol.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0c8ababb11377babf451bd8641abd5dd05a7d22e.png"/><br/><br/>We also added color customisation to the Bulwark.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5d3a700fdbf3bb0416a87a2b1df262bd14fce5cc.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c33da9c41e16b3b02e3bf0571ee317837dede092.png"/><br/><br/>We’ve implemented a Bestiary with lore entries through the Datavault Update and weapons class restrictions have been lifted though the Trygon Update!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/60a07d9a8fcec5ed82c4ae30e63d0d96d3361211.png"/><br/><br/>The lenses colour customisation was made available with the Obelisk update, months ago.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9873e218eaa1d9d3368181994aa523d042cd5292.png"/><br/><br/>Private PvP lobbies were implemented as well. And many others! 😊<br/><br/><br/>If your idea has received a lot of upvotes but still hasn’t gotten a response from the devs, it’s likely because it’s still too early for them to give a clear answer. They might be focused on other priorities for now, or they haven’t made a final decision on the matter yet.<br/><br/>We truly appreciate your enthusiasm and patience and we hope you understand that such things take time on our side. ❤️‍🩹<br/><br/>Also, please remember to check if the idea you’re about to drop hasn’t already been entered by another user. Avoiding duplicates makes the job much easier on our side.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH</div><br/>As usual, let’s keep in touch on Discord and Focus Together. You can also follow us on our socials: Instagram, X, Facebook, Threads and Bluesky.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield, Space Marines. <br/><br/><i>The Focus and Saber Teams. 🦾</i><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500571481680380533</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">​Hello Space Marines,</div><br/><br/>The 7.2 hotfix is now live on every platform. This patch aims at fixing various network issues, as well as black screens that could appear when finishing an Operation. <br/><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PATCH NOTES</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Fixed multiple network issues.<br/></b></li><li> Fixed a possible black screen issue when finishing operation.</li></ul>[/b]<br/>[/list]<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the value in the description of Heavy’s "Auxiliary ammunition".<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug on Bulwark's perks that could be triggered by friendly fire.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the Hive Tyrant that could get stuck in its charging animation in some specific cases.</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497193785816515049</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/9bb5853c8b524d66875299a646da26d866d14785.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>We’re back with Hotfix 6.1.3, bringing a host of fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III, from Kislevite supporters to Beastmen’s lost shards.<br/><br/>Let’s get into it!<br/><br/>— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Squigherd<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Highlights</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where The Ice Court and The Great Orthodoxy would get stuck at 100/100 supporters after quest battles without increasing tier<br/></li><li> Fixed Beastmen being able to settle without creating a Herdstone, causing them to permanently lose their shards.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where flying spellcasters would be constantly spinning round in circles.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues // Still Cooking</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Manually abandoning a settlement in a Bloodground as a Beastmen faction results in the 3DUI not updating properly and showing the settlement as not a part of the Bloodground.<br/></li><li> When loading a saved game from before version 6.1.3 as a Beastmen faction, the region occupation restrictions get updated on End Turn, not on load.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue so that Beastmen can no longer occupy regions in a Bloodground without actually raising a Herd stone. This used to be allowed in error and consumed a shard without providing an avenue to get it back.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players could open a panel using hotkeys during the transition from pre to post-battle<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where confederated leaders would not automatically get Followin' Da Plan points if confederated while wounded when playing as the Ironclaw Orcs<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when losing a settlement while an Ataman is traveling to it.<br/></li><li> Added additional negative diplomatic relations between Cathay factions and their enemy rebel factions to stop them finding too much harmony in the early game. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Skulltaker's tongue was missing during the intro cinematic to 'The Slayer Sword' quest battle<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Cockatrice didn’t have a recruitment cap when being recruited by Beastmen armies (Old saves will likely see some mild confusion, as existing Cockatrice in those saves will technically be the Tzeentch version, which is not capped).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where The Ice Court and The Great Orthodoxy would get stuck at 100/100 supporters after quest battles without increasing tier.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Flying casters could spin around when casting spells and moving simultaneously (although spinning is a good trick)<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Empire War Wagon units would bleed from their wooden // metal parts when hit.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where blood would spurt out The Vampire Coast’s Deck Gunners unit cannon when hit.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with how blood VFX displayed for Demigryph Knights.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Battle Maps</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in Zhufbar (Dwarfs) where units could fall through the ground in certain areas of the map.<br/></li><li> Fixing some overlapping assets that were visually glitching on the Erengrad (Kislev) battle map.<br/></li><li> Fixed shallow water in playable area being too deep on the Troll Country (Kislev) battle map.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue on Quenelles (Bretonnia) map where the camera could go inside the river on one side.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some buildings would incorrectly float on the Gaen Vale (High Elves) battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed issues where some terrain lacked collision and units were able to climb very steep surfaces on the battle map for Kemmler's Chaos Tomb Blade quest<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where water on the battle map wasn’t displaying properly for Mother Ostankya’s ‘Jinxed Land’ quest<br/></li><li> Fixed various issues relating to building placement and stretched textures on assorted battle maps<br/></li><li> Performed tree surgery by removing trees that were clipping through buildings and tidied various misplaced assets across various battle maps<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where textures weren't placed properly in some areas on The Black Pyramid (Tomb Kings) battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue so that rebel rocks now obey gravity on The Pillar of Bone battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where units were passing and clipping through a group of rocks on the Aymara Swamp battle map, they have now been thrown in the river to prevent this.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues after updating to 6.1.3 please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Imperialis Expansion - Meet the Familiars!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523089487392145673</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The <b>Lex Imperialis</b> expansion for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader is just around the corner, and today, we begin our reveals with its biggest and most exciting feature:<br/><br/><b>The Familiars!</b><br/><br/>From the hints we dropped in our latest AMA, and with the expansion revolving around the Adeptus Arbites, many of you have already figured out that the good boy is on his way. <br/><br/>What most of you probably didn't expect is that there is not one but <b>FOUR</b> creatures that may now accompany your Rogue Trader, thanks to the brand new <b>second-tier Overseer archetype</b>!<br/><br/>Abelard, introduce:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">1) The Cyber-Mastiff</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/10901e59314e3bcf961f618736fdbc433f0936a2.gif"/><br/><br/>Often seen accompanying Rogue Traders with the Arbites origin, these mechanized canine predators provide martial support during both combat and exploration, protecting their master with utmost ferocity. Notably, Solomorne Anthar, the new companion hailing from the ranks of the Adeptus Arbites, also employs one of these fearless beasts.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">2) The Psyber-Raven</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/060882ad49c7762354213fe42a4cfb49f12e633f.gif"/><br/><br/>Available to Psykers, these specially bred avian creatures channel and amplify their master's psychic abilities, increasing their range, damage and number of possible targets, as well as providing additional effects.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">3) The Servoskull Swarm</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/7c610c59ad38251677be6525567e9fa7f2df4e94.gif"/><br/><br/>A useful tool often employed by imperial Officers and Operatives, these constellations of hovering servo-skulls provide surveillance, relay their master's abilities across the battlefield, and excel at harassing the enemy.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">4) The Cyber-Eagle</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a065f0ef40e602ea1923ab1023d8fe54268d27bc.gif"/><br/><br/>Valued by imperial Officers and Operatives for their speed and agility, these cybernetic aerial predators soar high above the battlefield, diving on command to blind and maim their master's enemies. They may also serve as the perfect distraction, sowing confusion among enemy ranks, and even potentially causing friendly fire.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/6ddc018f169b32c66b7417efce1eb4dac4156604.png"/><br/><br/>Are you ready to unleash your new potential?<br/><br/>Stay tuned — we'll be sharing more about the new <b>Overseer</b> archetype, the new <b>Arbites</b> origin, and other info about the Lex Imperialis expansion soon!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication Breakdown!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520837698904129739</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/50a49917f42f1c39ca7b94d4cc715f943940b6c9.png"/><br/><br/>The Traitorous 6th have disrupted Hive communications with tainted technology.<br/><br/>You must root out these tech-heresies and restore regular Hive communications.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CjAlTL9y2O8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><b>To make progress in the event, find Tainted Communications Devices and complete the hacking sequence. Then, finish the mission. Each device will grant you 1 point of progress.</b><br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, April 24. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/66c55cabc88b396f591efc095d3fb644716c0d8f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
