<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Bomb Rush - Timed Mode 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/6537626672205704293</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks, time for some firewerkz!</b><br/><br/>For this weekend, we've a new Limited Time Event game mode, Bomb Rush, <br/><br/>Bomb Rush is Kill Konvoy with the bomb spawn rate turned up by x4!<br/><br/>This is an extra, optional game mode that sees players constantly racing to reach new bombs and detonating them on the enemy Stompa. It's much a faster paced game mode where defence is much more difficult, but speed and racing provide more of the focus.<br/><br/>This mode will apply to all 8vs.8 Kill Konvoy maps and will end on Monday <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0dac166cfa66c68b706612dc32092b9b9741c65b.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! <br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703537439791435817</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains and all Warhammer enthusiasts!<br/><br/>A great event called <b>Warhammer Day</b> is in full swing at this very moment! The endless war is raging in the grim darkness of the far future. Join the fight against vile enemies of Humanity and bring glory to the Imperium. May the light of the God-Emperor guide you on your way to victory!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/dca8927d0590393de9db5a9d8352c1519fd00505.jpg"/><br/><b>Warhammer Day</b> will take place till October 7, and countless discounts on the games in your favourite Universe are already waiting for you to claim. So let’s not waste any time and take a look at what good deals this grandiose event has to offer:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Unlimited power grants its bearer unimaginable opportunities. Become an all-mighty Rogue Trader and take command of the great von Valancius dynasty by getting the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game <b>at a 40% discount</b>! Forge the future of the Koronus Expanse!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><br/>A vile Genestealer threat, a new romanceable companion, and archetypes are ready for you to discover in the recently released Void Shadows DLC! Get access to this Expansion, as well as the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC by getting Season Pass <b>at a 40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Upgrade your experience with new in-game items and digital add-ons! The unique weapons, pet, new throne, and voidship model, as well as the artbook, soundtrack, and wallpapers pack are longing to be claimed as a part of Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack <b>at a 40% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Ultima Founding DLC announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4693404340619804511</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
To celebrate Warhammer Day, we are really excited to share some really important news about <b>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius</b>. <br/><br/>As part of the celebration, all our Warhammer games have joined a special sale. Please check our steam page to see all the details: <br/>https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/Slitherine<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Ultima Founding DLC </div><br/>The Primaris Space Marines will be joining the battle for Gladius Prime on December 10th. <br/>Featuring 8 new units, the Primaris are ready to step in the battle for the God Emperor  and the Holy Throne. <br/><br/>Unit lists:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primaris Intercessor<br/></li><li> Primaris Aggressor<br/></li><li> Primaris Hellblaster<br/></li><li> Primaris Inceptor<br/></li><li> Primaris Invader ATV<br/></li><li> Storm Speeder Thunderstrike<br/></li><li> Primaris Redemptor Dreadnought<br/></li><li> Primaris Repulsor Executioner</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696782040340188230</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines</div><br/>Congratulations, after more than a decade of waiting, you’ve finally pursued Lieutenant Titus’ journey and you’re now honoring your pledge to the Emperor!<br/>We have some news to share in this Community Update, make sure you read it carefully!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">First of all, thank you… 💙</div><br/>On September 9, we released a long-time project - Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2, and your feedback has overflown us with pride and joy. We saw you smile, laugh, purge xenos and demonstrate undeniable loyalty to the Imperium.<br/><br/>The amount of players kept increasing over the month, rallying more Space Marines to the cause, which is amazing. We want to let you know that we love the game as much as you do, and we’ll take good care of it, offering new content and listening to the community in the upcoming months.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a98158606c540cd7d874f94c1c764dfce8617dbc.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Upcoming content 💫</div>A hotfix will arrive very soon! It mostly intends to fix crashes and improve stability.<br/>In the future, expect quality of life improvements, additional customization features (such as new colors for the lenses), and more. For PC players: a 4K Texture Pack will be downloadable! It will be entirely free.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">YOUR FUTURE BRIEF</div>The new map for Operations mode, located on Planet Kadaku, will arrive in October. Here’s your brief:<br/><br/><i>The Tyranid invasion of Kadaku is ending. The planet’s organic material is being transformed into biomass, and Tyranid Capillary Towers stretch high into the skies above, where the Hive Ships wait to taste their victory.<br/>The Cadian forces have made a valiant attempt to push back against the Tyranids. A team of Space Marines arrives on Kadaku with a simple mission: help the Cadians destroy the towers. The Tyranids may win the planet, but the Imperium will make it as painful as possible for them.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ea8e4d47f0ca45ce397a78fe792d6c22b51cb365.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug Patches and Questions 👾</div><br/><b>Therefore, our duty is not done here.</b><br/><br/>We’ve seen that many of you were experiencing server issues and other bugs. We’re taking your feedback into account for our future updates. An important patch was deployed here. It corrected a few bugs and added features such as:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Private mode for Operations<br/></li><li> The Hub Sparring Arena<br/></li><li> Ultrawide support (for PC)<br/></li><li> Improved spawns in multiplayer<br/></li><li> Rebalancing of various enemies you encounter in Campaign and Operations mode<br/></li><li> Correction of bugs that prevented players from progressing through certain levels</li></ul>Nevertheless, we’re still working on the remaining bugs.<br/><br/>We’ve also brought answers to many questions raised by you, on different platforms (mostly Focus Together, Discord and Steam). Many of these questions were answered in our Message to Community, which you may find here.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f60c85e6b08d5337a57570cc7deb6bbd6c203400.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Be loyal to the cause, be respectful 🙏</div>It has been reported that some players were displaying hurtful behaviors or comments in-game. We do not tolerate that and will take action to prevent it. <br/><br/>First and foremost, we kindly ask you to remain respectful, mature and mannerly with your fellow Space Marines. You can never know how old the other players may be, how their day is going, how sensitive they may be… overall, you never know who your brothers and sisters are… It could even be Henry Cavill 😏 … you don’t want to insult Henry Cavill, brother, no you don’t.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fba66fe0818eada0763654837c9744c502e5f492.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">See you next month, for your next brief. 🫡</div>That’s it for September! These community updates will take place at the very end of every month. The goal is to keep players updated on upcoming content, updates, patches and news! So stay tuned and sign in to Focus Together to make sure you don’t miss a piece of it.<br/><br/>If you want to join the community and easily find mates to play with, you should join the official Space Marine 2 Discord Server! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Check the roadmap below!</b></div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For the Emperor.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titus Talks: Episode 3 is here... and it's about Space Marine 2!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696781406112877915</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!!</div><br/>The grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000 can be daunting to dive into! This is why we're are thrilled to introduce the second episode of the “Titus Talks” a 3-part video series presented by Lieutenant Titus himself, Clive Standen, and dedicated to welcoming newcomers to the rich expanse that is the 41st millennium. ✨<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Watch Episode 3: What is <i>Space Marine 2</i>?</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8uRz5UBuZaQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">This episode focuses on introducing players to game itself.</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> What is the backstory of Titus from <i>Space Marine 1</i>? <br/></li><li> What is Space Marine 2's gameplay like? <br/></li><li> Once I'm done with the campaign, what are mulitplayer modes like? </li></ul>Presented by Clive Standen, who voices Lieutenant Titus in the game, today’s video lecture is the conclusion to a three part series you can find on the Focus Entertainment YouTube channel.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/95c6c33219c5664bd4a2cc2f61e9ba8fb83754bb.png"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available now on PC. Get the Gold or Ultra Editions to secure your Season Pass!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>To get the latest info about <i>Space Marine 2</i>, follow our socials and:<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's dedicated on Focus Together<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's Discord server]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
