<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Barktide: The Pets of Fatshark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/507339561744990504</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">You’ve met Molly in our Introducing: The Cyber-Mastiff - Dev Blog so we thought it was time we introduced you to the rest of the pets of Fatshark!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Monty</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1aa441e1aa77fd0799bd21b28a59b7a0d0dd6595.jpg"/><b>Name:</b> Monty aka Monster or Egg<br/><b>Age:</b> 3<br/><i>Monty’s Owner is Kitefin!</i><br/><b>Bio:</b> Monty is a little mixture of several breeds (4, and I bet you can’t guess them all!), he is somehow super energetic and also the laziest dog I have ever met. He’d happily spend all day in bed if he could and actually runs away from me when I pick up his lead to take him out, but at the same time goes absolutely nuts for fetch and any kind of ball game. For a little while as well he did doggy agility and was not too bad at it despite his little legs. He refused to really do any of it until the day I bought cheese with me as a reward and then he decided he actually did know how to do it and was just being stubborn. Go figure.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> One of the naming choices for your Cyber-Mastiff is after Monty.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Scooby</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d66e01021c425b1d4fdaef2986b9785e96d0963.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Scooby (Scoobster/Scoobert/Bubek)<br/><b>Age: </b>7<br/><b>Bio: </b>Scooby is a mini Jack Russell that thinks he’s the star of his own cartoon. Anxiety? Absolutely. Goofy snack gremlin? Also yes. Training him to roll over was like teaching a goldfish to ride a bike. But once he got it, he started rolling for funsies and now assumes every spin deserves a treat. Classic Scooby logic. His hobbies include cuddling, snacking, and being everyone’s emotional support goofball.<br/><b>Fun Fact/Bonus talent: </b>Professional mushroom detective. Mushroom pickers have nothing on Scooby.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Bobby</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/d902981f1ad53bb08ea884fb7f1229d2b1c151e4.png"/><b>Name: </b>Bobby<br/><b>Age: </b>2<br/><b>Bio: </b>Bobby is a British Shorthair with the relatively rare lilac ticked coat variation. His personality is truly special—he’s almost like a little person. He follows me everywhere I go in the apartment, waits outside the bathroom for me, and, best of all, he absolutely loves playing hide-and-seek.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Every evening, I hide behind the bed and wait for him to jump out and ‘scare’ me. When he does, he lets out a proud little meow, his eyes sparkling with excitement, and then he dashes off to hide so I can find him.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Bobby has two favorite positions he loves to sit or lie in. Often, we’ll find him lying on his back with his belly up, which is his unique way of asking for attention. He also likes to sit upright like a little squirrel, with his front paws resting in front of him.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">One of Bobby’s favorite treats is boiled egg yolk—he usually pushes the egg white aside. His favorite time of day is when he gets to lie in the sun on the balcony.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> He has an Instagram account: @mr_bobby_thecat.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Dexter</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/ba152b9b486c26c097383012ecebf84183aebc2b.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Dexter aka Fatboy or Lupu<br/><b>Age: </b>7<br/><i>Dexter’s owner is Lev!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>Dexter is a swish tuxedo gentleman. He was rescued at 3 years old from a hoarder’s home having been neglected, and has an amusing habit of licking plastic, likely due to these earlier years. I was actually catfished by Dexter, as his adoption photo was very outdated, and when I went to collect him he was a much chonkier boy!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">A classic cat - he lives for food, comfort and mischief. He’s incredibly affectionate (has no concept of personal space) loving cuddles and snoozing under a duvet. On the odd occasion that he isn’t being lazy, he’s pushing his luck with questionable parkour and zoomies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hands down the most vocal cat I’ve ever encountered. He’ll always remind you when it’s time for food, often 2 hours before for good measure.<br/><b>Fun Fact:</b> His favourite toy is his shark. Great taste!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Duo Duo</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f66a48fd6971ff8c149984a6db2e08dc7dc61b45.jpg"/><b>Name: </b>Duo Duo<br/><b>Age: </b>11<br/><b>Bio: </b>I picked this piggy up from the streets thinking I did him a favor. Now he just sunbathes and screams for shrimps. No dignity remains.<br/><b>Fun Fact: </b>He will only eat poached shrimps from a specific brand.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Mochi &amp; Tai</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4a42413e005862fc5dfdf281cef86c2d75e3b797.png"/><b>Names: </b>Mochi (Left) &amp; Tai (Right)<br/><b>Ages: </b>8 Months (They’re both rescues, Mochi was found when he was around 2 months old, Tai was found about a month later. From what we can tell they’re the same age but it’s hard to tell when you find them on the street.)<br/><i>Mochi &amp; Tai’s Owners are Quickpaw!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>They’re SUPER close! While Tai was extremely scared of Mochi for the first couple of days, by the third day he realized he wasn’t aggressive and just wanted to play and they’ve been best buds ever since, they bonded really well! They’re always playfighting together or cuddling and grooming each other.<br/><b>Fun Facts: </b>Mochi is a climber, while Tai is a jumper.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Reymond</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/33836af815b475085ea6662ae1ba840f9b654ea3.jpg"/><br/><b>Name: </b>Reymond<br/><b>Age: </b>Around 5<br/><i>Reymond’s Owner is Catfish!</i><br/><b>Bio: </b>He was a foster cat of mine but fell in love with him and now he is staying! He was found in someone’s garden living off birdseed.<br/><b>Fun Fact: </b>He couldn’t meow when he first got to me, but now has learnt a very squeaky meow to communicate that he would like food.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">These are only a small handful of the amazing pets of Fatshark, we hope you enjoyed meeting them!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We know many of you are eager to see what’s coming next. We’ll be sharing more about the upcoming update soon, so keep an eye out for our next blogs!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 10.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/516346761000779977</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3"><b>​Hello Space Marines</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">A hotfix has just been pushed on every platform. Following your feedback, we <b>increased the amount of Accolades rewarded for daily Stratagems.</b> Also, the bug causing the Trygon to disappear in this week’s stratagem has been fixed, among other fixes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Read the complete patch notes below:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>PATCH NOTES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>GAMEPLAY AND BALANCING TWEAKS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Melee (PvE only)</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Power Axe:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Slash Momentum and Discharge perks places are switched.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Whirlwind attacks are widened and damage is increased by 50%.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Power Step attack damage is increased by 66%.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Slash Momentum perk description is showing correct numbers now.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Combat Knife:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heroic Combat Knife version “Power Gladius” bonus damage for perfect dodge increased to 120%.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Note that description is still incorrect, the bonus damage affects all attacks, not light attacks only.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Bulwark:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Shield Rush attack can no longer stun lock Terminus enemies.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Stratagems</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased rewards for daily Normal and Hard Stratagems to 10 and 15 respectively.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Suboptimal State Battlefield Condition HP penalty is reduced from 75% to 66%.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>PvP</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Multi-Melta:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">The interval between shots is now enforced when transitioning to the standing position. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Additionally, the rate of fire from hip fire has been increased from 35 to 50 rounds-per-minute.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>CUSTOMISATION</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of minor customisation fixes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mark VIII Errant Helmet without decorations is now available for purchase. (<i>Mark VII without decorations will be available later as well).</i></p></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Ultramarines Champion Armour Parts are now correctly locked by the Ultramarines Champion Pack DLC.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>LEVELS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Operation Vortex: </b>Armoury Data is correctly rewarded for killing the Vortex Beast.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>GENERAL FIXES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug causing the Trygon Prime to leave the boss arena to attack Cadians in Stratagem mode.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug with the Emperor's Vengeance perk (Tactical) not restoring Melta Charges for Heroic Bolt Rifle version (Combi-Melta).</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed: Stratagems didn't work when offline.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a rare issue in Helbrute Onslaught game mode causing a black screen after selecting a class. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor localization fixes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of minor bug fixes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2"><b>TECH</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Crash fixes and general stability improvements.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>KNOWN ISSUES</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">More than 4 Battlefield Conditions can currently be active in a single Stratagem mission, but the selection menu will only show 4 of them. Will be fixed and limited to 4 in an upcoming hotfix.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">On "Exfiltration", Bots are not following the player through the elevator to enter the base. This can be caused when enemies are still in the area. Completely clearing the area and rushing to the elevator before the next wave spawns should prevent this issue.</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 09:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.7.2 - 9th of September</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546745424093906943</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hotfix 6.7.2 - 9th of September</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This hotfix includes a handful of fixes and tweaks for Feast of Grimnir, as well as some grimoire fixes that mostly affect Horn of Magnus.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Feast of Grimnir changes:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added and re-shuffled placements of ammo boxes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked grenade spawners.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Made sure all grenade spawners also spawn fire grenades</p></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed collision issues in Horn of Magnus.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked the collisions of Grimoires to prevent issues where they weren’t grabbable when they should.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Feast of Grimnir fixes:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added extra collision in various places to prevent the Cog or Barrels from getting out of bounds.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Filled in some small holes in walls</p></li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 08:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Race Mode 🏁 + Level Editor Coming</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515220226701264588</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">This is an exciting time for <i>Speed Freeks,</i> because we're on the verge of releasing some <b>level editing tools</b> that will allow you to place structures, platforms, ramps, jump pads, decorations, VFX, etc in maps and then run races through them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Races will be played through the new <b>Kustom Rally</b> mode, either solo or multiplayer 🏁</p><p class="bb_paragraph">It's gonna be so cool <b>🤘</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You'll have assets like these to <b>build whatever you want</b>, races up towers, through obstacle courses, off huge jumps, etc. All decorated the way you think an Ork like you would do it!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c9ea0bbeac494eff278778cde21a8fdb00aab654.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f339e082bfdc3c73978f01a11b60bd84378c89f1.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aea0a96b2ec2d7d49a45f39f39ceab65357dcf95.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You can imagine the uniqueness and creativity will be so much higher, and we're so pumped to see what you gits come up with <b>💪</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll be adding our own creations to the game as well to be installed with the Creation Tools patch.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">And as far as we know, Speed Freeks will be the first Warhammer 40,000 game to include level editing tools like this where you can build custom structures and things from scratch. Very Orky :)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/70807a26bbba9ce2680231e42b257aba64731aed.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Before jumping into the rest of this blog, we thought it would be right to address the big squig in the room - which is that the game has a <b>player count</b> problem. We're well aware that there's not as many gits ingame these days as we would have hoped, and we're working to remedy that fact with enticing new content, as well as promotional pushes where we can.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To those of you who are just joining us now, or have stuck with the game through even a fraction of its development, we thank you so much for krumping with us. We're still working to improve the game as much as possible and as mentioned, have some really fun stuff coming.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you could jump ingame to welcome the new players with open arms (and a side of Dakka), that would be awesome.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We look forward to continuing the speedin' and krumpin' together. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4632f08ea6bbd65d79448452c0b0d37c241b0742.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now let's get stuck in!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>KUSTOM RALLY</b> 🏁 (BETA)</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f6f0aa113103b0b23f21c0cc6425863b78f5f328.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Blaze through a lineup of community made races in this fast-paced racing mode! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">This patch comes with some developer-created courses included, but you can also <b>share/download races </b>here in the</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> Steam Discussion Thread or on the SF Discord in the #kustom-races channel. See the pinned posts for instructions 📌</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We're currently working on cloud integration to allow easy uploading, browsing, and sharing of community creations with ease, so that's something to look forward to as well!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>CREATION MODE</b> 🛠️ (BETA) </div><p class="bb_paragraph">As mentioned, we'll soon be introducing level building tools to the game that will allow players a ton of creativity in making stuff. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the meantime, we've still got the same functionality as before with Free Roam, except we've renamed the mode to Creation Mode as it's more fitting. Keep an eye on this mode for juicy updates 👌</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Here's some bug fixes to the mode as well:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">We've added a distance marker to the active waypoint for better communication.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">When playing custom races, the subsequent waypoint preview now has a different icon in addition to being yellow instead of green, and the finish line waypoint is now red.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There is now a finish line and a start gate, and player movement and abilities are frozen until the race starts.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">Once the adding creation tools are in the game, we'll continue to improve them for more functionality and customization. Super pumped about this feature!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MODIFIERS</b> ☣️</div><p class="bb_paragraph">These used to be part of early access as limited time modes, but now players can enable them when creating a new lobby.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">It's surprising how much they can change the feel of a match ːsteamthumbsupː</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Here's the available mutators:</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dakka Frenzy (Deff Rally)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Higher fire rate and lower cooldowns = MORE DAKKA! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Bomb Rush (Kill Konvoy)</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Many more bombs are spawned during play. Let the explosive chaos begin!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Random Vehicle</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A random vehicle is chosen for you every time you respawn</p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph">Give them a try! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As always, thanks for playing our little Orky game. We love seeing new players come in and talk about how pleasantly surprised they were after a session, but also the dedicated players who continue to have fun, posting gameplay clips and chatting in the SF Discord.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Jump in there if you want to konnect with other gits 👌</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Excited to see how you guys like the upcoming patches!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <img src="https://community.fastly.steamstatic.com/economy/emoticon/SF_Wazza"/><img src="https://community.fastly.steamstatic.com/economy/emoticon/SF_Zag"/><img src="https://community.fastly.steamstatic.com/economy/emoticon/SF_Dakka"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aecee421bbf54d8a1eb182f40f061f36e90e8fcc.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 17:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Season Pass II is available now, along with the cosmetic DLCs of Patch 10.0!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500583527919650279</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">It's time Space Marines, the wait is over!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Season Pass II is available!</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The season pass for the second year of DLC content for Space Marine 2 is out.<br/>You can get it here!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3b03741092fadd64b499c859b2603b18cc9558d8.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h2">Black Templars Champion and Imperial Fists Cosmetics</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Both the Black Templars Champion Pack and Imperial Fists Cosmetic Pack are available now! </p><p class="bb_paragraph">The former includes a new Champion skin for the Bulwark class and Power Sword skin, while the latter adds over 40 new cosmetics and heraldry markings celebrating 7 of the Imperial Fists’ Successor Chapters.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4de486b1925a59cd56c2423ce44327eda097fd76.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Ultramarines Champion Pack will arrive later on PC</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects.</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
