<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>June Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500577186633221225</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2"><b>Hello Space Marines!</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A few days ago, we released Patch 8.0 - Siege Update, including the Siege Mode, White Scars and Blood Angels Cosmetics, along with several improvements and minor changes. If you haven’t already, you should definitely read the full patch here<b>.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfnMHm-HvSI5LHVaMNjbipHYJAL34Q1SMZhHaaIfa-l9Zf1CPwlHzIrUjnU7QL0gzqqt-7MlpGl8gQtHOqymJn7atNKCr82Z_JPMDvi35RmyDD8tJy0HeTbahL7e1HuBKMeMkXm2A?key=EmFw4LBOwmmVaxw8jiOYWA"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now let’s rewind a bit, and mostly: let’s discuss <b>what’s coming as the first year of content is slowly coming to an end.</b> Shall we?</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>WHAT COMES AFTER YEAR ONE? 🧐</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As promised, we’re excited to share more details with you, and even more will be revealed in the upcoming Community Updates <b>this July and August.</b> For now, here are a few things we can confirm:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re happy to announce that a<b> second year of both free and DLC content included in a new yearly season pass is on the way! </b>This extended support to Space Marine 2 has been possible thanks to your unwavering support, so once again, thank you very much for being part of it!. Expect new PvE missions, enemies, weapons, and… more 👀 It’s too early to provide more info, but stay tuned! 😉</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Also, to celebrate the first anniversary of the game, <b>a large-scale update is planned for September,</b> the 10.0 major update. Update 9.0 will not bring new content, but only balancing changes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Unfortunately, that also means that the new PvP mode we were planning to release alongside the 9.0 update will be postponed to this big 10.0 update as well. While we can’t show you how it looks, the least we can do is to reveal what this new mode will be about:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This new mode will take place on a new map.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">It will oppose 2 sides, but it won’t be Loyalist VS Chaos like in regular PvP. Instead, Chaos will face… Chaos.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Last but not least, you’ll be able to take control of the Helbrute. Yup.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">As this new game mode is centered around Chaos, <b>new Chaos armours will also be added to the game.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A new <b>melee weapon</b> will also be added as part of this big 10.0 Update: the <b>Power Axe</b>! It will have its own moveset, execution animations etc… We’ll show you more on this weapon later on, but here’s a first look!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b9d4da70b5f382d137a5fc2c8a7c87556b8e5053.png"/><i>Work in progress, final version is subject to change</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, we announced a while ago that we are working on a new class for PvE and PvP. We’re now advanced enough in its development to announce that the new class will be a <u><b>Techmarine</b></u>! We’ll reveal more about this new class in the next community updates, so stay tuned! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>PATCH 8.0 IN DETAILS ⚙️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Patch 8.0 - Siege Update was available via the Public Test Server on Steam. Thanks to your feedback, we’ve made a bunch of tweaks and improvements for the live game release of the Patch. So, thank you for your participation! Let’s briefly review the content, or read the full patch notes for more details!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>SIEGE MODE</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Siege Mode is the new big feature coming with the Siege Update! Check the May Community Update for more details about the gameplay mechanics of this mode.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For those who played on the PTS and provided us with feedback, we heard you loud and clear! You expressed your disappointment regarding the timer. So we changed it a bit. Now, it goes as follows:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">⏱️ <u>The timer has changed!</u>⏱️</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The biggest criticism regarding Siege mode from the community was the wave timer limit. It exists only for technical reasons, because killing lots of enemies causes memory fragmentation (which, to simplify, would cause a crash after a certain threshold).</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>We've made some optimizations so the Siege mode can last longer. Timer got reworked, instead of having a limited timer per wave that can get to a very short time on higher waves, there is a timer for the entire session and each time you beat a wave the timer increases. We've also adjusted the difficulty curve of infinite waves so enemies will get stronger faster after the 15th wave. These changes will make players die in fair combat rather than due to the timer. </i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Also, with some optimizations coming down later we think we can get rid of the timer entirely.</i></p></blockquote><p class="bb_paragraph">We truly hope you’re enjoying Siege Mode as much as we are and we’re still open to feedback!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>WHITE SCARS CHAPTER PACK</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Assault Class Champion comes with several cosmetics and 3 exclusive weapons skins for the Occulus Bolt Carbine, the Stalker Bolt Rifle, and the Combat Knife.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b066256ea388e1db5bd6cd8e09d0c10107cd25eb.jpg"/></p>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c0fc4a0e132d08919324e6e27654fe15b3958f0a.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0254e5bfaa406e0d3d52e12db225d7cd3bd87237.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f0a261a65d0e9e65f99d2e59ec33868f81f85c4.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6db692fa5ef96c40a3454b8eafdfcf58f7d9b219.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b73fa5f9b8a36fa2e713d59c294a66e6f6151489.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b4c834898fa174b67debd3bf94cb8ed02cab7f98.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>WHITE SCARS SUCCESSOR CHAPTERS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The White Scars Successor Chapters are the Dark Hunters, Destroyers, Mantis Warriors, Marauders, Rampagers, Solar Hawks, Storm Lords, Storm Reapers.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/655eb173ed2eca7c774a8e168c2a24b8467f1e0b.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>BLOOD ANGEL COSMETIC PACK</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e9b00e197758eebd0757f8b7881c56347bd9766e.jpg"/></p>[carousel]<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2fb39e0f5017cf83ce924c48783bd696c67ac436.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/46d0d37e4263b8b2ba15f7bd6d5127e61871dc7b.jpg"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6b8123edd3debacc0b18ab3e0d9d99dd7d4347a5.jpg"/>[/carousel]<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>BLOOD ANGELS SUCCESSOR CHAPTERS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Blood Angels Successor Chapters are the Angels Penitent, Angels Sanguine, Atlantian Spears, Blood Dragons, Blood Scythes, Flesh Eaters, Flesh Tearers, and Lamenters.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a6af15513e741d68664e97913333b2c31905a3b.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>TWITCH DROPS COME WITH PATCH 8.0 📽️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To celebrate the release of Patch 8.0, Twitch Drops return! This time, get the Mark VIII Errant Helmet, Mark XI Hell’s Teeth Pattern Chainsword and the Porphyr Shield Bolt Pistol!<br/><br/>The rules go as follows: from June 25 11PM CEST to July 14 11PM CEST: </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">30min watch time of any streamer playing SM2 → Mark VIII Errant Helmet</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">60min watch time → Mark XI Hell’s Teeth Pattern (Chainsword)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">120min watch time → Porphyr Shield (Bolt Pistol)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdrj3WB0VbvhcZI-Dz9M1RD72vY7GVVKqX-1uhAXPoAoR65LCr6lWw0dThHVvqFUkIcApWIaZ8YXJOMuh1elZW182ipXamShUgc6mCCkbUVBGeqbi8pthE4ecVKmK6DDXe-hWT2?key=EmFw4LBOwmmVaxw8jiOYWA"/></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>RTAO &amp; DLSS 4 SUPPORT</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>RTAO</b> experimental feature added: enabled in-game video settings.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>DLSS 4</b> provides better upscale, and multi-frame generation for 50xx series cards.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>FEW CHANGES FOR PVE AND QOL IMPROVEMENTS</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>PVE:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Class and weapon perks balancing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Possibility to have multiple terminus enemies spawning in Absolute Difficulty</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Option to turn off bots in Operations and Siege mode Private Lobbies</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Thunder Hammer on Bulwark (PvE only)</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b041bb391089db7897908c58b3687c564205eb56.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1"><b>FAN CONTEST 🧑‍🎨</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Last month we launched a Fan Art Contest with the May Community Update. You were asked to produce any piece of art related to the Campaign Mode of Space Marine 2! 🎨</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">WryWood did it brilliantly and won 2 keys for Space Marine 2! They came up with these two adorable figures of Brother Valtus and a Tyranid in the midst of a fight!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/51058fe476e123ac8b3a029fc1738c999478e2f8.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Such a big piece must have taken a lot of time and effort so make sure you drop a nice little comment under <u>WryWood’s post</u>, to say congrats! 🎊</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">As usual, let’s keep in touch on Discord and Focus Together. You can also follow us on our socials: Instagram X Facebook Threads Bluesky</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">See you on the battlefield, Space Marines. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>The Focus and Saber Teams. 🦾</i></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #70 (1.8.2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520843384949048569</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b946614a20957cd8af2f5eb5416a8e360d0a0310.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hotfix #70 (1.8.2) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed banter frequency: banter has been increased for all classes during missions. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Solved a common crash that could occur when browsing companion skins.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the server to crash when players would step in specific locations in several missions.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the description of Fan the Flames blessing so that the correct values are displayed.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing weapon names to be cut off when inspecting them.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was preventing tagging from working properly.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">More improvements to how cosmetics and rewards are displayed in the inventory.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some debug strings were visible in the tactical overlay.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Psyker 'on critical hit' talents would trigger when burn stacks are active on enemies.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing part of the character to become invisible while changing cosmetics.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated descriptions of the “Lightning Reflex” and “Counterattack” blessings to consistently use “Perfect Block”.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some lines in the Orthus Offensive mission would be inaudible.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the Zealot “Hexorcist's Breeches” lowerbody cosmetic item having the wrong footstep modulation.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the incorrect inclusion of the Radio Operator in the “Elitist” penance.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where an incorrect skull icon would be shown in the Mission Request popup.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed the icons for experience and Ordo dockets being in the wrong order on the Mission Terminal.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Difficulties can now be swapped by pressing on the diamond shapes in The Meat Grinder.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the “New Weekly Contracts” notification would show up even when Sire Melk’s Requisitorium was not yet unlocked.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased the spacing between the text and the border on the right-hand side of the special condition text.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lightened up the vignette effect on the zoomed-in view of the Mission Terminal in order to see more of the hive. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed the default value of the settings for the companion nameplate: all player Companion nameplates are now visible by default in the Mourningstar.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Heavily reduced the pixelated effect from mission board thumbnails.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the skybox would occasionally be visible after completing a Campaign mission.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Auric Difficulty Changes</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">New High Intensity added which will be active during High Intensity missions on the Auric level difficulty; this change will bring higher enemy count and increased spawn rate, more frequently occurring specials and hordes spawning.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Auric used to be Damnation with the guarantee of modifiers with High Intensity applied, that intensity has been applied as a baseline to new Auric, thus missions on the Auric Board may now appear as both High Intensity and Non-High Intensity.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic &amp; Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where parts of the Infantry, Helbore, and Recon Lasguns did not show with texture quality settings set to "High".</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some Cyber-Mastiff animations were blending with the player character in End of Round poses.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Several improvements to player animations.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue causing swing trails to be missing on Shock Maul and Suppression Shield weapons.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing headgear to overlap and cover the entire head.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the lower plate and cloth on the Psyker “Detio's War Plate” upperbody cosmetic clips with the chest piece while crouching.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some deformation issues on the Psyker “Vostroyan Chain Hood with Psykana Collar” headgear cosmetic.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Veteran “Ocular Augmetic and Blue Face Mask” headgear cosmetic would remove too much hair.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed instances of hair clipping on the Veteran “Witchhunter's Hat with Mask” and Zealot “Witchhunter's Hat” headgear cosmetics.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Arbites Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>General Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated localized description text for the following Arbites weapons.   </p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Exterminator Shotgun Mk III + VIII.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Subductor Shotpistol and Riot Shield.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a typo in the “That’s Not Fair!” Arbites Commendations Character Creation option.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed instances of the Arbites class occasionally using voice lines from other classes.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where it was not possible to deploy a Nuncio-Aquila while sprinting.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with Cyber-Mastiff nameplate being displayed in missions even though interface setting was set to off.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with the position of the Arbites Shock Maul on Hadron's table on the Empower menu.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a crash that might occur when throwing grenades with an Arbites character during Basic Training.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff was spawning when looking at player cosmetics in the Commodore’s Vestures.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue where 'Razor-Jaw Augment' didn't properly apply Bleed to all targets hit by the Pounce knockback.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where Keeping Protocol talent was increasing damage to enemies other than Monstrosities.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Shock Maul and Suppression Shield charge display was not showing any outline until the first bar was shown.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where an incorrect message was displayed when changing the appearance of your Cyber-Mastiff in the Barber-Chirurgeon.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where some enemy units were sliding on the floor after having been pounced by the Cyber-Mastiff.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Nuncio Aquila effect failed to disappear in the end mission cutscene.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue that was causing the weapon rarity text to run off the UI window for the Exterminator Shotgun.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Cyber-Mastiff could push Poxbursters even when not attacking anything.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Cosmetic &amp; Animation Fixes</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some clipping issues on both versions of the Arbites “Arbitrator Revelatum Plate with Covert Ops Coat” upperbody cosmetic.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the Arbites Precinct-specific decals would not always be applied correctly onto the related upperbody cosmetics.  </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some issues with the Arbites Precinct-specific decals being stretched or cut off while being applied on the following upperbody cosmetic items.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbitrator Patrol Plate.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbitrator Proctor Plate.</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the kneepads on the Arbites “Arbitrator Revelatum Fatigues (Lucis)” lowerbody cosmetic would appear slightly detached from the knee while squatting.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where the trinket attachment points were incorrectly placed on the Arbites “Shock Maul and Suppression Shield” and “Shock Maul” weapons.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where blood effects were not being applied on the Shock Maul and Suppression Shield head.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where human Backpacks were not available to the Arbites Class. Players who previously purchased any of the following premium cosmetics (backpacks) will now be able to equip them on their Arbitrator:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Pilgrim's Scroll Tube</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Vox-Caster "Theta-901"</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enlightening Reading</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Feretory With Sconces</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Players who previously purchased any of the following premium cosmetics (implants) will now be able to equip them on their Arbitrator:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Spectrus VI Model Bionic Eye</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">MkIVz Occular Augmetic</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">MkIIg Occular Augmetic</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Voicebox Rebreather (Osclum III Pattern)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Intra-Cranial Implant</p></li></ul></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT FIX for Host Disconnections, Achievements, Game Names</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515213885413786267</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">OI, quick one 'ere</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with hosts being disconnected for seemingly no reason</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with certain achievements not popping (Roamin' Ded Far, Da Best Krumpa, etc)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stopped showing a user's PC name as default game name if they didn't change it</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with a capture point race not showing properly in Burna Valley</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Some networking improvements</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">K, back ta krumpin'</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/1b8870bcfba7a27794da6d2dc19290e48cb6530c.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.4.0.195 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762733065</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Our tech-priests worked day and night to prepare another hotfix, Lord Captain!<br/><br/>Praise the Omnissiah, more errors were eliminated.<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Saves with the issues described in the hotfix 1.4.0.190 (arena in Commorragh and the Lord Captain remaining in a different form after Thassera) are now retroactively fixed;<br/></li><li> The game could crash when entering Plundered Void Station if you already visited it before the DLC2 patch - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of visual issues with Chinese fonts;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs in co-op related to the hologram of the familiar in combat;<br/></li><li> Sometimes characters could move beyond the boundaries of the map on the Feudal World, walking through a wall - fixed;<br/></li><li> Improved the elevator cutscene on the Feudal World;<br/></li><li> Improved effect for the wall explosion on the Feudal World;<br/></li><li> White color scheme was added for the Cyber-Eagle familiar;<br/></li><li> A few broken dialogue options in Lex Imperialis were fixed and will now work correctly;<br/></li><li> Cyber-Eagle abilities could remain after a respec when another familiar was chosen;<br/></li><li> The Cyber-Eagle is now consistently returning to soaring above the battlefield at the end of its Overseer's turn;<br/></li><li> Rite of Solar Nourishment now correctly grants +5 Agility to the Psyber-Raven;<br/></li><li> The Psyber-Raven's Warp Buffer talent now works as intended, reallocating the Perils of Warp to the enemies. Behold the Unsanctioned Psyker!<br/></li><li> The Psyber-Raven's Psy-Resonator talent now correctly regenerates +1 AP to the Overseer;<br/></li><li> Servo-skull swarm Symbiosis  talent now correctly regenerates +1 AP to the Overseer;<br/></li><li> Fixed non-responsive controller buttons on the character screen;<br/></li><li> Polishing updates to some portraits;<br/></li><li> Sister Argenta can finally receive her Adepta Sororitas helmet that was seen in the trailers, but was lost during the original game release:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e6a40c841dad60698e7a9d065f2c4c853ee2c63f.png"/><br/><br/></li><li> Beautiful flame effects were added to the Martyr shield and Last Stand shield:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e42682e2b53d411d24ead7e1cf1e37da9969c092.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/22f64716c183f0130b8e3b2e04be8f1e6c3b4b49.gif"/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Sale is live! Get the game and its additional content with up to 50% off!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762732991</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
It's Summer Sale time! <br/><br/>Whether you are an experienced Lord Captain that wishes to expand their trade protectorate with new worlds and engage in new adventures in the Koronus Expanse, or you are only yet to receive your own Warrant of Trade and inherit the most sacred title of a Rogue Trader of von Valancius Dynasty, this is a good time to consider one or more of the following options!<br/><br/>1. Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration:<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>2. Gain access to two major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Void Shadows and Lex Imperialis, and expand your campaign with two new companions, exciting new storylines and new interesting mechanics, receiving over 30 hours of content at an additional discount:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/>3. For Rogue Traders whose ambition is beyond measure! Get the base game, Season Pass 1, Digital Artbook, Digital OST, Wallpaper Pack and a selection of in-game items for the ultimate experience:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/36542/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Edition/<br/>4. More is on the horizon for Rogue Trader! Get Season Pass 2 to instantly gain access to new character customization options, and a future access to two more upcoming expansions, both of which offer 15 hours of gameplay: In DLC III - The Infinite Museion, you will delve into a secret vault curated by Trazyn the Infinite himself, and in DLC IV - Processional of the Damned, you will venture into the Processional — a massive, otherworldly graveyard of ships lost to the void:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3650060/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass_2/<br/>5. Get two massive CRPGs by Owlcat Games - Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous at once, and explore both of these amazing worlds in huge, branched stories that last for hundreds of hours:<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/41660/Owlcat_Games_CRPG_Bundle/<br/><br/>These are just some examples of the available content for the game - check its page to find out about more options!<br/><br/>Your crew awaits your command, Lord Captain!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
