<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Random Vehicle - Timed Mode  💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4676515207786597647</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Random Vehicles</b> is a limited time mode that challenges players to succeed without selecting their preferred vehicle. Often a fun way to warm up, and who knows, random mode might introduce you to different styles of gameplay that you might not have considered before. <br/><br/>For this weekend, until Monday, vehicle select screen does not exist. Players are given a random vehicle each time they spawn.<br/><br/>This mode applies to all 8vs.8 Deff Rally maps<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c053a6ed3708e01119672334b0cdf738f6c5f604.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 4.1 and Game Director commentary</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4530150757095178287</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Hi, Space Marines!</div><br/><i>As we discussed late last week, we’ve been monitoring your feedback since last Thursday’s Patch 4.0 and have decided to address your most pressing concerns with a new balancing update, coming <b>this Thursday</b>.<br/><br/>Before we get to the details of the new patch, we want to thank you all for being so involved with the game and making your opinions heard. While we noticed criticism with regards to difficulty adjustments—and rightly so—we’d also like to thank you for your very positive feedback on the new “Termination” map. No matter the feedback, we’re grateful that you feel so passionate about <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>. The key takeaway for me, personally, is that I forgot that once the game comes out, it's no longer a dev's game. It's yours first and foremost.<br/><br/>This is why, moving forward, we’d like to harness this energy by establishing Public Test Servers. They would let you try out major balancing updates and make your voices heard before they are pushed onto public branches. We’re hoping to make these available around early 2025, so stay tuned to our channels for more info</i>.<br/><br/>‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎  -  Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a98158606c540cd7d874f94c1c764dfce8617dbc.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Gameplay and Balancing Tweaks - Operations mode </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">AI director and enemy spawns</div><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>Here was our reasoning before Patch 4.0: When the game came out in September, the Ruthless difficulty win rate hovered around 60%. Weeks later, and with the changes introduced by Patch 3.0, we saw that the same win rate had jumped to over 80%, and we received a lot of feedback stating that the game had become too easy—even at its maximum difficulty (at the time).</i><br/><br/><i>With Patch 4.0, our aim was to tweak enemy spawns to increase the overall number of enemies rather than reverting to buffing their Health. Unfortunately, this had an impact on the easier difficulty levels as well.<br/><br/>For example, the win rate on the easiest difficulty dropped slightly after Patch 4.0, from 95% to 93%. This may not look like a lot, but numbers aren’t everything. Your feedback made it clear that the game had become more intense and stressful on lower difficulties, and this was never our intention. As I’ve personally emphasised in interviews, Space Marine 2 is all about the power fantasy, and Patch 4.0 negatively impacted it for many of you.<br/><br/>This is why we’re rolling back these changes. Extremis enemies’ spawn rates in Minimal, Average, and Substantial difficulties will revert back to their pre-Patch 4.0 levels and will be significantly reduced in Ruthless difficulty to hopefully strike a balance between how hard the game was at launch and how “easy” it became with Patch 3.0.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u>Minimal, Average, and Substantial Difficulties</u>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reduced spawn rate of Extremis enemies to match pre-Patch 4.0 levels</li></ul><u>Ruthless Difficulty</u>:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Significantly reduced spawn rate of Extremis enemies</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ea8e4d47f0ca45ce397a78fe792d6c22b51cb365.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Weapons (only in Operations mode)</div><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>We've been wanting to address the Bolter family for a while, as they've been underperforming across all difficulty levels. This has been a frequent piece of feedback from many of you, and the data confirmed improvements were needed across the board. The percent Damage increase is based on which classes have access to which kind of weapon and how the Bolters compete with the other options available.</i> <br/>‎  <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Auto Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 20%<br/></li><li> Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Heavy Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Stalker Bolt Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Marksman Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Instigator Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 10%<br/></li><li> Bolt Sniper Rifle -&gt; Damage increased by 12.5%<br/></li><li> Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Occulus Bolt Carbine -&gt; Damage increased by 15%<br/></li><li> Heavy Bolter -&gt; Damage increased by 5%</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/48cbeba86ee7252b6da6a6c181eb6b66f4bd42e5.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Difficulty</div><br/><u><b>⚙️ Ruthless: Player’s Armour is increased by 10%</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>We are partially rolling back the change from the previous patch on Ruthless difficulty following your feedback. With Patch 4.1, we’re hoping to find the right compromise between how easy Ruthless difficulty felt after Patch 3.0 and how it felt after last week’s Patch 4.0.<br/> <br/>The reason why it was reduced last week was that we noticed a very substantial bump in win rates on Ruthless after Patch 3.0, as Minoris enemies would no longer remove the entire Armour bar with their attacks, ranged AI Damage was nerfed across the board, and the ability to regenerate Armour by parrying normal Minoris attacks was added.<br/><br/>Additional note: Despite the last patch notes listing a decrease in Armour in Substantial difficulty, this change was mistakenly left out of our last update, hence why you won’t see it being reverted as part of this week’s patch.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u><b>⚙️ Lethal: “Tight Formation” system is removed</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>Before anything else, let us clarify our reasoning for the introduction of this mechanic. As we worked on adding a new difficulty tier, we needed to make sure this new challenge was meaningful and interesting. With “Tight Formation”, our objective was to add a new layer of challenge for our most skilled players by adding horizontal progression rather than just vertical progression (i.e., dealing more damage to ever stronger enemies). This game is about the power fantasy, and enemies that take dozens of melee hits break it. Thus the challenge needed to come from other sources.<br/> <br/>This system was also designed as a first step towards the introduction of gameplay modifiers down the line, both negative and positive—something World War Z players will be familiar with—but your feedback showed that the proximity requirements felt too restrictive. Classes like Assault and Vanguard felt especially penalised as playing them effectively requires a certain freedom of movement.<br/><br/>As a result, we’re removing the system entirely and will continue to work on modifiers until they’re ready. We will continue to monitor your feedback after the deployment of Patch 4.1 to make sure Lethal difficulty feels as challenging and rewarding as it should.</i><br/>‎ <br/><br/><u><b>⚙️ AI</b></u><br/><br/><i>DG</i>: <i>A recurrent piece of feedback we’ve seen is that the AI allies can feel useless at times. We already improved allies’ behaviour in Patch 3.0, and we hope this additional buff will help solo players complete their Operations.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bots deal 30% more damage to bosses.</li></ul><i>DG</i>: Fighting Zoanthropes is often reported as a source of frustration. Alongside the changes to the AI Director, we’re taking away some of their shields’ effectiveness to alleviate some of that frustration.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Zoanthrope: Shield swap cooldown with another paired Zoanthrope is increased by 10%.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f60c85e6b08d5337a57570cc7deb6bbd6c203400.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes &amp; Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a bug that caused roll distance to be shorter than before.</li></ul><i>DG</i>: <i>This was probably the most impactful and annoying consequence of Patch 4.0. While i-frames were the same, the distance difference made it much less effective versus ranged attacks. With this bug fixed, you should feel a great improvement in your fights against ranged enemies and bosses.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed bug with unlocking Lethal difficulty rewards decals.<br/></li><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.</li></ul>Our teams are constantly working on improvements to the game’s stability. This patch is no exception, so you should encounter fewer crashes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0987068ebeefc14bd9004c2edbde7945e0fcb9a9.png"/><br/><br/>That’s it for Patch 4.1! Your feedback is absolutely invaluable to us, and we’re looking forward to hearing your thoughts on this new update. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Emperor protects.</div><br/><i>The Space Marine 2 team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darktide 101: The Sound of Darktide - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157956347822135</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/01ef06e14efbb8c704f98f66f0e55847f3cd6eaf.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Introduction</div>In Darktide we wanted all sounds to feel coherent and real, even though the Warhammer 40,000 universe is full of concepts based on fiction. It’s very easy as a sound designer to fall into cliches when making futuristic or fictive designs. You know, a sci-fi gun doesn’t have to go “pew-pew” when you shoot it. Me and the team actively avoided these cliches, because first of all it’s boring, and second of all, the Warhammer 40,000 universe has its own unique sounds.<br/><br/>My name is Johan W., one of the sound designers here at Fatshark. And in this dev blog I’m gonna go into some details in the process of creating the sound direction for Darktide.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">How It Started</div>A good place to start is to bring up Anders D. G., our Game Director. He was the one sitting on the vision for Darktide. We had a lot of chats about sound and music in general and shared references about how the world of Darktide should feel.<br/><br/>To me personally though, everything kind of started with a very particular sound. It’s a synth preset I did. I named it the Darktide Distortion Bend. There was nothing special about it really, but each time I played it, I got into a headspace I liked. It sounded dark and gritty, it had an analogue synth feel and it felt powerful and dangerous. This is a bit fuzzy I know, but I thought that described my idea of Darktide pretty well. From there, I started comparing everything I did to see if they’d fit together.<br/><br/>You can actually hear it in the very first teaser trailer we did (that wobbly distorted revving sound around 01:05 in the video).<br/><br/>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide - Official Teaser Trailer<br/><br/>And in the second trailer…<br/>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide - Official Gameplay Trailer<br/><br/>And in the sound of you dying…<br/>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1DIQNC3yeNAABI7q42VaQvzp9nFI8cOmp/view?usp=drive_link<br/><br/>The distortion bend-sound was actually my starting point even for the Lasgun, which we knew was gonna be one of the most important weapons to get right from the start. And we knew for certain that it wasn’t gonna sound like a generic sci-fi laser weapon. For that reason it went through tons of iterations just to find the balance between grittiness, punchiness and finding out what the “las”-part of the weapon was gonna sound like for Darktide. We wanted to create a lasgun sound that remained faithful to the source material. It also had to be at least somewhat satisfying to use, if anyone was gonna use it. I ended up working with mostly analog noises from electrical gear, some frying pan noises and some real gun sounds as well, just to up the realism. I decided to focus on the heat from the photons, instead of the “crack” that has sometimes been described (although there are a lot of cracking sounds when you’re running out of ammo instead). (Shoutout to my previous lead/boss Danijel Djuric who did the first prototypes for the Lasgun. I continued everything where he left it when he left the company.)<br/><br/>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UKBHbp8CaDEPW6WsA68GJHn0TUJRiT3r/view?usp=sharing<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9f62aadd1351b4b5c7bc6acd011bdd47b504261f.jpg"/><br/><br/>When I say analog noises, I mostly talk about this set of module synths that served me very well for Darktide. Not just for Lasguns but almost every psyker sound has something to do with this one.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3f8bdea576c88b73a981c514dcda34ab4e5df28e.jpg"/><br/><br/>Once a few more areas of the game started to shape up. We started to more accurately grasp what the sound of Darktide should be about. Eventually I tried putting it into words. The idea was that every sound we put in the game should follow this set of guidelines.<br/><br/>I’m just gonna copy paste what was written. It was only meant internally for the sound team. It’s very technical and perhaps super boring to most of you. But I feel like some of you might find it interesting. So here we go!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">The Sound Direction of Darktide</div>The soundscape of Darktide is made out of metal, dirt, analogue gear, broken electronics, old huge machines. Nothing is well oiled, so heavy squeak, creek, stress and spark sounds are a big part of the soundscape. “High-tech” doesn’t belong in this world. If something is digital it should feel like an old computer with broken harddrives and clunky buttons. It’s much closer to cyberpunk than sci-fi in that sense. High-pitched beeps and classic laser type of sounds are strictly forbidden, pure heresy. With Darktide we are not just creating a game-play experience, we are bringing a universe to life. That mindset should be reflected in how we design this game. It should feel like we are in a place too large to grasp, and the player is just a tiny piece in a large story taking place. We do this by emphasizing the scale of things.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Oversized Realism</div>Every single worldized audio source in Darktide should sound real, even though we are making a surreal game. We also want most things in Darktide to sound huge, larger than most items that exist in real life. This is a challenge, because it sounds contradictory. How do we create realism if there’s no real-life reference to compare it to? Here’s the answer… If a sound has a natural frequency balance, dynamic range and width that corresponds to the distance it’s being heard from, it’s going to sound realistic. So if we are designing, say, a pistol sound, we should first imagine it being at least twice the size of a real-life pistol and then reflect on how that would sound if it was real. If we are able to create a huge pistol sound, but also stay within a realistic frequency balance, dynamics and width, it’s going to fit into the Darktide universe.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Even Magical Sounds Should Be Organic</div>Every concept that involves unrealistic materials or sources of power should still be based on something organic. For example Las-weapons are based on electric sounds and old electronic gear. That way we can make it sound organic because there are a lot of real life recordings to use and get inspiration from. Plasma-weapons are based on water and some analogue synthesis. The warp mainly consists of pulsating analog circuits and glitches. This way we can maintain the feeling of realism even with the most unrealistic concepts. You will also much easier get high quality textures in the sounds when using real recordings as assets.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Dark and Gritty (But Not Harsh to Listen to)</div>Darktide should sonic-ally be pleasant on the ears, but nothing in this universe should feel pleasant. A successful example of this is when a sound feels gritty but not harsh on the ears. It’s very important to separate the sound design from the mix-quality of the sound. Both aspects need to be fulfilled in order to fit in the game. Always reflect before committing on a design choice, “Could I make this sound feel even darker?” Usually the darker the better. If a sound feels cute, happy, funny it doesn’t belong in this world. The only occasion we can allow ourselves to be comical is a dark sense of humor. In Darktide you can never go too horrifying or brutal.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Spatial Audio</div>The whole soundscape of Darktide is based on the principle that everything that can be spatialized, should be spatialized. Always 3D over 2D as long as it makes sense. Even stingers should strive towards always being 3D because we want to present it as an in-world sound. We wanna avoid non-diegetic sounds, even if that is the more traditional way of doing it. The only exception should be UI and player experience sounds.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Prioritize Game-Play in the Mix</div>Even if the design goal for Darktide is immersion and realism, game-play needs to be the priority when necessary. The human perception is limited and can’t hear everything at all times, especially from just a pair of speakers. So priorities need to be made in order to keep the mix readable. We should always strive for danger sounds (things that can hurt the player) and game-play informative sounds (e.g. hits, abilities, stingers, to be prioritized. It’s incredibly complex and we don’t always get it right, but we try our best.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Combat</div>Okay, so combat… The direction for the combat sounds went through some turns during production. We started off with the goal of making it feel as real as possible. Battlefield was a reference in several discussions about how the guns should feel (not sound). We thought that pure realism would fit the game direction perfectly, painting the perspective of the regular people, etc. If you’re just a disposable soldier, the gameplay should probably feel like a battlefield was our thinking. And the enemies should be loud and powerful to convey your insignificance even more. This was a total 180 turn from the Vermintide sound design, where you are this cinematic hero where your actions are loud, fun and powerful. I remember this shift in design approach when I first got my hands on the thunder hammer. I got the brief from Mats (combat designer) that it should sound like a lightning strike right in front of you and it should feel like you’re just melting everything. I knew I couldn’t do it realistically, it had to be cinematic and fat as hell. By that time, we had started to work with some “kill confirm” sounds. I wanted to make them big and satisfying too in a way that could work alongside big thunder hammer sounds. All of a sudden we started to enter a territory that was closer to Vermintide where we had big and punchy sounds during combat, and I think everyone agreed that this was just so much more fun to play with. I still wanted to restrain us and not just drop the realism part. I still believed it was possible to do both. Here’s where the “oversized realism” direction I talked about earlier started.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/faa31f25c2cdf30b377e27a0a92f03f66485ad20.jpg"/><br/><br/>I’m glad we ended up putting in so much effort in making the combat feel fun and rewarding, shout out to Sebastian G. who helped out so much on the gameplay code side. He was the one enabling me to add different hit sounds based on where you hit, how hard you hit, with what you hit and what you hit it with, if the enemy died from the hit and so on. It really helped us make the combat more immersive and satisfying. I really enjoyed the detail that you get different kill confirm sounds based on what enemy type you killed. All these small parts came together pretty good, it just makes you wanna smash things, am I right?<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Enemies</div>There is a lot to talk about the enemies. I won’t go into detail on how they were designed. That’s something we can talk about in another dev blog as it wasn’t me who did most of them. Anders N. did most of the work here, and of course our great VO designers David W., Ola and David F… My main focus was to make them work in the mix, and make sure the sounds fit the gameplay loop. This might have been the most challenging part of the whole sound mix actually.<br/><br/>If you miss a sound cue during a mission you might die, but if the game is just full of sound cues all the time, they’d stop being cues and just turn into noise. You’d also lose most of the immersion if we went full-on arcade with stingers all over the place. We had to be very selective of what to present to the players, but never select the wrong things. <br/><br/>Anyway, instead of putting the main focus on making the most sophisticated hierarchical mixing system, I wanted the main problem solving to take place in the actual sound design. For example, instead of making a trapper three times as loud as a mauler in order to hear, we wanted to make sure they didn’t even compete in the mix. Because sometimes you’d even wanna hear the mauler over the trapper. Basically the goal was that multiple enemy sound cues could play simultaneously and still be readable. To try and achieve this we had to make sure each enemy not only had unique sounds, they also had to be differentiated in terms of timbre, pitch, duration, loudness, etc. as much as possible. We had to use all kinds of mixing and psychoacoustics tricks to make them stand out from each other as much as possible. To fully understand why and how this works you need some basic understanding of sound theory and acoustics. This took us a long way, but more was needed to be done in a chaotic game such as Darktide.<br/><br/>Another way we worked to make the special enemies stand out in the mix was to just have them behave differently game-play wise. Poxbursters are designed to be heard from a distance so you have time to shoot it. Trappers are supposed to be sneaky so they are heard mostly when they are close by. Mutant chargers are meant to be heard over time with more low frequency content. Snipers with a very specific “dodge or die” sound that only happens once. Chaos hounds have a distinct spawning sound, which is supposed to make you aware that dogs are coming, then you have to wait and see where they show up. Other enemies like the flamer are purposefully more reliant on the visuals to not bloat the mix too much. Same goes for bosses, you don’t really need super clear sound cues for them, because you can’t miss them.<br/><br/>All these small parts, a lot of mixing, (which I won’t go into here), makes the enemies audible even in the most chaotic moments. That was our goal at least.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Levels</div>The ambience of Darktide had a pretty clear direction from the beginning. It was also one of those things we could start to work on before a lot of the game mechanics were fully in place. We knew that it had to feel huge, industrial and obviously grimdark. But we wanted to do it realistically. Usually when creating big environments you try to utilize nature and animals to make the space feel alive. That wasn’t really possible in Darktide. You are almost never outdoors, everything is made out of metal and seemingly no wild life. To make the environments feel alive we had to use other tools. As I described earlier we wanted the players to feel small and vulnerable in this world. To further convey this we focused on adding sounds that felt huge and distant. Big metal stress sounds, huge fans and machinery going off in the distance. In some areas there is warfare going on, or speakers playing propaganda, but it’s all fairly distant sounding. I think that just adds to this feeling of size to the place. And also your insignificance as a player, the world is simply too big to care for you. Maybe my colleague Jonas Hellberg can tell you more about the level events and how he makes huge world sounds in another dev blog.<br/><br/>The propaganda played out in the levels is actually a quite fun medium that we’ve used a lot to further tell a story about the different areas of Atoma. What’s being said from them is based on missions and if the Imperial cultists are occupying that area. On some missions it is cultists that play their own propaganda through the PA-systems.<br/><br/>Another important aspect of the level sound design is that we kept a very high quality of the reverbs, which are all impulse responses of real spaces. Every ambience loop is in surround formats and we use sound portals to properly propagate the sounds through corridors, open doors, windows etc instead of them traveling directly through the walls. That is a big upgrade from the Vermintide games that I think made a huge difference in the end.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Music</div>The music of Darktide is today a huge part, some say the biggest part of Darktide’s sound. And it’s all thanks to our composer Jesper Kyd, who exceeded our expectations to say the least. But this wasn’t the case throughout the whole production. Jesper came in fairly late in the production process. We released our first three trailers without a composer just because we hadn’t found the right one yet. Who the hell did the music for the first three then you might ask? Well that’s not important. Let’s just agree that it got so much better when we finally decided to ask Jesper. Anders De Geer presented our vision, we gave him some more sound mix pointers, and he was able to translate it into music so well. We wanted gritty organic analog sounds, and he had a bunch of old analog synths that he was itching to use. A match made in heaven? He got a lot of creative freedom, since we kind of had a very similar vision of the game we never really had to direct him much at all. His work kind of just molt together with our sound design, and there we had the sound of Darktide presented to us for the first time.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>Alright, well, that’s it for now! I hope you found this somewhat interesting, and hopefully It revealed some more insight into how I (along with the rest of the team) shaped the sound for Darktide that we all know and (hopefully) love. It took a lot of effort to ship this game, from a lot of talented people. I’m so proud of what we’ve done thus far. And a lot more is to come!<br/><br/>If you have any questions about some of our design decisions, or any of the more tech-specific words I used, or if there is more you want to know on the topic, please comment below! Me or someone else in the team would happily talk more on any topic, preferably sound related. I’m sure StrawHat will pass them along to me and I’ll do my best to respond.<br/><br/>Ok thanks bye!<br/><br/>– Johan]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 5.3 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4532401922168893826</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/2aa0693bcfb5dc17a775175be8c0fddbfc64518b.png"/><br/><br/>Hello everyone, Mitch here, Design Director on Total War: Warhammer III, back with another dev blog - this time for patch 5.3!<br/><br/>Having now seen your reaction to patch 5.2 I can say it’s been really wonderful; it was inspiring to see all of your reactions to the new content, reworks and fixes and in particular your excitement for the future of the game. Speaking of the future, we’re already well underway with patch 5.3 and so I’ll walk you through the changes and additions coming as part of our next patch, before that touching on the topic of game balance as well as taking the chance to acknowledge some of the feedback we’ve seen following 5.2 and our recent Dev Chat video where among other things we asked for more of your thoughts.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3"><b>📜 Read full 5.3 Dev Blog here</b></div></div><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #51 (1.5.4) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4539157321628805552</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cc881a4ff16e80234fb139208c6f4a1a5703f925.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div><br/>Hotfix #51 (aka 1.5.4) is out now and you can find the patch notes for it below! It is out now on Steam and it will shortly follow on our other platforms. <br/><div class="bb_h2">Render Settings Reset</div>With 1.5.0 and the introduction of FSR 3.1 Frame Generation we accidentally defaulted the Frame Gen setting to be on. This was unintentional and we apologize for the inconvenience. With this hotfix, the launcher will be doing a proper re-detection of your render settings and reset the frame generation setting to off. This applies even if you have explicitly turned on Frame Generation. You will have to turn it on again, and you might want to tweak other render settings to your liking after the first time you launch the game.<br/><div class="bb_h2">Deprecating Fullscreen Exclusive (FSE) Display Mode</div><div class="bb_h3">What?</div>With 1.5.4 we will be deprecating our Fullscreen Exclusive (currently named "Fullscreen") display mode and adding the ability to set custom resolution for the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode. You will not see any performance degradation from this change.<br/><div class="bb_h3">Why?</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We have now added the ability to set custom resolution for the "Borderless Fullscreen" which was the last remaining blocker for making the "Borderless Fullscreen" fully usable.<br/></li><li> The Fullscreen Exclusive display mode no longer serves a purpose when it comes to improving the performance of Win10/DX12 exclusive titles after Microsoft's improvements to borderless window modes*. <br/></li><li> For quite some time we have seen a lot of issues connected to the Fullscreen Exclusive display mode.<br/></li><li> With the latest release we also added FSR3.1 FG which added even more crashes with a similar connection to the Fullscreen Exclusive display mode and it is clear that the focus on testing for Fullscreen Exclusive display modes from our partners is dropping.<br/></li><li> The borderless window approach to fullscreen shows significantly more stable and user friendly behavior for players that frequently alt-tab in and out of the game.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">How?</div>Going forward we are renaming "Borderless Fullscreen" to only "Fullscreen" and will have only two display mode options "Window" or "Fullscreen". We are also decoupling the resolution from the window size, meaning that you will now be allowed to set any resolution for the game when using the new Fullscreen (previously "Borderless Fullscreen") mode. Previously you were always locked to using the desktop resolution if you used the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode. This caused players that had a 4k desktop resolution but hardware that wasn't able to push the game to sufficient frame rates at 4k, to be unable to use the "Borderless Fullscreen" mode.<br/><br/>* https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/demystifying-full-screen-optimizations/<br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">"The DWM manages the composition/organization of the desktop display content from various applications, meaning it controls what is rendered and presented to the front of your display and what is held in the background. However, this control has historically resulted in a slight performance overhead vs FSE, where the game has full control.<br/><br/>To get back this performance overhead, we enhanced the DWM to recognize when a game is running in a borderless full screen window with no other applications on the screen. In this circumstance, the DWM gives control of the display and almost all the CPU/GPU power to the game. Which in turn allows equivalent performance to running a game in FSE.”</blockquote><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes and Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some of the weapons with a Special activate action failed to correctly refresh their activation if the Special action was performed again while in the active duration of a previous Special activation.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where shots from the M35 Magnacore Mk II Plasma Gun failed to penetrate Bulwark shields.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Valkyrie briefings would sometimes not finish before loading into a mission. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where you would occasionally see a <text> subtitle when getting close to a character in the Mourningstar.  <br/></text></li><li> Fixed an issue where subtitle text from Morrow would sometimes remain displayed after the VO ended.  <br/></li><li> Fixed some issues with Darinda Dukane’s animations.  <br/></li><li> Updated the description of the Ceaseless Barrage blessing to correctly match the gameplay mechanics.<br/></li><li> Updated software that should address the issue of players being unable to see or type in chat.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash related to enemy spawning that could occur during certain mission events.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that could cause a crash when navigating the Mastery menu using a gamepad without any Blessings present.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some gaps would appear while wearing the Zealot “Pious Banneret's Garb” upper body cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the rivets on the Veteran “Lucius KM VIIIB Death’s Head” and “Lucius MK IIIA Death’s Head” headgear cosmetics wouldn’t always line up correctly, creating incorrect shadows.  <br/></li><li> Made slight changes to the collar of the Veteran “Krieg Greatcoat MkI” upper body cosmetic to avoid clipping with the “Lucius KM VIIIB Death’s Head” and “Lucius MK IIIA Death’s Head” headgear cosmetics.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the shoulder pad on the Psyker “Kobaloi Topcoat” upperbody cosmetic would appear to be offset from the arm.  <br/></li><li> Fixed some clipping issues while wearing the Psyker “ "Timeworn" Psyker Jerkin (Taros Tan)” upper body cosmetic together with the “ “Timeworn” Psyker Regalia” lower body cosmetic.  <br/></li><li> Fixed the insignia on the Zealot “MK IX Pot Helm and Rebreather” headgear cosmetic being depressed into the helmet.  <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where certain faces would lightly clip into the visor of the Zealot “Votarist’s Pot Helm with Rebreather” headgear cosmetic.  </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><b>Fsr 3.1 Frame Generation Does Not Do Anything During Excessive Fullscreen Effects </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FSR 3.1 Frame Generation excludes the entire screen from generation when there are a lot of fullscreen effects playing that impact all pixels on screen. This will cause frame gen to just copy the previous rendered result which results in the framerate looking like framegen is disabled while frame counters saying that it is running correctly. <br/></li><li> <b>CURRENT WORKAROUND:</b> If players disable Lens Quality, it addresses this issue for the time being.</li></ul><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.<br/></li><li> <b>UPDATED:</b> A fix for this will be shipped with the next hotfix.</li></ul><b>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).<br/></li><li> <b>UPDATED: </b>A fix for this will be shipped with the next hotfix.</li></ul><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
