<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Update on Maintenance for Unlocked and Loaded</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209641366647</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b1aabf58ac8086f06ba6bdef51aeffdd37373329.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>We put this message in the patch notes, but it’s been missed by some so we’re dedicating a post to it, as well. <br/><br/>As you might imagine, transferring over all the weapons and blessings in the game for our existing players –  from the old system to our new system – is a huge task. <br/><br/>There are two important things to note.<br/><br/><b>First</b>, we have disabled certain Mastery and Shrine of the Omnissiah features, as well as the Armory Exchange and Melk’s Requisitorium while the update is continuing to roll out. <br/><br/>This means if you’re checking things right now, you will not see any progress or mastery. <i>However, it does not mean you lost it. </i><br/><br/>While this is happening, we’ve received reports that some players have not been granted the Mastery or Blessings they’re owed. It is likely due to logging in after the above maintenance had started. We’ll let players know when they can log in and check their Mastery progression.<br/><br/><b>Second</b>, some players are experiencing crashes. If players are running the game with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation enabled, and they are tabbing between the exclusive full screen and windows, they may crash. Further, if players run FSR 3.1 Frame Generation, but without any upscaling enabled (such as FSR 3.1, DLSS or XESS), they will crash upon entering the Mourningstar. <br/><br/>The current workaround is to:<br/><ol><li> Use borderless fullscreen;<br/></li><li> If they’re running the game with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation: Enable one of the Upscaling alternatives (FSR 3.1, DLSS or XESS).</li></ol>Alternatively:<br/><ol><li> Disable FSR 3.1 Frame Generation</li></ol>^ <i>We are working on a fix for this to be included in a hot fix. </i><br/>Thank you for your patience today as we work to get everyone up and running again soon. <br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked and Loaded - Patch Notes - Pt. 2 - OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209640886462</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1dabef94954825aa2c801dcc021140565c690cfd.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Welcome to PART 2 of the patch notes.</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weapons</div><div class="bb_h1">Weapon Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">Thunder Hammers</div><br/>The Thunder Hammer family of weapons suffered for being over-specialized into the Monstrosity-removal niche, while being very underwhelming against most other threats and in general failing at keeping up with the increased intensity of high difficulty missions.<br/><br/>With the following changes we aimed at rebalancing the weapon to preserve its single-target focus, but also to make it more well rounded and more exciting to use in all situations.<br/><br/>While the upper end of the damage on Special activated attacks against the Unyielding armor type has been lowered to prevent unhealthy 1-shots of Monstrosity enemies, the damage against Carapace Armour has also been significantly increased to conversely be able to more effectively handle Elite enemies like Maulers and Crushers (potentially dispatching them with a single well placed hit).<br/><br/>The Light activated attack damage profiles have been improved to reward weakspot hits and to more easily eliminate any human-sized enemy.<br/><br/>The self-stun after a Special activated attack has been significantly reduced on both marks, and differentiated between Light and Heavy attacks.<br/><br/>This will make it way easier to find a window of time to deliver its devastating activated blows without being overly punished by other enemies.<br/><br/>Also, most Light and Heavy attacks have been improved in their damage and reach, to make the weapon more reliable in dealing with lesser enemies when not activated.<br/><br/>Both marks of the Thunder Hammer weapon family have also received some additional targeted changes, explained just below!<br/><br/><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>It’s also a hammer.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Detailed Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All Marks<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the damage profile for Light Special activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from {2.0,3.0} to 2.0.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the damage profile for Heavy Special activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from {3.0,5.0} to 3.0.</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 1.0 to 1.5.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the headshot/critical damage bonus multiplier on all Light attack profiles:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Finesse boost from 0.3 to 0.5.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the damage of the Light Strikedown attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {150,300} to {180,350}.</li></ul></li><li>Improved the damage of the Heavy Relentless attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1st target attack power distribution from {150,300} to {180,350}</li><li>2nd target attack power distribution from {80,160} to {100,200}</li><li>3rd target attack power distribution from {50,100} to {75,150}.</li></ul></li><li>Fixed several windup and attack actions which could be canceled by sprinting.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Crucis Mk II Thunder Hammer</div><br/>The Crucis Mk II mark always boasted the higher damage compared to its Ironhelm Mk IV brother, but delivering that damage to the intended target was often difficult due to the horizontal direction of its Heavy attacks and the effective lack of cleave on Special activated attacks.<br/><br/>This led to not uncommon scenarios where a Heavy activated attack could be completely absorbed by a single intercepting Poxwalker, leaving the target enemy unscathed.<br/><br/>To give players more control on the situation, we added a new overhead Heavy attack to the weapon, only chainable after the Special activation action for a short period of time.<br/><br/>Also, a small amount of cleave was added to the Heavy activated attacks, meaning that the swing will be able to go through at least one lesser enemy.<br/><br/>These changes combined will make the weapon more reliable in delivering its devastating damage to the intended target.<br/><br/>Additionally, the damage profile of the Light 3 attack has been improved to reward players completing the attack chain instead of resetting it.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes - Crucis Mk II Thunder Hammer</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the Self-stun duration after connecting with a Special activated attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light stun from 1.3 to 0.3</li><li>Heavy stun from 1.3 to 0.5.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the hitboxes and damage windows for most attacks to be more aligned with their animations.</li><li>Improved reach for all Light attacks and the Push follow-up attack.</li><li>Tweaked the speed and chain time for the Light 1 and Light 2 attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slightly reduced the attack speed</li><li>Improved chain time to Light 2 / Heavy 2 attack start from 0.65 to 0.55.</li></ul></li><li>Light 2<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the attack speed.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li>Added a bespoke improved Light Strikedown damage profile to the Light 3 attack<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution {200,380}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured 0.75</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Slightly improved reach for all Heavy attacks</li><li>Changed so that the Heavy 2 attack chains into Light 3 / Heavy 1 instead of Light 1 / Heavy 1 to give an alternate access to the improved Light 3 attack.</li><li>Special activated attack changes:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a small amount of cleave to Heavy activated attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cleave distribution {1.0,3.0}.</li><li>Attack power distribution {400,800} when cleaving.</li><li>Cannot cleave through Elites, Specialists, Monstrosities and Captains.</li></ul></li><li>Added an attack start chain from the Special activate action, chaining into Light 1 and a unique Strikedown Heavy attack with a vertical animation.</li><li>Improved the duration of the Special activate buff from 4s to 5s.</li><li>Significantly improved the Light activated attack properties:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {300,600} to {400,750}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured from 0.3 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour from 0.3 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Maniac from 0.3 to 0.5</li><li>Overall Finesse multiplier curve from {0.25, 0.75} to {0.65, 1.15}.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Ironhelm Mk IV Thunder Hammer</div><br/>The Ironhelm Mk IV received few additional specific tweaks, but will still benefit greatly from the overall changes to the Thunder Hammer weapon family.<br/><br/>The improved reduction in self-stun duration after a Heavy activated attack will help in further distinguishing it as the more nimble and well rounded Thunder Hammer mark.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes - Ironhelm Mk IV Thunder Hammer</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the Self-stun duration after connecting with a Special activated attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light stun from 0.7 to 0.25</li><li>Heavy stun from 0.7 to 0.4.</li></ul></li><li>Tweaked the hitboxes and damage windows for most attacks to be more aligned with their animations.</li><li>Improved reach for all Light attacks and the Push follow-up attack.</li><li>Slightly improved reach for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 3 attacks.</li><li>Improved the Light activated attack properties:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution from {250,500} to {300,600}</li><li>Finesse boost vs Unarmoured from 0.75 to 1.0</li><li>Finesse boost vs Flak Armour from 0.75 to 1.0</li><li>Overall Finesse multiplier curve from 0.25 to 0.65.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Boltgun / Bolt Pistol</div><br/>In this release we added a set of targeted buffs aimed to increase the overall reliability of the iconic Boltgun and Bolt Pistol weapons, but also to significantly improve their performance against specific enemy types and in various situations.<br/><br/><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>We are aware of some issues regarding the aim of the bolt weapons, particularly in the recoil and sway when shooting continuously.<br/><br/>Unfortunately the issues are rooted quite deeply in the interaction between multiple different systems, so a complete fix was not possible for this release. We are going to continue investigating a solution and provide an update on our progress at a later date.<br/><br/>In the meantime, we have added some tweaks on the Sway and hitscan behaviors which should at least alleviate part of the issue.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Detailed Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Both Families</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the intensity of the Sway from 1.0 to 0.3.</li></ul></li><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make the weapon to be overall slightly less unwieldy when aiming, and also make it less likely for the aim position to be significantly displaced when transitioning from hipfire to ADS.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extended the radius of the hitscan for the bolt projectiles.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will make the hitscan detection to be more generous and allow for shots that would have slightly missed the target to still be considered a hit.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the bolt properties to ignore limbs on non-Monstrosity enemies when the projectile trajectory would have also hit their torso or head.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will avoid situations where a bolt could be intercepted by the limbs of the enemies even when aiming at their center of mass, resulting in heavily reduced damage.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 0.4 to 0.5 (both near and far range).</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Infested from 0.5 to 0.9 (near) / 1.0 (far).</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Bolt-type weapons were penalized when shooting against Infested enemies. This tweak will normalize the damage in order to make them more reliable against this armor type.</i></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Locke Mk IIb Spearhead Boltgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the wield speed, from around 1.9s to 1.6s.</li><li>Improved the stagger properties of subsequent hits on the same target.</li></ul></li><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This will make it easier to open up Bulwark shields and reach stagger thresholds on other hard to stagger enemy types.</i></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Godwyn-Branx Pattern Bolt Pistol</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added cleave properties to the bolt projectiles<ul class="bb_ul"><li>From no_cleave to {1.0,3.0}.</li></ul></li></ul></li><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it possible for the shot to hit the intended target instead of being fully absorbed by even a single minor enemy.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced some chain timings after the Special Push action:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Chain to hipfire Shoot from 0.56 to 0.4</li><li>Chain to Unwield from 0.54 to 0.4</li><li>Chain to Special from 0.9 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></ul><div class="bb_h1">Additional Weapon Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>“Devil’s Claw” Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extended the block property of the Special parry to remain active for a short period of time at the start of the riposte attack.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stamina is still drained as normal when blocking attacks during the additional block duration.</li><li>0.2s additional block duration.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is to avoid situations where the player could still be hit on a well timed parry if multiple attacks were incoming at the same time.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Slab Shield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added ranged block properties during the Push action, in addition to the already existing melee block properties.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Block properties of the shield were still maintained during a Push, but only against melee attacks. Now the Block properties of the Push action should also cover ranged attacks.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Branx Pickaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Special bash attack:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stagger_category from “melee” to “uppercut”.</li><li>Impact power distribution increased on the first 3 targets:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>[1] from {16,33} to {30,70}</li><li>[2] from {8,20} to {10,60}</li><li>[3] from {6,18} to {10,35}.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Branx pickaxe Special attack is a Bash instead of the Pull used in the other two lighter marks, but its stagger output was often underwhelming against bigger targets. After the changes, this attack should now be more reliable in staggering any kind of non-Monstrosity enemy, even when in groups.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.87 to 0.8</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 1.05 to 0.8</li><li>Heavy 2 into Block from 0.69 to 0.62</li><li>Push follow-up attack into Block from 1.1 to 0.9.</li></ul></li><li><b>Borovian Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.63 to 0.6</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 0.9 to 0.7</li><li>Heavy 2 into Block from 0.63 to 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Reduced the windup time for the Heavy 1 attack when chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.8 to 0.72.</li></ul></li><li><b>Karsolas Pickaxe</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the chain timings after specific attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 2 into Light 3 / Heavy 1 start from 0.56 to 0.55</li><li>Heavy 2 into Special from 0.75 to 0.6.</li></ul></li><li>Reduced the windup time for the Heavy 1 attack when chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.71 to 0.6.</li><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Push follow-up bash attack when hitting a Weakspot.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it easier to quickly control single enemies with carefully aimed attacks, at the cost of some Stamina.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Agripinaa Mk XIV Quickdraw Stub Revolver</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the Cleave properties of the shots.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cleave distribution from {1.0,2.0} to {2.0,4.0}.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li><b>Rashad Mk II Combat Axe / Antax Mk V Combat Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the damage and stagger against Maniac enemies for all Heavy attacks.<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 1</li><li>Armor impact modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The Heavy attacks of the Combat Axes were unfairly penalized against Maniac type enemies, to the point where it was often preferable to use Light attacks instead.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Achlys Mk VIII Combat Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned the Heavy 2 and Heavy 3 attacks to the Heavy 1 attack profile.</li><li>Tweaked the damage and impact modified against specific armor types for all Heavy attacks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor damage modifier vs Carapace Armour from 0.6 to 0.8</li><li>Armor damage modifier vs Unyielding from 2 to 1.75</li><li>Armor impact modifier vs Maniac from 0.5 to 0.75.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Heavy attacks of the Achlys Mk VIII Combat Axe are now all aligned to use the “spike” version of the attack profile, which also got some rebalancing with improved damage against Carapace and lowered damage against Unyielding. This will make the mark a bit more unique compared to the other two versions of the Combat Axe.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Lucius Helbore Lasguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the buffer time for the hipfire shoot input to avoid unintended inputs to be registered when exiting the ADS stance immediately after shooting.</li><li>Aligned the minimum ammo usage for minimally charged shots between marks:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Mk I from 3 to 2</li><li>Mk II unchanged at 2</li><li>Mk III from 4 to 2.</li></ul></li></ul></li><li><b>Lucius Mk II Helbore Lasgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned the Sway values to the other marks.</li></ul></li><li><b>Tigrus Mk XV Heavy Eviscerator</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reduced the windup timings for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attacks, depending on the attack chain:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heavy 1 chained from base start / Light 4: 0.4 (unchanged)</li><li>Heavy 1 chained from Light 2 / Heavy 2 from 0.76 to 0.65</li><li>Heavy 2 chained from Light 1 / Heavy 1 from 0.85 to 0.65</li><li>Heavy 2 chained from Light 3 / Push follow-up from 0.6 to 0.4.</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>These changes will reward opting to use Heavy attacks when going further down into attack chains, instead of resetting the chain.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Orestes Assault Chainaxes</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slightly improved the Dodge Distance range on the Mobility stat, from {0.8-0.9} to {0.9-1.0}.</li><li>Slightly improved the Block cost.</li><li>Slightly improved the Sprint cost at lower Defences stat values.</li></ul></li><li><b>Orestes Mk XII Assault Chainaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Significantly improved the movement speed curve for the Heavy 1 and Heavy 2 attack windups.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make the Heavy attacks of this mark more dynamic and easier to use in more situations.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved the stagger properties of the Push follow-up attack.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This attack was meant to be a quick interrupt against enemy actions, but often failed at staggering key enemies like Ragers. The new values should allow to more reliably create space, still at the cost of Stamina due to the Push.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the hitbox of the Heavy 2 attack to be more aligned to the animation.</li><li>Shock Mauls<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the buffer time windows for attack inputs to be more lenient.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make it less likely for Light attack inputs to be lost if performed too early after attacks with long chain times.</i><br/>Weapon Bug Fixes<ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Ironhelm “Hacker” Mk IV Assault Shotgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the aim direction could be incorrectly moved if switching to another weapon immediately after firing.</li></ul></li><li><b>Lawbringer Mk VI Combat Shotgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Special shell shots failed to be correctly scaled through the Damage stat.</li></ul></li><li><b>Force Staves</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Celerity Stimm would fail to raise the charge speed of the secondary charged attacks.</li></ul></li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Blessings</div><div class="bb_h2">Updated Tiered Blessings</div>Blessings that were previously only available in 1 or 2 Tiers, have now been expanded upon to be available for all 4 tiers, with relevant values.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Pool Additions per Weapon</div>The number of Blessings available for the different Patterns has not been consistent, with some Weapons like the Blaze Force Sword having 12 different Blessings, while others like the Ogryns Power Maul only having 4. With the introduction of the new Itemization System we’re trying to make this more even between the Weapons. Going forward, all Weapons should have at least 8 different Blessings to choose from.<br/><br/><b>Braced Autogun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ceaseless Barrage</li><li>Roaring Advance</li><li>Inspiring Barrage</li></ul><b>Spearhead Boltgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puncture</li><li>Terrifying barrage</li><li>Fire Frenzy</li></ul><b>Assault Chainaxe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Heavy Eviscerator</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Tactical Axe</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Slaughter Spree<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Guaranteed Critical Hit (Next Attack) on Weak Spot Critical Hit Kill.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Relentless Strikes<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+4-10% Power for 2s on Hit (Same Enemy). Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Agile<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Refreshed Dodge Efficiency on Weak Spot Hit. +2.5-10% Melee Weakspot Damage.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Heavy Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Chained Deathblow<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+5-20% Critical Chance for 3s on Weak Spot Kill.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Bladed Momentum<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hitting multiple enemies in one sweep gives 4-10% Rending for 2.5s. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li>Thrust</li></ul><b>Duelling Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Relentless Strikes<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+4-10% Power for 2s on Hit (Same Enemy). Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Agile<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Refreshed Dodge Efficiency on Weak Spot Hit. +2.5-10% Melee Weakspot Damage.</li></ul></li><li>Thrust</li></ul><b>Purgation Flamer</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Everlasting Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Critical strikes fill the current clip with 2-5 bullets from your ammo reserve.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Penetrating Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1-4% Brittleness when applying Burn Stacks on a direct hit. Stacks up to 20%.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i>When we previewed the balancing notes a couple of weeks ago, this said “1-4% Rending on Burn Stacks. Which was updated to clarify 1-4% Rending on Burn Stacks. Maximum 20%). The Rending text was an oversight and it was always meant to be Brittleness, due to it being applied on an enemy and any player being able to take advantage of the buff once it’s been applied.</i>[/*]<br/><b>Inferno Force Staff</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Penetrating Flame<ul class="bb_ul"><li>1-4% Brittleness when applying Burn Stacks on a direct hit. Stacks up to 20%. (See Dev Note above).</li></ul></li><li>Showstopper</li><li>Blaze Away</li></ul><b>Electrokinetic Force Staff</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Transfer Peril</li><li>Sustained Fire</li><li>Surge</li></ul><b>Helbore Lasgun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Hot-Shot<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Weak Spot Hits gain 20-50% Cleave.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Armourbane<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Target receives 2-8 Stacks of 2.5% Brittleness on Charged Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Heavy Laspistol</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Concentrated Fire<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to +2-5% Critical Chance on Chained Ranged Weak Spot Hit (Any Target).</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Desperado<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+5-12.5% Critical Chance for 2s on successful Dodge.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Latrine Shovel</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Smackdown<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+7.5-15% Critical Chance for3s on Special Action Hit (Staggered Enemy).</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li></ul><b>Bully Club</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: No Guts, No Glory<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+50% Toughness Regeneration per second for 2-5s on Elite Special Action Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Grenadier Gauntlet</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Disruptive<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hitting at least 3 enemies with your secondary attack grants 15-30% bonus to Power on melee attacks for 3.5s.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Explosive Offensive<ul class="bb_ul"><li>6-15% Power bonus for 5 seconds after hitting multiple enemies with your weapon special explosion.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Gauntlet Momentum<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+2-5% Power for 1.5s on Chained Melee Hit (Any Target). Max Stacks 10.</li></ul></li><li>Point Blank</li></ul><b>Twin-Linked Heavy Stubber</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Terrifying barrage</li><li>Fire Frenzy</li></ul><b>Power Maul</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Power Surge<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Special Attacks on Armored Enemies cause an additional Shockwave. Special Attacks have +10-25% Explosion Radius.</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li><li>Perfect Strike</li><li>Supercharge</li></ul><b>Battle Maul &amp; Slab Shield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Last Guard<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Block Breaks push Enemies, 15s cooldown. -15-30% Block Cost.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Offensive Defence<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gain a stack for each stamina spent blocking. Your next attack gains +4-10% melee power per stack and consumes one stack. Last 3.5s. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li>Opportunist</li><li>Perfect Strike</li></ul><b>Rumbler</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Explosion Zone<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+3-6% Explosion Radius for every shot fired during continuous fire. Stacks 5 times.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Shrapnel<ul class="bb_ul"><li>+1-4 Bleed Stacks from close range explosions.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Clonk<ul class="bb_ul"><li>15-30% Reload Speed for 3s on Projectile Weakspot Hit.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Plasma Gun</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>New</i>: Power Blast<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gain between 2-5% and 10-25% Crit Chance based on charge level when firing.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Energy Leakage<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increases power up to 7.5-20%, scaled on overheat.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Focused Cooling<ul class="bb_ul"><li>-30-60% Heat generation on Critical Hit.</li></ul></li><li><i>New</i>: Optimised Cooling<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased Charge Speed scaling inversely with Heat Level. 4-10% to 20-50%.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Crusher</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Opportunist</li><li>Thrust</li><li>Slaughterer</li><li>Thunderous</li></ul><b>Power Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Thrust</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Changes</div>To make all Blessings have a difference in strength between Tiers, we’ve changed the following Blessings.<br/><b>Unstoppable Force</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also provides 2.5-10% Heavy Melee Damage based on Tier.</li></ul><b>Power Cycler</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 2.5-10% Melee Stagger based on Tier.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Blessing Bug Fixes and Additional Changes</div><b>Punishing Salvo</b><br/><i>Specifically on the Infantry Autogun.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bug where the description was displaying the wrong values. “…14-20%…” to “…35-50%…”.</li></ul><b>Trauma</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed issue where the Stagger values were too low. Was 7.5-15%. Is now 14-20%.</li></ul><b>Headhunter</b><br/><i>Specifically on the Recon Lasgun.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed bug where the description was displaying the wrong values. “…2-5%…” to “…3.5-5%…”</li></ul><b>Dumdum</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the stacks and duration could be refreshed by Damage over Time effects (e.g. Burn).</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Those effects will still be affected by the damage bonus of the blessing.</i><br/><b>Terrifying Barrage</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the blessing failed to trigger for secondary charged attacks of the Equinox Mk III Trauma Force Staff and the Nomanus Mk VI Surge Force Staff.</li></ul><b>Adhesive Charge</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the bonus damage of the blessing failed to be applied.</li></ul><b>Deflector</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the block cost reduction bonus to also be active when blocking melee attacks</li></ul><b>Overpressure</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also affects Damage over Time effects (particularly, Burn).</li><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked and Loaded - Patch Notes - Pt. 1 - OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209640960080</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1dabef94954825aa2c801dcc021140565c690cfd.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Welcome to PART 1 of the patch notes.</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div><br/>Welcome to the Unlocked and Loaded update! We’re excited for everyone to get their hands on this one. Here are the patch notes for the update. It just went live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms. <br/><br/>(<b>Note</b>:<i> It takes a little bit of time after the release before the old servers are completely disconnected and players are migrated over to the new one. Try reloading the game to switch sooner.</i>) 🙏<br/><br/>(<b>Additional Note</b>: <i>To ensure a smooth release across all platforms, the Armory Exchange and Melk’s Requisitorium are currently closed for maintenance while the new update is being rolled out.<br/><br/>We’ll notify you once the maintenance has been completed! Thank you for your patience, Acolytes. You can follow the update on Twitter or Discord.</i>)<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209641366647 <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Itemization Overhaul </div>We’re finally ready to unveil the Itemization Overhaul we’ve been working on for players. <br/><br/>The Itemization Overhaul reinvents weapon progression, giving players more freedom to experiment and progress with weapons. The overhaul introduces two new systems, Mastery and Power, that provide players with clear avenues to get the weapons and gameplay they want.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Mastery</b>: Players simply have to use their weapon of choice through missions which will result in gaining experience in that weapon’s Mastery track. As players gain experience, they will unlock three different types of rewards and unlock more power: Blessing Points, Weapon Marks, and Perks.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Blessing Points</b>: Allow players to unlock different tiers of Blessings.</li><li><b>Weapon Marks</b>: Players will unlock various weapon marks attached to the Mastery track of the weapon’s family they are progressing in.</li><li><b>Perks</b>: Perks tiers unlock automatically as players advance in a given mastery track.</li></ul><li><b>Power</b>: With the new Power system, players will be able to see and improve their weapon's stats, by spending resources at the Shrine of the Omnissiah. The new power system gives players the possibility to increase the base stats of any weapon allowing it to reach its maximum potential.</li></ul><b>Dev Note</b>:<i> <b>We will not be removing any existing weapons.</b> Existing weapons will remain exactly the same. The only difference is that players will be able to see their weapons’ stats potential. If a player’s weapons are not at their maximum potential, they will be able to upgrade them accordingly. We will not be removing any Blessings, Perks or anything else. </i><br/><br/>There is a LOT to it, and if we included it all in the patch notes here, there would probably be at least 5 parts to these notes on the Forums / Steam. We’ve written everything down in our latest dev blog: the Itemization Overview. We hate to ask you to go to another page, but it’s quite long on its own. <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/U34qXI5tBjk?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Mission Type: Operations and New Mission: Rolling Steel</div>Introduces a new type of mission, Operations, which provides a shorter and more cinematic experience. In Rolling Steel, players are thrust into a high-octane adrenaline scenario where they must stop a moving train hijacked by the cultists. The mission also introduces a timer as an overarching objective, providing a new challenge and elevating the gameplay’s intensity. Players can read more about this mission in our dev blog. This operation will be live on the regular mission board (as well as on Auric). <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/dde72e8ea1cbd2dfbb3a8331e6971e2117ce9c7b.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Social Feature: Party Finder</div>Darktide is built to be enjoyed with others and our Party Finder feature makes teaming up with like-minded players easier! Players will be able to find each other based on four criteria: Game Mode, Difficulty, Language and assorted Tags to define what the group is about. This will be an evolving feature that will improve alongside community feedback. Players can read more about the Party Finder in our dev blog, too.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a28f63ef548e3610c6a97268f1848ba6033916b8.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Unrelenting Hordes (Moebian 21)</div>A platoon of Moebian 21st soldiers has been infected by the Blight. Their armour will make them harder to deal with than the usual hordes you encounter. <br/><br/>Rannick's sure there is something afoot. Keep your eyes peeled for any clues as to what the Cult are doing.<br/><br/><b>Play missions with a set of new Special Conditions,</b> “Infected Moebian 21st”, and as a team collect Grimoires or Scriptures to earn rewards.* This condition will only be available during the event and will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals.<br/><br/>*Similar to past events, the progress will be shared across all members of the strike team. <br/> <br/>This event will start on Thursday, September 26, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/de41172185b98501b3f8fa68f120d15c8ff73893.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Penances</div>For this update, we’ve also added new Penances related to the new Itemization, and new rewards to the Path of Redemption Progression Track, increasing it to a new Maximum of 5000 Points. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Extended Availability of Weapon Families for Human Classes</div>As part of this update, we will extend the availability of specific weapon families to all human classes (Veteran, Zealot, Psyker).<br/>These weapons were previously locked to only one or two of the three classes, but will now be usable by all of them.<br/>However, we made sure that the weapons that are key to the identity of each class will remain uniquely available to that class.<br/>We hope that this will expand the gameplay experience and open up new interesting builds for players!<br/><br/><b>Detailed list:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Turtolsky Heavy Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Veteran and Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Maccabian Duelling Swords</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Veteran and Zealot</li></ul></li><li><b>Orestes Assault Chainaxes</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Braced Autoguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li><li><b>Accatran Recon Lasguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Zealot</li></ul></li><li><b>Combat Shotguns</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>added also to Psyker</li></ul></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">Features and QoL</div><div class="bb_h2">Bulk Actions</div>One of the major quality-of-life features coming with the Itemization Overhaul in the Unlocked and Loaded update revolves around Bulk Actions. We have included the option to Discard/Sell weapons in bulk. We have also implemented a filter system that allows players to get rid of certain weapons in bulk right away. For example, players could set a filter to remove all Redeemed rarity weapons in their inventory.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/65eb63ba175a38be693f95d5263c9b894bdd2a07.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Favourite Weapons</div>Since bulk action is always a bit of a risky operation that could see a player lose their best weapon, we also implemented a “favourite” feature. Players will be able to set weapons as their favourites through the Loadout menu. When listing a weapon as a favourite, it will never show in the Bulk Actions menu or in the Sacrifice menu at the Shrine of the Omnissiah. Players will know it is their favourite as it will have a recognizable icon. In addition, there is no limit to the number of weapons players can set as their favourite.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0fbae7fdf258db718786415dda9ca60035ae2827.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Discarding AKA. Selling Weapons</div>Players used to only get Credits when selling weapons, and the amount of Credits was determined by the item’s Rating. This will still be the case once Unlocked and Loaded is deployed. But in addition to the Credits, players will get additional crafting resources based on the rarity of the weapon sold. From Profane (Grey) to Anointed (Blue) rarities, players will only get Credits back; at Exalted (Purple) players will get Plasteel in addition to Credits; and finally, at Transcendent rarity (Orange) players will get Diamantine added to the mix.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/65eb63ba175a38be693f95d5263c9b894bdd2a07.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Mourningstar Improvements</div>With her initial research on the Clandestium Gloriana findings complete, Hadron has unveiled the improvements to her Shrine of the Omnissiah. This brings some much-needed (according to Commissar Dukane's Quartermaster) improvements to the armaments and options available to the Rejects.<br/><br/>Swagger makes an appearance on the Mourningstar, whose presence adds an air of mystery and tension to the already gloomy atmosphere. <i>"I know Rannick and Hadron seem to trust him. They must have their reasons, I suppose, but there's something not right about that Swagger fellow hanging around on the Mourningstar if you ask me."</i><br/><br/>Commissar Dukane has started making herself comfortable aboard the Mourningstar. Make sure to mind your manners around her and don't go eavesdropping!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">AMD FSR updated to 3.1</div>AMD FidelityFX™ Super Resolution 3 (FSR 3.1) is the latest evolution of AMDs advanced open-source upscaling technology. FSR 3 introduces cutting-edge frame generation technology, delivering significant framerate boosts in supported games, and a new "Native AA" quality mode for enhanced image quality.<br/><div class="bb_h3"> KNOWN ISSUE </div><div class="bb_h3">The Game Crashes When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode and With Upscaling Disabled While FSR3.1 Frame Generation is Turned On</div>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen mode or with upscaling disabled. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.<br/><br/>If you want to use FSR 3.1 frame generation it is recommended to use it with Borderless Fullscreen or Windowed screen modes and with FSR 3.1, DLSS or XESS upscaling enabled. We are working on a fix to ship.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A notification dot will now appear on the Penances and Commodore’s Vestures buttons in the pause menu when something new has happened since the last time you visited.<br/></li><li> A button for the Commodore’s Vestures is now available in the pause menu while in the Mourningstar, similar to the menu in the Operative select screen.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">Known Issues</div><div class="bb_h3">Penances Shown As Not Completed</div>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</div>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Crash When Selecting Marks/Cosmetics/Inspect After Selecting To Delete An Item</div>When using a controller, after discarding a weapon the game may fail to correctly reobtain the focus on the list of weapons.<br/><br/>While in this state, the game will crash when trying to access the Marks/Cosmetics/Inspect screens, as no weapon would be selected.<br/><br/>As a momentary workaround, please make sure to have a weapon in focus before accessing the above screens immediately after having discarded any item.<br/><br/><i>(We intend to ship a fix in 1.5.1.)</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Some Weapons May Show Their Max Stat Potential Incorrectly</div>On rare occasions when looking at a weapon card, the max potential stats distribution shown might not correspond to the actual values.<br/><br/>This will be usually signalled by a total potential stats value lower than 380.<br/><br/>The issue is only visual; the weapon card will update to the correct values once the first Empower operation is done on a weapon with incorrect values.<br/><br/><i>(We intend to ship a fix in 1.5.1.)</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">UI Remains Greyed Out After Going Through All The Mastery Help Tiles</div>Looking at the help functionality that is available in the Blessing menu, the screen will remain dark after the help closes.<br/><br/>While navigation in the menu will not remain available, the only way to remove the darkened UI will be by going back on that screen and re-entering it.<br/><br/><i>(We intend to ship a fix in in 1.5.1.)</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mastery Level Value is Missing in The Marks Swap Screen</div>When in the Marks swap screen, the Mastery level value required to obtain locked Marks may fail to be correctly displayed.<br/><br/>The issue is only visual, and the locked Marks will be correctly available upon reaching the required Mastery level in the weapon family.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Incorrect Information in the Sacrifice Weapon Screen Tooltip</div>The tooltip in Sacrifice Weapon screen incorrectly states that only Anointed (blue) rarity weapons (or higher) are able to be sacrificed.<br/><br/>The issue is only in the tooltip text, as the minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Incorrect Visual Rounding of Weapon Stats</div>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).<br/><br/>This is only a visual rounding issue, as the actual stats total will always effectively be 380 for every weapon.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Minor Typos in the Description of Specific Blessings</div>The “Showstopper” Blessing has an additional “%” character.<br/><br/>The “Penetrating Flame” has an additional “%” character, and an incorrect additional “that apply” in the sentence.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Auspex Tooltip in Rolling Steel Localization Issue</div>The “Move” text in the HUD tooltip when using an Auspex for the new hacking minigame in the Rolling Steel will appear localised in English but is missing in other languages.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked and Loaded - Patch Notes - Pt. 3 - OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209640849139</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1dabef94954825aa2c801dcc021140565c690cfd.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Welcome to PART 3 of the patch notes.</div><br/>Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Classes</div><div class="bb_h2">Psyker</div>When we started overhauling the Classes for Patch #13, we did it one Class at a time. The first one we tackled was Psyker. As a result, the Psyker ended up with a lot less Passive Nodes available compared to the others, resulting in less room to Customize your preferred build. In this Patch, we hope to remedy that.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Psyker Talent Updates</div><b>Scrier’s Gaze</b><br/>To further define this Ability as the go-to choice for those wielding non-Force Staff Ranged Weapons.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants Suppression Immunity for its initial Duration.</li></ul><b>Malefic Momentum</b><br/>To incentivize weaving between Warp Attacks and Regular Attacks<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants +4% Damage to non-Warp Attacks for 8s after a Warp based Kill. Stacks 5 Times.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Psyker Talent Tree Updates</div>With more nodes having to fit into the tree, we’ve restructured it a bit. All builds you have been playing up until now should still be available for you, but you might have to take a slightly different path to get there.<br/><b>Inspiring Presence</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">New Psyker Talents</div><b>Warp Unbound (As a modifier to Scrier’s Gaze)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Scrier’s Gaze prevents you from overloading from Perils of the Warp during its lingering effect.</li></ul><b>Charged Strike (As a modifier to Smite)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Your Heavy Melee Attacks electrocute enemies, damaging them, without stunning them.</li></ul><i>On the Left Side of the Tree:</i><br/><b>Perilous Assault</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to 50% Weapon Wield Speed (based on Peril).</li></ul><b>Channeled Force</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+30% Damage to Force Staff’s Primary Attacks after Fully Charged Force Staff Secondary Attacks. Lasts 5s.</li></ul><b>Empyric Shock</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6% Warp-Damage Taken by victims of your Force Staff’s Primary Attack. Max Stacks 5. Lasts 10s.</li></ul><i>On the Right Side of the Tree:</i><br/><b>Lightning Speed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+10% Melee Attack Speed.</li></ul><b>Warp Splitting</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to 100% Cleave, based on Peril.</li></ul><b>By Crack of Bone</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Melee Weakspot Kills Quell 5% Peril and Reduce further Peril Generation by 20% for 4s.</li></ul><b>Souldrinker</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Killing an Enemy with Soulblaze restores 5% Toughness and grants 5% critical Hit Chance for 5s.</li></ul><i>On your way to the Warp Siphon Keystone:</i><br/><b>Penetration of the Soul</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+10% Rending on Warp-Attacks when above 75% Peril.</li></ul><b>Empyric Resolve</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>-40% Peril Generation. -30% Toughness Replenished.</li></ul><i>On your way to the Disrupt Destiny Keystone:</i><br/><b>Tranquility Through Slaughter</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Non-Warp Ranged Critical Hits Quell 4% Peril.</li></ul><b>Surety of Arms</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+25% Reload Speed while below 75% Peril. On Reload, generate up to 25% Peril based on the Percentage of the Clip Restored.</li></ul><i>Above Empowered Psionics:</i><br/><b>Crystalline Will</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Overloading through Perils of the Warp no longer knocks you down, but you still take the appropriate Corruption Damage.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/462990330877a8383215cb4fbf599d5270a93510.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Veteran</div><div class="bb_h2">Veteran Talent Updates</div><b>Skirmisher</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration 5s to 8s.</li></ul><b>Opening Salvo</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>First Percentage of Ammo: 10% to 20%.</li></ul><b>Kill Zone</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ranged Damage: 15% to 20%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Veteran Talent Tree Updates</div><b>Vanguard</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. Replaced by ‘One Motion’.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>Vanguard wasn’t performing as we wanted, and it was mostly viewed as a blocker to the talents below it.</i><br/><b>One Motion</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>+25% Weapon Swap Speed.</li></ul><b>Relentless</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. It is now included in Executioner’s Stance per default.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Relentless was pretty much a must pick for the viability of the Ability.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Zealot</div><div class="bb_h2">Zealot Talent Updates</div><b>Invocation of Death</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed from 1.5s Cooldown reduction on Melee Critical Strike to: +200% Cooldown Regeneration for 4s on Melee Critical Strike.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>We missed the mark on the last change to ‘Invocation of Death’, leading to frustration. We hope this brings it to a satisfying and balanced state. <b> In the previous patch notes, this was set to 175%, but we have increased it to 200%.</b></i><br/><b>Sainted Gunslinger</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reload Speed per Stack: 3% to 6%.</li><li>Max Stacks: 10 to 5.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The purpose of these changes is to allow the talent to reach its full potential faster.</i><br/><b>Vicious Offering</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 7.5% to 10%.</li></ul><b>The Voice of Terra</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 2.5% to 4%.</li></ul><b>Fortitude in Fellowship</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness Coherency Modifier: 25% to 50%.</li></ul><b>Ambuscade</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage: 20% to 30%.</li></ul><b>Stalwart</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also provides 25% Toughness Damage Reduction while ‘Fury’ is Active.</li></ul><b>Perfectionist</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ability Cooldown Increase: 50% to 25%.</li></ul><b>Master-Crafted Shroudfield</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration: 6s to 5s.</li></ul><b>I Shall Not Fall</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness Damage Reduction per Stack: 5% to 6.5%</li></ul><b>Restoring Faith</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heal 25% to 20%.</li><li>Time for Full Heal: 5s to 4s.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>These changes were made because Restoring Faith made taking stray damage a bit too forgiving.</i><br/><b>Swift Certainty</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprint Speed: 10% to 5%.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The Dodging effect of Swift Certainty is already a very strong effect. We’re lowering the movement speed slightly.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn</div><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn Talent Updates</div><b>No Pushover</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reworked. New Description:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Your Pushes have +250% Stagger. Can only trigger once every 8s.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>The Old ‘No Pushover’ was frankly not up to par. Maybe this spices things up a bit?</i><br/><b>Big Boom</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explosion Radius: 22.5% to 27.5%.</li></ul><b>Reloaded and Ready</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ranged Damage: 12% to 15%.</li><li>Duration: 6s to 8s.</li></ul><b>Bruiser</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Combat Ability Cooldown: 5% to 4%.</li></ul><b>Massacre</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Duration: 6s to 10s.</li></ul><b>Steady Grip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Toughness: 3-5% toughness regeneration per second.</li></ul><b>Delight in Destruction</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage Resistance per Stack: 10% to 8%.</li></ul><b>Too Stubborn to Die</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Health Threshold: 25% to 33%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Ogryn Talent Tree Updates</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Swapped places of Toughness Damage Reduction Operative Modifier, and Suppression Boost Operative Modifier, on the Bottom Right part of the Tree.</li></ul><b>Thick of the Fray</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed. It is now included in Point-Blank Barrage per default.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Additional Miscellaneous Talent Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the Zealot class base Aura “The Emperor’s Will” remained active after selecting the “Loner” Aura talent.</li><li>Fixed an issue where an additional stack of the Psyker “True Aim” talent was gained when inflicting stagger to an enemy during the cast of “Brain Rupture”.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>A stack of the talent will still be gained when completing the cast.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the Psyker “Mettle” talent to only receive a maximum of 1 stack for each Critical attack, regardless of the amount of enemies hit by the attack.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocked and Loaded - Patch Notes - Pt. 4 - OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209640820293</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1dabef94954825aa2c801dcc021140565c690cfd.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Welcome to PART 4 of the patch notes.</div><br/>Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bug Fixes and Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Zarona Combat Shotgun special attack damage was not affected by the Damage stat.</li><li>Solved an issue with melee weapons push-follow attack not entering the sprinting state.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the windup animation for the Heavy 2 attack on the Turtolsky Mk VI Heavy Sword would be incorrect when chained from a Light 3 attack.</li><li>Removed the snap of the camera when swapping weapons while recoiling for Double-Barrelled Shotguns.</li><li>Fixed the Agni MK Ia Shock Maul and the Indignatus Mk III Shock Maul having odd animation blendings between specific attacks, and solved an issue in which their hitstop animations were not properly playing when hitting an armoured enemy during push follow-up attacks.</li><li>Added a small amount of chain timing to cancel into Blitz or Ability after connecting with a Special activated attack on the Ogryn Brute-Brainer Mk XIX Latrine Shovel and Brute-Brainer Mk V Latrine Shovel.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is to prevent an immediate cancellation of the backswing of the Special activated attacks.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Brute-Brainer Mk XIX Latrine Shovel’ and ‘Brute-Brainer Mk V Latrine Shovel’ didn’t get attack speed bonuses from Talents and Blessings for the majority of their attacks.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Brute-Brainer Mk III Latrine Shovel’ didn’t get attack speed bonuses from Talents and Blessings for its first Heavy attack.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Indignatus Mk III Shock Maul’ and the ‘Agni Mk Ia Shock Maul’ didn’t get attack speed bonuses from Talents and Blessings for their Special attack.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Fixes for Talents, Abilities and Blitz Abilities</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Veteran’s Shock Trooper: The talent is now correctly not working when ammo is completely expended.</li><li>Fixed an issue where entering Veteran’s ‘Executioner’s Stance’ wouldn’t activate ‘Weapons Specialist’.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Tweaks to Weapons, Talents, Abilities and Blitz Abilities</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack speed from Celerity Stimms now increases the speed of Force Staff attacks.</li><li>Terrifying Barrage now proc when killing enemies with secondary attacks for Voidblast Force Staff (formerly: Trauma Staff) and Electrokinetic Force Staff (formerly: Surge Staff).</li><li>Run ‘n’ Gun blessing: incremented weapon spread reduction for the Double-Barrelled Shotgun (formerly: Assault Shotgun) from 0% to 10%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Combat</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Kills from fire barrel explosions and resulting fire on the ground will now contribute to the “Situational Awareness” Penance.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><div class="bb_h3">Transit Hub HL 16-11, “Chasm Terminus”</div><b>Hab Dreyko</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed an invisible collision.</li></ul><b>Chasm Station HL-16-11</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players would clip through the floor after being rescued from a hang ledge.</li></ul><b>Ascension Riser 31</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed collision issues around the train cars in the Locomotive Storage Bay area.</li><li>Fixed collision issues at the start of the mission.</li><li>Fixed a respawn location that could cause players to fall through the floor.</li><li>Fixed minor gaps in the geometry in Ironside Alley / Refector’s Quarter</li><li>Moved a spawn location for Scriptures</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Habzone HL-19-24, “Throneside”</div><b>Comms-Plex 154/2f</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an unreachable pickup.</li></ul><b>Archivum Sycorax</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed some locations where players could fall out of the map.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players could sprint past gates before they closed and get locked.</li></ul><b>Enclavum Baross</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where players would spawn outside the final event and be unable to enter the arena.</li><li>Fixed out-of-bounds exploits.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Freight Port HL-32-2, “The Hourglass”</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fix an issue where some environmental pieces used in The Hourglass had the wrong collision setup</li></ul><b>Relay Station TRS-150</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a collision-related exploit.</li><li>Fixed several stuck spots.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players would end up in the falling state when close to the edge of an elevator.</li></ul><b>Refinery Delta-17</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed respawn point priorities.</li><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li></ul><b>Vigil Station Oblivium</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an unreachable pickup.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Habzone HL-70-04, “The Carnival”</div><b>Warren 6-19</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Snipers were able to shoot through certain walls.</li></ul><b>Mercantile HL-70-04-510</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed an issue where enemies could open an airlock gate.</li><li>Fixed issues with elevator collisions.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Manufactory HL-17-36, “Metalfab 36”</div><b>Consignment Yard HL17-36</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds collision issues.</li></ul><b>Power Matrix HL-17-36</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Inter-Zone Void Sector Omega-12</div><b>Clandestium Gloriana</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed several out-of-bounds exploits.</li><li>Fixed several collision issues in some indoor areas.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Orthus Offensive</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where Crusher enemies would run away after breaking the wall to the gas tutorial room.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">VO and Audio</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Both Swagger and Commissar Dukane have arrived aboard the Mourningstar, setting the ship’s rumour mill in motion.</li><li>New mission briefing for Smelter Complex HL17-36:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Following the rediscovery of the Clandestium Gloriana and the secret of Moebian Steel, Enginseer Kayex is attempting to replicate the process in Manufactorum Hl-17-36. But the Traitorous 6th have other plans …</li></ul></li><li>New player VO when tagging Stimms.</li><li>New player conversations when facing the Beast of Nurgle and Chaos Spawn.</li><li>Player characters will now comment when giving other players utility items.</li><li>Player characters will no longer call out void shields as hitting armour.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Weapon names have been updated to a new scheme to simplify naming conventions throughout the UI. (Please see the section above for all the changes.)</li><li>Added filter options on the Armory Exchange’s Requisition Weapons and Curios store to select between item types (melee, ranged and curios).</li><li>Crafting operations now tell why an operation is not available to be performed.</li><li>Added new backgrounds to weapon inspect and weapon cosmetics screens.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Heavy 3 attack was missing in the detailed breakdown screen of the Inspect menu for the Indignatus Mk III Shock Maul.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Vanguard Light attacks were displaying incorrect details in the breakdown screen of the Inspect menu for the Ogryn Power Maul.</li><li>The progress bar for decoding objectives now blinks in orange when stalled.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the extraction UI marker could be visible when joining the mission after it started.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the nose would clip through the bandana on several cosmetics:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Zealot “Cowl of the Avenger” headgear.</li><li>Veteran “Recon Company Beta Vanguard Helm” headgear.</li><li>Veteran “Militarum Issue Helm (1st Mancunio Campaign)” headgear.</li><li>Veteran “Memento Mori Flak Helm” headgear.</li></ul></li><li>Fixed an issue where certain beards would clip through the Zealot “Mortis Rag Mask” cosmetic headgear.</li><li>Fixed a black texture patch on the Zealot “Dedicated Mendicant’s Vestments” upper body cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the cloth appeared invisible from the back on the Psyker “Empyrean Surcoat (Ice Mourn)” upper body cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed hair clipping issue on the Veteran “Munitorum Issue Mark III Garrison Cap” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed eyebrows clipping on Ogryn “Grox-Hide Eye Patch” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed eyebrows clipping on Zealot “Magistratum Scrivener’s Helmet” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed the screen on the right arm displaying inverted information on the Veteran “Militarum Battlegear (Sun Scorch Camo)” upper body cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the elbows could clip through the backside of the arms on Psyker “ “Timeworn” Psyker Jerkin (Taros Tan)” upper body cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the items on the belt of Psyker “Kinetic Witch’s Redemption Raiment” upper body cosmetic would appear warped.</li><li>Fixed some small clipping issues on the Ogryn “Headscarf with Goggles (Taros Tan, XXXXL)” headgear cosmetic.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Other Miscellaneous Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash that could occur when disconnecting or dying shortly after having thrown a Krak Grenade or Assail Shard.</li><li>Fixed an issue that could cause a crash when a Scab Sniper tried to aim outside of the playable area.</li><li>Fixed an issue causing third-person sounds to be played for several weapon effects when spectating another player.</li><li>Fixed an issue where sound effects such as muffling or distortion from for example being knocked down or netted would be overridden when inside a Telekine Dome.</li><li>Mitigated a visual issue where the reload animation of Double-Barrelled Shotguns (formerly: Assault Shotguns) could break when triggering the “Both Barrels” Blessing during bad network conditions.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Part 1. Part 2. Part 3. Part 4.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
