<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/641297020996289632</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines,</div><br/>We deployed a hotfix on <i>Space Marine 2</i> that fixes multiple issues that appeared with the 5.0 update. <br/><br/>You'll find the complete patch notes down below.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><b>General Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug that caused the Perfect Parry window for <i>Fencing</i> melee weapons to be shorter than intended. We reverted the values to pre-patch levels.<br/></li><li> Fixed a server-related issue that would cause a loss of control on PC.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where one of the Chainsword Artificer version was dealing more damage than intended.<br/></li><li> Fixed: “Iron Hands Steel” emblem colour was red instead of black.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that caused Keyboard mappings to be reset after installing the new patch.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to change controls for the Ability button (you might have to change controls one more time).<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Jump Pack ability would spend more than 1 charge in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug in the Campaign mission “Skyfire” (part 2) where a script would not start properly in rare cases.<br/></li><li> Modified: The new mechanic for Blocking weapons “Adrenaline Surge” now restores 2 armour segments instead of 1 when discharged.<br/></li><li> Locked access to the Research Center until the Adeptus Mechanicus gives its blessings.<br/></li><li> Restored progression for modded version of the game (warning popup will still appear and say otherwise, but progression should be saved nonetheless).<br/></li><li> Several crash fixes.</li></ul><br/>Thanks for your continuous support. Shall you encounter issues with this new update, let us know on Focus Together or on our Discord Server.<br/><br/>The Emperor Protects.<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511749</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3d46c256ba2490462ec65b341d5a7d4b64aa3d03.png"/><br/><br/>Hey everyone,<br/><br/>We’ve adjusted our hotfixing plans slightly to prioritise the splash attack issues that have been present since the release of Update 6.0. We have just rolled out Hotfix 6.0.1, which addresses these issues:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Reverted various splash attack max target counts to match at least the minimum number of splash zones units have in metadata.<br/><br/><i>Dev note: In 6.0.0 we made a change to the maximum number of targets a splash attack can hit based on a weapon strength ratio, this change was originally intended to apply to single entity units only and inadvertently was applied to monstrous infantry, cavalry and infantry units. This caused a series of issues with how our splash attacks are calculated, we have reverted the changes to these units while maintaining the single entity splash attack changes. After this hotfix you will see monstrous infantry, cavalry and infantry return to their pre-patch 6.0.0 state. There is a chance this may still affect some units, so please do keep reporting any issues you come across so we can investigate further.</i><br/><br/></li><li> Added missing text strings from a small number of tooltips.<br/><br/><i>Dev note:  Whilst we're aware of other issues present in the game at the moment, currently set to be addressed in a further Hotfix releasing later this week, we had the opportunity to include this one as part of today’s fix, and isn't representative of our current prioritisation of certain issues.</i></li></ul><br/>By implementing these necessary changes today, it has also rolled out some additional battle balancing adjustments that we’ve been working on. A full list of these changes will follow later today as an addition to our 6.0 Battle Balance Details thread, so please check back for the full details!<br/><br/>Although today's hotfix does not include any of the items originally disclosed in our known issues post, please rest assured that we will be back later this week with an additional hotfix to address those and more.<br/><br/>As always, thank you for your ongoing feedback and for your patience while we investigate and address these issues. If you encounter any new problems after updating to version 6.0.1, please let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Who is the 100th Legendary Lord?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511318</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Four contenders, each staking their claim for the coveted title of 100th Legendary Lord™.<br/> <br/>Golgfag, Skulltaker, Gorbad, Arbaal. Who will come out on top? There's only one way to find out...<br/> <br/>FIIIIIGHT! ⚔️<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8EqoO8e7PJE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 15:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction is OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/514069779412157179</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/626689ac31ac99588fcf9927c551c3fa2a1f8238.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>The day is finally upon us! Golgfag, Skulltaker and Gorbad have joined the fray - Omens of Destruction has arrived in Total War: WARHAMMER III alongside Update 6.0!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/46584/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Omens_of_Destruction<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574900/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Gorbad__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130740/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Golgfag__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3130750/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Skulltaker__Omens_of_Destruction/<br/><br/><b>PLEASE NOTE:</b> Although every effort will be made to get the bundle link up and running as close to 3PM GMT as possible, there may be a slight delay in the link being accessible. If you have trouble accessing the link at 3PM GMT please wait a moment and try again.<br/><br/>Check out the launch trailer now:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OD5lbyN-EG0?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>If you haven't already, you can read the full release notes at the link below:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">UPDATE 6.0 RELEASE NOTES</div><br/><br/>Whose campaign will you be jumping into first? We look forward to hearing about your exploits!<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Bardin Goreksson &amp; Warpfire Thrower</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/509566731895701564</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>last</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun. This week's spotlight will be on the hearty <b>Bardin</b> and the nasty <b>Warpfire Thrower!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div>As said in the the previous post, we changed the end date for the event from Sunday to Wednesday, which was more than enough to reach and beat the new ambitious target of 250K kills!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/416bf23cd4e304f304252b63875723aac82853f0.png"/><br/>The rewards for the previous spotlight were delivered yesterday, so check your inventory! As a note, the Hero Pose might take a few restarts before it applies properly to your account. Sorry about that!<br/><br/>Congrats to everyone for your continued hard work! Now just the final stretch!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly, all earned by the community as a whole through completion of the Kill-Counter. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Bardin Goreksson &amp; Warpfire Thrower Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between December 12 - December 18.</b> All rewards will be granted after the end of the spotlight.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>An exclusive skin for the Warpfire Thrower!</b><br/></li><li> <b>120 shillings.</b><br/></li><li> <b>100 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A brand new Portrait frame.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A Hero Pose for Bardin!</b></li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a781e4c46cde9c74da545037248884a1429b3d3c.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Bardin Goreksson</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/38c89e690a980e66d78e96e544ae622a393a619f.png"/><br/>Bardin Goreksson introduced himself to the world as an unstoppable avalanche on the battlefield, an ale-swigging hurricane at the inn, and a steadfast friend by the campfire. A bulwark of comradeliness and good cheer, Bardin became the glue binding our unlikely band of heroes. <br/><br/><b>Learn more about Bardin Goreksson here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Warpfire Thrower</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/3a96fad476c7d4cdcdcc32596076eca8d71dcdbd.png"/>The The Warpfire Thrower is whispered of in many quarters – chiefly for the horrors it has wrought in the cramped confines of dwarfen holds. With the smouldering projector aimed, the simple flip of a switch births roiling clouds of warpfire that scours all from the gunner’s path.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Warpfire Thrower here!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
