<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #60 (1.6.7) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536593303852810323</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f25bd44022d68107336ddb85cf02b225ed6f8fff.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey everyone, </div><br/>We’ve got another quick update this week. Hotfix #60 (1.6.7) is currently rolling out and it’ll be available for everyone across our platforms today.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a server crash which could happen when players joined the Mourningstar.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where deaths which bypassed the downed state were not considered as failing the requirements of the "The Insane" penance.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Dev Note:</b> <i>“The Insane” penance: Complete a Havoc Assignment of 35 or higher without anyone getting downed.</i></li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue where the arms of the player character could disappear at certain camera angles when wearing the "Padre's Truskan Pattern Fatigues with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)" and "Truskan Sanctionite's Greatcoat with Flak Vest (Glacial Might)" upperbody cosmetics.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #59 (1.6.6) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/536592669875372717</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/cd496fffc43c60ab11e722fa5cb0bcecbf0ffd98.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>As mentioned in our last post, Update on Hotfix #58 (1.6.5), there as an issue in the game that could cause some players to crash when interacting with the Sacrifice function at the Shrine of the Omnissiah.<br/><br/>This was fixed in today’s hotfix.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that would happen when accessing the Sacrifice or Discard menus without any available weapon to sacrifice/discard, or when returning to the above menus after having sacrificed/discarded all the available weapons for that character.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/529836636819686186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1"> Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/><b>New Year, New Content!</b><br/><br/>We hear you're hungry for content, and we're happy to see how excited you are about the game!<br/><br/>First off, please don’t forget to check the roadmap for 2025! Worry not, even if this roadmap ends in 2025, that doesn’t mean the game will not receive new content after that! But first things first, let’s focus on this year. If you missed it, the updated roadmap is here:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0d21154a89b3463d365f0e7355c8c3a332d35a70.jpg"/><br/>Secondly, we'd like to remind you that Space Marine 2 will continually be updated with content and technical support throughout 2025. <br/>You’ll progressively get new skins, new PvP and PvE maps, custom lobbies for PvP, the Horde Mode is coming this year as well, PvE prestige ranks and new weapons as well. 🔥<br/><br/>Community Events will also keep coming throughout the year.<br/><br/>The Datavault Update we’re about to break down will arrive in <b>February</b>!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">💙 <u>Thank you for your unwavering support</u></div>Space Marine 2 has been out for 4 months, and your continued enthusiasm means the world to us.<br/><br/>We’re not done with it! You can expect updates every two months. We’d love to do more, but we’re committed to delivering polished updates, which takes time and care! Thank you for your patience, understanding, and unwavering support.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NEW PVP MAP - TOMB</div>A new PvP map is about to be implemented in the 6.0 update! We already hinted that it will be set in a closed environment with many narrow passages pushing you to engage more in Closed Quartered Battles.<br/><br/>It takes place beneath the surface of Demerium, amongst the haunting structures of in a Necron tomb. It’s a closed environment with many narrow passages. Pay extra attention because there are blind spots. There’s also a wider area to let you switch combat style.<br/><br/><br/>❔ Which class do you think you will be playing on this new map?<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/862a7b9286a08a1774e99ef5ea5eefedfd0d406c.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/cecf8aeb84657488f907386491e649743daf7735.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0944da711460b17398eae901c8f477de837cb5a8.jpg"/></div></div></div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/85504f5e9b8ffe58f0ef7f70f537c40e61c43e46.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NEW ENEMY - BIOVORE 🦂</div>The Biovore is a new enemy in PvE, in all maps featuring Tyranids. It’s an Extremis enemy, a dreadful foe both in distance and melee combat. Beware of the Spore Mines ithe shoots.<br/><br/>Don’t forget to dodge and then aim at the Spore Mine to destroy them before impact. 💥<br/><br/>Do not falter, Brother. You’ve got this.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/81adbec012f346c50d1cf5e82667776ccc384592.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6d9012f8c0aeb73ce1137893578cb67d3b475b3e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/daecab1a0acf4c1a4d1de9b32da668b5e5e1fddf.jpg"/></div></div></div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9c491892d8237bbb7b76eb5c6bc0198efcf12de1.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SALAMANDERS CHAMPION 🦎</div>We announced it last month: The Salamanders Champion is here! One of the Loyalist First Founding Chapters of the Space Marines.<br/><br/>Available for the Sniper class, with both skins for your Champion and for your Bolt Sniper Rifle: adorn that green paint, those flames and go dominate the battlefield.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/67a1893fea1f5357fed8f127e395be289e75a43d.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1eeda2b0f655b1f3f5c6ffb27c18eeab47c73913.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/64ceaa4ecfa097d213288aeb032ca4b5cc6be565.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">RAVEN GUARD COMING! 🐦‍⬛</div>The Raven Guard are joining the fight! New cosmetics will soon be available with the season pass including the fan-favorite: ✨🦅 beaky helmet 🦅✨ (MK VI “Corvus”) and Raven Guard trinkets.<br/><br/>Take a first look at it:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ec80a47041d92b72324d6dca4171aa8161be0ee9.jpg"/><br/>The MK VI “Corvus” helmet comes both with and without the Raven Guard emblem, allowing you to customize your Space Marine for your convenience. ✨<br/><br/>❔ How excited are we about these cosmetics?<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7bb187d8fc927d0de45788aabf194a8de7655075.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/08c9841fb1e0ba442a6fa2e1466345b2e97d454b.jpg"/> </div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">DATAVAULT 📚</div><b>The Datavault makes its entry to the Battle Barge!</b><br/><br/>In this new area, you will find unlockable information on most elements from the game in the Research Centre, as well as cosmetic rewards. To unlock them, you will need a new special currency, earned via in-game achievements (called Ordeals), in all modes (Campaign, PvE and PvP). Time to challenge yourself! 🎖️<br/><br/>Those achievements will be listed beside the unlockable info.<br/><br/>Here’s the kind of Ordeals you’ll have to complete to unlock the currency:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Complete any Mission in Operations mode on Average Threat Level or higher.<br/></li><li> Knock back Spore Mines to kill Tyranids.<br/></li><li> Make a Carnifex stun itself in Operations mode.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">PERKS REWORK 🔧</div>In a past Community Update, we mentioned that we were not completely satisfied with the quality of perks. We’ve reworked some of them, and these enhancements will be introduced in the next update release. More changes will come on the perks in the future, and we hope this first change on the perks feel more satisfying and engaging. We’re all ears, so don’t hesitate to share your feedback!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FOV SLIDER FOR PC 🎥</div>You expressed how eager you were to get a FOV Slider since the launch. While implementing it has been technically challenging, we’ve finally managed to produce a slider worthy of our standards, introduced in version 6.0.<br/><br/>We hope this new feature will meet your expectations!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">For 16/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV Slider set at 1 (1920x1080p screen):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f01a34be12efa9e380d545fd89721d7420825fe3.jpg"/><br/></li><li> ​FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/581a5d77800e6ab12dca0f4ec2988b5be9f4174a.jpg"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/04e3bf9f62f3c8056c020fe27599d5495058816f.jpg"/></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">For 21/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV slider set at 1 (3440x1440p screen) (minimum, current version):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c46392d276bba98f7ff8a0051a98289a23d0cd37.png"/><br/></li><li> ​FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7e5d582239d1bcde39702ffdcd8845d444696443.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fd9dfeeed22ca2da239b5a5df006affc2ca248d5.png"/></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">For 32/9 screens:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FOV Slider set at 1 (5120 x 1440p screen):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/31f1932d168b60c6a46ca2dcb43f86cc536ef2f3.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.23:<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/613eafb92b8bf7f2f3eb5369fa333665b75f7edb.png"/><br/></li><li> FOV Slider set at 1.45 (max):<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c1c0b39582d2c56877c20ecc9c29505de427a34a.png"/></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">AND MORE ✨</div>New finisher animations on Zoanthropes, Scarab Occult Terminators and Rubric Marines.<br/><br/>A new functionality will be added, allowing you to upgrade your Master-Crafted and Artificer Armoury Data to Relic by trading them. You can also sell your Armoury Data to get Requisition Points.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/91ab5714125468ff04fa38f66029339a0bec4891.png"/><br/><i>Talk to this Tech-Priest to trade your Armoury Data.</i><br/><br/>A new difficulty mode with cosmetic rewards will be added for the braves able to successfully complete Operations in this more intense difficulty: a bloodstained Knife Combat and a new pauldron. Note that this new difficulty will only be available if you have completed at least 1 Operation in Lethal Difficulty. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/90db0516a4336ce773c4c33b8ce5bc6a2370b75f.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7e77aef3da9881186301fabc7586d1d71c0b9d89.jpg"/><br/><br/>Base Decals available for Right Pauldrons (This one’s for you, Deathwatch players)<br/><br/>A new option to share your skin between PvE and PvP modes will be added. You’ll no longer need to remake the same skin for both modes! This option also allows you to share your patterns between classes.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fffe1d74dfaaede6def1ac4e011b56a6fb23a3b3.png"/><br/><br/>PvP Crossplay Toggle On/Off: allows console players to play with PC players. You now have the option to be matched with either PC players or Console players independently.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/40ed33697ff25a3933bae3ac724534fb7aa54c26.png"/><br/><br/>🕺 Emotes 🕺 Strengthen the bond with your fellow Brothers with the new emotes! So go ahead and use them without moderation.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9b98b9c43156bec5c0a4230aa5f389ff1c43facd.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">That’s it for this month!</div><br/>Don’t hesitate to provide feedback on the upcoming content in the comments below, or on our official Discord Server, where almost 60K Space Marines share their thoughts on the game and find PvP or PvE matches every day. We’re eager to hear from you.<br/><br/>We’ll see you next month for another Community Update.<br/><br/><br/><i>With love &amp; respect,<br/><br/>From Saber and Focus.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects ⭐</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The big Owlcat Reddit AMA 2024 - Answers are ready!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/503941572582178844</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We are finally ready to publish the answers to the massive Reddit AMA that took place in December. <br/><br/>That's a LOT of things you wanted to know, and we tried to answer as many as we could! Read and discuss! <br/><br/>There are so many questions, that it didn't fit into a Steam page, so we invite you to visit our website:<br/><br/>https://owlcat.games/news/92<br/><br/>Enjoy!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 12:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/515199580404450038</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/0d41133979c8b72557fa31089016b21ea98c7b5d.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks!<br/><br/>As alluded to earlier in January, we're back with another hotfix for Total War: WARHAMMER III. Hotfix 6.0.4 introduces a plethora of fixes and tweaks to improve your gameplay experience. Here's a couple of highlights from this hotfix:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Lords would not disengage from a settlement after selecting certain post battle options. This includes, but is not limited to, The Changeling when establishing a Trickster Cult and the Vampire Coast when establishing a Pirate Cove.<br/></li><li> Ogre armies can now recruit Regiments of Renown when they are within the circle of influence of an Ogre Camp.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where reinforcing AI units will be given the same order location and will clump together as they all try and pile on to complete their order.</li></ul>Read on for the full list of changes...<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when attempting to reset skill points for female characters. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when changing the factions on the left side of the Intrigue of the Court panel while playing as the High Elves. <br/></li><li> Fixed a possible crash that could occur when saving and reloading a save file after a manual battle. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when trying to imprison a Military Convoy Lord. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that would occur when trying to select an Ogre Lord with over 100,000 Meat resource. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when using Eltharion’s Athel Tamarha imprisonment mechanic on an Ogre Tyrant or a Caravan Master. <br/></li><li> Fixed a very rare crash caused by a frame-based issue that would occur when triggering a VFX particle system e.g. artillery demolishing a structure during a siege. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash in The Lost God Prologue campaign caused by selecting Spartak Matrosov in the Beacon settlement and pressing attack target.  <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when clicking or hovering over the zoom to army location button in the Challenges of Khorne screen while dragging the map.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Lords would not disengage from a settlement after selecting certain post battle options. This includes, but is not limited to, The Changeling when establishing a Trickster Cult and the Vampire Coast when establishing a Pirate Cove. <br/></li><li> Resolved an issue where Concealment Bombs were granted innately in the campaign, ensuring that the skill to grant them is now relevant/useful.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where armies obtained via Allegiance (borrowed from allied factions) with Scrap/Aspect/Mutation upgrades had access to those upgrades. Viewing the upgrades is now limited to cases where they exist, are not locked/excluded, or the army is loaned. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue so that AI factions will now hire mercenaries from your Ogre camps. <br/></li><li> Eternal War spawned armies no longer trigger Daemons Reforged, aligning with the intended design. <br/></li><li> Ogre armies can now recruit Regiments of Renown when they are within the circle of influence of an Ogre Camp.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where WAAAGH! armies would erroneously execute underway interceptions. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed the Manufactory panel being inaccessible if no further upgrades were available. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug for Orcs &amp; Goblins where the Scrap Upgrades button would grey out when a unit is instantly recruited. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where a tooltip explaining that settlements razed by Khornate factions are blocked from occupation wouldn’t appear. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Orcs &amp; Goblins or Wood Elves could access Scrap or Aspects on Skaven units, causing Throt's Lab UI to appear broken. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with Challenges of Khorne battles where Challenge armies on the campaign minimap didn’t have icons. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with Challenges of Khorne battles so that players can now know if the Challenge army will be reinforced beforehand. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Recruitment cost reduction rewards for Arbaal's Challenges were missing from event notifications, despite appearing in the Challenges of Khorne screen. Notifications now correctly display all rewards when receiving or completing a Challenge.</li></ul> <div class="bb_h2">BATTLE </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved some instances where ranged units will clump while reforming but we're still looking into further issues with this.<br/></li><li> Improved Gotrek and Felix’s initial survivability in ‘The Adventures of Gotrek and Felix’ quest battle (to Gotrek’s dismay).  <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where replays wouldn’t have projectile upgrades saved into them e.g. Elspeth’s Helstorm rocket batteries upgraded in the Imperial Gunnery School would fire 3 instead of 4 rockets in a volley.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Unyielding Assault failed to prevent Melee Attack reductions from Fatigue.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">AI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where reinforcing AI units will be given the same order location and will clump together as they all try and pile on to complete their order.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">AUDIO</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Kholek was missing persistent VFX sounds in campaign. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Vampire Counts Corpse Carts were missing sound effects. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Foundry of Bones - Chaos was missing the lava lake and river sounds. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where certain environmental loops did not stop after a cutscene. </li></ul><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues or bugs after updating to Hotfix 6.0.4, please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
