<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 News - Twitch Drops 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162775980702</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8ad5db286be549fbdfaa5679a41085167a8207e6.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/8fa4aca9d240a46f428052afefea63b3b1e9a7a4.png"/><br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks! </b><br/>Tuesday we unleashed da WAAAGH! and we couldn’t be more pleased with the rain of dakka spewed across our varied game modes and levels. <br/><br/><b>To celebrate, we’re offering you more free loot to snazz up ‘ya wagon with. </b><br/><br/>Between now and Monday September 2nd, you’ll be able to unlock up to 3 cosmetic items depending on how long you watch a stream, with <b>drops enabled</b>, in the Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks category on Twitch.  Those items are: <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">SHREDDA RIM</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/88d95b9bab5a8a9e33fa1418e2190f29600b9943.png"/><br/>- 20 minutes watch time<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">ZOG GUBBINZ</div> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d14afd4650eec3d46dbac129dea61f6f60b7c9ea.png"/><br/>- 1 hour watch time<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">MANGLA RIM</div> <img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f9b03140af80ccd063fd884c09911801b0006cad.png"/><br/>- 2 hours watch time<br/><br/>For you to receive these items ingame, you need to link your Speed Freeks Pros Account to Twitch. Go to your Pros account then “Settings” in the top right &gt; Connections &gt; Twitch. <br/><br/><b>Simple. </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/735fde9d06f985f4dd91fd604f9021d935664399.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Not a fan of Twitch? Fear not, these items are not exclusive and can be unlocked individually through purchase in the Mek Store.  <br/><br/>Thanks again for all your support and racing antics. We hope to bring you more rewards like this in future. <br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump into our extended multiplayer gameplay trailer!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4326355898839555163</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello, Space Marines!</div><br/>This is it: <b>one month to go until the release of Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2!</b><br/>In the meantime, as we know you're eager to discover more about the game and its multiplayer mode... <b>Dive into our new extended gameplay trailer!</b> <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/moaWKtTq1zc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Slay your enemies!</div><br/>Whether you play in Operations (PvE) or Eternal War (PvP) mode, choose one of <b>six playable classes </b> (Tactical, Assault, Vanguard, Bulwark, Sniper, and Heavy) and earn Armoury Data and Requisition Points to spend on your Space Marine’s appearance thanks to the game’s <b>deep customization system</b>. You can either unlock the game’s many Chapter presets, or create your own custom Chapters by piecing together individual cosmetic items, be it armour or weapon skins! <b>The more you play, the more cosmetics you will earn! </b> ⭐<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7a52fb9bb939884e854a211c37021a4b5b07ee02.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Free content updates after release</div><br/>Space Marine 2 doesn't stop at the release: we will add more content, starting with <b>new “Operations” missions, PvP maps, new enemies, and new weapons</b> through <b>regular free updates</b> available to all. In addition to this free content, if you own a Season Pass, you will be granted additional cosmetics and Chapter heraldry through seasonal, themed DLC that will celebrate the many fan-favorite factions of the Warhammer 40,000 universe! <br/><br/>But we don’t want to tease too much yet… More details will be shared very soon. <br/>👀<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/5a38f252d0da44239da71e3d4cb0c937ce08fe35.jpg"/><br/><br/>Thank you all for your incredible support since the reveal of the game, we can’t wait to finally give it to you. <br/><br/>Get ready, Space Marines, for it’s only starting! 💥]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Hit Registration and Cheating 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797812386918</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We've been seeing many reports about hit registration issues and rest assured, this is our top priority to fix.<br/><br/>We've also seen reports of "cheating" associated with the hit registration issue, but those people are not cheating, it's just something going on with the net code.<br/><br/>We have however seen a few reports of confirmed cheaters and we're already taking steps against them.<br/><br/>Apologies for the issues so far! We're just two days into launch now and with the game live and being consistently played by thousands of players, new issues are popping up that we hadn't seen before, we're doing our best to address them. <br/><br/>Thanks for your patience and support.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Server Disconnect Compensation 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797809444568</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Thanks for jumping in Speed Freeks Day 1 of Early Access. We had some server issues at release which caused some of you to be disconnected from matches. This has been fixed by the team with a new server roll out earlier today. <br/><br/>As a thank you for your support and to honor the playtime you lost due to server instability we will be sending out a 1 Day Scrap Boost through our email system, the same one we send our newsletter out with.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9fbb1b9ad50530626b697dac1fcc681be427c2a.png"/><br/> <br/>If you’ve already signed up for the newsletter you will be sent the Scrap Boost automatically. If you haven’t signed up yet fear not, it’s easy to opt in and you will also get the cute little Squig Gubbinz cosmetic topper when you follow. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2623f614a356cf931a23e04980689799fc1db4e8.png"/><br/><br/>To sign up for the newsletter simply log into your Speed Freeks account and click the follow button.<br/>https://prismray.io/games/speedfreeks <br/><br/>To redeem the Scrap Boost click the Redeem Code button in your profile and enter the code that was provided in the email. <br/>https://support.prismray.io/hc/en-us/articles/22351440941073-How-to-Redeem-a-Code<br/><br/> <br/>Sincere thanks for your feedback and support, and welcome to the WAAAGH!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back from Summer - Next Hotfix Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4353377496597045467</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Heyo everyone, <br/><br/>A quick message from us to say we’re back from summer break and we’ll have our first hotfix coming next week! The plan was for it to come this week, however we hit a technical snag we need to iron out first. 🙏<br/><br/>We’ll see you next week!<br/><br/>- The Darktide Team<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
