<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Quest - Redeem your code in just a few steps!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/550127015582236791</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3"><b>Hi all! 🫡</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Here's a quick tutorial on how to participate in the Discord Quest and quickly redeem your code once the quest is completed!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>1. Take part in the Discord Quest</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Accept the Quest on Discord by clicking <u>this link</u> 🔗</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Play Warhammer 40,000 on Steam for at least 15 minutes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Get your in-game reward as a code!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3"><b>2. Redem your code</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Once you have a Redeem Code, head over to <span class="bb_removedlink" data-community-tooltip="The URL that was linked here has been removed by our filters.  Usually this is done to prevent phishing and malware attacks.">{LINK REMOVED}</span><u>this link</u>, sign up or create an account to redeem it!</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">To proceed, you will need to go to your account, redeem your reward and copy/paste your Redeem Code.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Once your code is successfully redeemed, the reward will be available in the full game once your link your PROS account in-game by scanning the QR Code.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note, the Redeem Code is valid from Coordinated Universal Time (UTC): October 16, 2025, 9:00:00 AM to October 23, 2025, 8:59:59 AM.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/DISCORD_QUEST-2.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORKTOBER patch New Maps + News</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/655961606822297798</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Dat <b>Deffkopta</b> 'az warmed da 'earts ov you'z gits, it 'as</div><p class="bb_paragraph">What a great response to last week's reveal of the new vehicle. We think you guys will have a blast playing it 🚁</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/fdf9e1adbd900906fbd42216d024958c95eeb94b.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You don't have to wait long, because the <b>Deffkopta</b> is coming in next week's Orktober patch, along with a couple new maps: <b>Scrap in Da Yard</b> for Kill Konvoy, and <b>Deff Gorge</b> for Deff Rally.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">More on that later...</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">ORKTOBER </div><p class="bb_paragraph">Now, with that great news comes some unexpected news, which is that the upcoming <b>LEVEL EDITOR</b> has been <b>delayed</b> to instead launch in another big update for <b>November</b>. We felt this was the right choice since cloud <b>Workshop</b> <b>support</b> wasn't going to be ready for next week, and there's still some polish things we'd like to add to the editor, which we think the community will really appreciate.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Now, some of you gits might be thinking "Why doz dis matta to a speedy, smashy, krumpy git like me dat just speedily smash's and krumps ova gits?"</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Well, my mean and green friend, a <b>level editor</b> with a shared <b>Workshop</b> means that there will be lotz and lotz of new, community-made levels to play with each other - and if what we've seen so far from our testers is any indication, there will be some <b>INSANE</b> <b>maps</b>.</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">And if you're the type of git who likes to make maps, even better.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Our testers and us devs have had some amazing sessions of a host creating maps in realtime, <i>while others played them as they were being built</i>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">These play sessions can turn into absolute lunacy, especially when in voice chat together.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">For example, this was the beginning of a silly level we started making as a team in realtime.<br/>But this is nothing compared to how much more you can do with the editor.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d19e99c4275f99c91c1ec52d5384dd9356915e88.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">So yeah, as we've said before, we are <b>super excited</b> to share this feature with the player base and can't wait for you guys can see what people build - either right in front of your eyes while playing, or by downloading it from the Workshop.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/> </p><div class="bb_h2">DA MAPS 🗺️</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Alright, wot about sum more info on da update next week ya?</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've got two new maps, one for each <b>Kill Konvoy</b> and <b>Deff Rally</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Kill Konvoy - Scrap In Da Yard</b> takes place in a - you guessed it - massive scrapyard. There's moving scrap everywhere, lots of verticality to take advantage of, and a massive trench in the second half which leads to a big scrap dump for the final stretch.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We think this is one of the best Konvoy maps yet, and we think you'll agree once you play it a couple times 👍</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/12ac9dfc13732a526cef153d6148ed15b99737ce.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It's also got a spooky secondary lighting version:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4db8b1cdd9ed38eb2398b0465bb913900bbecc90.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deff Rally - Deff Gorge</b> is a DR version of Kill Konvoy - Da Gorge, after a snowfall and the area has been somewhat abandoned. The level's alternate lighting is quite striking having a sunset contrasting with the snowy ground.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Gorge makes for a great race playground, and you'll see what we mean when you play it. There's also an area that has players race through a forest, a first in Speed Freeks.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2596c12d411b84bcb4aa721df6345ca474ee645d.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0b0ce87b0a10bd780e9a24cb39e810caf5f02993.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f2d598885360d6c535eed4043f5a4e69e76daf5e.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/></p><div class="bb_h2">DA MUSIC 🎵</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Any proppa git likes a badass tune, and our resident musicians Cave Bat have created a fantastic new tune for the main menu, so you can jam out while customizing ridez and checking stats.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Really happy with how this song turned out, so we're eager to see what da freeks think of it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/></div><div class="bb_h2">DA STEAM DECK</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Just a quick note about steam deck, is that we've seen a severe issue reported where performance will drop to 0-3 fps for periods of time - we're assuming due to shader compilation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is strange because it seemed to have starting happening a couple months ago, either after one of our patches (where we didn't change anything related) or a Steam OS update.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We're investigating the issue and will try to have something done for next week's update but we can't promise anything at this time, since although we can reproduce it, it's difficult seeing what the cause is.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll keep you <b>Steam Deck</b> users up to date on any fixes for this. Sorry for the poor experience right now.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">See you gits in da skies next week!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">(And in flames on da ground...😈)</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Plenty more news coming after this upcoming patch as well, so be sure to check in and drop us a WAAAGH! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">We've got an active and dedicated community already on the official SF Discord, so smash your way onto it if you fancy chatting and playing with other gits</p><p class="bb_paragraph">JOIN DA DISCORD</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.3.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/567015514185924925</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/63f1a81243285a9535610e9900079e56b809cfc1.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hey folks,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We've just rolled out Hotfix 6.3.3 for Total War: WARHAMMER III, resolving a couple of ownership requirement issues that arose in the wake of Patch 6.3 which was affecting FLC content. This was due to the removal of Total War Access as a requirement for ownership causing some content to be locked, when this shouldn't be the case.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">After this, Hotfix 6.3.4 will be the next update to arrive in WH3, which we will share more details on next week.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Until then, see you on the battlefield!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">— The Total War Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Hotfix 6.3.3</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed ownership requirements for some FLC content following the removal of Total War Access as a requirement, including:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">30th Anniversary Regiments of Renown</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Gotrek &amp; Felix</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Goblin Great Shaman</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Great Bray Shaman</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Glade Captain</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Catchweb Spider Shrine mount</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> </p></li></ul></li></ul><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle via the Discord Quest!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/507342099205587439</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Greetings Brothers and Sisters! 🫡</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>Unlock the Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle now! 💥</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Complete the <i>Space Marine 2</i> Discord Quest by playing the game on Steam! For 15 minutes of playtime, you get to unlock the <b>Porphyr Shield Bolt Rifle</b>. Discord will provide you with a code, to redeem your reward <b>in the full game</b>. Don't forget to link your <b>Discord</b>, PROS<b> </b>and <b>Steam accounts</b> together</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Non-owners: play the demo for 15 minutes to earn the reward.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Owners: play the full game for 15 minutes to earn the reward.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This event starts on October 16</b>, at around 3PM UTC and ends on October 23rd at 9AM UTC.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ce37226c06cbc3ce93c58d34ca64d63cd9fd9bd4.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3">Good luck and have fun!</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment Announce Trailer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/567015514185924790</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Tides of Torment are coming in, and the waves will wash up to our shores a terrifying trio of Legendary Lords: Aislinn, Dechala, and Sayl on December 4th!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BsEX51KP6U8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
