<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Big News Incoming Tomorrow + Temporary Downtime</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/541105873081073854</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI LADZ!  Quick one here...<br/><br/>We needed to drop a heads up about some <i><b>very</b></i> exciting SPEED FREEKS news we'll be sharing tomorrow, May 16th!<br/><br/>Unfortunately, as a byproduct of the exciting changes, the game is going to be unavailable to download for new players for a period of time while we re-tool some things on the backend. Existing players will be unable to connect to matchmaking and play during this period.<br/><br/>This downtime was something we expected to occur tomorrow afternoon, but ended up taking effect 12 hours earlier than anticipated - so we apologize for the inconvenience. But we expect that our players will be quite happy with what we are going to reveal once we do.<br/><br/>We'll share additional information ASAP as to when players can can get back to racin' n' krumpin', plus drop the exciting news about the future of the Speed Freeks tomorrow.  We're eager to share...<br/><br/>SEE YOU'Z THEN!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level the Battlefield with the New Archetype and Origin in Lex Imperialis!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523090745159059756</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
As the situation across the Koronus Expanse continues to escalate, the von Valancius dynasty is in dire need of new tactical advantages.<br/><br/>The new second-tier archetype <b>the Overseer</b> as well as the new <b>Arbites</b> origin introduced in the Lex Imperialis expansion offer the perfect solution to this problem.<br/><br/>Let's find out more!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/af11cf147518a0947f8ef32c51365f9db7b47862.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Meet the Overseer</div><br/><b>Overseers</b> are flexible support specialists who deploy familiars — cybernetic creatures that can assist their masters in various ways. During combat, these loyal servants dash across the battlefield at great speed, amplifying their Overseer's offensive abilities, disrupting enemy maneuvers, and delivering additional damage with their claws and teeth. During exploration, they may also provide aid by pulling levers, dragging items, or uncovering hidden objects.<br/><br/>Familiars can’t be controlled directly (except in some rare cases), but they can be issued a variety of commands during their master’s turn, allowing them to perform a wide array of tasks. Each of them has its own stats and can be attacked as well as fall unconscious.<br/><br/>The Overseer stands out among second-tier archetypes in that it can be unlocked not only by picking one of the relevant first-tier archetypes (in this case, Officer or Operative) but also by having one of the relevant origins (ie, Sanctioned Psyker, Unsanctioned Psyker such as Idira, or the newly introduced Arbites origin).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2c74fe063a54b85b746e80c671a7107f37683355.jpg"/><br/><br/>Depending on the pathway used to unlock the archetype, an Overseer may employ:<br/><br/>1)<b> A cyber-mastiff</b>, available only to Overseers with the Arbites origin. It provides both powerful martial support as well as off-tanking capabilities.<br/><br/>Ability example:<br/><br/><i><b>Apprehend</b><br/><br/>The Overseer chooses an enemy in their line of sight. The cyber-mastiff then immediately attempts to run to that enemy. If it does not have enough MP, it instead moves as close to them as possible. Upon reaching the designated enemy, the cyber-mastiff makes a melee attack, dealing +50% more damage and inflicting the <b>apprehended</b> effect. This effect lasts for as long as the enemy and the cyber-mastiff are adjacent to each other, or until another order is given.<br/>This ability can be used multiple times per turn, but each subsequent use within a round increases its cost by +1 AP.<br/><br/><b>Apprehended:</b><br/>Whenever the Overseer makes a successful attack against an apprehended creature, the apprehending cyber-mastiff also makes a free melee attack against it that deals −50% less damage. If the creature tries to move away from the cyber-mastiff, the cyber-mastiff has a ((familiar's WS + familiar's STR) / 3)% chance to cancel that movement. Also, if the creature moves more than 1 cell away, the cyber-mastiff follows (without cost to its MP) and attacks it.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/821f0b32ab99e1d4809498303f49ed5bb5a0c375.gif"/><br/><br/>2) <b>A psyber-raven</b>, available only to Sanctioned and Unsanctioned Psykers. It has the ability to amplify and relay psychic powers far across the battlefield.<br/><br/>Ability example: <br/><br/><i><b>Warp Relay</b><br/><br/>Whenever the Overseer targets their psyber-raven with a non-attacking, single-target psychic power (excluding those that grant extra turns), the effect of that power is instead applied to all relevant targets (allies or enemies) in a 4-cell radius around the psyber-raven, without affecting the psyber-raven itself. Any enemy creature within that radius also gains the <b>under surveillance</b> effect.<br/><br/><b>Under Surveillance:</b><br/>The Overseer of the psyber-raven ignores this creature's cover.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/939d93b504165682ff4c80f5500d248558bafbf7.gif"/><br/><br/>3) <b>A cyber-eagle</b>, available to Officers and Operatives. It has the ability to apply various debuffs, attack enemies from a large distance, and disrupt enemy targeting and movement.<br/><br/>Ability Example:<br/><br/><i><b>Obstruct Vision</b><br/><br/>The Overseer chooses an enemy in their line of sight and an unoccupied cell adjacent to it. The cyber-eagle moves to that cell (can move through occupied cells) without provoking attacks of opportunity. Once the cyber-eagle reaches that cell, the designated enemy makes an attack toward the cyber-eagle's side, using whichever attack costs the least AP. If that enemy has a ranged weapon, it makes a ranged attack with an additional +50% chance to hit its ally.<br/>While the cyber-eagle is in that cell, the designated enemy is <b>obstructed</b>.<br/><br/><b>Obstructed:</b><br/>An obstructed creature cannot leave its cell through regular means and can only make attacks toward the obstructing cyber-eagle's side. If this creature has a ranged weapon, its shots have an additional +50% chance of hitting an ally. Whenever the cyber-eagle dodges this creature's attack, it immediately attacks the creature back, dealing +(2 × cyber-eagle's AGI)% more damage, without a cost to its AP.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/3b7c1edd2265f866d437855abfead272faf6fdfe.gif"/><br/><br/>4) <b>A servo-skull swarm</b>, also available to Officers and Operatives. It provides a wide range of utility and protective abilities and can also deliver AoE damage.<br/><br/>Talent example: <br/><br/><i><b>Safe Shelter</b><br/><br/>If the Overseer or any of their allies are protected by partial cover in a 4-cell radius around the servo-skull swarm, they are instead considered protected by full cover.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/2eb91519343506f365f729974ef7fbfbd78cfd26.gif"/><br/><br/>Each Overseer can only have one familiar, but if multiple requirements are met, there will also be multiple choices of familiar available. For example, if Idira takes Overseer as her second-tier archetype, she will not only have access to the cyber-eagle and servo-skull swarm thanks to her Operative Archetype, but can also pick the psyber-raven due to her being a Psyker.<br/><br/>The only exception to this system are the Xenos the Lord Captain has in their retinue. Since all the available familiars are of Imperial design, Xenos cannot become Overseers, even if they fit the described requirements. Sorry, Yrliet!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/6571e6c9a9fe04e7582ddd0ab74820a040905fcc.png"/><br/><br/>Most of the Overseer’s talents and abilities revolve around improving the stats of their chosen familiar, expanding their range of abilities, and unlocking direct synergies with either the Overseer’s origin or their first-tier archetype.<br/><br/>Each familiar has a special inventory slot for protocols. Protocols are a new type of item scattered throughout the game world that allow for further customization of familiars. For example, here’s one of the options for the cyber-mastiff:<br/><br/><i><b>Indomitable Rage</b><br/><br/>The cyber-mastiff gains +10 Weapon Skill and deals +100% more damage.<br/>In addition, whenever the cyber-mastiff hits an apprehended enemy, it also gains a stacking + (2 × WS bonus) bonus to Strength for 1 round.</i><br/><br/>And finally, you’ll be pleased to hear that there is no limit on the number of Overseers you can have in your party. So, if you were missing the opportunity to unleash utter mayhem with 12 friendly units in combat like you could in our previous games, you will soon have all the tools you need to do it again!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Meet the Arbites</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/ee9ae51590eda3198714ee7538b34d83dd6fb53b.gif"/><br/><br/>The Lex Imperialis expansion also comes with a new origin option: the Arbites. With a background in the Adeptus Arbites, Rogue Traders who hail from the ranks of these hardened veterans know first-hand why the brutal laws of the Imperium must be upheld, with rich experience in dealing with traitors, renegades, and rebels of all kinds.<br/><br/>Similar to Psykers, this origin has multiple specialties, offering a number of distinct playstyles and effective synergies with various archetypes:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Subductor</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/0a70e279c0b26f8e4a90ccdddec9f06f044e9b3b.jpg"/><br/><br/>Arbites with this specialty excel at ruthless melee combat, relying heavily on shields for both protection and pressure.<br/><br/><b>Primary stats and skills: </b>WS, WP, Coercion<br/><b>Recommended archetype: </b>Warrior<br/><br/>Ability examples:<br/><br/>- Dash through enemies with a shield to knock them out<br/>- Deal additional damage from shield attacks<br/>- Negate critical damage from short distances<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Vigilant</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/33954a372011a4d818bc90c50085c7b1e42d1416.jpg"/><br/><br/>Arbites with this specialty are shotgun professionals, bringing the effectiveness of this weapon type to a whole new level.<br/><br/><b>Primary stats and skills: </b>BS, WP, Coercion<br/><b>Recommended archetype: </b>Soldier<br/><br/>Ability examples:<br/><br/>- Enemies hit by a shotgun receive more damage from subsequent attacks<br/>- Use special ammo types that deal increased damage, apply additional effects, or reduce enemy stats<br/>- The option to use two-handed shotguns in one hand<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Castigator</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/422877c56e67145b5b123a092377ecb394d0e708.jpg"/><br/><br/>These Arbites specialize in ensuring that the guilty submit to the Lex, and receive their due punishment by any means necessary.<br/><br/><b>Primary stats and skills: </b>Fel, WP, Coercion<br/><b>Recommended archetype: </b>Officer<br/><br/>Ability examples:<br/><br/>- Bark an order at nearby enemies to immobilize them<br/>- Judge an enemy to reduce their stats and increase damage dealt to them<br/>- Force nearby enemies to move in a specific direction<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/12d0b2c07ef1b8fa2bc6ee28b681d6f30ff168b8.png"/><br/><br/>Like what you’re seeing so far?<br/><br/>In our next article, we will be looking at the brand new equipment type available — Shields!<br/><br/>Stay tuned!<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The big annual community survey is here!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/501699281359470977</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The big annual community survey is here!<br/><br/>Our proud parliament of owlcats keeps growing, with more amazing people joining us and sharing our passion for deep, story-rich games. We’d love to get to know you better! <br/><br/>Take part in this survey to help us understand our community and shape even more incredible projects together:<br/><br/>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/P9XHP2L]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your brief for the May Community Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500572747038984445</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Brace yourselves, Space Marines!</div><br/>The May Community Event starts on May 14 and ends on the 21st! <br/><b>Throughout the event, Requisition rewards are increased by 50% </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0c6aed77a0edc514b63620a6501272028dedf3be.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlesector &amp; Gladius will take part in Warhammer Skulls Festival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/511831746088536160</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We are excited to announce that <b>Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector &amp; Gladius</b> will be taking part in the Warhammer Skulls festival.<br/><br/>We can't wait to show you what is coming: The Warhammer Skulls showcase will begin on Thursday May 22nd 5pm UK time,  and the festival will last a whole week until Thursday May 29th.<br/><br/>Games Workshop is going to kickstart the festival with a showcase on their Twitch channel, so make sure to tune in on Warhammer Twitch channel at <b>5 pm BST on May 22nd</b>.<br/><br/>Discover more about the Warhammer Skulls festival here.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
