<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.2 Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500566410271917830</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines,</div><br/>As announced in the February Community Update, hotfix 6.2 has been deployed on every platform. <br/>This is a small patch that mostly focuses on crash fixes and minor balancing tweaks in preparation of a major Patch 7 that would focus on weapon perks and weapon loadouts rebalance.<br/><br/>As usual, if you encounter issues with this update, let us know by making a bug report here.<br/><br/>You'll find the complete patch notes down below.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">PATCH NOTES</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Datavault ordeal Shredding Shrapnel now requires to kill 2 enemies simultaneously with a single frag grenade instead of 3.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the AI Director that could sometimes spawn too many spore mines for a very long period.<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues that would cause Assault class to teleport back after using its Jump Pack ability.<br/></li><li> Minor localization fixes.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Perk PvE Updates</div><br/><i>Overall we are quite happy with 6.0 perks rebalance, we are seeing way more build variety for all classes across all difficulties and seeing people experimenting with their builds more. That being said, there are still some perks that will require more attention or even full rework. We will be monitoring the situation and will be making necessary tweaks.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c741d6ad228423769275bff7e195c4362308e0d3.png"/><br/><br/><b>Heightened Vigour: </b><br/>- Fixed not triggering by perfect Parry or Block in some cases.<br/><br/><b>Close Targeting: </b><br/>- Damage increased from 15% to 25%.<br/><br/><b>Concentrated Fire: </b><br/>- Bonus duration of the Auspex Scan zone increased from 40% to 60%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1abf8c6d07944560f7c6535488e606fe81f15ea4.png"/><br/><br/><b>Perseverance:</b><br/>- Damage reduction bonus increased from 15% to 25%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/49a8b1e1d75b916ba063b4bcda14fc04e773850c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Restless Fortitude:</b> <br/>- Damage reduction bonus increased from 20% to 40%.<br/><br/><b>Tactical Prowess:</b> <br/>- Minimum enemy HP for auto finisher increased from 25% to 33%.<br/><br/><b>Unmatched Zeal: </b><br/>- Health regen bonus increased from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b008de073c9e7e17f7c5410a6ebec4145b7304ca.png"/><br/><br/><b>Block Break: </b><br/>- Damage increased from 25% to 50%.<br/><br/><b>Evasion: </b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct cooldown of 30 seconds instead of 15 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Efficient Readiness:</b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct 20% movement boost instead of 10%.<br/><br/><b>Pattern of Excellence: </b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct cooldown of 30 seconds instead of 180 seconds.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This perk was buffed in the 6.0 patch, but localization was not updated and it was missing in patch notes.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6dc73b997ce968ed4d170cec92bf099029c43431.png"/><br/><br/><b>Chapter Banner (starting perk): </b><br/>- Bonus health increased from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><b>Emergency Countermeasure: </b><br/>- Cooldown reduced from 120 to 90 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Defensive Mastery: </b><br/>- Cooldown reduced from 120 to 90 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Glory's Shield:</b><br/>- Now the perk protects not only from Ranged Damage but from all incoming Damage.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This should improve support Bulwark build a lot, since this perk doesn't impact Banner cooldown</i><br/><br/><b>Invigorating Icon: </b><br/>- The ability regeneration slowdown has been fixed, but the regeneration penalty is now -50% instead of -100%.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This perk has been discussed a lot in previous patch notes and here are my honest thoughts on this.</i><br/><br/><i>We've made a mistake making this perk in the first place. It changes the class behavior too much from what was originally intended. Bulwark is supposed to tank enemies and support his team mates, he isn't a dedicated healer. But players are now used to this playstyle a lot and now absolutely any change to this perk will cause negativity from the community. <br/><br/>The perk itself is so powerful that it is simply mandatory, plus it also changes how the ability is used. Unlike other classes where abilities are used whenever the player wants, it turns the banner into an ability that the player saves for the very last moment.<br/><br/>In our game it is absolutely fine, if you want to use it that way, but the problem is that with certain other perks you can bring its cooldown to ~20 seconds. This means that not picking this perk will be detrimental to your squad. No matter what the numbers on the neighboring perks, players will always stick to the ability to fully heal when needed.<br/><br/>We want to come back and rework this perk or, rather, perk column in later patches, but this requires some time of experimenting and testing. For now we are tweaking numbers to make a compromise between previous patch and community feedback.</i><br/><br/>- Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8884de443755dac7bb5665350a070df9cb37914c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Fortitude: </b><br/>- Health increases from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><b>Conversion Field: </b><br/>- Radius increased from 10 to 20 meters.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weapons Balancing</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Power Sword</div><i>We are very happy with the current melee balance. All melee options are now viable and getting picked by players across all difficulties. However, we see that Power Sword isn't strong enough, compared to much easier to wield Chainsword. It takes more skill to use the Power Sword properly, but the benefit wasn't that great. We want to adjust this a little.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Overall base damage increased by 5% <br/></li><li> Power Stance combo damage additionally increased:<br/></li><li> Attack 1 +10%<br/></li><li> Attack 2 +20%<br/></li><li> Attack 3 +30%"</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.<br/></li><li> General connectivity improvements.</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC Hotfix 6.3.4 - Easy Anti-Cheat update + Hotfix 6.3.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546728306451416317</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>We’ve just pushed a patch that swaps our old version of Easy Anti-Cheat for the newest version. The previous version is scheduled to shut down on March 4, which would’ve meant no protection to the game from cheats or tampering unless we did this upgrade.<br/><br/>A couple of things to note about this change:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> For normal gameplay, <b>there should be no notable difference.</b> The game will continue to run normally in both Official and Modded realms, and no extra actions need to be taken from you as players to continue playing.<br/></li><li> Operating Systems that had incompatibility issues with our EAC may find those issues gone with this update. We still can only officially support Windows 10 &amp; 11, but nonetheless there might be one barrier less in that aspect.<br/></li><li> The system necessary to support Sanctioned Mods is changing. This means that <b>until sanctioned mods are updated by their authors, they might not work in the official realm.</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We are currently in communication with mod authors to find the swiftest solution to this issue for all sanctioned mods.</li></ul></li><li> Connecting to other lobbies might take longer than usual at first. Will go back to normal after some time.<br/></li><li> <b>Versus Quickplay will be temporarily disabled</b> as we update the servers.</li></ul>We're working to fix the issues with Sanctioned Mods and Versus Quickplay Dedicated Servers as soon as possible, we'll keep you updated.<br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.3.4 patch notes - 3rd of March</div><div class="bb_h2">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Replaced the Kamu Easy Anti-Cheat for Epic Online Service<br/></li><li> Improved error messaging for banned players to show reason &amp; duration.<br/></li><li> Temporarily disabled Versus Quickplay / Dedicated Servers.</li></ul></blockquote><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.3.5 patch notes - 4th of March</div><div class="bb_h2">Fixs</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where re-installing the game would not re-install EasyAntiCheat correctly.</li></ul></blockquote>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Blog - New Versus Map: A Grudge Served Cold</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546728306451416292</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/543be07ae542f09609fa3d005a5708c87d3c282e.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div>As mentioned in our previous announcement, another Vermintide 2 level has been adapted and added to the pool of playable Versus maps: A Grudge Served Cold!<br/><br/>We thought you might be curious about why or how a map is turned into a Versus level, so we interviewed one of our level designers, Pål, who redesigned the level...<br/><br/><b>Why was A Grudge Served Cold picked to be the next Versus map? What features or aspects of it made it seem like a good fit for Versus?</b><br/><i>“The level was built in a way that converting it to Versus would be quite a fast process, compared to other levels. The layout is open to water on the left-hand side and mountain ranges to the right and it doesn’t have too many empty backfaces or “half-built” structures like many other levels have.”</i><br/><br/>Areas that Heroes never get to look at in normal gameplay often aren’t meant to be looked at, but because the Pactsworn specials can move around all over the place by climbing or even leaping, patching up all of those views is important.<br/><br/><i>“We also wanted to have another art style, where both snow/winter mixed with the Dwarfen environment made it feel fresh."</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/ca6d147d9a3289e530de19a112ea41c93dcb927c.png"/><br/><br/><i>"It also features a nice mix between tight passages or “corridors” and open spaces, and it also provides quite a lot of verticality.”</i><br/><br/><b>What, overall, makes for a good &amp; fun Versus level?</b><br/><i>“Definitely a mix between open spaces, verticality, chokes, interiors, and exteriors.”</i><br/><br/><i>“Levels that are “geometrically complicated” in their set-up are also hard to convert to Versus (‘Tower of Treachery’ would probably be quite hard to do, for example).<br/>Maps with too many long chokepoints and tight passages are also not fun (‘Hunger in the Dark’, as an example)”</i><br/><br/><i>“Maps that have some built-in events that make sense in the world already (such as the gate you blow up in Screaming Bell to pass through the plaza) are great, but levels that offer opportunities for new Versus specific events to be added are also good.”</i><br/><br/><i>“We wanted the “portfolio” of levels to offer everything that makes Vermintide 2 fun, and the levels are better if they allow a lot of new areas to be added for Skaven, so the players see some new parts and experience what the world looks like from different perspectives (such as standing on a high cliff and looking down at the Heroes).”</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/e3aaebd2302edf4d67e0660c1f6a2a7d18c2ff75.png"/><br/><br/><b>For ‘A Grudge Served Cold’, are there any highlights of new or changed places, objectives, pacing, etc.?</b><br/><i>“‘A Grudge Served Cold’ was a bit too long and had to be cut at the beginning. We also added some interiors such as caves and safe rooms inside the Dwarf interiors.”</i><br/><br/><i>“The main events are still as they are in Adventure mode, but we added a few capture zones, and a payload to reduce the endless running and allow the pact-sworn to break the Heroes’ dash.”</i><br/><br/><i>“It was supposed to be only 2 rounds, but the length of the level made it into 3 rounds. We added a night environment to the last round to make it feel like some time has passed, and also because it looks nice.”</i><br/><br/><b>What would you look for if you had to turn another map into a Versus level?</b><br/><i>“ ‘Garden of Morr’ is a level that looks to have a very fun Versus layout, but the geometry is quite complicated to work with, with many small units stitched together, and lots of holes where Heroes can’t look.<br/><br/>On the other hand, it’s not nice to have too many large, solid structures, because if we need to make changes, artists need to spend time separating them, exporting new units &amp; more.”</i><br/><br/><i>“‘A Parting of the Waves’ looks to be a great Versus level as well.”</i><br/><br/><i>“All-in-all, we move, delete, add, and heavily rework the levels, but on the “surface,” they should look just like the Adventure levels. But pretty much all the units in a level are somehow tweaked, rotated a little, moved, and fixed so Versus works. It’s mostly about making the pact-sworn feel like Heroes because they have access to a lot of level areas that the Heroes can’t reach. So shortcuts, vantage points, etc. are very important.”</i><br/><br/><i>“You also create a “net” of transition points with the climb units, which in theory should cover the whole level, but it’s important to not add too many (the UI becomes bloated).”</i><br/><br/><i>“We also scaled down the enemy compositions, terror events strength, and roaming enemies a lot, since we have the 4 pact-sworn players using the Horde ability all the time.”</i><br/><br/><i>“If I were to convert another Adventure level to Versus, I would look for a bit more ‘wild and crazy’ layout level to push the Versus experience even further and avoid repetitiveness. For example Bögenhafen’s ‘The Pit’, which is a huge open town map with plenty of possibilities to add cool events.”</i><br/><br/>The new map will be added to the pool of Versus maps on March 6 alongside the Anniversary event! Check it out then!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500566410271917053</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines 🫡</div><br/>Let’s recap what occurred in February on Space Marine 2 a bit and then we’ll tackle future topics! We know you're eager for Patch 7 to drop! There's still a bit of a wait, but in the meantime, we'll be sure to tease you a little.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FEBRUARY RECAP</div><br/>This month we released the 6.0 Datavault Update, containing new free and Season Pass content. You may check the entire changelog here! 📖<br/><br/>Mostly, the biggest features that were added to the game are:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Datavault, with new cosmetic rewards<br/></li><li> The Biovore<br/></li><li> New PvP Map “Tomb”<br/></li><li> Salamanders Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Raven Guard Cosmetic Pack including its Successor Chapters<br/></li><li> FOV Slider<br/></li><li> Perks rework</li></ul>Following that, we released the 6.1 Hotfix to help with a few remaining bugs and connectivity issues, mostly. Again, you can read the patch notes here.<br/>We are aware that with these two updates, a few issues remain, such as: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FPS drops<br/></li><li> Too many spore mines spawning at the same time</li></ul>We’re actively working on it.<br/>Hotfix 6.2 will arrive next week. It shall fix the spore mines issue and bring some balancing tweaks.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">IMPERIAL VIGIL COMMUNITY EVENT</div><br/>We heard about your desire to have an emblem-less Mk VIII Errant Helmet, so here’s your chance! ✨ This cosmetic is entirely free, the only requirement is to link your PROS account to Space Marine 2.<br/>Here’s your brief: “Achieve a victory with each of 6 classes in Operations Mode to win the emblem-less Mark VIII Errant Helmet”<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/876731048e75bea664881bc7949c13b396be58a9.png"/><br/><br/>The event lasts until March 3rd.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NOTE ABOUT COMMUNITY EVENTS</div><br/>We have noted that the Community Events have received cold feedback since we introduced them as an additional way to unlock cosmetic items. We saw that many of you mentioned FOMO generated by the events. Rest assured, we are not looking to transform Space Marine 2 into a full live service game. The items available through events WILL be available later, for everyone. We want Community Events to be a way to unlock the items in advance, for the most dedicated players, and not to be a source of frustration and stress for everyone.<br/><br/>However, that means we must provide a smooth experience in unlocking said items, which has not been the case so far. We deeply apologize for the trouble, and are currently working on a simplified process to unlock the items, to make the experience less constraining.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WHAT’S COMING…</div><br/>The 7.0 Update is in the making! ✨ We’re working on it and we’ll give you a more precise date once we get one. 🙌<br/><br/>This update will bring several awaited features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> One Chapter Pack<br/></li><li> One Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Private PvP lobbies<br/></li><li> A new weapon (only in PvE for now)<br/></li><li> New Operation<br/></li><li> Weapon perks rebalance<br/></li><li> Class weapon loadouts rework<br/></li><li> PvE Prestige Rank: once you reach level 25 on a class, you can buy a Prestige Level that will unlock a unique Prestige Perk. Choose them wisely, because you won’t be able to change your selected Prestige Perks before unlocking the 4 Prestige Levels. On top of that power boost, each class will have a unique cosmetic reward that emphasizes the class’ iconic armour part. <br/></li><li> and more!</li></ul>Stay tuned, we’ll soon come with more info.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">HORDE MODE</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6f4bd2012c6235fab5e95505ccc44b45a4d0c5db.png"/><br/><br/>…..So apparently you’re waiting for the Horde Mode.<br/><br/>You’re very eager to get more info on the Horde Mode, it’s one of our top priorities right now. <br/>One thing we can say is that it will be very different from the Space Marine 1 Horde Mode, and that there are surprises we can’t wait for you to find out about. 😉<br/><br/>Once we get really interesting things to show you about it, we will do it!<br/><br/>Bear with us 🙏<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">PUBLIC TEST SERVER</div><br/>We’re also excited to share our goal to launch our Public Test Servers  in just a few weeks! 🙌 Expect it to take place in March and before Patch 7.<br/>Once we get a specific date, we’ll make an official statement on our socials and Discord!<br/><br/>This will give you early access to upcoming features and the opportunity to share your feedback, helping us refine the content before its official release.<br/><br/>It will exclusively happen on Steam, neither on EGS nor consoles. It will be very easy to install because it will act as a separate game.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">COMMUNITY FEEDBACK ON THE NEW ABSOLUTE DIFFICULTY - A word from our Game Director</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">We would like to hear your opinion regarding Absolute difficulty.</div><br/>Overall, we are quite happy with how intense the difficulty itself is. We see that it requires a lot of concentration and we feel like it’s fun in terms of how many enemies you have to face, how hard they hit you etc. <br/><br/>At the same time, we see some comments that it’s a bit easy. Yet on the other hand we don’t want to mess it up and would like to hear the voice of the community first.<br/>Here is some data and context.<br/><br/>According to our stats, the average win rate on Absolute difficulty is ~60% (significantly higher than Lethal difficulty that sits at 50%), which seems a bit higher than we expected.<br/>At the same time such high win rate is explained by three facts:<br/><ol><li> Absolute difficulty is locked for new users<br/></li><li> Only ~12% of daily play time is spent on Absolute difficulty.<br/></li><li> Only ~15% of weekly active players play at least 1 match on Absolute difficulty</li></ol><br/>This means that only a small portion of very hardcore and well-prepared players are playing the Absolute difficulty, and we must find a proper balance between wishes of the hardcore players and more casual players that simply want to have fun.<br/><br/>I will be completely honest; I think we are almost at our limit in terms of how we can make the game harder without making it unfair and not fun. We can’t significantly increase the number of enemies for performance and memory reasons. Greatly increasing enemy damage and hp will make it so players will die randomly and will make enemies bullet sponges, which will not be fun.<br/><br/>We do not want to implement a new difficulty, because that would split the matchmaking pool even more. We have to stick to the existing 6 difficulties.<br/><br/>The proper way of doing this would be implementing a set of gameplay modifiers (i.e. tight formation gameplay modifiers that we’ve tried to release earlier), combination of which would make each challenge unique. And I’m happy to announce that we are already working on the system, however this will take some time.”<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">For now, we can tweak some parameters and we would like to hear your opinion on specific items:</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 1:</div>Would you like to see Dual Terminus enemies and more Terminus enemies in general on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/><i>We can make it so there will be way more Terminus enemies on a level, potentially 2 at the same time. Plus we can lift restriction that prevents Terminus enemies from spawning on levels that have final bosses (i.e Hive Tyrant)</i><br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 2:</div>Shall we slightly increase enemy health and damage on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/><i>Some of the builds can break health thresholds and start one-shotting enemies. We are only talking about small health and damage tweaks that should not cause enemies to become bullet sponges.</i><br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 3:</div>Would it be better to have more limited ammo refills on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/>Vote here<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 4:</div>Do you want even more aggressive enemies on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/>We will try to implement the adjustments as soon as we can.<br/><br/><i>- Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>​Please do not take into account the total number of points spent on an answer. We will only consider the number of entries each answer has received for equity reasons.</b></div><br/><div class="bb_h1">EXCLUSIVE WALLPAPERS ON FOCUS TOGETHER</div><br/>Twelve new exclusive Space Marine 2 wallpapers have dropped on our community platform Focus Together. Make sure to create an account here and get them for free!<br/>Here’s a sneak peak of some of them:<br/><br/>Once you’ve created your account, you can directly link your Steam account to it. By doing so, you will earn different badges, avatars and titles to pimp your profile, so sign in now!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/754f328ed8ab7dcb2a920fded4233f6bd2b39c9a.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">EMOTES WERE WORTH A SHOT!</div><br/>Since the release of the Datavault Update, you’ve shared countless screenshots showing the different emotes, and we love it!!<br/><br/>Here’s a little compendium but if you want to see more, you should definitely check the wall of screenshots on our Discord! <br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/dedee6d1073f6bf364bfbceb55b4862f8322365f.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/114535732445bbf52b3eb20b419716d9059a2b9e.jpg"/></div></div><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1f4071e296ec74e487dc8c298c927f7812d21f36.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/09beb4a8dab61169c4a755a187f26de9223c1438.jpg"/></div></div></div>Props to adomic. , husky_jb, sisokalis and marcel_nemet for the shots!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">That’s it for this month!</div>Don’t hesitate to provide feedback on the upcoming content in the comments below, and in the ideas section of Focus Together.<br/>We’ll see you next month for another Community Update.<br/><br/><i>With love &amp; respect,<br/>From Saber and Focus.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects! 🙏</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.1 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497188710547194704</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/5cc792a3f0c79370a2d0787ae9f9a9550cc6cd7d.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>The time has come for us to talk more about what’s coming to Total War: WARHAMMER III in Patch 6.1, and today we have one of our talented Designers here to shed some light on the changes and additions you can expect to see when it arrives in mid March.<br/><br/>Before we hand over the mic, we’d like to say a huge thank you to everyone who has opted in to our Campaign AI Beta on Steam over the past few weeks. We’ve had some great feedback that we’re already hard at work parsing through, and will be closing this current round of Beta testing this Friday 28th February at 11:00 GMT. The Beta feedback survey will remain open until Sunday 2nd March at 21:00 GMT, so if you haven’t already, please do take a few minutes to share your thoughts with us and have your voice heard to help shape the future of Campaign AI. We’ll be in touch in the near future with an update on our next steps, and hopefully set a date for the next Beta round.<br/><br/>With that said, it’s time to hand over to Will to talk more about what’s coming with 6.1 in mid March.<br/><br/>Enjoy!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 PATCH 6.1 DEV BLOG 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
