<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites - Dev Blog: The Voices of the Lex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254834881</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hey Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With the introduction of Arbitrators to the Mourningstar and to celebrate the upcoming release of our new DLC we’re going to talk a bit about the voice work. Matthew Ward, Michael Knight and David Wahlund tell us what it’s like working with Darktide’s cast and the process we go through to get the performances just right.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What does the audition procedure look like?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Matthew Ward: </i>The casting process for Darktide never really stops. We’re always adding new characters to the game, which means that we’re always in contact with new talent, either for specific roles or with an ear to getting them involved at some point in the future when something suitable arises. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">As to how we find our actors, it’s always a mix. Some are from blind casting processes where our studio partners source self-taped auditions in line with a casting brief that we provide. Others we approach based on their past work in one medium or another, and more via recommendations from the recording studios or existing cast members. It’s a broad spectrum approach that over the years has given us a great mix of industry veterans, rising stars and the odd member of video game royalty.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In almost every case, the casting process ends with a directed live audition session at one of our studios, where we hone the actor’s interpretation of the character and hopefully hit that sweet spot of what works for them and matches what we’re looking for.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Of course, sometimes we hear something we didn’t <i>know </i>that we were looking for, and that’s really where the magic happens.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Michael Knight</i>: I’m constantly blown away by the talent we manage to draw to our game. I think it speaks to the effort that’s always been put into the voices we feature in the Tide games.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are there many Warhammer: 40,000 fans among the contenders?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It’s not something that we stipulate, but it’s always a bonus when it comes together that way, as the accompanying knowledge and enthusiasm always shows. Greg Jones and Alex Jordan are some examples from our longstanding cast, Michael Geary from our more recent intake. And of course, we have several actors who are familiar with the Warhammer: 40,000 setting from their work on other projects.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK:</i> We also often find people who’ve never interacted with the IP being fascinated by its depth (and darkness!)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How specific are the VO directions? I've seen footage of actors holding prop guns and running on the spot to get the right dynamic and exertion sound for the lines. Is there any more like that?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>Some of our actors - and they know who they are - would probably refuse to record if they didn’t have their stand-in weaponry to tote around. I’m almost entirely sure that’s healthy, and I’ll always say that if there’s any chance that they might be listening. Or armed.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">But seriously, everyone’s method is different. We record almost exclusively with head-mounted microphones, which allow the talent to roam - or literally throw themselves - around the recording booth if they want. Others get the motion and inflection we’re looking for while standing still or perched on a chair. Whatever gets the results, gets the results.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the weirdest direction that has been given to a VA for this game?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>I don’t know about “weirdest”, but something that always gets good results is directing the actor to shout at the recording engineer. It’s nothing personal (at least I hope not) but that always gets a great result. As far as I know we haven’t yet traumatised an engineer. In fact, most of them tend to end up grinning. People are strange.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>David Wahlund: </i>A maybe unknown and odd part of voice work is the exertions, efforts or grunts. It's the vocals that are not verbalized. In an action game we have a lot of these. When you swing the sword or get hit by a bullet for example. We have 15 different categories. Some efforts or grunts can be used in several different situations. For example a jump grunt can be used when you get pushed etc. These are all quite private sounds. Sometimes, especially when time is short, you might need to give an example yourself. That’s certainly weird the first time you do it. But by doing it yourself you might also take the edge out of the weirdness in the situation for the actor.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How does the performance process for the monstrosities work? How do you decide, or communicate to the actor "that's what we want this thing to sound like"?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>DW: </i>As Matt mentioned earlier, the actor's interpretation is super important. We need to give them as much details and context as possible so that they can be creative<b>. </b>When it comes to creatures or monster-like humans, animations and graphics play a big part. So if you can give as much visual information as possible that will certainly help. What does the mouth look like? How does the creature move? All details matter.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>What's the average length of a recording session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW:</i> Because we ask for a lot of shouting from our actors - “Darktide Conversational Level” has become a bit of a running joke because it’s really not that conversational - most sessions run for an hour, although some of our hardier actors are happy to record for longer sessions. It’s a style of performance that’s very demanding on not only the voice but the whole body.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How many lines on average are recorded in a session?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>We plan for around a hundred lines a session. Often that goes higher - when the actor’s in the zone - and sometimes it goes lower, especially when it gets <i>very </i>shouty. It’s always a balance between speed, quality and the actor’s comfort, with the latter being the absolutely most important of the three.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>We’re always adding new voice lines. How often does Fatshark have recording sessions?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>It varies depending on what we want to capture. The Arbitrator sessions have been pretty full on (roughly 150 recording hours since the start of the year), but for other updates where we only need to add more NPC lines, it might just take a couple of hours. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">We might not invite an actor back into the booth for months (or even years), or sometimes they’ll be in for a couple of hours for several weeks (or months) in a row. It’s all about matching our needs to their availability. Most are very busy individuals, so we try to get our asks in early.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading our dev blog on what goes into the performances and the work behind your new Arbites Class, releasing on <b>June 23, 2025 </b>on all platforms. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll do our best to answer them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today on Steam.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbites Gameplay Reveal &amp; Deluxe Edition Announcement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254833683</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">During today’s PC Gaming Show, we gave you a first gameplay glimpse at the Adeptus Arbites and announced the Deluxe Edition. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Check out the gameplay trailer below to see the Arbites unleashing their loyal Cyber-Mastiffs upon lexbreakers, and delivering judgment with extreme prejudice.</p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" ay5tdet0j2c?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We’re not done yet.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">In the lead-up to launch, we’ll be releasing more reveals. We’ll also be sharing more over the coming days, including a longer gameplay video on June 12. Additional dev blogs on the Arbites' talent tree, weapons, and more, will be published in the weeks prior to release. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>On June 23, you’ll be able to purchase the Arbites Class in two different editions:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Standard Edition: $11.99 / €11.99</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Deluxe Edition: $18.99 / €18.99</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Cosmetic Upgrade (Upgrade to Deluxe): $7.99 / €7.99</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>The Deluxe Edition includes the class and cosmetics for your Arbitrator and Cyber-Mastiff:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Arbites Class</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Unique Class Outfit</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Unique Companion Outfit</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">1 Portrait Frame</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">4 Weapon Skins</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/391adc4a4acb50ff80eeccd7e63e5a69c746b72b.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thanks for sticking with us through this reveal, we’re beyond excited for you to take control of the Arbites on June 23, 2025! Make sure to wishlist the Arbites Class now so you're ready to restore order on Tertium Day 1.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.16.1 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/511834275001141169</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The team is currently hard at work. We'll have news about new content soon.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Changes since 1.15.1</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">New</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added barks for the Onslaught Pack units.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved Squighog Boyz movement sound effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved Fade Away sound effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Adjusted Transonic Blade visual effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Adjusted Baleblast visual effect.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Rubric Marines no longer bleed or scream, they are bloodless shells animated by sorcery.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Tweaked Transonic description.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Updated translations.</p></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue with saving games and associated crash that could occur with simultaneous turns off.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Squighog Boy flavor mentioning four-legged Squigs.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Canoptek Reanimator movement sound not playing.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Canoptek Reanimator only having one Atomiser Beam.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Ruins of Vaul not rewarding some units and items.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Vaul's Wrath Support Battery not being Very Bulky.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed network read and write speeds displaying incorrect numbers.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Potentially fixed an attack arrow rebuild crash.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed some typos.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/489630/" width="850"></iframe>
"][/dynamiclink]</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Arbitrators - BTS Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520841474254833699</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To celebrate the upcoming release of our new DLC and the introduction of Arbitrators to the Mourningstar, we’re going to delve into the lore behind them. As always, we want to give you an overview, but we’ll be leaving some things unsaid for you to discover for yourself.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">To the people of the Imperium, the officers of the Adeptus Arbites are instruments of repression. Visible and feared enforcers of Imperial tyranny, the Arbitrators uphold the Emperor’s justice, but the laws they ruthlessly enforce have nothing to do with protecting the innocent or the weak. The Lex Imperialis exists to ensure the perpetuation of the despotic Imperial machine, for the alternative is anarchy and the extinction of Mankind.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">By contrast, the primary duty of the Adeptus Arbites is to make sure that the Imperial tithe is paid in full and on time. Their squads of armoured officers put down industrial riots that would endanger a world’s production quotas, close down traffickers bleeding useful workers away from their rightful position and break up illicit trading cartels that imperil sub-sector economies or, worse, treat with xenos. Planetary governors who evade their tithe payments can also find themselves under the Arbitrators’ eyes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The men and women who dispense justice as Arbitrators are grim and uncompromising individuals. Arbitrators must be harsh in the execution of their duty; mercy is a weakness unbecoming of an officer of the Lex Imperialis.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>To find out more about the role the Arbitrators are going to play in the war for Atoma, we spoke to Michael Knight and Matthew Ward.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Are the Arbitrators going to be Rejects? Do they start aboard the Tancred Bastion?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Michael Knight: </i>The Arbitrators are definitely <i>not </i>Rejects. They’ve always had a presence on Atoma, working to enforce order and ensure that the Imperial Tithe was met. In fact, the Tancred Bastion was actually an Adeptus Arbites prison ship. Not only do they hold Grendyl responsible for the mass breakout that followed Wolfer’s escape, they’re really not happy that Zola has put convicts to work as a private army.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Matthew Ward: </i>In fact, they’d dearly like to be in charge of the warzone.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK: </i>Totally. The problem they have is that an Inquisitor’s relationship to the Lex Imperialis (the law that governs the Imperium) is… let’s say it’s “complicated”. As an Arbites player, you’ll arrive on the Mourningstar some time after the events of the Reject prologue, ready to join the fight.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How are the Arbitrators introduced to the Narrative?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>As Mike’s already hinted at, they were always active on Atoma - we just haven’t crossed paths with them yet. Up until now, Marshal Vortern has stood by and let Grendyl’s Warband handle the invasion, but now he’s decided that the Arbitrators will be taking a more active role.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>How many different Personalities can Arbitrator players choose from?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>As with the other (non-Ogryn) classes there are three distinct Personalities to choose from, with a male and female version of each. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Authoritarian, performed by Devora Wilde and Mark Takeshi Ota, is very much a by-the-book Arbitrator, unflinching in their duty to the Lex Imperialis. By contrast, the Fatalist, played by Lara Sawalha and Michael Geary, is much more aware of the price that law-keeping exacts. Last of all is the Maul, brought to life by Alix Wilton Regan and David Boyle. They’re a lot more…</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK: </i>Antisocial.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>Yes, that’s a good way to put it.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Is there going to be an Arbitrator NPC aboard the Mourningstar?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MK: </i>There is indeed. Proctor-Exactant Zorin serves as Marshal Vortern’s representative aboard ship, directing the efforts of the Arbitrators under his command. He might not have a huge impact right away, but he’s a constant reminder to all that the Emperor’s judgement is now present aboard the Mourningstar. We may even see him running missions and more in the future. Rannick and his team are already resentful of how Commissar Dukane has inserted herself into the War for Atoma. The last thing they need is another source of interference. But the Lex is the Lex. There’s only so much they can do, especially as Grendyl’s still refusing to show his face.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Do you think they’ll learn to work together?</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>MW: </i>We’ll have to see. What’s the worst that can happen?</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thank you for reading our dev blog on some of the lore and narrative behind your new Arbites Class, releasing on <b>June 23, 2025 </b>on all platforms. We’ll be looking out for any questions over the weekend and we’ll do our best to answer them.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This is the Will of the Lex.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Arbites Class today.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">[dynamiclink href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3710910/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Arbites_Class/"][/dynamiclink]</p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Public Test Server opens once again!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500574650502221838</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hi Space Marines! ⭐ </div><br/>The Public Test Server opens once more today! Check out this quick FAQ to help you get started and ready before launch.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s a Public Test Server?</div><br/>Space Marine 2’s Public Test Server works as a separate version of the game featuring WIP content and features. Share your feedback to help us refine the patch before its official release. Your input provides an important perspective that will be reviewed by the developer team and have an impact on further game updates.<br/><br/><b>Since this is a test environment, expect the unfinished content and possible bugs. As you will access it through a different game version, your progression will not be tracked.</b> For each PTS update, you will land on the game with levels maxed out and all weapons unlocked.<br/><br/>Please note that the DLCs won’t be available, regardless of whether you own them.<br/>‎ <br/>Since the PTS is "Public", you are free to create content based on it. No NDA will be included.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Which platforms can access the PTS?</div><br/>The PTS is only available on PC via Steam. It is not accessible on consoles (PlayStation/Xbox) or through the Epic Games Store.<br/><br/>Now, let’s see how to install it 👇<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">📝 <u>Tutorial on how to access PTS via Steam:</u></div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Just follow these simple steps:</div><ol><li> Open the Steam client.<br/></li><li> Log in with the account that owns Space Marine 2.<br/></li><li> Go to your Steam Library.<br/></li><li> Look for “<b>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 - Public Test Server</b>” under your Space Marine 2 entry.<br/></li><li> (Optional) Right-click on your Library entry and go to Properties. In the “General” tab, set the game’s default Language to “English”. <i>Translations may still be work-in-progress when you try the new content out on the PTS. <b>As a result, we recommend setting the game to English</b>.</i><br/></li><li> Once you’ve clicked on this entry, install the Public Test Server content. This install instance is not related to the base game, your files will remain in separate directories and all future updates will also be distinct, meaning that your current progression will not be affected by the time you spend on the PTS.</li></ol><b>When the install is complete, the Public Test Server is ready to launch!</b><br/><br/>Click “Play” like you would with any other game!<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Can I try every single feature that will be implemented with the next Patch?</div>Most upcoming content will be available to you. However, we won’t share content that is too buggy or hasn’t undergone the necessary approvals on our side at the time of the PTS release. Also, some content might be present on the PTS, but not accessible to the players. For instance, you may see new Champions in the Armouring Hall but won’t be able to try them unless you own the Season Pass.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How long will the PTS be active?</div><br/>The PTS will run until Patch 8.0 officially launches.<br/><br/>After that, it will go dormant until the next major PTS update.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Will my progress be saved?</div><br/>No, because the PTS runs as a completely separate game version. It does not carry over your previous progress in the game; instead, it provides all players with a default maxed-out level and weapons. This ensures that you won’t have to spend time to unlock all the features, especially the Prestige Ranks.<br/><br/>It will also not save your progress nor transfer it to the official game version afterwards.<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Is multiplayer available on the PTS?</div><br/>Yes, even private PvP lobbies will work so you can invite your Brothers and Sisters to play!<br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Do mods work with the PTS?</div><br/>Mods won't work with the PTS. <b>Enabling them will cause the PTS to crash at launch. Please, make sure to disable them beforehand.</b><br/>‎ <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How can I give feedback?</div><br/>We need your feedback!<br/><br/>As mentioned in previous Community Updates, the primary purpose of the Public Test Server is to gather your feedback on new content, changes, and balancing tweaks we plan to implement in the game.<br/><br/><b>Our main focus will be on PvE Siege Mode and Absolute Difficulty balancing.</b><br/><br/>We’ve set up dedicated forum threads on Focus Together to let you voice your opinion, which you can find here.<br/><br/>Thank you for helping us make Space Marine 2 the best it can be!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
