<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805557883738</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>We’re proud to inform all of you that we’re participating in <b>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</b> which has already begun! Be sure not to miss this entertaining event, as well as pleasant discounts on our titles - <b>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</b> and <b>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous</b>!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c5109ca10883ecfe4e76748b32c1258dc786545c.jpg"/><br/>There’s no time to waste, explore the event right now. Note that the Fest will be held till October 7th!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>The grim and dark universe of Warhammer has never been so close. Don’t miss your chance to grab the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game with <b>40% off</b>! It’s time to guide your people through the challenges of the Koronus Expanse!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Get the Season Pass and try the just-released first DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader – Void Shadows! Explore the sinister secrets of your voidship with a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Get Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock unique in-game items, digital add-ons, and the legendary voidship model!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>A journey full of danger, new friends, and foes lies ahead! Feel the true RPG experience and embark on a mission to save the world from a great peril in Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous with a <b>70% discount</b>. Choose your path in the story and explore where it leads you!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Unlock the ultimate experience of three DLCs full of new content by getting Season Pass 1 at a <b>70% discount</b>. Make your Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous unforgettable.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>The more DLCs, the merrier! Another three DLCs can be obtained as a part of the Season Pass 2 with <b>50% off</b>! Continue your journey as the Knight Commander, meet new companions, and explore new archetypes!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Please note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grim Darkness Challenge comes!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805558231855</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>To celebrate the launch of the Void Shadows DLC and the introduction of Grim Darkness (“Ironman”) Mode for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, Owlcat Games is happy to announce a large competitive event: <b>The Grim Darkness Challenge!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What is The Grim Darkness Challenge?</div><br/>It is an intense competitive event for streamers, where, over the course of two weeks, participants will compete live in beating (or making it as far as they can in!) Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader on <b>Daring difficulty in Grim Darkness mode</b> - a newly introduced brutal gameplay mode where only a single save is allowed and is rewritten every time a player exits the game. All decisions and consequences in this mode are final, reloading is impossible, and if the party is defeated—the game is over!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Registration</div><br/>In order to participate, you need to either be a streamer that is already a part of our partnership program Owlmates, or have a channel on Youtube or Twitch with at least 5000 subscribers and a reasonable number of views on recent videos. We’re ready to discuss corner cases (for example, some leeway may be given to non-English-speaking streamers with national audiences), but also reserve the right to deny registration without explanation if we consider it necessary.<br/><br/>For registration and all questions, contact Owlcat CM Starrok (Starrok on Discord or u/OwlcatStarrok on Reddit), or Owlcat CM Nathillien (Nathillien on Discord or u/OwlcatNathillien on Reddit).<br/><br/>Registration will remain open until October 14.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Victory conditions</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Winner is determined by beating the game or reaching the furthest Act without the player’s party ever being defeated.<br/></li><li> If multiple players have reached the same act or have beaten the game, tiebreakers are resolved by the number of quests completed (you can check completed quests in the journal).<br/></li><li> If still tied, the victory is determined in favor of the player who spent the least in-game time on their playthrough. </li></ul><br/>The challenge will begin on <b>00:00 GMT October 22</b>, and last for 2 weeks until <b>23:59 GMT November 4</b>, or until all players have successfully completed their playthroughs or were eliminated. <br/><br/>And remember: in the Grim Darkness of the far future, there is only one winner, and their feat will be rewarded with a unique prize!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">In-game Rules</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Grim Darkness mode must be enabled;<br/></li><li> Daring Difficulty must be enabled;<br/></li><li> Void Shadows DLC must be installed and enabled;<br/></li><li> All free and cosmetic DLCs can be enabled;<br/></li><li> Any background or character-selection choices are allowed;<br/></li><li> Any ship type is allowed;<br/></li><li> Only single player is allowed;<br/></li><li> No mercenaries are allowed (only story companions);<br/></li><li> No mods can be used;<br/></li><li> It is prohibited to shutdown or alter the game in any way in order to prevent a death, make a different choice, or redo a skillcheck. Live with the consequences of your choices!</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Technical Requirements</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After each game session, the participant must upload the following stats to the provided Discord channel:<br/>- Time played this session;<br/>- Total time played in campaign;<br/>- Current Act # reached<br/>- Number of completed quests (visible in the quest log)<br/>- Party setup that was used most of the time for this session (companions and archetypes). Builds don't need to be uploaded, but must be available on request.<br/><br/></li><li> Playthroughs must happen strictly LIVE, with the streams and their records saved in case a need arises to check them. If you have connection issues, please save the game and continue when your connection is restored.<br/><br/></li><li> All participants must manually make a backup of their save after every session (by default it is located in C:\Users\ <username> \AppData\LocalLow\Owlcat Games\Warhammer 40000 Rogue Trader) to prevent unexpected progress loss due to power outages, Steam Cloud issues, bugs, and other force majeure factors.<br/><br/></username></li><li> If continuing or finishing the playthrough is impossible due to a non-gameplay related reason (a bug, power failure, hardware or software issues, etc.), contact the organizers. We may be able to let you continue from a previous backed-up save or restart the game, depending on the circumstances.<br/><br/></li><li> We strongly urge all participants to use the #GrimDarknessChallenge hashtag in their media.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Cheating and Exploits</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It is forbidden to exploit bugs and a clearly unintended use of game mechanics to gain a gameplay advantage. If you are in doubt as to whether the situation can be classified as such, contact the organizers.<br/></li><li> No mods or external software may be used to modify the game or save or to alter them in any way.</li></ul><br/>Participants who break any of the rules above may be disqualified at the organizers' discretion.<br/><br/>Good luck!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.2.1.10 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805546851000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! We are deploying a hotfix to deal with a few annoying issues discovered by the community over the days since release of the Void Shadows DLC.<br/><br/>Consoles will receive the same update within 24 hours.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Some space battles could become stuck after defeating all enemies - fixed;<br/></li><li> Abilities in space combat could become unavailable after the first use - fixed;<br/></li><li> In rare cases, UI in space combat could disappear - fixed;<br/></li><li> The main enemy of the battle in Astropathic Chapel refused to die if the difficulty was set to Custom and NPC stat modifiers were set below a certain threshold - fixed;<br/></li><li> Since the last update, the player could experience severe lag when using some abilities such as burst attacks - fixed;<br/></li><li> The main menu button “Continue” used to ignore the existence of Grim Darkness saves, forcing the player to load game manually through the Load Game menu - fixed, now continuing the game is possible as normal;<br/></li><li> Making four incorrect choices in <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>The Haunting of Zacchary Weisz</span></span> quest no longer causes all party members to instantly die (which caused a Grim Darkness game over), only inflicting damage and trauma instead;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.6</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4656249009455105640</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/2333528b1825f6b2be97bd29739697751fcebb32.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/> <br/>We're releasing another hotfix today to address a couple of emergent issues:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved a potential crash that could occur at the end of a turn after updating to 5.2.5.<br/></li><li> Removed references to older, unreleased content from our game files.</li></ul><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><b>DEV NOTE:</b><br/><br/>The act of removing these references in today's Hotfix will also require us to revise our active cache of rollback builds, which will temporarily remove the option to roll back to an earlier release. With this release, the available rollback builds will be set to 0, and today’s build will go on to serve as the oldest rollback version as we release new updates to the game over the coming months.<br/><br/>We apologise to all our players who currently make regular use of our rollback releases, we know how beneficial this feature has become for many of you, and the responsibility for that falls entirely on us.<br/><br/>As mentioned during the launch of version 5.2, we aim to maintain one rollback build for each category: update, patch, hotfix, and release, for a total of 4 rollback builds. This supports players running heavily modified campaigns, helping to minimize delays while their mods are updated. Each subsequent build following today’s 5.2.6 Hotfix will remain available as a rollback option until we have one build in each category - 4 in total - at which point the oldest will be replaced by a newer one.</blockquote> <br/>As always, thank you all for your feedback and bug reports. If you experience any new bugs or issues after updating to 5.2.6 please be sure to report them over in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #48 (1.5.1) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209644504997</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6c662319b9afaf3bdc458118e8ce0d010c8854ea.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Our latest hotfix #48 (1.5.1) is out now on Steam and it will shortly launch on our other platforms. <br/><br/><b>Miscellaneous Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash occurring when enabling FSR 3.1 frame generation without upscaling.</li><li>Fixed a crash occurring when applying the ‘Pierce’ Blessing to the Ogryn Kickback and Rumbler.</li><li>Fixed a crash occurring when using a controller during discard and ending up having no pre-selected weapon when going back on the screen.</li><li>The max potential stats preview will now display correctly on all weapons.</li><li>The help functionality in the Blessings screen of the Mastery menu will no longer keep the screen dim once it gets removed from the screen.</li><li>Fixed a series of typos where Strength was incorrectly showing as Power in Blessing descriptions.</li><li>Fixed a typo in the description of the “Showstopper” Blessing.</li></ul><b>Party Finder Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash that could happen while in the Party Finder menu when failing to retrieve details from joining players.</li><li>Removed hidden keyboard keybindings for starting and canceling party advertisements.</li><li>Players will now automatically get back to the Mourningstar after joining a new party while having the menu open.</li><li>Crash fix that could occur in the Party Finder menu when multiple people request to join your party.</li><li>Fixed an issue where parts of the UI in the Party Finder could fail to be correctly updated when new players joined the Strike Team.</li><li>Removed access to the Party Finder while playing the Prologue with a new character.</li></ul><b>Cosmetic Fixes</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the arms of the Veteran “Militarum Tox-Field Trench Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic would look differently sized at certain angles</li><li>Fixed an issue on the Veteran “Militarum Tox-Field Trench Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic where the sleeping bag would deform on certain body types</li><li>Removed a small black patch from the collar of the Zealot “Militarum Tox-Field Chaplain’s Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upper body cosmetic</li><li>Fixed an issue where the cylinder on the back of the Zealot “Field-Repaired Acheron-Pattern Rebreather” headgear cosmetic would occasionally deform</li><li>Fixed an issue where the gloves on the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic would occasionally deform</li><li>Fixed an issue where a leather belt on the back of the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic clips with the jacket</li><li>Fixed an issue where the following cosmetic headgears was clipping with certain high-collared upper bodies<ul class="bb_ul"><li>Veteran “Steel Legion Flak Helmet (Parade Polish)”</li><li>Zealot “Votarist’s Pot Helm with Rebreather”</li><li>Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)”</li></ul></li><li>Fixed some clipping issues with the Ogryn “Mk IVc Pot Helm with Gas Mask (XXXXL)” headgear cosmetic</li><li>Fixed some issues with lack of movement on parts of the cosmetic backpacks “Reliquary Array” and “Artillery Carriage Spare”</li><li>Multiple fixes to the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic</li></ul><b>Known Issues</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li><b>Mastery Level Value is Missing in The Marks Swap Screen</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>When in the Marks swap screen, the Mastery level value required to obtain locked Marks may fail to be correctly displayed.</li><li>The issue is only visual, and the locked Marks will be correctly available upon reaching the required Mastery level in the weapon family.</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Information in the Sacrifice Weapon Screen Tooltip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The tooltip in Sacrifice Weapon screen incorrectly states that only Anointed (blue) rarity weapons (or higher) are able to be sacrificed.</li><li>The issue is only in the tooltip text, as the minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li><i>(Previous:This is only a visual rounding issue, as the actual stats total will always effectively be 380 for every weapon.)</i></li><li><b>Update:</b>This is now known to not be a visual issue only. Rather, it involves different values being delivered by the backend that expected. This is being investigated.</li></ul></li><li><b>Auspex Tooltip in Rolling Steel Localization Issue</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The “Move” text in the HUD tooltip when using an Auspex for the new hacking minigame in the Rolling Steel will appear localised in English but is missing in other languages.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances: Stand By For Action and Rapid Response</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>These penances were accidentally included in this release and was not supposed to be included, we will remove them in 1.5.2.</li></ul></li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Flash used to be the working name for Operations and this two penances are two old test penances that flew under the radar, we’re sorry for any confusion stemming from this.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3"><i>Edit: Known Issues Updated September 27, 2024</i></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Zealots are Unable to Purchase Recon Lasguns in Brunt's</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Exactly as the title says, Zealots aren't able to purchase Recon Lasguns.</li></ul></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Please see the update to the Stat Rounding Issue (done above).</b></li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
