<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Community Survey: Major Update 1.5 and Lex Imperialis DLC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/496088177467983099</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Lord Captains!</b><br/><br/>Some time ago we've launched the major update 1.5, and enough time has now passed for you to form an opinion. We’d really love to hear what you think!<br/><br/>What worked well for you? What didn’t land as expected? Your perspective helps us refine the experience and steer the future of the Koronus Expanse.<br/><br/>We invite you to take part in a big community survey about both the Update 1.5 and the Lex Imperialis DLC.<br/><br/>Your feedback is invaluable — and greatly appreciated:<br/><br/>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/6TF3WX3</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/f86bd05492f0eafbbd5c266483884845f343f8d5.jpg"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Darktide is Free to Play This Weekend!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/618810005643069677</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f590459b4b20a9cb9425fd1cac5559a46ba83879.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With humanity pushed to the edge and the hive on the brink of collapse, the Imperium is forced to enlist whoever it can - misfits, rejects and outright criminals. That means you! In Warhammer: 40,000 Darktide you and your strike team battle through a relentless, fast paced co-op experience set in the iconic grimdark future of Warhammer 40,000.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850" xz0g-lybujo?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"'></iframe>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Darktide recently celebrated its third anniversary since launch, and there’s never been a better time to join the fight for humanity. Earlier this week Fatshark released a fully loaded content drop, introducing a <b>new map</b>, <b>new live event</b>, and the debut of outrageous <b>Hive Scum Class</b> ...and so much more! This major content drop is designed to welcome returning veterans and give new players the perfect entry point to the meat grinder.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1361210/" width="850"></iframe>
</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Game Live Event: The Day of Atonement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/508473076443251106</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe ajkmh57uais?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Warband!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Day of Atonement in-game event is now live! <b>Starting today until December 22</b>, test your might in favor of your patron to prove your fervor and repent for your sins!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">In-Game Live Event: The Day of Atonement</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The stolen rations were tainted and now the hab blocks teem with infected. Atone for your deeds at the altars of Saint Messelina Gloriana. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <i>"Disturbing news has reached us from the poorer hab zones in Tertium. The recovered rations that were recently distributed to the unfortunate souls who reside in these districts appear to have been tainted. A great sickness has spread through these areas.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>My masters in the Ecclesiarchy have called for a Day of Atonement. You must beg our dear Saint Messelina Gloriana for her forgiveness and protection for our beloved Tertium.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Pray at her Blessed Altars and scour the hive for any Holy Relics you can find. Only through devotion can we hope to save our city.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>- Sister Hestia Prine"</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>To make progress in the event, you need to play missions with the Atonement condition, interact with the shrines presented in the missions and defeat the enemies which show up after activation. Along the way you can also gather holy relics for additional event progress. </b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The rewards will be <b>Ordo dockets, Plasteel, Diamantine and a cosmetic insignia.</b> As a special celebration reward, those who complete the last tier of this anniversary event will receive <b>500 Aquilas</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/72e11bca6a81b42bc43725503870dfdd28d51786.png"/> </p><p class="bb_paragraph"> <b>Pray at the Blessed Shrines and search for holy relics to unlock the following rewards:</b></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>200:</b> 50,000 Ordo Dockets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>600:</b> 3,000 Plasteel</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>1000:</b> 4,000 Diamantine</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>1600:</b> 3,000 Plasteel</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>2500:</b> 100,000 Ordo Dockets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>3600:</b> New Insignia</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>4500:</b> 500 Aquilas</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e700de79b8874e18ab7140f6074ba98f94e5b7ee.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 7.0 and Tides of Torment OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510724876254839100</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The day has come for Aislinn, Dechala, and Sayl to join the ranks of Total War: WARHAMMER III alongside patch 7.0 🌊🐍🔮<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O1T9f92zbgc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Don't forget to check out full patch notes 7.0!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 PATCH NOTES 7.0 👈</div><br/><br/>Not only that, Immortal Empires is now unlocked for owners of Total War: WARHAMMER I and WARHAMMER II 🔥<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 READ MORE HERE👈</div><br/><br/>Get your Tides of Torment copy here: <br/> https://store.steampowered.com/app/3450970/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Sayl__Tides_of_Torment/ <br/> https://store.steampowered.com/app/3450980/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Dechala__Tides_of_Torment/ <br/> https://store.steampowered.com/app/3450960/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Aislinn__Tides_of_Torment/ <br/> https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/59473/Total_War_WARHAMMER_III__Tides_of_Torment/<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><p class="bb_paragraph">Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Lords of the End Times - Announce Trailer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510724876254839632</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Nagash, the great necromancer himself. Long whispered about in the darkest corners of the lore, he returns with one goal: to drown the world in undeath.<br/><br/>Lords of the End Times — the next DLC for Total War: WARHAMMER III — is coming Summer 2026.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jPIpN9OKKR4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
