<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction Wallpaper giveaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511753</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b3f62518ae322610fa97becbe818213c8a887181.png"/><br/><br/>Spruce up your desktop in time for Omens of Destruction with our latest wallpaper drop! 🖥️🎨<br/><br/>Head to the Rewards section of the CA Community to download now! 👇<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CA Community Rewards</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Hotfix ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/601890524829320367</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>OI, SPEEK FREEKS!</b><br/><br/>We're just dropped a hotfix for various things below, including some stuff for Alternate Weapons which will be playable again this weekend. Be sure to jump in for some new kinds of krumpin'!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issue with player progression needing a client restart to be shown properly in the menu<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with Steam Deck / Linux players no longer being able to play because of Easy Anti-Cheat being a right git.  If you still get kicked to the menu and see an error pop up, just matchmake again and things should work fine after that.<br/></li><li> Reverted change to status bar text on HUD using red outline which apparently made some players' eyes bleed<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with Kustom Boosta-Blasta and Megatrakk Scrapjet getting speed loss<br/></li><li> Fixed bots using alt weapons that weren't synced properly.<br/></li><li> Fixed performance issue with the kill kam where it was tanking framerate when loading<br/></li><li> Fixed/updated game mode text for Deff Rally to reflect racing changes made in last patch<br/></li><li> Reduced size of central game mode HUD element to reduce clutter.  More room ta see da krumpin'!<br/></li><li> Updated Looted Wagon crosshair so it reflects cooldown of the Kannon.  This is a test to see how players like it (you will).  If they do, we'll apply the same system to other vehicles<br/></li><li> Grot bomm now has a big flare on it so it's easier to see coming and increased sound distance. Reduced it's max duration from 13 sec to 10, which also fixed a bug with VFX disappearing<br/></li><li> Kustom Boosta-Blasta alternate weapon fire rate set to 0.6 (from 1.2), damage set to 33 (from 22), splash radius set to 12 (from 10).  This weapon will be playable this coming weekend!<br/></li><li> Updated popup message text when getting kicked to the menu because of Easy Anti-Cheat issues<br/></li><li> Made the Grot Mega Tank rokkit knockback consistently pop enemies up instead of randomly spin them out<br/></li><li> Returns Shokkjump Dragsta lock on crosshair</li></ul>If you haven't already, check out our survey and help shape the future of the game!<br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/dffc9865e78ec717e30a35320c40c6a47c727808.png"/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Click for Feedback Survey</b></div><br/>Keep the feedback comin' and letz get back to Krumpin!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Turkish language comes to Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/786538109548364899</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<b>Lord Kaptanlar!</b><br/> <br/>Gününüzü heyecan verici bir haberle şenlendirmek isteriz: Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader, Türkçe oluyor! Türk oyuncularımız, bugünden itibaren ana dillerinde metin ve alt yazılarla oyuna dalabilecekler.<br/> <br/>Menü, alt yazı ve oyun içi metinlerle beraber tam bir Türkçe dil desteği sunmaktan gurur duyuyoruz. Bu yerelleştirme seçenekleri oyuna pürüzsüzce entegre edilmiştir. Desteklenen diller arasında geçiş yapmak için ayarlar menüsüne girmeniz yeterlidir. Bu güncellemenin Türkçe konuşan oyuncularımıza Warhammer 40.000: Rogue Trader'ı daha erişilebilir kılacağını ve muhteşem bir oyun deneyimi sunacağını umuyoruz.<br/> <br/>Türkçe yerelleştirmenin şimdilik sadece ana oyun için mevcut olduğunu lütfen unutmayın. Void Shadow DLC metin çevirileri eksiktir ve bu metinler şu an İngilizcedir. DLC yerelleştirmesi sonraki bir güncelleme ile eklenecektir.<br/> <br/>Daimî desteklerinden dolayı topluluğumuza teşekkür etmek istiyoruz ve bu haberi Türkçe konuşan oyuncularımıza sunmaktan büyük heyecan duyuyoruz. Koronus Enginliği'ni ana dilinizle ilk kez keşfe çıkmaya hazır olun!<br/> <br/>Mürettebatınızı hazır edin Lord Kaptan! Macera sizi bekliyor.<br/><br/>__________<br/><br/><b>Lord Captains!</b><br/><br/>We would like to brighten your day with some exciting news: the Turkish language is coming to Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader! Starting today, our Turkish players will be able to immerse themselves in the game with text and subtitles in their native language.<br/><br/>We are proud to introduce full Turkish language support, including menus, subtitles, and in-game texts. These localization options are seamlessly integrated into the game; to switch between supported languages, simply go to the settings menu. We hope that this update will make Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader more accessible and provide our Turkish-speaking players with an outstanding gaming experience.<br/><br/>Please note that for now, the Turkish localization is available only for the base game. The Void Shadow DLC texts are missing translations and are currently written in English. The DLC localization will be added later.<br/><br/>We'd like to thank our community for their ongoing support, and we're excited to bring this news to our Turkish-speaking players. Prepare to explore the Koronus Expanse in your native tongue like never before!<br/><br/>Ready your crew, Lord Captain! The journey awaits.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 13:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.0.57 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/786538109548364959</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/>Our tech-priests prepared another small update to apply a few fixes to your voidship.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hunter's Withdraw talent no longer provides infinite dodges against all types of attacks;<br/></li><li> The game could freeze while travelling on the global map - fixed;<br/></li><li> On the first part of the Critical Task quest and the activation point for the fuel lever did not appear - fixed;<br/></li><li>The Warp effect could trigger even if the party was not in battle - fixed;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Update - New playable monster: Rat Ogre! Patch 6.2.0</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/509566731895702858</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div>This update brings a new dangerous toy for the Pactsworn side in Versus: A new playable monster, the Rat Ogre!<br/><br/><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5d00ba0c96365b000104ac5f/2dc0740c-942f-4cda-bbc0-b6b44aa8e773/Rat_Ogre_169.png?format=1000w"/><br/>When the time comes for a Monster to spawn in a Versus match, Pactsworn players can choose between the Bile Troll and the Rat Ogre. While both are monsters, their way of assaulting the Hero team is very different, and so it is up to the players to choose the right tool for the job (or just the most fun!)<br/><br/>The Rat Ogre’s specialty is scrambling the Hero team through a frenzied assault. It excels at separating the Heroes and taking advantage of the chaos to chase after stragglers, pummeling away with wild, ferocious attacks that don’t give the defender room to breathe.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How to play the Rat Ogre</div>Similar to the Bile Troll and the Heroes, you’ve got light attacks and heavy attacks. Tapping your attack button (Default Keybind: Left Mouse Click) results in a series of fast but powerful attacks. Holding down the attack button results in a Heavy Attack, a downward slam with both fists that deals massive damage but is tricky to pull off!<br/><br/>Holding the secondary attack button (Default Keybind: Right Mouse Click) allows the Rat Ogre to prepare to Leap! Charge the leap for a short while and then aim. Once charged, you can release the button to launch yourself through the air, knocking any Heroes you land upon away and sending them flying all over. Perfect for making a dramatic entrance and throwing those pesky Heroes into disarray.<br/><br/><i>You can also find this information in the in-game Handbook!</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">What’s next?</div>We’re super excited about the release of Versus, it was a massive milestone for a project that we love and we’re glad that it’s been overall a fun time and well-received by the community!<br/><br/>But what’s next for Versus? Beyond the Rat Ogre, we’re looking to add more little things and tinker a bit more in the coming year! There’s a lot of very valid feedback that you guys have given that we want to address and we hope to be able to do that bit by bit in 2025. There are also small additions planned, such as Custom Settings to player-hosted games.<br/><br/>Other than Versus, we’ll continue working on the rest of the Verminous Dreams campaign maps (hope you’ve been having fun with The Forsaken Temple!), as well as a previously mentioned Weapon Pack which is still in the pipeline. Beyond that, well, we can’t reveal everything, can we?<br/><br/>Barring hotfixes, this will be the last Vermintide 2 update of the year, and what a blast it has been! <br/><br/><i>We hope you enjoy the Holidays and the Gifts of the Wolf Father, and we hope you’ve had as much fun with this game this year as we have! See you next year, drengbarazi. <br/>- The Vermintide 2 Team.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch 6.2.0 patch notes</div>As a heads up, due to a sudden issue with our patch building process, this update will be around a 25 gb download on PC. We apologize once again for the inconvenience, we thought we had seen the last of it. We’ll continue investigating to hopefully avoid more patches like these in the future.<br/><br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	(Versus) Enabled the Rat Ogre as a Monster option for Pactsworn.												<br/> </li><li>	Hero Poses should no longer be counted as inventory items when calculating inventory space and should allow players that have reached the inventory cap due to poses to once again open chests.												</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed a crash when clicking on future rewards on Gifts of the Wolf Father. Re-enabled the ability to see what's coming next in the Gifts of the Wolf Father calendar.												<br/> </li><li>	The Forsaken Temple fixes:												<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Fixed enemies getting stuck on the wrong side of the chasm of the second Grim path.											<br/> </li><li>	Patched up safe spot hole											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked wonky hang ledge by temple chasm											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked trigger for end event door marker to not show after door is opened											<br/> </li><li>	Made sure 2 barrels always spawn around the plaza											<br/> </li><li>	Tweaked terrain around drop into drained lake											<br/> </li><li>	Added collision to stuck spot in end event fake elevator											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue with the end event stairs.											<br/> </li><li>	Patched up spot where a waystone piece could be be lost or cheesed											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed crash when two players interact with an elevator in "The Forsaken Temple" at the exact same time.</li></ul></li><li>	Fixed a rare crash when attempting to preview Pactsworn skins before they've loaded.												<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a Chaos Wastes crash when using a Grenade mid-mission.												<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fort Brachsenbrücke - Prevented cannonballs from getting stuck in the elevator</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">An update regarding the data loss issue:</div>Hey all, just checking in again with a progress update and some further information to share.<br/><br/>Our backend developers have a 3-step plan to restore the missing data:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Stage 1: Gather and collate account data from storages we have, and transfer this to another system which will be used for rebuilding missing account data<br/></li><li> Stage 2: Conduct some wizardry in this system to organise the data (e.g. get the latest/highest/correct value for each statistic for each player) and prep it for being merged back in to our backend data<br/></li><li> Stage 3: Update the backend and merge the rebuilt data into existing account data.</li></ul>Stage 1 is in full swing and data is currently being downloaded and transferred to our system required to rebuild the missing data. This is a tremendous amount of account data, and will take some time to complete. We’re exploring whether we can scale this process up and complete it any faster, but for now an approximate estimate is that this stage will take a few weeks to complete.<br/><br/>Please bear with us, and we’ll continue to provide updates when we have more to share.<br/><br/>A big thank you for your continued patience during this process.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 10:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
