<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.1.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497193785816515049</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/9bb5853c8b524d66875299a646da26d866d14785.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>We’re back with Hotfix 6.1.3, bringing a host of fixes and tweaks to Total War: WARHAMMER III, from Kislevite supporters to Beastmen’s lost shards.<br/><br/>Let’s get into it!<br/><br/>— Steve Coleman // Senior Community Manager // Squigherd<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Highlights</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where The Ice Court and The Great Orthodoxy would get stuck at 100/100 supporters after quest battles without increasing tier<br/></li><li> Fixed Beastmen being able to settle without creating a Herdstone, causing them to permanently lose their shards.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where flying spellcasters would be constantly spinning round in circles.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues // Still Cooking</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Manually abandoning a settlement in a Bloodground as a Beastmen faction results in the 3DUI not updating properly and showing the settlement as not a part of the Bloodground.<br/></li><li> When loading a saved game from before version 6.1.3 as a Beastmen faction, the region occupation restrictions get updated on End Turn, not on load.</li></ul><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue so that Beastmen can no longer occupy regions in a Bloodground without actually raising a Herd stone. This used to be allowed in error and consumed a shard without providing an avenue to get it back.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where players could open a panel using hotkeys during the transition from pre to post-battle<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where confederated leaders would not automatically get Followin' Da Plan points if confederated while wounded when playing as the Ironclaw Orcs<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when losing a settlement while an Ataman is traveling to it.<br/></li><li> Added additional negative diplomatic relations between Cathay factions and their enemy rebel factions to stop them finding too much harmony in the early game. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Skulltaker's tongue was missing during the intro cinematic to 'The Slayer Sword' quest battle<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Cockatrice didn’t have a recruitment cap when being recruited by Beastmen armies (Old saves will likely see some mild confusion, as existing Cockatrice in those saves will technically be the Tzeentch version, which is not capped).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where The Ice Court and The Great Orthodoxy would get stuck at 100/100 supporters after quest battles without increasing tier.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General // Gameplay</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Flying casters could spin around when casting spells and moving simultaneously (although spinning is a good trick)<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Empire War Wagon units would bleed from their wooden // metal parts when hit.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where blood would spurt out The Vampire Coast’s Deck Gunners unit cannon when hit.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with how blood VFX displayed for Demigryph Knights.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Battle Maps</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in Zhufbar (Dwarfs) where units could fall through the ground in certain areas of the map.<br/></li><li> Fixing some overlapping assets that were visually glitching on the Erengrad (Kislev) battle map.<br/></li><li> Fixed shallow water in playable area being too deep on the Troll Country (Kislev) battle map.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue on Quenelles (Bretonnia) map where the camera could go inside the river on one side.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some buildings would incorrectly float on the Gaen Vale (High Elves) battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed issues where some terrain lacked collision and units were able to climb very steep surfaces on the battle map for Kemmler's Chaos Tomb Blade quest<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where water on the battle map wasn’t displaying properly for Mother Ostankya’s ‘Jinxed Land’ quest<br/></li><li> Fixed various issues relating to building placement and stretched textures on assorted battle maps<br/></li><li> Performed tree surgery by removing trees that were clipping through buildings and tidied various misplaced assets across various battle maps<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where textures weren't placed properly in some areas on The Black Pyramid (Tomb Kings) battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue so that rebel rocks now obey gravity on The Pillar of Bone battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where units were passing and clipping through a group of rocks on the Aymara Swamp battle map, they have now been thrown in the river to prevent this.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/><br/>As always, if you run into any new issues after updating to 6.1.3 please report them over in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Imperialis Expansion - Meet the Familiars!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523089487392145673</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The <b>Lex Imperialis</b> expansion for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader is just around the corner, and today, we begin our reveals with its biggest and most exciting feature:<br/><br/><b>The Familiars!</b><br/><br/>From the hints we dropped in our latest AMA, and with the expansion revolving around the Adeptus Arbites, many of you have already figured out that the good boy is on his way. <br/><br/>What most of you probably didn't expect is that there is not one but <b>FOUR</b> creatures that may now accompany your Rogue Trader, thanks to the brand new <b>second-tier Overseer archetype</b>!<br/><br/>Abelard, introduce:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">1) The Cyber-Mastiff</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/10901e59314e3bcf961f618736fdbc433f0936a2.gif"/><br/><br/>Often seen accompanying Rogue Traders with the Arbites origin, these mechanized canine predators provide martial support during both combat and exploration, protecting their master with utmost ferocity. Notably, Solomorne Anthar, the new companion hailing from the ranks of the Adeptus Arbites, also employs one of these fearless beasts.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">2) The Psyber-Raven</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/060882ad49c7762354213fe42a4cfb49f12e633f.gif"/><br/><br/>Available to Psykers, these specially bred avian creatures channel and amplify their master's psychic abilities, increasing their range, damage and number of possible targets, as well as providing additional effects.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">3) The Servoskull Swarm</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/7c610c59ad38251677be6525567e9fa7f2df4e94.gif"/><br/><br/>A useful tool often employed by imperial Officers and Operatives, these constellations of hovering servo-skulls provide surveillance, relay their master's abilities across the battlefield, and excel at harassing the enemy.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">4) The Cyber-Eagle</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/a065f0ef40e602ea1923ab1023d8fe54268d27bc.gif"/><br/><br/>Valued by imperial Officers and Operatives for their speed and agility, these cybernetic aerial predators soar high above the battlefield, diving on command to blind and maim their master's enemies. They may also serve as the perfect distraction, sowing confusion among enemy ranks, and even potentially causing friendly fire.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/6ddc018f169b32c66b7417efce1eb4dac4156604.png"/><br/><br/>Are you ready to unleash your new potential?<br/><br/>Stay tuned — we'll be sharing more about the new <b>Overseer</b> archetype, the new <b>Arbites</b> origin, and other info about the Lex Imperialis expansion soon!<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication Breakdown!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520837698904129739</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/50a49917f42f1c39ca7b94d4cc715f943940b6c9.png"/><br/><br/>The Traitorous 6th have disrupted Hive communications with tainted technology.<br/><br/>You must root out these tech-heresies and restore regular Hive communications.<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CjAlTL9y2O8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><b>To make progress in the event, find Tainted Communications Devices and complete the hacking sequence. Then, finish the mission. Each device will grant you 1 point of progress.</b><br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, April 24. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a cosmetic insignia.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/66c55cabc88b396f591efc095d3fb644716c0d8f.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 7.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500571481680379989</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!⚔️</div><br/>A Hotfix has just been released on Space Marine 2. Its main focus is to solve the <b>connectivity issues</b> that are occurring since the release of the 7.0 update last week. We’ll keep working on <b>improving the connectivity over the upcoming days</b>. Let us know if you see improvements with this hotfix, or if you still encounter issues.<br/>On another note, this patch also brings <b>small balancing changes</b> to some weapons, weapon perks, and class perks.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>PATCH NOTES 7.1</b></div><b> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Fixed several crashes.<br/></li><li> Fixed several connectivity issues.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that locked Assault's Relic Regalia as a Prestige 4 reward.</li></ul></b><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Weapons</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Power Sword</b></u></li></ul>Power Rake and Power Whirl damage greatly increased.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Neo-Volkite</u></b></li></ul>Volkite Discharge damage increased by 12.5%.<br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Weapon Perks</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Plasma Incinerator</b></u></li></ul><b>"Perpetual Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Fast Venting"<br/><b>"Adamant Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with “Plasma Collection"<br/><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Common Speed"<br/><b>"Charged Cooling"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Adamant Restoration"<br/><b>"Common Speed 1"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Fast Venting"<br/><b>"Common Speed 2"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Common Cooling"<br/><b>"Perpetual Velocity"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Honed Precision"<br/><b>"Fast Venting"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Blast Radius"<br/><b>"Plasma Collection"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Efficient Charge"<br/><b>"Adamant Restoration"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Charged Speed"<br/><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Adamant Velocity"<br/><b>"Charged Speed 1"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Perpetual Velocity"<br/><b>"Charged Speed 2"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Great Might"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Heavy Plasma Incinerator</b></u></li></ul><b>"Elusive Fire"</b>: The perk has been replaced with "Brutal Rampage"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Plasma Pistol</u></b></li></ul><b>"Blast Radius"</b>: Switched position in the skill tree with "Efficient Charge"<br/><b>"Efficient Charge"</b>: Switched position in the skill tree with "Blast Radius"<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b><u>Power Sword</u></b></li></ul><b>"Reeling Blow"</b>: effect increased from 30% to 40%. Duration increased from 4 to 8 seconds. Cooldown increased from 10 to 15 seconds. <br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Perks</div></b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u><b>Vanguard Prestige Perk</b></u></li></ul> <b>“Exigency Charge”</b>: Fixed an issue preventing the bonus from activating properly. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Sniper Prestige Perk </b></u></li></ul><b>“Versatile Precision”</b>: Fixed a bug that caused this perk cooldown to be more than 15 seconds<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <u><b>Heavy Prestige Perk</b></u></li></ul><b>“Auxiliary Reload”</b>: Now properly triggers when killing an Extremis (or higher) enemy.<br/><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h2">Global Perks QoL</div></b> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All perks that are triggered from perfect parry will now trigger from perfect block as well (even if description doesn’t mention that).<br/><br/></li><li> All perks (class, weapons, prestige) that are triggered by “killing 10 enemies in a rapid succession” changed to “killing 7 enemies in a rapid succession”. Time window between kill to keep the kill streak going is increased from 5 to 6 seconds.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your brief for the April Community Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500570844611739691</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Listen up, Space Marines!</div><br/>Get ready for the new Community Event on Space Marine 2! 🤩<br/> <br/>This time, your mission consists in collectively bringing down 200,000 Trygons to obtain the <b>Mark X Tacticus breastplate</b>. This is the perfect moment to rally and engage side by side in battle.<br/><br/>If you are victorious, this is the prize you'll receive:<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f56e27b6ccd91e004e2a8c8bd6da8b0b4d7ddc9.png"/><br/> <br/>The event starts on April 17 and runs until the 27. <br/>It requires a connection to PROS.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e785444e0b43efd977b239ec3397a01a19878e95.png"/><br/><br/>Onward, Space Marines!<br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects. ⭐ </div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 10:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
