<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Special Event Live - Cry Havoc!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317557</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Commissar Dukane has ordered the Warband to support the Moebian 53rd's latest offensive, so that untested fighters can be forged into reliable soldiers and soldiers into trustworthy veterans.<br/><br/>To celebrate the second anniversary of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, and the free update Grim Protocols, the game is hosting an event that will reward players with crafting materials - such as dockets, plasteel and diamantine - as well as a unique weapon trinket. To earn these rewards, players have to complete Havoc Missions or win a mission where at least one team member is below level 30. (by completing any mission in which any team member - including the player - levels up).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/348a6ce4a2681feae810c0225b860072caf2386a.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/72898b546bfe298a32f6c983e2867164068d0755.jpg"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 17:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havoc Update - Completing Auric Maelstrom Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317555</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/180e8ccebcbe8431233856e754a6cae1c42a9ec5.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>Thank you to everyone jumping into Grim Protocols. We’ve been reviewing the comments from all the players who are trying out Havoc and we’ve made a tweak on something. <br/><br/>To unlock Havoc, players are required to play a Maelstrom mission. If they play an Auric Maelstrom, they are boosted to Assignment Rank 10. <br/><br/>We’ve been monitoring feedback and we don’t believe this boost was enough. We’ve made a change to the backend where players who complete an Auric Maelstrom are now boosted to Assignment Rank 16. If you’ve already been boosted to Rank 10, you should be able to play another Auric Maelstrom to boost to Rank 16.<br/><br/>We chose Assignment Rank 16 because that is the level Auric Intensity is activated with the Emperor’s Fading Light. <br/><br/>To support the different skill levels that might be able to complete a Havoc-equivalent Maelstrom mission, we don’t want to boost too high. Some players who complete an Auric Maelstrom mission might’ve thought it was easy, while others struggled through it. <br/><br/>We’ll be continuing to monitor players to see if this is an adequate boost in levels or not. We’ll be monitoring the other feedback for Havoc, as well. <br/><br/>P.S. If you are having trouble finding parties for Havoc, make sure to select E in the Party Finder to clear your selected tags. We’ve found some players have tags selected that are mutually exclusive from Havoc and it prevents them from seeing the open parties. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction - Meet Golgfag Maneater</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4476109467940814904</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/895a76c8a4bc26fcf1e4cae90ab5626700e2e349.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings, Total War fans!<br/><br/>We’re back for our second in-depth exploration of Total War: WARHAMMER III Omens of Destruction. <br/><br/>This week, the smell of battle, belching and barbequed man-flesh permeates the air as we welcome a significant reinforcement to the Ogre Kingdoms army, Golgfag Maneater, the notorious mercenary captain whose renown has inspired all other Ogre mercenaries to adopt the title of ‘Maneaters’, alongside his fearsome forces.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Read the full blog here!</div><br/><br/>Golgfag's gameplay showcase will premiere at 3PM GMT this Thursday 5th December, so be sure to check back then to feast your eyes on how this mean mercenary plays!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AUGNU2wx0zw?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Later this week we'll be back with our Free-LC blog featuring the Blood God's Destroyer, Arbaal the Undefeated, so until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Protocols Free Update OUT NOW - Patch Notes - Pt. 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317498</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/180e8ccebcbe8431233856e754a6cae1c42a9ec5.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Grim Protocols - Patch Notes Pt. 1</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oC1HRacColU<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div><br/>We're trying something new and including a TL;DR section. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">TL;DR for Grim Protocols</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>New Game Mode - Havoc</b>: Think you’ve mastered the threat over Tertium? Think again. Havoc is a new end-game experience that will test the resolve of the most seasoned operative. Be ready to face daunting challenges and earn new cosmetic rewards.</li><li><b>New Mission - Dark Communion</b>: Return to the Carnival and explore its darkest corners. Steel yourself as you face hordes of cultists who will stop at nothing to achieve their dark communion.</li><li><b>Three New Weapon Families</b>: tear through waves of enemies by wielding the destructive might of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords, and the Ogryn Heavy Stubber.</li><li><b>Anniversary Special Event</b>: to celebrate the second anniversary of Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, the game will host an event that will reward players with a unique weapon trinket.</li><li><b>And more</b>: including the expansion of the Penance progression track with new challenges and rewards, as well as quality of life improvements such as an extension of the Party Finder feature.</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Game Mode: Havoc</div><br/>Listen up, Rejects! You've all had it too easy so far. At least, that's what Commissar Dukane thinks. You've had your training in weapons handling, and now it's time to put that to use. The Commissar has declared this mission now under the purview of the Astra Militarum and intends for it to be carried out in a manner befitting its illustrious reputation. Report to the 53rd tactical command to receive your orders. Perform well and there might even be a medal in it for you. But I wouldn't hold your breath.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a1fe3676cd20f6f75e68b81d630a9609f306055e.jpg"/><br/><br/>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oUzMxKl9qqM<br/><br/>Havoc is a new tiered progression system we have been working on for Trust Level 30 players. This system consists of different levels, known as Havoc Assignment Ranks. There will be 40 Assignment Ranks in total for Havoc. The highest Assignment Rank that a player successfully clears will give them a Havoc Clearance Level. <br/><br/>The mode is designed to offer fresh and exciting challenges for both new and veteran players. Our goal is to make the highest tiers truly demanding, even for our most experienced players. This will be an ongoing process, and we on the design team are eager to collaborate with the community to develop even more difficult challenges for this mode in the future.<br/><br/>To begin your journey with Havoc you need to be playing on an eligible level 30 character, where you will receive a notification upon logging in saying Darinda Dukane wishes to speak with you. She will give you the task of finishing a Maelstrom mission in order to qualify. <b>UPDATE: If a player completes an Auric Maelstrom mission, that player will be immediately given access to Havoc Assignment Rank 16 (previously 10).</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a6fdbf3cfd2ba617aee47550c5ad00b9f094d475.png"/><br/><br/>Each Assignment Rank will incrementally grow in difficulty, with increasing negative modifiers and varying mutators. Players won’t only face increased hordes or enemies, they’ll also encounter 2 challenging mutators and 2 new mutators:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Cranial Corruption</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A percentage of enemies have been afflicted with a Cranial parasite leaving them with no fear or thought; these enemies are immune against suppression and will explode if killed by headshot.</li></ul><li><b>Infected 21st Moebians</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Infected Moebian 21ths replaces poxwalkers and newly infected. </li></ul><li><b>Pus-hardened Skin</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A percentage of enemies have been blessed with hardened skin rendering them more protected against ranged attacks.</li></ul><li><b>The Blight Spreads</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A percentage of the enemies have been afflicted with a nasty Nurgle plague, turning them into gooey liquid upon death with a chance to infect nearby enemies.</li></ul></ul><br/>Players can attempt as many Havoc Assignment Ranks as they wish in a week. Each player will have 3 attempts to clear their own Havoc Assignment Rank before they’re demoted (1) Assignment Rank. (Note: This doesn’t affect a player’s Clearance Level, which is the highest successfully cleared level). Of course, you can’t go lower than Assignment Rank 1. If a player is attempting another player’s Assignment as a member of a party, and the party is not successful, it is only the Assignment Rank owner that loses (1) attempt. <br/><br/>Each player’s Assignment Rank will mostly be unique, meaning it could be any of the missions in Havoc rotation, with any combination of mutators. However, the negative modifiers will remain the same for everyone as the levels increase.<br/><br/>To complete an Assignment Rank, players can either create a party in the Party Finder using their own unique Assignment Rank, or they can request to join an existing party using the Party Finder and complete someone else’s Assignment Rank. Note: Players can also create a party by inviting friends through the Social menu. Players are allowed to attempt Assignment Ranks higher than their own current Assignment Rank through this option. <br/><br/>Additional Note: The Party Finder has been extended to include Havoc. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/daf4afd077e9790671d78f531b2b4ceaa1aece35.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/85673e0023cf2c56490614ded004068d125a5f9c.jpg"/><br/><br/>At the end of each week, a player will earn a Weekly Cache of materials that corresponds to their highest cleared Assignment in that week. At the start of the next week, a player’s Assignment Rank will update based on the highest cleared Assignment from the previous week. Note: The player’s Clearance Level, which represents the highest all-time Havoc Assignment completed and updates in real-time, will not go down each week.<br/><br/>There have been some changes since the last communication about Decay in Havoc after reviewing player feedback. Currently: If a player does not partake in at least (1) Assignment Rank (either their own or from a friend or through the Party Finder) during the week (<b>whether successfully or unsuccessfully</b>), then their current Havoc Assignment Rank will go down (1) Rank.<br/><br/>Along the way to Havoc Clearance Level 40 there are earnable frames, insignias, titles and cosmetics. The cosmetics are all-black versions of the 53rd Moebian cosmetics. (You won’t need to beat Level 40 in order to receive the cosmetics.)<br/><br/>We’ve already written a couple of dev blogs on the topic of Havoc where you can read more (Introduction to Havoc, Q&amp;A about Havoc). Please be aware that some things may have changed since these were written.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5ff53a7d3a90b240e37226ff78fcc9d0230e49cd.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6e6a65cabf48ab1677eb5b4c264edfa57de259c1.png"/><br/>Ogryn<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1eee7c8464df965ddbf7df3ecf5d9ff435393af4.png"/><br/>Zealot<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0d2f85ae11092bf74abe49a410d78608c0560a2b.png"/><br/>Psyker<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9a0d547a3802b2f9a5d0e59cfb9d4506afd1ade6.png"/><br/>Veteran<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Mission - Dark Communion</div>Interrogator Rannick sends you back into the dingy alleys of the Carnival on the trail of the Tainted Stimms. But a storm rages over the Cathedrum of Messelina Vengeant and ritual bells peal across the empty streets. What fresh horror have the heretics mustered behind the Cathedrum doors?<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7bf3e084f43947d939e34bf2123c180a4c6170eb.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Cry Havoc!</div><br/>Commissar Dukane means to forge untested fighters into reliable soldiers and soldiers into trustworthy veterans. <br/><br/><b>To make progress in the event, either complete Havoc missions; or complete any mission with new Rejects (aka Rejects under Trust Level 30).</b><br/><br/>This event will start on Tuesday, December 3, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a new Weapon Trinket.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/348a6ce4a2681feae810c0225b860072caf2386a.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/72898b546bfe298a32f6c983e2867164068d0755.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Weapons</div>We are introducing three new weapon families into Darktide! Tear through waves of enemies by wielding the destructive might of the Two-Handed Force and Power Swords, and the Ogryn Heavy Stubber.<br/><div class="bb_h2">2h Powersword - Relic Blade</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3778d4edc53be9a890ea84b736621f6d1b5798b3.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Overview</b><br/><br/>The Zealot 2-handed Powersword is a giant greatsword with barely contained energy.<br/>It sports huge, sweeping swings and a unique sprinting Heavy stab attack that is perfect for charging into the fray.<br/><br/>This weapon possesses great damage and incredible reach, with easy to use but still deep movesets available between the two marks.<br/><br/>While not particularly nimble, it has a generous Stamina profile, providing flexible frontline pacing of heretic swarms.<br/><br/>The Special action activates the sword, further improving its already remarkable attack properties at the cost of increasing Heat.<br/><br/><b>Weapon Special</b><br/>The 2h Powersword's Special action empowers the sword, improving its swings while it is active.<br/><br/>It particularly buffs the weapon's Cleave values, Damage Multipliers against certain armour types (e.g. Carapace armour) and Impact values (particularly for specific Heavy attacks). <br/><br/>Activating the Weapon Special will start filling a Heat bar. Each activated swing will also increase Heat by a small amount.<br/><br/>When the weapon is deactivated, the Heat bar will passively cool down.<br/><br/>If the Heat bar is completely filled, the weapon overheats. On overheating, the weapon deactivates and cannot be activated until the Heat bar is completely emptied.<br/><br/>The weapon will also deactivate from the following actions:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Automatically, when swapping out of the 2h Powersword.</li><li>Manually, when performing the Special action while the weapon is already activated.</li></ul>After performing the Special activate or deactivate action, the attack chain will not be reset.<br/><br/>Additionally, the weapon will receive Block properties while activating or deactivating.<br/><br/>This will provide flexibility to weave in the Special action in between attack combos.<br/><br/><b>Munitorum Mk II Relic Blade</b><br/>This 2h Powersword mark is especially easy to use, with immediate access to both sweeping Light Vanguard attacks and powerful Heavy Strikedown attacks.<br/><br/>Additionally, a unique chain from Push to Heavy 4 allows a faster way into the looping Heavy 3 and Heavy 4 Vanguard attacks.<br/><br/><b>Attacks</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1 / Light 2: Moderately fast, horizontal Vanguard attacks with good cleave.</li><li>Light 3: Fast stab Strikedown attack with good armour penetration and finesse multiplier.</li><li>Light Sprint/Slide: Fast, diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with good cleave (only available while in Sprint or Slide state).</li><li>Push-attack: A stab Strikedown attack with similar properties as Light 3.</li><li>Heavy 1 / Heavy 2: Slow, vertical Strikedown attacks with great damage and finesse multiplier.</li><li>Heavy 3 / Heavy 4: Slow, horizontal Vanguard attacks with great cleave.</li><li>Heavy Sprint/Slide: Long reaching stab Strikedown attack with good armour penetration and finesse multiplier (only available while in Sprint or Slide state); entering the windup animation for this attack gives a small speed boost.</li></ul><b>Suggested Horde combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; H3 &gt; H4 &gt; H3 &gt; …<br/>L1 &gt; L2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; L1 &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/><br/>… &gt; H3 &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/><br/>Push &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/>Push &gt; H4 &gt; H3 &gt; …<br/>Light Sprint/Slide &gt; L2 &gt; ...</blockquote><b>Suggested Single Target combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/>H1 &gt; H2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; H1 &gt; ...<br/><br/>Push-Attack &gt; H2 &gt; …<br/>Heavy Sprint/Slide &gt; H1 &gt; …</blockquote><br/><b>Munitorum Mk X Relic Blade</b><br/>This 2h Powersword mark trades access to fast Vanguard attacks for a plethora of Strikedown attacks.<br/><br/>The unique chains from Light 1 to Heavy 4, from Heavy 3 to Light 2, and from Heavy 4 to Heavy 3 allow to quickly loop together all the Strikedown attacks in free-flow combos.<br/><br/><b>Attacks</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1 / Light 2: Moderately fast, vertical Strikedown attacks with good single target damage.</li><li>Light 3: Moderately fast, slightly diagonal Vanguard attack with good cleave.</li><li>Light Sprint/Slide: Fast, diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with good cleave (only available while in Sprint or Slide state).</li><li>Push-attack: A horizontal Vanguard attack with similar properties as Light 3.</li><li>Heavy 1 / Heavy 2: Slow, slightly diagonal Vanguard attacks with great cleave.</li><li>Heavy 3: Slow, uppercut Strikedown attack with good damage and great finesse multiplier.</li><li>Heavy 4: Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with good damage and finesse multiplier.</li><li>Heavy Sprint/Slide: Long reaching stab Strikedown attack with good armour penetration and finesse multiplier (only available while in Sprint or Slide state); entering the windup animation for this attack gives a small speed boost.</li></ul><b>Suggested Horde combos</b><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; H2 &gt; …<br/>H1 &gt; H2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; H1 &gt; H2 &gt; …<br/><br/>Push-Attack &gt; L3 &gt; …<br/>Push-Attack &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/>Push &gt; H2 &gt; …<br/>Light Sprint/Slide &gt; H2 &gt; ...</blockquote><b>Suggested Single Target combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; H3 &gt; H4 &gt; H3 &gt; …<br/>… &gt; H3 &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/><br/>L1 &gt; H4 &gt; …<br/>… &gt; H4 &gt; L1 &gt; …<br/>Push &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/>Heavy Sprint/Slide &gt; L2 &gt; …</blockquote><div class="bb_h2">2h Forcesword - Blaze Force Greatsword</div><b>Overview</b><br/><br/>A weapon for the truly incomparable minds, the Psyker 2-handed Forcesword inherits most of the speed and elegance of its smaller 1-handed sibling along with additional damage, reach and a very unique Special (continue reading below for further details).<br/><br/>It has a deep moveset that rewards players who can master its quirky combos and conditional attack starts: both marks have unique chains with specific attacks only available during Sprint or Slide states, or even immediately after wielding the weapon.<br/><br/><b>Weapon Special</b><br/>The Special of this weapon is divided into two parts: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Upon performing the Special action, the blade will be imbued with warp energy for a very short time.</li><li>The first follow-up attack (either Light or Heavy) will always perform a horizontal swing that releases the stored energy as a ranged Warpshock Slash.</li></ul>The Warpshock Slash travels a short distance, cleaving through most enemies while damaging and staggering them.<br/><br/>At its base power, the Warpshock Slash has moderate damage, while its Impact value will only stagger lesser enemies.<br/><br/>However, the Warpshock Slash level can be empowered by active combat:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Whenever an enemy is killed by damage from the 2h Forcesword swings, their life essence will be stored temporarily. Stronger enemies provide more essence when killed.</li><li>Upon reaching a minimum essence gauge threshold, the next Special attack will be empowered. If the essence gauge is completely filled, the next Special attack will be empowered even further, granting a reality-tearing Warpshock Slash attack.</li><li>When performing the Special action to imbue the blade with power, all essence is consumed. The Warpshock Slash attack's power is calculated based on the essence gauge threshold rounded down.</li><li>The essence gauge will also slowly passively deplete if no additional essence is gained after a short period of time.</li></ul>Note that essence from a dying enemy will still be awarded to 2h Forcesword players that damaged but did not kill the enemy in a short grace time period immediately before its death.<br/><br/><b>Covenant Mk VI Blaze Force Greatsword</b><br/>This 2h Forcesword mark has immediate access to powerful Strikedown attack loops but can reach its Heavy Vanguard attack only when chaining from specific Light attacks.<br/><br/>This makes the weapon very suited to deal with single foes but also will require a bit of skill when facing dense hordes.<br/><br/><b>Attacks</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1: Diagonal Vanguard attack with good speed and cleave.</li><li>Light 2: Diagonal Vanguard attack with good speed and cleave (also performed directly instead of Light 1 when in Sprint state).</li><li>Light 3: Diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with good speed and cleave, an improved finesse modifier and a unique chain to Heavy 3.</li><li>Light 4: Vertical Strikedown attack with good damage and finesse modifier.</li><li>Light Slide: Diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with similar properties as Light 3; chains into Light 3 or Heavy 1 (only available while in Slide state).</li><li>Light Wield: Diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with similar properties as Light 1; chains into Light 1 or Heavy 1 (only available immediately after wielding the weapon).</li><li>Push-attack: A single target force push, with good range and extremely high Impact.</li><li>Light Push/Push-attack follow-up combo: Horizontal Vanguard attack with similar properties as Light 1; chains into Light 4 or Heavy 3 (only available when chained from a Push or a Push-attack).</li><li>Heavy 1: Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with good damage and finesse multiplier.</li><li>Heavy 2: Slow, stab Strikedown attack with great damage and finesse multiplier, and improved armour penetration; chains into Light 4 or Heavy 1.</li><li>Heavy 3: Slow, slightly diagonal Vanguard attack with great cleave; chains into Light 1 or Heavy 1 (only available when chained from Light 3 and Light Push/Push-attack follow-up combo).</li><li>Heavy Wield/Sprint/Slide: Vertical Strikedown with similar properties as Heavy 1; chains into Light 3 or Heavy 1 (only available while in Sprint or Slide state, and immediately after wielding the weapon).</li></ul><b>Suggested Horde combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; L3 &gt; H3 &gt; L1 &gt; …<br/>L1 &gt; L2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; L1 &gt; ...<br/><br/>Push &gt; Light followup &gt; H3 &gt; …<br/>Push attack &gt; Light followup &gt; H3 &gt; …<br/>Light Slide &gt; L3 &gt; …<br/>Light Wield &gt; L1 &gt; …<br/>(While Sprinting) L2 &gt; …</blockquote><b>Suggested Single Target combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/>H1 &gt; L4 &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/>… &gt; H2 &gt; L4 &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/><br/>Push Attack &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/>Heavy Wield/Sprint/Slide &gt; H1 &gt; …</blockquote><div class="bb_h2">Covenant Mk VIII Blaze Force Greatsword</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b73602cb948ac46648af985c199709508f62b36a.jpg"/><br/><br/>This 2h Forcesword mark has immediate access to many different Vanguard attack loops, but can reach its Strikedown attacks only when further into the combo. <br/><br/>Particularly, its extremely strong Heavy stab can be reached only after a push-attack, therefore requiring a small amount of setup.<br/><br/><b>Attacks</b><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1: Horizontal Vanguard attack with good speed and cleave.</li><li>Light 2: Horizontal Vanguard attack with good speed and cleave; chains into Light 3 or Heavy 1.</li><li>Light 3: Diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with good speed, cleave and an improved finesse modifier.</li><li>Light 4: Diagonal uppercut Vanguard attack with good speed, cleave and an improved finesse modifier (can also be accessed while in Slide state).</li><li>Light Wield/Sprint: Diagonal Vanguard attack with similar properties as Light 1; chains into Light 1 or Heavy 1 (only available while in Sprint state and immediately after wielding the weapon).</li><li>Push-attack: A single target force push, with good range and extremely high Impact; chains into Light or Heavy follow-up combo attacks.</li><li>Light Push-attack follow-up combo: Fast stab Strikedown attack with good armour penetration and finesse multiplier (only available when chained from a Push-attack).</li><li>Heavy Push-attack follow-up combo: Slow stab Strikedown attack with great damage, armour penetration and finesse multiplier (only available when chained from a Push-attack).</li><li>Heavy 1: Slow, slightly diagonal Vanguard attack with great cleave.</li><li>Heavy 2: Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with good damage and finesse multiplier.</li><li>Heavy 3: Slow, vertical Strikedown attack with good damage and finesse multiplier; chains into Light 4 and Heavy 2.</li><li>Heavy Wield/Sprint/Slide: Slightly diagonal Vanguard attack with similar properties as Heavy 1; chains into Light 1 or Heavy 1 (only available while in Sprint or Slide state, and immediately after wielding the weapon).</li></ul><b>Suggested Horde combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">L1 &gt; L2 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; L1 &gt; …<br/>H1 &gt; L2 &gt; …<br/>L1 &gt; L2 &gt; Block cancel &gt; L1 or H1 &gt; …<br/>… &gt; L2 &gt; H1 &gt; …<br/><br/>Light Wield/Sprint &gt; L1 or H1 &gt; …<br/>(While Sliding) L4 &gt; L1 or H1 &gt; …<br/>Heavy Wield/Sprint/Slide &gt; H1 &gt; …</blockquote><b>Suggested Single Target combos</b><blockquote class="bb_blockquote">H1 &gt; H2 &gt; H3 &gt; H2 &gt; …<br/><br/>Push Attack &gt; Light Followup &gt; H1 or Push Attack &gt; …<br/>Push Attack &gt; Heavy Followup &gt; H1 or Push Attack &gt; …</blockquote><div class="bb_h1">Ogryn Heavy Stubber</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/dd26abed2f5ee535c754e874228b94079b5fbb6d.jpg"/><br/><br/><b>Overview</b><br/><br/>While sporting only half of the barrels and magazines compared to their Twin-linked brethren, the Heavy Stubbers make up for it with increased punch and precision on each shot, especially when bracing the weapon in secondary fire.<br/><br/>With high-caliber bullets and huge penetration and stagger values, no foe will remain standing after the smoke dissipates.<br/><br/>When correctly pacing the shots, this will allow Ogryns to snipe enemies even at longer distances, while still having the option to go full auto in situations that require less thoughtful strategies. <br/><br/><b>Weapon Special</b><br/>The Special of this weapon is a high-power flashlight. While Ogryns are not fully used to such advanced technology, they still find ways to make it work.<br/><br/>May it be a light to you in dark places.<br/><br/><b>Primary Fire</b><br/>Full auto mode, with high spread and recoil. Becomes rapidly inaccurate even at medium distances, but can still be useful to create Suppression when covering the team’s advance against entrenched enemies.<br/><br/><b>Secondary Fire</b><br/>Semi-auto mode, with slow rate of fire. Bracing the weapon enables more accurate shooting, especially when waiting for the spread and recoil to settle.<br/><br/><b>Krourk Mk IIa Heavy Stubber</b><br/><br/>40 rounds magazine, with good fire speed in both primary and secondary stance.<br/><br/>While less powerful than the other marks, the Krourk Mk IIa has increased mobility and faster wield and reload speeds, making it a very reliable firearm to quickly deploy in tense situations.<br/><br/><b>Gorgonum Mk IIIa Heavy Stubber</b><br/><br/>30 rounds magazine, with average fire speed in both primary and secondary stance.<br/>The Gorgonum Mk IIIa has significant power in each shot, while still not completely sacrificing mobility and fire speed.<br/><br/>A good middle ground to bring in any engagement.<br/><br/><b>Achlys Mk II Heavy Stubber</b><br/><br/>20 rounds magazine, with slow fire speed in both primary and secondary stance.<br/><br/>The Achlys Mk II mark trades nimbleness for enormous power: while its wield time is high and the handling is cumbersome, it makes up for it with the highest damage, armour penetration and cleave of all the Heavy Stubbers.<br/><br/>A great ranged weapon for smart Ogryns with tactical awareness of the fight (or just for players who want problems to disappear).<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Quality of Life Additions</div><div class="bb_h2">Player Reporting</div>Player Reporting was introduced in Hotfix #53 (1.5.11) and it goes live for all platforms today. To find the reporting option, players will need to open the player’s account details in the Social menu and select the Report entry. From there, you’ll be brought to the Report Player screen.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/bea6bdcdfc68f8e361d0d2a3743bd092345041d2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/025055e7bbf30c833b255f7a8c47775f43a745da.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Disconnect Punishment for Leaving a Game</div><br/>Disconnecting / ALT+F4:ing to circumvent being “downed” to complete harder penances (e.g. the Auric Storm Survivor penance) or bypass the downed/hogtied states has been an issue especially in higher difficulties, and to this end, we’ve introduced more checks when players reconnect. Players will now respawn back with the health count they had upon leaving, instead of being spawned with a minimal % of hp, and players who disconnect/ALT+F4 to get around being downed will now spawn back hogtied. <br/><br/>Further, if a player leaves mid-mission without reconnecting, it will automatically count as a loss for that player. However, the players in the mission will still be able to complete the mission; and if they do, it will count as a win for the remaining players.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>This is the end of Pt.1 for the patch notes. Please continue on to Pt. 2!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 10:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Protocols Free Update OUT NOW - Patch Notes - Pt. 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4456970437737317496</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9238b10b59ebf532d3bc80f964b9189d869ecab1.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Grim Protocols - Patch Notes - Pt. 2</div><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>Make sure to check out Pt. 1 of the Patch Notes. <br/><br/>Here is Pt. 2. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Weapon Changes</div><b>Obscurus Mk II Blaze Force Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a new Light attack, available only when chaining from and to the Heavy 2 attack, or while in Slide stance</li><li>Improved the offensive properties of the Light 2 attack</li></ul><b>Dev note</b>: <i>The OG Psyker Force Sword was missing a combo to deal with groups of enemies, as it was not possible to chain after the Vanguard Heavy 2 into any non-Strikedown type attack.</i><br/><br/><i>With this release, we introduced a new Light attack with properties similar to the Light 1 attack, but with a diagonal uppercut swing direction instead.<br/><br/>This attack can be accessed only when chained after a Heavy 2, while also chaining back into it for a very straightforward attack combo.<br/><br/>This attack will now also be used when performing a Light attack while Sliding (while this will add no significant mechanical changes, it will look much cooler).<br/><br/>Additionally, the Light 2 attack shared the same profile as the Light 1 attack, while having a much more punishing swing direction.<br/><br/>We created a new bespoke profile for it with improved offensive properties, such as higher damage and a larger bonus when connecting with weakspots, to make it more rewarding and satisfying to lob off enemies' heads.<br/><br/>With these additions and the improved damage that the Heavy 1 attack received in a previous update, the Obscurus Force Sword should now be on much more level ground with its siblings.</i><br/><br/><b>Obscurus Mk II Blaze Force Sword / Illisi Mk V Blaze Force Sword</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked Dodge template:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dodge distance scale from (0.8,1.1) to (0.9,1.2).</li><li>Dodge speed scale from (1.0) to (1.0,1.1).</li></ul></ul><b>Dev note</b>: <i>The Dodge characteristics of the Obscurus and Illisi Force Swords are now aligned to the improved values previously used only in the Deimos mark.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Class Changes</div><b>Psyker</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased the Base Toughness of the Psyker from 60 to 75.</li></ul><b>Zealot</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ‘Chorus of Spiritual Fortitude’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>No longer canceled when vaulting. Also, added a short delay to when the ability can be unwielded, to prevent removing accidentally by double tapping the input.</li></ul></ul><b>Ogryn</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Talent Tree Layout Changes**</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘Reloaded and Ready’ has moved to the position where ‘Big Boom’ was</li><li>‘Big Boom’ has moved to the position where ‘Pacemaker’ was</li><li>‘Pacemaker’ has moved to the position where ‘Towering Presence’ was</li><li>‘Towering Presence’ has moved to the position where ‘Reloaded and Ready’ was</li><li>Swapped places between the ‘25% Suppression Bonus’ node and the ‘5% Ranged Damage’ node, that were set before and after 'Coward Culling’</li></ul></ul>** <b>Dev Note</b>: <i>Upon logging in, Ogryn players will have to redistribute their talent points.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Gameplay / Enemy Changes</div><b>Gunners</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased damage falloff:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dreg Gunner increased from 15m to 30m.</li><li>Scab Gunner increased from 15 to 35m.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lowered reduction from 0.6 to 0.5.**</li></ul><li>Ogryn Reaper increased from 15 to 25.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lowered reduction from 0.6 to 0.2.**</li></ul></ul></ul><b>Dev Note</b>: <i>The numbers are different to reflect the intended divergence between the two factions, where over time we intend to make the Dregs more melee heavy, while the Scabs should act like the elite guard they are. ** The reduction number is the amount of damage lowered past the range specified.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Removed hitstun from Gunner attacks.</li><li>Scab Gunner hitmass increased from 2.0 to 5.0.</li><li>Removed pushback from Ogryn Reapers ranged attacks.</li><li>Dreg and Scab Gunners will now strafe in addition to their other abilities:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dreg Gunner additional strafe spread set to 1.2.</li><li>Scab Gunner additional strafe spread set to 0.3.</li></ul></ul><b>Ragers</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the armour type of the Scab Rager torso &amp; center mass from Flak to Carapace.</li><li>Slightly lowered the attack speed of the Dreg Rager combo.</li></ul><b>Shotgunners</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dreg Shotgunner hitmass increased from 2.0 to 4.0.</li><li>Scab Shotgunner hitmass increased from 2.0 to 5.0.</li><li>Removed pushback on Shotgunner attacks.</li></ul><b>General</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased enemies’ in-combat detection radius from 15 meters to 25 meters.</li></ul><b>Dev Note</b>: <i>This only applies to aggro detection from attacking players.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Path of Redemption Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added 5 more reward tiers to the Path of Redemption track, including the face-covered Loyalist Moebian 6th helmets.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Bug Fixes and Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">Weapons and Blessings</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where rapidly firing a Bolt Pistol with the Run 'n' Gun Blessing while sprinting would cancel sprint.</li><li>Fixed issue where the 'Rising Heat' Blessing didn't specify what Stat was increased - Strength.</li><li>Changed the description of the 'Surge' Blessing on the Voidblast and Electrokinetic Force Staves to specify that only the Primary Attack can fire twice.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the 'Point-Blank Barrage' had an incorrect description. </li></ul><b>Dev Note</b>: <i>It previously didn’t include the effect of the old “Thick of the Fray” talent, which has since been baked into the Base Ability.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Tenderiser’ Blessing of the Ogryn Cleavers had wrong values in its description.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>from 7.5-15% to 10-25%.</li></ul><li>Fixed an issue where the ‘Warp Flurry’ Blessing would interact incorrectly with the charged secondary fire of Psyker Force Staves when the charge speed bonus became too high.</li><li>Fixed an issue with Celerity (blue) Stimms where the high attack speed buff gave longer intervals between possible attacks instead of the intended shorter interval when using Psyker Force Staves. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Classes</div><b>Psyker</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed issue with the Psyker's Telekine Dome where it would sometimes be placed elevated from the ground.</li><li>Disrupt Destiny Keystone: Fixed an issue with enemy marking selection. </li></ul><b>Dev Note</b>: <i>Marking is now more predictable.  At a fixed interval of time, the closest target to the player within line of sight will be marked. If a marked target is killed, the closest target to the killed enemy within line of sight of the player will be marked.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Combat</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where ranged hits penetrating multiple enemies would only be registered as having hit a weakspot if the last enemy was hit on a weakspot.</li><li>Mutants no longer collide with the Psyker's Telekine Dome after the player dodges their charge.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The previous Hotfix (1.5.11) pulled three missions from the mission board (Chasm Station HL-16-11, Magistrati Oubliette TM8-707 and Excise Vault Spireside-13). They have all been re-introduced into the rotation today, December 3rd.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Transit Hub HL 16-11, "Chasm Terminus"</div><b>Hab Dreyko</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where a Grimoire could spawn in a location not accessible to players.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Habzone HL-70-04, "The Carnival"</div><b>Warren 6-19</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>As a result of updating shared gameplay areas in Dark Communion, Warren 6-19 will look slightly different now (mostly backdrop)</li><li>Some optimization was done in Uptown (shared area) that will also affect Warren 6-19.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Manufactory HL-17-36, "Metalfab 36"</div><b>Power Matrix HL-17-36 </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The shaft that descends towards the overheating reactor ("The Long Way Down") has been reworked slightly and now features ice and snow buildup from the coolant system.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Operations</div><b>Rolling Steel</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We now disable backfill when the "Impact Imminent" timer is active (aka players cannot join in the last 30 seconds of the mission).</li><li>Increased timer duration by 10% across all difficulties.</li><li>Fixed batteries despawning when jumping on the upper parts of the train carts.</li><li>The bomb defusals have been re-worked to only stall for the last third of the decoding.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Stability</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We have identified an Out of Memory crash after long sessions of gameplay on some consoles. This has been addressed in this update.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">VO and Audio</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue that could cause idle sound effects (e.g. from Chainswords) to never stop playing after being knocked down.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Dolby Atmos would sometimes not apply properly.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">UI/UX and Animation</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a new item marker on the inventory for insignias, titles, portrait frames, emotes and poses.</li><li>Added warning on the inventory tabs to better identify where an error in the selected loadout might be taking place.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Mark names could be displayed incorrectly when looking at the Mark rewards in the Mastery menu.</li><li>Added UI element to display active voice chat speakers at all times during play.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The option to disable it is available in the interface options (this setting is not available on some consoles).</li></ul><li>Changed Auspex Drill target placement to make it easier to navigate with a keyboard.</li><li>Fixed an issue where some buff icons, most notably the sprinting and coherency icons, were using a reddish tint.</li><li>The mission voting screen will now show the name of the player initiating the mission.</li><li>Fixed a UI animation issue in the Empower screen.</li><li>The objective text in the Rolling Steel mission no longer overlaps the timer bar in some languages.</li><li>The background scene for the cosmetic preview in the operatives menu has been visually updated.</li><li>The background scene of the operative screen has been visually updated.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Cosmetics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We’ve added movement to the Stance-type cosmetics, which you can see either in the Stance select or in the post-mission end of round screen.</li><li>Fixed several issues where hood-type cosmetic items would clip with certain types of hairstyles.</li><li>Fixed issues with the Veteran “Militarum Tox-Field Trench Jacket (Burn Sulphur)” upperbody cosmetic clipping with pants while crouching.</li><li>Fixed the Psyker “Aetheric Veil (Taros Tan)” headgear cosmetic having transparent collar from behind when in the cosmetic preview.</li><li>Fixed hair clipping through the Veteran “Commisar's Cap (Red)” headgear cosmetic  </li><li>Fixed issue with eyebrows clipping through the visor of the Zealot "Votarist's pot helm with rebreather" headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed issues with the Psyker "Crucius Sepulturum-issue Shadowveil" headgear cosmetic hiding the beard.</li><li>Fixed an issue with some eyebrows clipping through the mask on the Zealot “Votarist’s Pot Helm with Rebreather” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed some clipping issues around the neck on the Veteran “Lucius MK VIIIB Death’s Head” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed issues with the Ogryn “Kruppskul Helm (Brute-sized)” headgear cosmetic removing eyebrows and incorrectly modulating the voice.</li><li>Fixed instances where the fabric in the Veteran “Militarum Heavy Battlegear (Protectus Pattern IX)“ upperbody cosmetic would render with body clipping through,</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Other Miscellaneous Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Several fixes for typos in subtitle text.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Known Issues</div><b>Important Note:</b> <b>Hotfix #54 (1.6.1) is scheduled to release Thursday, December 5, 2024. </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Brightness and Motion Blur settings are not available in Video options on some consoles.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>These will be added to the game with Hotfix #54 (1.6.1).</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>After resuming from Rest mode, players on some consoles may not be able to join text or voice chat when joining back into the Mourningstar. For players experiencing this issue, returning to character selection or restarting the game will solve this issue. </li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will be fixed in Hotfix #54 (1.6.1).</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Correct localization is missing from some end of round messages when playing Havoc.</li><li>The localized text for the “Cry Havoc!” event may not fully match the English writing.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will be fixed in Hotfix #54 (1.6.1).</i> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Localization is not present for all new Penance rewards and will show up in English regardless of set language.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This is fixed in Hotfix #54 (1.6.1). </i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The controller vibration on some consoles(and in rarer cases on PC) can stay persistent upon rescue if you die while sawing an enemy using a Chainsword, Chainaxe, or Eviscerator. This can also happen with the Force Greatsword if you die or get knocked down while on a high Special charge level.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This is fixed in Hotfix #54 (1.6.1).</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The final reward from the live event may not immediately show up in your inventory. Players can relog in order to ensure it appears.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This is fixed in Hotfix #55 (1.6.2).</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>We rolled out some changes to certain regions (Japan, Germany and Austria) to be better aligned with age rating boards. Germany and Austria were incorrectly given more restrictions than intended. With the upcoming Hotfix #54 (1.6.1), Germany and Austria will have most of their gore setting restored to what it was previously, with the exception of post-death ragdoll interactions to be in line with recent Steam rule on German regulations and to align settings with console regulations (on-death ragdoll animations will still be present). This means German and Austrian console players will get access to the same gore settings - except for post-death ragdoll interactions. This puts it in line with the settings on other consoles. For Japan, all settings will go back to as they were, with the exceptions to comply with regulations.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 10:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
