<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Protocols - Dark Communion Mission - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/512943879502168737</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/e9954f52ba71e57c1623ed6e9233403b36f05c9e.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone, </div>For Grim Protocols, we are releasing a new mission known as Dark Communion. To celebrate its release, we interviewed some of the devs and Fatshark team members who helped bring it to life. <br/><br/>We’re going to talk a bit about the narrative that inspired it, the level design process, the art and the visual effects. As always, we want to give you an overview of the process of creating the mission, but we still want to leave some things unsaid for players to discover for themselves when they boot up the map for the first time. <br/><br/>Let’s dive back into the carnival.<br/><br/>P.S. We waited to share this dev blog until a few days after release so everyone could have a chance to try it out without any spoilers.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Level Design</div><br/>With Dark Communion we wanted to forward the narrative of the Moebian 6th activities in The Carnival, as well as their relationship with the Cult of Admonition. This level sends players deeper into the heart of the Carnival district, following reports of sinister, ritual activity and a growing presence of heretic cultists. You’re being sent in to investigate these reports, but as always, things can and will escalate, so keep your eyes peeled and your weapons ready.<br/><br/>While building the previously seen missions set in the Carnival district, we had already planned to revisit it when the time was right. As such, players are likely to have already noticed, for example, the Cathedrum of Messelina Vengeant, seen in the background near the beginning of Warren 6-19 - now you will get to see it up close, and purge the heretics on its steps.<br/><br/>The other parts of the mission follow our usual modus operandi of interconnectivity. We wanted to revisit certain parts with a new coat of paint, and introduce new combat spaces that are different, while staying true to the DNA of the already established architecture.<br/><br/>As always, Jesper Kyd also created a masterpiece of a track for this mission. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bringing it Back to the Carnival</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Is this a continuation of the Carnival maps?</div><br/>Absolutely, but not only that. This level sees the culmination of the threads that began in the Carnival and continued through last year’s Orthus Offensive. We now know that Wolfer and the Traitorous 6th have made the Carnival a base of operations for their foul, tainted stimm production. While the warband continues to stymie their progress, their shipments are still getting through, as evidenced by that unfortunate business with the Moebian 21st, poor souls. Killing Rodin Karnak was a blow to their plans, but we already know that Rinda is still at large. Somehow, they brought her back from the brink of death. She’s calling herself the Herald of Admonition now. This mission promises to shed more light on what is driving the Traitorous 6th and their tainted stimms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Will future missions continue the story that’s being played out in Dark Communion?</div>Without giving away the mission ending, there are definitely new leads to follow after the conclusion of Dark Communion. Though, what those are, you’ll have to find out alongside the warband. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Who are the Cultists?</div>Originally assumed to be rabble-rousers and disorganised, disenfranchised gangs of hive citizens, we discover in Dark Communion that this is not the case and something much more sinister lies behind these yellow-clothed maniacs.<br/><br/>Since the mission is to ruin the ritual, does that “close” Rodin’s story? What would have happened if the ritual had worked?<br/><br/>When dealing with the fell powers of Chaos, it is unwise to write off any victory as final. The warband seems to have dealt with the threat for now, but who knows what effect those foul energies could have on Tertium.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Does this mission herald the start of a new narrative arc? Gloriana felt self-contained narratively, but Dark Communion raises a lot of questions.</div>To us, Dark Communion is a continuation of several of the previous story arcs in the game, it harkens back to the story we started to tell with the release of the Traitors Curse update but also starts to show us that there is more to the cult of Admonition than the warband has previously understood. We’ve got loads of plans for future storylines.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Art Design</div>For Art Design, we reined in Environment Artist Jonatan W. to give his thoughts on working on Dark Communion. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6e760b62f500cf31f1a3a735f643237e14aae017.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What was it like designing the art for this mission? </div>Most of my work was on the setpieces for the end event, but designing that was really fun. There was already a rough blockout for the event in the level that had Stimm tanks from one of our older levels with cables running up to a chaos star that was hanging over the altar. That gave me a good idea of what to make. <br/><br/>After clarifying with the level designers what the objectives were and how you would interact with the event, the actual work on designing and creating the units began.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">What kind of feeling were you trying to capture with the end event?</div>Since the event is set inside of a cathedral, I thought it might be cool to make something that resembled church organs in its silhouette. I thought it would frame the altar and Rodin in a nice way when you enter. <br/><br/>I came up with the design of the two large vat tanks that would pump out fluids to Rodin from a central dispenser and started blocking it out. For some reason, I got the image of a horror monster being brought to life and retro-tesla coils stuck in my mind and thought that designing something like that would be neat, and fit into the whole vibe of trying to resurrect Rodin.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Were there any challenges?</div>Yes there were some technical and performance limitations to consider. Making destructible units always has some inherent challenges, not only from a technical standpoint but also from an art perspective! Like making nice transitions in destroyed states and getting VFX and sound in to sell it properly.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Visual Effects</div>Hi everyone, I’m Felicia and I work with visual effects (VFX) for Darktide. When I got the task to work on the new mission - Dark Communion, I knew that this was right up my alley. Scary and spooky Warhammer 40k with cultists and a ritual and a lot of new effects? Sign me up! <br/><br/>After the level designers had done the blockout for the level I knew that it was gonna be a cathedral that you could see from the start of the mission and the direction I got was that you were supposed to see that something scary and big was happening over there. I usually try to look at real life videos for visual effects (like snow, explosions, steam, rain etc.) but how does it work when it comes to more illusion-like effects and references that I can’t find in the real world? Then you have to imagine what it will look like and mash things together. Like what indicates a spooky atmosphere above a cathedral? I knew it had to be big. I thought of some kind of thunderstorm that was just above the cathedral and experimenting with different behaviors and it ended up with a spiral of clouds to make it more unique than just a thunderstorm. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7bf3e084f43947d939e34bf2123c180a4c6170eb.jpg"/><br/><br/>After the clouds above the cathedral, then most of my work came in the end event inside the cathedral where the ritual was going on. <br/><br/>The second thing I started to work on was the shields that are a big part of the end event and the gameplay. For these I got concept art so that I knew kind of how it would look. So I knew that it would be green and look a little bit like northern lights in its behavior. It’s a mesh with a material on it so it’s not any particles except when the shield goes down when smoke is pushing the player back as the shield goes down.  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fe5ec1bd24a5c7fc5b197cd1570b574e08bbb6b4.jpg"/><br/><br/>We also have the cultists that are keeping the shields up to protect the ritual. When it comes to these effects I just knew that I wanted it to be kind of rough but still have subtle things that you wouldn’t notice at first but it does a lot for the feeling. Like adding a distortion when the cultists effects are hitting a shield so it kind of wobbles on the shield as an impact from the cultists.   <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/3914c263d6b1d0048d919a0eaafb923168f3f70f.jpg"/><br/><br/>When you have destroyed all the shields you get to the altar where you will destroy tanks, resulting in a big energy explosion. It was gonna be a build up over some time, so I did 4 different stages and I was thinking of some kind of implode explosion with a lot of energy.  So at first it would start off with a small indication that the energy is getting bigger and bigger in the energy source (the corpse) until it finally reaches maximum and then explodes. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0cd72d700a28fdcc8e8da0da46ab711169ac532d.jpg"/><br/><br/>And the last thing that happens is Rodin’s soul leaves his body and flies out of the cathedral windows. How does a soul look/feel like leaving the body? That was the question I asked myself and I thought of some smoke that is spawning from the body and flies in different directions so you can’t mistake it as smoke from an explosion, to make them stand out so you as a player understand that it’s something more than just smoke. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/befa042a77132029ca45e7223c6122e02999c4bb.jpg"/><br/><br/>Hope you liked to step into my visual effects mind and ideas that became the effects for Dark Communion, this was a really fun mission to work on and I hope you’ll enjoy it as much as I do! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><br/>That’s our sneak peek for Dark Communion! We hope everyone enjoys jumping into the Carnival again, and we look forward to seeing what everyone thinks. We’ll be reading the comments. <br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forsaken Temple: FREE New Map releasing next week!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954130778</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<i>"I don't know what they want with it, but if even half the stories of Athel Lithri are true, you better go up there and stop them."</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>We've been teasing it for a while now, but it's finally time to reveal the next step in the Ubersreik 5's adventure! The first of three missions in the new Verminous Dreams campaign, <b>'The Forsaken Temple'</b> is coming out next week, <b>free on all platforms!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">The Forsaken Temple</div>Devoted readers of Lohner's Chronicles (spying on someone's personal journal is very rude, by the way) would know that dear Franz was recently visited by an Elf of the Divine persuasion, who gave him a cryptic warning of things to come.<br/><br/>While he never spoke a word about this to our Heroes, his investigations nonetheless led him to uncover hints of Skaven presence in the ruins of what could be an ancient and even mythical Elven temple: Athel Lithri.<br/><br/>Whatever it is that the Pactsworn plan to do with that temple, it can't be anything good. Time for our Heroes to take a peek and hopefully put a swift end to any verminous schemes going on there.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New upcoming Premium Hero Cosmetics: The Mythical Masquerade</div>Just in time for the new adventure, Lohner got a glorious shipment of new outfits and hats, all inspired by some of the most iconic characters from Warhammer Fantasy!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/a4da60a97b53fbeb2f5abef42d72b992ad60d651.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bardin and Kruber get to pair up as an iconic duo, wearing vestments inspired by <b>Gotrek Gurnisson and Felix Jaeger!</b> These hero skins and hats are equipable on Bardin’s <b>Slayer career</b> and Kruber’s <b>Mercenary career,</b> respectively.<br/></li><li> Proving that he ALSO can sport a magnificent beard, the imposing <b>Count Boris Todbringer-inspired</b> hero skin and hat are equipable by Saltzpyre’s <b>Bounty Hunter career.</b><br/></li><li> Delving into mysticism, Kerillian has access to an outfit inspired by <b>Naieth the Prophetess,</b> equipable on <b>all of Kerillian’s careers.</b><br/></li><li> With a sudden propensity for walking around with a cup of wine (at least, we think it’s wine!), Sienna gets a new regal look with this armour inspired by <b>Isabella Von Carstein.</b> This hero skin and hat are equipable on her <b>Pyromancer and Necromancer careers.</b></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omens of Destruction - Meet Arbaal the Undefeated</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647306053</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8b765e7deb199e0faab1cad3805d439784dd39c8.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings, Total War community!<br/><br/>Welcome to our next instalment of the Omens of Destruction blog series.<br/><br/>He’s the ultimate Chaos Warrior, one of the most ferocious of Khorne’s mortal servants who has sent untold thousands of skulls to the Brass Citadel with the blade of his axe. Undefeated for millennia, the Destroyer of Khorne is coming to WARHAMMER III in a storm of fury and destruction.<br/><br/>Introducing....<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 ARBAAL THE UNDEFEATED 👈</div><br/><br/>Now that you've been formally introduced, keep an eye on our community channels linked below for some extra little info about Arbaal, including his starting position and Lord select screen!<br/><br/>Next week we'll be getting ready to krump some heads with Gorbad, gits! Stay tuned.<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus Spotlight - Victor Saltzpyre &amp; Packmaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/4490747434954130758</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn!</div> <br/>Welcome to the <b>fourth</b> out of five weekends of the Versus Spotlight events. Every week, we’ll take a closer look at one of the Ubersreik 5 and one of the Pactsworn Specials. Unlock unique time-limited rewards, learn more about the spotlight Hero and Skaven, and do it all while having fun. This week's spotlight will be on good ol' One Eye <b>Saltzpyre</b> and the cruel <b>Packmaster!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Previous Spotlight's Rewards</div><b>An update on the way the rewards are handed out:</b><br/>Due to feedback from the community, as well as some technical issues on our end regarding this, we've decided to change how rewards for the Spotlight are given out.<br/><br/><b>All rewards for the spotlight will now be earned upon completion of the kill counter.</b> That means all of the currency, portrait frames and Hero poses will be unlocked for the community (alongside the Pactsworn skin, as before). <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/19dc4fb35544431416ee2b9e8fdf27660a633542.png"/><br/><b>This change is retroactive and will also affect the rewards of the first weeks of the spotlights.</b><br/><br/>The rewards for the previous spotlight have just been delivered, so check your inventory! As a note, the Hero Pose might take a few restarts before it applies properly to your account. Sorry about that!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">This Week's Rewards</div>There are unique rewards to unlock weekly, all earned by the community as a whole through completion of the Kill-Counter. There are currency rewards, portrait frames, skins, and weapon poses to be earned.<br/><br/>Saltzpyre &amp; Packmaster Spotlight rewards will be earnable <b>between December 5 - December 8.</b> All rewards will be granted the following week.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Kill-Counter</div>Rally together as community to <b>eliminate Heroes</b> in Versus to complete the <b>Kill-counter</b>. If the community completes the counter, you will all unlock:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>An exclusive skin for the Packmaster!</b><br/></li><li> <b>120 shillings.</b><br/></li><li> <b>100 Helmgart Sellsword Marks.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A brand new Portrait frame.</b><br/></li><li> <b>A Hero Pose for Saltzpyre!</b></li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/94aaeb04ac74619e028983a5fbc3b90728422f8d.png"/><br/><br/>Since all rewards are tied to the kill tracker, and since you've all been smashing through every target so far, we've decided to up the ante and increase the target kills from 40K Hero kills to 250K! Get crackin', players, that's a lot of Heroes to kill.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/214b4f4b445b197bd3f636e2f464888b7e325464.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Victor Saltzpyre</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/89d0e4175586a7e1fae30ac1d0d28aa379dda7df.png"/><br/>For Victor, life has ever been a never-ending battle against heresy and destruction – the beleaguered Reikland is but a vaster stage upon which to strut his hour. Though it is hardly in Victor’s nature to trust such outcasts as are his companions in these dark days, he accepts that righteous work can sometimes be accomplished by stained souls and soiled hands.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about Victor Saltzpyre here!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Packmaster</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/dc614ed00590381e3c2746c9e78af6084dcc48bb.png"/><br/>The Packmasters of Clan Moulder excel in driving packs of ravening beasts into battle, but in the crush of the swarm they favour other tactics. Clan Moulder is ever seeking new subjects to further its vile breeding experiments, and every Packmaster covets the bounty paid for a particularly noteworthy prize.<br/><br/><b>Learn more about the Packmaster here!</b>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 16:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Golgfag Gameplay Showcase</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647305592</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Loud, Boastful, In-charge.<br/><br/>Become the greatest Mercenary and shape the outcome of conflicts across the world as Golgfag Maneater 👹<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AUGNU2wx0zw?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
