<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>WE ARE NOW 2 MILLION PLAYERS!!!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4599952112536595143</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Dear Marines, we made it!</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">There are now 2 million players on <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>.</div><br/>This incredible milestone makes us proud and grateful. <br/>This was only possible thanks to YOU 🫵 the players, and all the love and support you've been sending towards us!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fb86648f368ae84122b3fdb58e9f88fe2fd5827f.png"/><br/><br/>Please believe us when we say we're reading all of your feedback with great attention. It takes time because of the amount of messages we have to deal with, obviously. But we see and hear you.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">A first patch will arrive soon enough!</div><br/>We are also completely aware of the differents bugs you've been encountering. We're working hard to fix them. It will include:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ultra Wide Support<br/></li><li> Private PVE lobbies<br/></li><li> Sparring area</li></ul>If you encounter a bug, report it on Focus Entertainment's new community platform!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Thank you to the 2 million Brothers and Sisters out there, protecting the Imperium together. 💙</div><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on 6.0 and Interim Patches - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4615714711227038997</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Greetings folks!<br/> <br/>Back in June I sat down with Rich, Sean and Victor from the WARHAMMER III development team to share some juicy new details on what's coming to the game in the next DLC, as well as our approach to interim patches coming between now and the next DLC's arrival. In case you've been living under an Ogre-sized rock these past couple of months, you can check it out right here.<br/> <br/>Recently I hopped back on the sofa to chat with Rich and Sean, plus Design Director Mitch Heastie, to chat more about what's coming in 6.0 get some insight on what sort of content you can also expect to see in our future interim patches.<br/> <br/>Allow your eyes to absorb it here:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LTHkI2GSVJw?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>As with last time, this is a pretty new format for us, so please do share your thoughts with us along with any suggestions on what you'd like to see more of next time!<br/><br/>You can also head over to the official Discord server and the CA Community to share your hopes and dreams regarding future refreshes and reworks. Who knows, maybe Mitch will agree with you and make some magic happen!<br/><br/>We aim to be back with more news on our next major patch, 5.3, towards the end of October, so until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— <i>Steve // Senior Community Manager</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.2.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4615714711226603571</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/8389698d4a6f5d79efcf7d5ba26360450631d106.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>We’ve just rolled out Hotfix 5.2.3 which brings a pretty hefty number of fixes and tweaks to the game.<br/><br/>Let's see what we've got today:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h2">GENERAL</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tweaked the porthole lighting in both campaign and battle to eliminate a slight red hue caused by sunlight. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a rare crash where a previously resolved dilemma remained in the event feed, causing the game to crash if the related character died later in the campaign.<br/></li><li> Fixed a freeze/crash that occurred when creating more than 254 settlements to one of the old ones with Nakai. <br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when disbanding a unit from a Waaagh army.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">​GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where characters occasionally moved large distances after razing settlements, resulting in them being in different regions than the one they just razed. Now, after razing, an attacking army will move away one hex beyond the zone of control radius, while a surviving army will move three hexes away from the settlement. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where playing as Slaanesh and using the ‘Pleasure Hunt’ pleasurable activity could sometimes apply its effects multiple times. <br/></li><li> The Star-Metal Talons upgrade in Ikit Claw's Forbidden Workshop no longer grants vanguard deployment to Warp Grinder units, as they already have this attribute. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where effects providing immunity or damage resistance to attrition also affected desertion, such as in cases of bankruptcy. <br/></li><li> The Elector Count of Hochland position no longer provides a movement range bonus twice.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">​ABILITIES/SKILLS/TRAITS</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hero units that join Cathay caravans will now have spells or abilities where appropriate. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where upgrading a Chaos Sorcerer (Death) to a Nurgle Chaos Sorcerer (Death) would result in gaining the wrong trait. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some effects meant for Nurgle characters were incorrectly applied to the Slaanesh Chaos Sorcerer.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ANCILLARIES</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​The Experimental Explosive item gained from Cathay caravans can now be transferred to other characters. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">​TECH TREE</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where researching the ‘Grand Throne Chamber’ technology would unlock the Dwarf Lord ‘Mikael Leadstrong,’ who is meant to be obtained through legendary grudges. </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">RECRUITMENT</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​The effects of different levels of province control no longer impact recruitment costs for Tomb Kings, as they do not incur recruitment costs. <br/></li><li> Character recruitment from buildings like The Deeps &amp; Gardens of Morr was overriding normal character recruitment. Now, only the recruitment option with the highest lord rank will be displayed.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">MISSIONS/VICTORY CONDITIONS </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where some missions would double their settlement count when reloading saves. </li></ul>​<br/><div class="bb_h3">CAMPAIGN UI/UX </div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Harmony effects on buildings would display as a negative value when adding Yin. <br/></li><li> Added help page buttons to the Nurgle Plagues and Tamurkhan's Chieftains panels. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where players couldn't undo spent skill points for heroes. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Spices UI panel displayed landmarks alongside resource buildings at the Fortress of Dawn. <br/></li><li> Removed text references in the help pages to Chaos factions automatically declaring war to align with the intended design. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the help pages would open behind the Bloodlines panel when playing as Vampire Counts. <br/></li><li> Fixed a display issue with army zone of control where old VFX instances remained after moving an army in ambush stance. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the scroll position in the Allied Recruitment panel would reset when selecting a unit from an outpost as the first unit to be recruited; the scroll now stays in its correct position after selecting a unit, improving the recruitment flow. <br/></li><li> Clicking on the pin of a recruitable unit card should now correctly pin/unpin the card. <br/></li><li> Tweaked the entry in the effect lists of the Item Gained event popup to resolve occasional text bleeding issues in the UI. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Athel Loren landmark buildings did not display the landmark icon or tooltip. <br/></li><li> Resolved an issue where clicking on Pieces of Eight mission scrolls as the Vampire Coast incorrectly navigated to the Missions panel. The scrolls now correctly direct players to the Pieces of Eight panel, ensuring smoother navigation during treasure hunts.</li></ul>​<div class="bb_h3">CAMPAIGN ENVIRONMENT</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue on the campaign map where a horse in the Tor Saroir region (Averlorn start position) was clipping through an altar, improving visual consistency in the area. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div> <br/><div class="bb_h3">​GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where High Elf towers and some of the walls behind them would disappear after being destroyed in siege battles, while still functioning as intact barriers. Towers now leave rubble behind, and walls remain visible post-destruction. <br/><i><b>DEV NOTE:</b> We are aware of ongoing related issues with other High Elves siege map destruction and are continuing to investigate. </i><br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the enemy reinforcements displayed in the Event Message did not match those shown in the Objectives Panel for the Battle for the Armour of Glimril Scales quest battle. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Altar of Spawns settlement was not using the Norsca minor settlement battle map.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">​BATTLE AI</div>​<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The AI is now less likely to use the General unit for solo harassment or outflanking. <br/></li><li> The AI-controlled Lord will no longer withdraw when ambushed if it has a good chance of winning. <br/></li><li> Fixed pathfinding on certain river maps to prevent the AI from attempting to cross through the water. <br/></li><li> Fixed a rare bug where enemy units were routing toward the player's units. <br/></li><li> Now, the reinforcements AI will join the fight more quickly if the main army is engaged in melee. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the AI was attempting to go to the river while the enemy was already on the same side. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the defending AI was constantly reforming in land battles. <br/></li><li> Now, the AI will attempt to synchronize the river assault groups based on the player’s positioning when passing through different crossings.<br/><i><b>DEV NOTE:</b> Previously, if the player was defending at only one location, the AI would lose units while those crossing at another location did not engage in combat. Now, the first group will wait until the second group crosses the river, allowing them to attack together.</i></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS GENERAL / ANIMATIONS</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Razorgor would move too far from the chariot during one of the attack animations. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Daemon Prince of Khorne was missing one of the weapons during flying attack animations. <br/></li><li> Hans Valhirsson, the ghost dwarf, is no longer allowed to appear in ranked armies. <br/></li><li> Resolved an issue where parts of the Reiksguard and Empire Knights' helmets would disappear when viewed from behind at different levels of detail (LODs) during battles. <br/></li><li> Resolved an issue with the High Elf Princess's torso and arm armor textures distorting at certain LOD, ensuring consistent visual quality at different camera distances. <br/></li><li> Fixed the missing arm and blackened cape of High Queen Khalida at LOD3 and LOD4 levels. <br/></li><li> Fixed the visual problems with the leg armor of the Steed of Slaanesh model at different LODs. <br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Lahmian Vampire Lord's head texture does not appear correctly at certain LOD levels.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ENVIRONMENT</div>​<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Addressed several visual issues, including missing objects, texture problems, floating objects on the Badlands Wastelands map and Ice Witch Mountains – Kislev Mountains map, misplaced assets in the Haunted Forest, Dragon River Run, Black Ark, and pixelated fallen trees on the Baron’s Bluff map, among others. <br/></li><li> Moved certain objects out of the playable area on the Parched Pass - Southlands Mountains map to align with the intended design. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where an ogre camp battle map would occasionally load incorrectly in the Badlands marsh area of the campaign map. <br/></li><li> Fixed a lighting issue in the Battle of the Great Hall of Greasus. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where ground units could be deployed mid-air on the Karak Azgaraz – Dwarfs map. <br/></li><li> Fixed camera collision issues with certain assets, including those in multiplayer maps.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">​BATTLE UI/UX</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ​The unit card for 'The Big One' in Thorek Ironbrow's quest battle, 'Klad Brakak,' is now correct. <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Unit Info UI element would not appear during replays if it had been disabled during the actual battle; players can now toggle unit details in replays, so they are no longer stuck with the settings from the most recent battle.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">MULTIPLAYER</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the battle difficulty selected in the multiplayer campaign lobby would change by one tier for each player when the campaign started. <br/></li><li> It is no longer possible to issue orders to a military force while a player is selecting a new general for the orphaned army.</li></ul><hr/><br/><br/>As always, thanks for your bug reports and feedback. If you run into any new issues after updating to 5.2.3 please report them over in our dedicated sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/><b>—The <i>Total War</i> Team</b><br/><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #47 (1.4.13) Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4567301015235942240</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/86354910ba87be04246f7a5b371c85eda5573c13.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo everyone, </div><br/>Hotfix #47 (aka 1.4.13) is now live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms. You can find the notes below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug fixes &amp; changes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the UI notification for completed penances could be displayed in the Mourningstar even in cases where there was no completed penance reward to redeem at Hestia’s Shrine Penitentax.</li><li>Fixed a rare crash which could happen when failing to retrieve the information for the latest News.</li><li>Fixed several instances where undefined text would be displayed in Blessing descriptions.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Krourk Mk IIId Blast Goggles” Ogryn headgear cosmetic would hide the eyebrows of the character when equipped.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Krieg Greatcoat (Marked by Faith)” Zealot upperbody cosmetic would fail to be correctly rendered in the area around the fingers. </li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Hadron’s Shrine of the Omnissiah is Under Renovation</div><br/>As you can see Hadron workshop is undergoing renovation, but our grumpy Tech-priestess still does weapon maintenance under the counter. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Updates to Weapon Blessing Descriptions</div><br/>We performed a pass on the descriptions of several Blessings, making sure that the information displayed was correct and aligned to their actual gameplay effect. <b>There will be no changes to the gameplay effects of the affected Blessings. </b>There are visual changes only.<br/><br/>We also added some additional text to further detail the mechanics of some Blessings.<br/><br/><b>Additional Note:</b> <i>The values in the descriptions will be updated for all languages. However some additional explanatory text will be only present in English for this hotfix (1.4.13). This additional text will be added for all languages in the Unlocked and Loaded update this month.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Blessings applying Brittleness on enemies</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The shown debuff value for each stack of Brittleness has been changed to 2.5%, instead of 5%. This is a presentation change only however, as the game was already using 2.5% for the actual gameplay effect.</li></ul><li><b>Can Opener:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the max stacks.</li><li>Fixed the displayed Brittleness value.</li></ul><li><b>Shattering Impact:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the max stacks.</li><li>Fixed the displayed Brittleness value.</li></ul><li><b>Thunderous:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the max stacks.</li><li>Fixed the displayed Brittleness value.</li></ul><li><b>Rending Shockwave:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the max stacks.</li><li>Fixed the displayed Brittleness value.</li></ul><li><b>Falter:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the bonus Impact damage.</li></ul><li><b>Gets Hot!:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the damage increase applied on Critical Hits.</li></ul><li><b>Headhunter (for Recon Lasguns only):</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed the displayed Critical Hit chance bonus:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tier 1: 3.5%, from 2%</li><li>Tier 2: 4%, from 3%</li><li>Tier 3: 4.5%, from 4%.</li></ul></ul><li><b>Punishing Salvo:</b> </li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Corrected the text to specify that the Bonus from this Blessing is applied also on the second shot, in addition to the third and fourth.</li></ul><li><b>Sustained Fire:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Corrected the text to specify that the Bonus from this Blessing is applied also on the second shot, in addition to the third and fourth.</li></ul><li><b>Haymaker:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Updated the text to include that other “on kill” effects are not triggered on Instakill. </li></ul><li><b>Run 'n' Gun:</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added details about the Spread reduction. </li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> For the Assault Shotgun, the description will show a reduction of weapon Spread of 10% that will be added in the Unlocked and Loaded update.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2 is now available!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6300059162639165425</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2"><b>Great news Brothers! Space Marine 2 is OUT for all!</b></div><br/>The fates have been woven so that on the ninth day of the ninth month of 2024, Lieutenant Titus will return to battle against the forces of darkness... <b>The day has come. </b><br/><br/>Years of passion, dedication, and hard work have gone into the creation of this game. We can't wait to see you all defend the Imperium as one of humanity’s strongest warriors, against the enemies of the Imperium! ⭐<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Prepare for War With the Launch Trailer!</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5zcJKGdb0a8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>Across all modes, embody the brutality and superhuman skill of a Space Marine as you fight against the worst the galaxy has to offer. Smash xenos skulls in close combat with superhuman strength and a flesh-sundering chainsword.<br/><br/>Enjoy the campaign alone or with friends as every mode is fully co-op enabled, with customisable characters for PvE missions and PvP battles that can be upgraded as you play. <br/><br/>More content is also on the way with additional missions, new enemies, new weapons, and much more now in development for post-launch support! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">More details in our post-launch roadmap below.</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><br/>A first update will come this week. It should fix: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Multiple crash fixes (start of the game, 1st cutscene crash, etc...) <br/></li><li> Optimized CPU usage<br/></li><li> Server improvements <br/></li><li> Render bug improvements</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">To stay informed about the latest news</div> <br/>Focus Entertainment's new community platform is out!<br/><br/>Join <b>Focus Together</b> and get ready to:<br/><br/><br/><a class="bb_link" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Flogin.focus-entmt.com%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fec44739cc231ee0e0f0b4631eb2aa240e1fea0f.png"/></a><br/>💬 Shape your own gaming experience<br/>⭐ Win points and exclusive rewards<br/>👾 Earn unique badges, titles and avatars<br/>🤝 Contribute to our new games development<br/><br/>__________<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2"><b>A love letter to the license, and to the fans.</b></div><br/>Thirteen years ago, <i>Space Marine</i> was released, and ever since, fans have been eagerly awaiting a sequel. It has been an incredible honor for us at Saber Interactive, Games Workshop, and Focus Entertainment to be part of this amazing project. We poured our hearts into it, striving to create an experience that would make fans proud and fill them with wonder. Trust us when we say we cannot wait to hear your feedback and see you have fun crushing heretics, or emptying your magazine with (or on??) your most loyal Brothers.<br/><br/>Obviously, none of this would have been possible without the tireless support from the fans. You've been there since the announcement and we are grateful for that. Because of your enthusiasm and your passion, the whole process was incredibly rewarding. <br/><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> is now in your hands. We sincerely hope you will love it. 💙<br/><br/>With love, for the Emperor.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f828b535b505aee502217168ab71a2ddf89b9077.png"/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
