<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 will be playable at Gamescom!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/6300059162638181237</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines! 🗡️</div><br/>We’re two weeks away from the launch of Space Marine 2! And as always, we’d like to thank you for your continuous support,<b> as the Collector’s Edition is now completely sold out!</b><br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h3">Take a closer look at the latest trailer!</div></b><br/>A brand new trailer has been revealed during Gamescom. You can watch <b>the trailer</b> below! <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_DchUEbEAt8?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/>And since we’re talking about Gamescom, we have some great news for you! <b>The game will be playable during the entirety of the event at the Xbox and AMD booths</b>, so you can give yourself a little preview of what crushing Tyranids feels like before the release!<br/><br/>We see every single one of your messages, we’re happy to see that you are hyped as much as we are!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/bc282f09092bbd0dc6853692bad04d9537da31aa.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/785f3bf07c277de994f893f743e39505fb7cff5b.jpg"/><br/><br/>Until then, do not forget to prepare for your eternal service, Brothers.<br/><br/>For the Emperor! ⚔️]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 5.2 LIVE NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/6077130981080185621</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/20ee96c20a979eec1b1672fae388eda28764b63d.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings!<br/><br/>Patch 5.2.0 is here, bringing a wealth of new content to Total War: WARHAMMER III. This update is the first to include some little "refreshes" of legacy content, as detailed in Mitch's 5.2 dev blog we shared last week.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">📜 Patch 5.2 Dev Blog</div><br/><br/>This patch also includes a number of bug fixes and quality-of-life improvements, including a rework of the definitions for our rollback builds on Steam, which will make it easier to identify and select the version you need, should you need it.<br/><br/>Here’s a glimpse of what’s new:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A new feature for the Dwarfs: The Deeps<br/></li><li>A rework of the Chaos Cult feature<br/></li><li>A new small 'global' feature: Unusual Locations <br/></li><li>An update to the Cathay's Ivory Road feature</li></ul><br/>To dive in to the nitty-gritty, head here:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">📜 Patch Notes 5.2.0</div><br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Blog - Versus Open Beta Test</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/6716642128543606899</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes and Pactsworn,</div><br/>Hi my name is <b>Joakim Setterberg</b> and I’m the Design Director on Vermintide 2. In this devblog I want to talk about Versus’ upcoming <b>Beta August Test</b> - or BAT - coming August 21st. With the BAT we’re wrapping up most of the larger systems and features of the core game mode. With a few exceptions, our main focus up to release will be to work with surrounding systems and refining the content, to polish the Versus experience and, to quote the team, <i>“fix the jank”</i>.<br/><br/>First, a note on feedback. <b>For every test we do we collect as much of your feedback as possible to find out what we can improve and fix.</b> We sort it, rank it, and talk about what we want to accomplish for the next test. Sometimes there’s a straight-forward way to solve a problem or to implement a suggestion, but other times we’ll go in a slightly different direction, if we believe a problem lies elsewhere. That takes us to our two big features we’re introducing for the BAT: the <b>Pactsworn Horde ability</b> and <b>matchmaking</b>.<br/><br/>Feedback from the last test, the RAT, showed that you wanted something more for the Pactsworn gameplay - like abilities or talents. We also saw requests for notifications when director controlled Hordes were about to spawn, or calls to introduce a Pactsworn special with horde summoning as a singular purpose. These were good requests, but we felt that the Pactsworn side would play even stronger if Hordes were more integrated in active player combat, rather than being played reactive. In the finest Clan Moulder tradition <i>we stitched everything together</i>.<br/><br/><b>The Horde ability gives all Pactsworn specials a way to summon a small Horde on their own,</b> introducing a tactical element to the gameplay loop. This means that Packmasters can summon cover-kin to blend in for sneaky charges, Ratling Gunners can distract Heroes with melee fodder before laying down fire, or the team can sync up and trigger all Hordes at the same time and overwhelm the opposition. <b>The Horde ability is on a timed cooldown,</b> which decreases faster with successful attacks with your current Pactsworn special and carries over between deaths.<br/>We are excited to see how you interact with this new feature and hear what you think about it, looking forward to your feedback on this one.<br/><br/>A bit trickier were various feedback regarding Pactsworn or Hero balancing, speed running, match quitters and a general feeling of unfairness: all valid points, which we’ll be tackling moving forwards, but this also highlighted one big underlying issue: <b>the lack of matchmaking.</b> In the Alphas there were no guardrails preventing (for instance) solo queuing new players to meet an experienced four-stack, meaning that the experience could vary wildly from session to session. We believe that some of the “unbalanced experience” feedback may originate from this.<br/><br/>For the Beta, we’ve opted to <b>rework our current matchmaking system.</b> It's always been in our mind to improve it as much as possible, and after hearing your feedback from the Alphas we decided to go with a new solution for Versus. The new system should, on average, result in <b>lower queue times,</b> finding servers closer to you (resulting in <b>lower latency</b>), and <b>more even games</b> (for example, by trying to pair together premade groups). It will also allow us to more easily monitor the matchmaking in real-time and act quicker if we notice that something isn't working as we intended.<br/><br/>It won’t stop variously skilled players from meeting up occasionally, but at least the system should be able to favour other match setups. We hope that this will lead to more balanced and fun games, as well as lay a better foundation for future feedback.<br/><br/>On the usability side <b>we are adding gamepad support</b> for those who enjoy button mashing over keyboard smashing. Now that we are rounding up the core feature set we can finalize button assignments and focus on input tweaking to bring the controller experience up to par.<br/><br/>On the quality of life, balancing and bug fixes side there’s a number of things that are changed since the RAT. Some highlights include:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> We’ve updated the <b>Pactsworn UI</b> to display more useful information.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enemy healthbars now also display stuff like <b>remaining Wounds</b> and shows <b>regular and temporary HP</b> as separate.<br/></li><li> Your <b>Pactsworn’s abilities</b> and moves are all displayed in the HUD and it also shows <b>their cooldowns.</b><br/></li><li> <b>Allies </b>now have their <b>names and respawn timers</b> shown above their heads, hopefully making teamwork easier.</li></ul></li><li> We have <b>moved all healing supplies</b> to be more prominent on each level’s main path. By becoming easy to see “hot spots”, we should be able to create even more interesting and intense scenarios, inviting the Pactsworn to use them for ambushes.<br/></li><li> Based on prior test feedback we’ve made the <b>Bile Troll a bit slower</b> and less twitchy, but also gave him the ability to <b>hold his vomit attack</b> to aim it better before launching it.<br/></li><li> <b>Buffed the Ratling Gunner</b> by speeding up his ramp up and reload times as well as improving his effective range.<br/></li><li> <b>Nerfed the Globadier slightly</b> by making the initial damage of a globe lower but making that damage ramp up dramatically over time. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Mindlessly throwing globes won’t be as effective anymore, but catching unfortunate Heroes in a bad spot will create just as much chaos as before.</li></ul></li><li> <b>Tweaked some objectives on Against the Grain</b> to deter speedrunning and running ahead.<br/></li><li> <b>Tweaked the VFX for the Warpfire Thrower and Globadier.</b> On top of looking better, these should be easier to read in first person and more accurately show the actual area of effect.</li></ul>For all of these features we are of course looking for further testing and feedback.<br/><br/>After the BAT ends, we aim to do at least one more Beta test focusing on some final systems and whatever adjustments come from the feedback we receive during this test. We unfortunately can’t give any details on what it’ll contain at this time, but we’ll tell you guys more when we get there.<br/><br/><i>On behalf of the entire Vermintide team, thank you for helping shape Versus into something great. See you in a BAT!</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datascrape XVIIa/fxi: “Awakening” - Admonition Missive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/6781944323126178761</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b348bb29748c2c5c290a0d8ff0f3a7335dfeb765.jpg"/><br/><br/>https://youtu.be/Sk-xRz9eAqc <br/><br/><b>Acquisition Agent: Wyrmwood 78<br/><br/>Veracity Rating: 12-Alpha<br/><br/>Subject: [REDACTED]<br/><br/>Action: Monitor<br/><br/>Cross-reference: “Urmal”, [REDACTED], [REDACTED]<br/><br/>Entry Begins:</b><br/><br/><i>Falter not, wither not.</i><br/><br/>Those words have lodged firmly in my mind. There have been endless words and fanatical ramblings – enough to last several lifetimes – and most are just background noise. That statement, though… it carries weight. Enforced inactivity leads to a degradation of body and mind and so I must keep both active. The first comes with physical recovery. The other will hopefully come from committing some of my myriad thoughts to this journal.<br/><br/>How long have I been here? Days, certainly. Weeks, perhaps. Months? Possibly. I no longer know. There has been much pain, but I know that pain must be endured so that the body may be reshaped and that is what is happening. There is pain, at times excruciating, but I endure. I must endure. Because if I don’t, who will there be left to dole out retribution for my loss? Rodin’s death at the hands of the warband will not go unpunished and must be addressed. I swear it.<br/><br/>I have so many questions that have no answers. Who brought me here? Why was I spared when he was not? What happens next? All I seem to have are questions and time to think about them. What is time, really? When you get down to it, I mean. Is it even a real thing? Is it just a construct of a social system that has an obsession with its own mortality? What other species counts down the seconds to its own oblivion in the way that the Imperium of Mankind does? Such limited scope. Such narrow vision. Entropy is an inevitability: why bother wasting an existence waiting for it when you could be living?<br/><br/>It seems I have a second chance, including the opportunity to think and come out with the same foolish rhetoric of my new companions.<br/><br/>It’s ridiculous. I’m a fighter. A soldier. I’m no orator or scribe given to flights of fancy. But things change. People change. I should be dead, but I am not. They talk to me earnestly of the Grandfather’s gift, of what I will become to them, but I fail to see the appeal. These people brought me here and I will play their game. For now, at least, we are travelling the same way, flotsam and jetsam borne ever-onward by the unrelenting tide of time.<br/><br/>There are choices ahead but I will not be distracted from my core objectives. I will avenge my brother and I will pay my debt to these people. Once those duties are discharged, what happens next remains to be seen. Thoughts of the way forward don’t burden me, neither am I afraid of them. He always said to me that there was no fear that cannot be overcome, no belief that cannot be challenged, no hope that cannot be dissolved in the acidic bile of truth. No, there is no fear.<br/><br/>There is something, though. Trepidation, anticipation, excitement… the breath you draw before you dive, not knowing if you’re going to surface after you hit the water. The step off the cliff-edge, trusting that the fall is not going to smash your body to smithereens. The thrill of continued existence against all the odds. It’s invigorating and gives me strength and purpose to do what must be done.<br/><br/>I have already survived against all likelihood. I will endure and I shall not falter. My brother, you will not be forgotten.<br/><br/><i>Falter not, wither not.</i><br/><br/>Take a breath and jump.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herald of Admonition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/6781944323126122350</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0151e31e0dfa2899977ea659435a5e4f3ed2c68b.png"/><br/>Rolling blackouts are plaguing sectors of the hive. Worse, we’ve heard reports of someone, or something lurking in the darkness. We need devoted rejects to get down there and sort this mess out.<br/><br/>Play and complete missions with a new Special Condition, “Terror in the Dark” to earn rewards. This condition will only be available during the event!<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, August 15 and run until Thursday, August 29. The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/><i>Note: This event is only available on the normal board on 3/4/5 difficulties (regular malice, heresy and damnation).</i><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
