<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Havoc Game Mode - Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4476108195413098968</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hello Everyone,</div><br/>We’ve long seen the comments from players saying they want more of a challenge from Darktide. Players would like to continually challenge themselves and improve their skills. You want to face the horrors of the tide.<br/><br/>We’re excited to announce the next major game feature we have been working on for Darktide: <b>Havoc</b>.<br/><br/>If you’re a player who relishes overcoming obstacles and seeks to measure and improve your abilities, then Havoc has been crafted specifically for you.<br/><br/>This dev blog is an introduction to Havoc and to answer initial questions. We’re still performing tests for it, and we’ll announce a release date as soon as we are confident! We will be following this dev blog up with another Q&amp;A, similar to what we did with Itemization.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">What is Havoc?</div>Commissar Dukane and the Moebian 53rd Steelheads have arrived on Atoma, keen to prove their mettle and quash this uprising. Havoc missions represent Dukane’s influence on the war for Tertium. She believes in firm, swift, decisive action, striking at the heart of the traitor forces and ensuring each mission takes the maximum toll on the enemy.<br/><br/>An uncompromising taskmaster, she demands the best from all her charges, rewarding those she deems worthy with yet more perilous missions, or as she might say, opportunities for greatness.<br/><br/>Let’s break this down further.<br/><br/>Havoc is a new tiered progression system we have been working on for Trust Level 30 players.* This system will consist of different levels, known as Order Levels. There will be 40 Order Levels in total for Havoc.<br/><br/>Each Order Level will incrementally increase in difficulty, with increasing negative modifiers and varying mutators. Players won’t only face increased hordes or enemies, they’ll also encounter 4 brand new mutators, including one the community has recently encountered: the Infected 21st Moebians.<br/><br/>** Only Trust Level 30 players will be able to access Havoc.<br/><br/>A player’s Havoc Rank is the highest level they’ve reached and successfully completed in Havoc.<br/><br/>A Havoc Order is the current mission a player is facing. Each Havoc Order is unique and personal to the player in terms of what mission and what mutators.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Key Features of Havoc</div><div class="bb_h2">1. Tiered Challenges</div><br/>There will be 40 Havoc Order levels for players to progress through for Havoc. With each level missions will become incrementally more difficult, allowing players to gauge their skill progression. To unlock Havoc, players must first complete an Auric or Non-Auric Maelstrom mission.<br/><br/>For each Order level, more negative modifiers are introduced. This increase is additive, meaning the previous modifiers will carry over to the next Havoc Order, plus any new ones on top of it. For example, if an Order level 1 reduces toughness regeneration, then Order level 2 will reduce toughness regeneration and another negative modifier on top of it. So on, and so forth until Order level 40 provides the most challenging content in the game.<br/><br/>A player will need to beat an Order level once in order to progress to the next Order level. A player will have 3 attempts to beat a Havoc Order level before being demoted down one Order level.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">2. Personalised and Dynamic Havoc Orders</div><br/>While the modifiers are pre-defined for each Havoc Order, the mission and mutators applied to each order level will be unique and randomized for each player. This means Order Level 1 for one player will not look the same as a level 1 Order for another player.<br/><br/>If a player fails to complete the Havoc Order after an attempt, the player can continue to attempt the same unique mission and mutator combination. However, the enemies and spawns will appear in different places throughout the mission, which brings a level of variety and unpredictability so no two runs are the same.<br/><br/>As mentioned above, players will have 3 attempts per Order Level before being demoted one level.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">3. Fluid Ranking System</div><br/>Havoc will update a player’s Order Rank on a weekly basis. If a player was unable to complete their Havoc Order before Havoc is updated for the week, they’ll remain at the same Havoc Order. But they’ll have a different mission and mutator combo to attempt.<br/><br/>If a player does not succeed in progressing forward in any Order Levels during the week, they will be decayed 1 Havoc Order the following week.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">4. Cooperative Gameplay</div><br/>Players are not alone in their journey. Havoc encourages inviting friends to help progress through the Havoc Ranks together. While using the Party Finder to form a team, players will choose which friends’ Havoc Order to challenge together. The only requirement is to be at least level 30. If players form a group, it doesn’t matter if one friend is Havoc Rank 1 and the others are Havoc Rank 20. They can all play together.<br/><br/>For example’s sake, let’s say we had a group of four players: Player A (Havoc Rank 20), Player B (Havoc Rank 19), Player C (Havoc Rank 19), Player D (Havoc Rank 1).<br/><br/>If those players formed a group and successfully beat Player A’s specific Havoc Order 21, at the end of the mission, all of the players will have a new Havoc Rank of 21. However, those players’ Havoc Order (aka the personal mission currently available to them in Havoc) will not change until the following week.<br/><br/>The following week, all players will be Havoc Rank 21 and they’ll have a Havoc Order level 22 to complete.<br/><br/>Players will always be promoted the following week based on their highest completed Havoc Order level the week prior. In this example, even though Player D started at Havoc Order 1, they are brought up to Havoc Rank 21 since this is the highest difficulty they completed the previous week .<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">5. Party Finder Integration</div><br/>One of the reasons we wanted to introduce the Party Finder was specifically for Havoc. Because the difficulty is so high, it wouldn’t work to simply Quick Play into a Havoc mission. Because of the varying combinations of mutators and missions, and the increasing difficulty, players will want to prepare their talents and weapons based on the challenge they’re facing. Using Quick Play would not allow players to properly prepare for the challenge.<br/><br/>There will be a separate section in the Party Finder for players to create and join Havoc parties. You can create a party based on your own Havoc Order or join others. If friends are forming a party together, they’ll need to choose which player’s Havoc Order they’d like to attempt together.<br/><br/>Again, anyone can join any party regardless of their own Havoc Rank or the current level of their Havoc Order, so long as they’re Trust Level 30.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Missions, Mutators and Conditions</div>When Havoc is launched, it’ll have 8 missions in the mission pool. These were chosen based on a few criteria, like zone, mission type, win rate in upper difficulties, etc. Operations (like Rolling Steel) are not planned to be a part of this rotating mission pool at this time, due to them being different in nature to our other missions.<br/><br/>Havoc will introduce 4 bespoke mutators which players will only find in Havoc. Havoc Order levels will be able to have up to 2 mutators active at one time. The community has already encountered one of these during the latest event: the Infected 21st Moebians. We think you’ll enjoy the other ones we have planned. We’re going to keep them as a surprise for now and share them closer to release.<br/><br/>Conditions will also be a part of the mix for possible Order levels for players to tackle. However, not every Order level will include a condition. It’ll be more spread out, with a condition being present ~5 Order levels. This includes Lights Out, Ventilation Purge and Tox Gas. (Note: Ogryns soon will no longer be suffering from the dark.)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Future Content and Updates</div>In the future, we’ll rotate the missions that are available for Havoc. Also, any time a new mission is added in an update, it will enter the mission pool. (As mentioned above, Operations are not planned to be a part of this rotation.)<br/><br/>We also plan to add more mutators over time for Havoc. So let us know if you have any ideas that you’d like to see in the future.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Rewards for the Brave</div>You might be wondering, how will players be rewarded? Players will receive materials and Mastery XP. There will also be a cache based on your weekly progress within Havoc, where players can earn extra Plasteel and Diamantine.<br/><br/>Beyond materials, there will also be frames, titles and insignia to be earned throughout the Penance system. We’ll also be adding an all black Moebian 53rd cosmetic set, which will be earnable through playing. (Note: Players will not need to get to Order Rank 40 to earn this cosmetic set, don’t worry.)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Ready to Face the Tide?</div>Alright, that’s a wrap on the Introduction to Havoc. We’re working hard on testing and putting together the final touches for this upcoming game mode. Once we’re ready, we’ll be able to share a release date.<br/><br/>Similar to our Introduction to Itemization, we’ll be following this up with a Q&amp;A dev blog to answer any player questions we see! Please stay tuned and join the conversation.<br/><br/>Thank you for your support.<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 17:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on 6.0 Design &amp; Audio - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4487367194477330698</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hey folks!<br/><br/>Back in June we put out our first "What's Next?" video, where you heard some of the WARHAMMER III development team to reveal the first details about our next DLC. You guys seemed to like it, so we went and did another one, and invited Mitch along to talk about our interim patches too. You also seemed to like this, so the question is; are you in the mood to hear even more about the next DLC and update 6.0? <br/><br/>No? Oh okay, fair enough, guess we'll sign off now then...<br/><br/>But wait... if you DID happen to be interested, then you'll be happy to know we have another video for you! This time we are joined once more by a familiar face, Senior Game Director Rich Aldridge, for an update on development, along with Designer Josh King and Project Audio Director Chris Goldsmith, to dive a little deeper into their respective disciplines and what they've been working on for this upcoming DLC and update 6.0. (We're even in a snazzy new studio!)<br/><br/>Come for the DLC news, stay for the gross sound effects and shouty voices...<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jonQ2jNsVos?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>We have a lot more goodness coming your way towards the end of the month, including the first official DLC trailer, some tasty blog content, and a deeper look at the new Legendary Lords in their respective gameplay showcases. We'll also have some giveaways kicking off over on Discord where you'll have multiple chances of winning codes for the DLC on launch!<br/><br/>If you want to keep up to date with all of this, then be sure to join the official Total War Discord server and follow our social channels linked at the bottom of this blog.<br/><br/>Until next time, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— <i>Steve Coleman (KingGobbo) // Senior Community Manager</i><br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #52 (1.5.10) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4476108195413098948</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f1202d0d0337e924f373a218d2dcf6a92b601668.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heya Everyone,</div><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: The Grandfather’s Gifts</div>The Lord of Decay has blessed his most beloved followers with hideous tentacles. So imbued are they with his foul pestilence that they explode when shot.<br/><br/>Dispatch them at close quarters to avoid this.<br/><br/><b>Complete missions featuring the blessed enemies to progress and collect rewards.</b> This condition will only be available during the event and it will appear on both the Standard and Auric mission terminals. Look out for missions with the “Mutated Horrors” condition.<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, November 7, 2024. The rewards will be Ordo dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. Those who complete the last tier of the event will receive a new Portrait Frame. (<b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Be aware the frame might not show up immediately in players’ inventories after receiving the notification. Players may need to re-log, or at least leave and re-enter the Mourningstar.</i>)<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/550190a3d4d84a5cbf154d0f9f8777ebbf41c08c.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/919347318793f380732186d8401324039b7b12cc.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bug Fixes and Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Social menu could fail to correctly display the status of other players and also block invitations/join requests.<br/></li><li> Fixed memory leak crashes which could happen when inspecting weapon stats.<br/></li><li> Fixed issues where the max potential for weapon stats could change when empowering a weapon.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Weapon level calculation is now handled in a more reliable manner. Some weapons that had their total stats below 380 at max Empower level will now be at 1 level below max (490 instead of 500) - meaning players will need to go to Hadron’s and empower from 490 to 500.</i><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where FSR 3.1 Frame Gen would appear as disabled when playing excessive fullscreen effects, using lens distortion or showing certain GUI elements (e.g. the screen effect when a Stimms buff is active).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Nvidia DSR/DLDSR would not work in fullscreen display mode.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where weapon penances were unlocked in the Mourningstar and claimed, but were not shown as completed.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the game would sometimes render only in a corner of the screen while in fullscreen display mode but on lower resolution than the monitor.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Windows chime sounds could play when using Alt+Tab to switch between fullscreen and windowed display modes.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the “activated” status of weapon Special actions could be canceled by getting stunned. <i>Partial Fix. (We've received some reports that this fix does not apply properly to the Power Sword or Thunder Hammer. We're investigating this. Thank you!)</i><br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description text for the Armourbane blessing would display incorrectly for Tiers 3 and 4.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some sound effects (e.g. reload sounds) would be played predominantly only on one side.</li></ul><div class="bb_h1">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <span class="bb_strike">Fsr 3.1 Frame Generation Does Not Do Anything During Excessive Fullscreen Effects</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Penances Shown As Not Completed</span> <b>(Fixed in this Hotfix)</b><br/></li><li> <b> Purging Flames Penance is Bugged</b><br/></li><li> <b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Bomb Rush - Timed Mode 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4550415957644981246</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><b>Oi, Speed Freeks, time for some firewerkz!</b><br/><br/>For this weekend, we've a new Limited Time Event game mode, Bomb Rush, <br/><br/>Bomb Rush is Kill Konvoy with the bomb spawn rate turned up by x4!<br/><br/>This is an extra, optional game mode that sees players constantly racing to reach new bombs and detonating them on the enemy Stompa. It's much a faster paced game mode where defence is much more difficult, but speed and racing provide more of the focus.<br/><br/>This mode will apply to all 8vs.8 Kill Konvoy maps and will end on Monday <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/2c4494b2dea4a5c3d9b764ca454c1d2fc66c6461.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! <br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4472730495692570698</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines! 🫡</div><br/>This month we released new content: the new Termination map and the new Lethal difficulty. We’ve loved seeing you provide feedback and challenge yourself with the new difficulty. We also took into account the constructive criticism and have implemented some balancing features and tweaks into the game. We truly hope you’re enjoying the game.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">4.5 M PLAYERS 🎊</div><br/>Let’s start this off with great news: we are now over 4 and a half million Space Marines defending the Imperium!<br/><br/>Seeing the community grow so wide, so fast, makes us incredibly proud. We’re working hard to provide new content for you, listening closely to your feedback, and we cannot wait for you to discover what’s next for <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>! <br/><br/>So, thank you, four and a half million times 💙<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/45d0ddb201ff3076925d7d50bab0eaa025335886.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">IMPROVEMENTS BROUGHT TO THE GAME</div><br/>As for every single release, we closely read the feedback from the players. Therefore, we’ve seen that the new content did not meet everyone’s expectations and that the adjustments disappointed many of you.<br/><br/>To make amends and fix the issues that Patch 4.0 brought, we released a hotfix (4.1), which you may find right here. It brings gameplay and balancing tweaks on weapons, difficulty, AI and much more. Make sure you read the patch note! ⚙️<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">UPCOMING CONTENT</div><br/>Another update is coming soon with a brand new weapon: The Neo-Volkite Pistol! <br/><br/>The Neo-Volkite Pistol is a thermal weapon with accumulative damage. Its heat rays have a deadly impact on organic matter, incinerating flesh into ash with explosive force and jets of flame. A weapon of choice against Tyranids! ☢️🔥<br/>The Bulwark, Assault and Vanguard will have access to the Neo-Volkite as a secondary weapon.<br/><br/>On top of this addition, this update will also come with buffs for several firearms.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f182956c202bc3bccf61cc89a68d1560ae830eda.gif"/><br/><br/>Later this year – around early-December – will come the much awaited<b> Dark Angel Chapter Pack</b>, along with a new enemy, the Tzaangor Enlightened and a new PvE map set on Demerium: “Obelisk”.<br/><br/>On another note, we’ve seen your feedback about “Blocking” weapons feeling unsatisfying to play with, and are currently in the process of reworking them!<br/><br/>Be patient Marines!<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39308af705c0b0ffd996813ea1e63517d7240aba.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/dc429323ea2a1546c6cc36077ac8fb4c0b132860.gif"/></div> </div></div><div class="bb_h2">YOUR IDEAS</div><br/>You are constantly submitting new ideas on Focus Together to our great delight. Let’s answer some of them:<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CONTENT ADDITIONS</div><br/><b>New Melee weapons</b><br/>→  Adding a new melee weapon is something we’d love to have later. However, it also takes a lot of time and production resources to integrate. Be sure that we’ll let you know once we’re more advanced on that subject.<br/><br/><b>More Campaign missions</b><br/>→ We’re currently not thinking about adding new campaign missions in Space Marine 2. We rather focus on creating new Operations and Eternal War content.<br/><br/><b>Eternal war party size</b><br/>→ We’re currently working on implementing custom PvP lobbies. You’ll be able to invite your friends, alongside various other options to customise your experience (score limit, time limit, class limit and so on)..<br/><br/><b>Heretic Astartes playable in Operations</b> <br/>→ This will not be implemented due to Space Marine 2's specific setting, how Operations are designed and even the game as a whole. All of the dialogue is written as Astartes talking to other Astartes for example. Missions are also designed so that our characters fight to help the Imperium's war effort.<br/><br/><b>Add the possibility to replay the Campaign Prologue</b><br/>→ Whilst not a priority at the moment, this is something we might consider in the future.<br/><br/><b>Consider adding a bonus reward for players using quickmatch</b><br/>→ This is something we are considering adding in the future.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CUSTOMISATION</div><br/><b>Colour lenses</b><br/>→ We are ready to release the colour lenses with the next big update, which will bring the Dark Angels Chapter Pack.<br/> <br/><b>More than 4 customisation slots</b><br/>→ This is not a priority right now, we prefer to focus on developing other features at the moment. We’ll come back later on this.<br/><br/><b>Customisation add-ons</b><br/>→ More customisation will come in the future. More precise customisation options is a must have as well.<br/><br/><b>More helmet customisation and patterns</b><br/>→ This is something we’re actively working on. It will arrive in the lifespan of the game.<br/><br/><b>Ability to recolor cloth pieces / tabards</b><br/>→ We can consider adding this option later down the line. But creating a satisfying level of quality for this feature is harder than it looks.<br/> <br/><b>Lieutenant colour customisation</b><br/>→ This has been greenlit. More customisation is coming for helmets, corresponding to other Chapters.<br/><br/><b>Change the skin colour of your Marine</b><br/>→ We’re currently working on an option to add head customisation to your Space Marines.<br/><br/><b>Allow Deathwatch icons to be placed on the right shoulder</b><br/>→ Yes, this is something already in the works.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">LET’S CELEBRATE HALLOWEEN 🩸🕷️</div><br/>Our VP community is very prolific so let's do a quick shoutout to some creators, by highlighting the GORE in <i>Space Marine 2</i>!!<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Titus crushing Tyranids as a Deathwatch warrior, shot by @JoniTrasel on X.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6fa155144e88d8bf98a0606862e4460187858626.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">In the midst of a battle on Avarax, Titus strikes a pose among his victims. Shot by @MaraKnightVP on X</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1d270b1a5660c432472a38340b3dc8cadc38e0e8.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">@Selka_VP shared this shot of Titus ripping a Lictor in half! How cool.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e4cfdef589e0bb27ac3124f99ee170cd32d3d3e1.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Last but not least: A Helbrute covered in organic matter while getting slayed by a Space Marine. Shared by @foxhoundrep on Discord.</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c29de88392942b9bf9299a6412622550cb65a8d9.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">THAT’S IT FOR OCTOBER 🦇 </div><br/>To keep yourself updated on the latest news about Space Marine 2, make sure you sign up to Focus Together! And join an already-wide community of players on the official Discord!<br/><br/>See you next time.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For The Emperor. ⚔️</div><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
