<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Blog - Hive Scum: Class Design &amp; Talents</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/627816814267597946</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Hardened criminals, ruthless bounty hunters, violent psychopaths: Tertium’s Hive Scum are coming to Darktide as the next DLC class.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>In case you missed it, check out the </i>reveal trailer here<i>.</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Hive Scum comes in hot with a ton of class features. As <b>experts at fast paced, frenzied gameplay</b>, they bring several new and unique things to the table for the forces of the Mourningstar. For the first time in Darktide, we will have <b>true dual-wielding, both in close combat with the twin shivs, and at range in the form of twin-wielded stub and autopistols</b>. But that is not all, as they also come with new makeshift weapons, like <b>crowbars and bonesaws</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">There will also be plenty of options to create your unique Hive Scum; <b>new faces, tattoos, hairstyles </b>and even (for the first time) <b>face paints </b>that will let you customize them to your heart's content. They also have a unique place in the story, as they are from Tertium, and are here to protect their home territory.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">All of this will have its own time in the spotlight before <b>release on the 2nd of December</b>, but <b>today we will dive into the design and talents of the class</b>, focusing on what you can build around and the new mechanics of stimms and toxins! For this we tracked down Teodor here in the office, so we are handing over to him now! Take it away, Teodor!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Teodor, born and raised in Stockholm, Sweden. \[...] I’m a Game Designer and I’ve been on Darktide and Vermintide. I started here working on weapons back in the day and slowly moved over to class design, but I’ve always been in that sort of ‘Player mechanics’ space. In my free time I make music and I cook a lot! I love food. Food and drinks are great.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Class Design</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Before we had even picked the Hive Scum as our next class, we took a look at our existing classes and started categorizing them. Each class can fulfill multiple niches depending on the build, and each build fits separate archetypes for Melee and Ranged.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">From looking at the types of builds, player fantasies and opportunities for player expression that we already had represented in our existing classes, we were able to see what archetypes were missing or didn’t have much representation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“\[...] so we have the Zealot as an aggressive melee character, but we don’t necessarily have an overly aggressive <b>ranged </b>character that, you know, hovers in close range, almost where other classes would opt into using a melee weapon.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">From this starting point we began to explore concepts and ideas, eventually landing the Hive Scum as the ideal candidate. Not only did it suit itself perfectly to the niches we wanted to fill, but it’s a direct contrast to our previous DLC Class, the Arbitrator, in both gameplay and theme.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">In both ranged and melee, the core idea behind the Hive Scum is a very mobile, aggressive style that emphasizes dodging, maintaining the offensive as you dance in and out of attacks while showering the enemies in a hail of bullets or blows.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s like a ‘I don’t need to block, I don’t need to be big and strong because I am so fast and so precise, you will never hit me’ type of deal. So for \[Hive Scum] we really leaned into those aspects.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As we kept developing the Hive Scum we were able to expand on that, with the narrative and the gameplay elements building on each other, a back and forth that influenced not just the abilities and talents of the class, but also the weapons, how they’re used, and how everything looks. And this also led us to a few unique mechanics…</p><div class="bb_h2">Chem Toxin</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Unique to the Hive Scum, the Chem Toxin is a new mechanic coming to Darktide. Similar to Burn or Bleed, this homebrewed toxin is its own Damage Over Time effect which the Hive Scum can apply through various ways, such as some of the unique weapons or one of the Blitzes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It is quite potent, and multiple applications can stack up until a certain limit. Certain talents also interact with the Chem Toxin by triggering effects when applying it and things of that nature (more on that further down!)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Stimm Lab: The Cartel Special</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Another new mechanic unique to this is the Stimm Lab! Thanks to their underworld connections, the Hive Scum are able to get some special materials and make their own custom Stimms called the Cartel Special!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Just like the main talent tree, you gain 1 point to spend in the Stimm Lab for every level, picking different bonuses to add to your Cartel Special. Players who opt into making their custom</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Stimms through the Lab will start each mission with their Stimm equipped and will be unable to use any of the Stimms found in missions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This Cartel Special Stimm will recharge on its own, and the cooldown will depend on how many points you’ve spent in the Stimm Lab: the more potent the effect, the longer the cooldown!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>This mechanic is optional: </b>By not selecting any upgrades in the Stimm Lab, your Hive Scum will be able to use normal Stimms like the other classes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">The three “archetypes”</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Just like with our existing classes, the talent tree allows players to mix and match talents to make their own custom builds, but there are three underlying “archetypes” that act as the foundation for each branch, which represents different player fantasies that the Hive Scum can represent. While <b>not official names</b>, we called these “Gunslinger”, “Ruffian”, and “Chemist” during development, so for ease of writing we will use these names here</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“And then, of course, over time these three playstyles blend together and become a Talent Tree. At some point you have to ‘let go’ of the fact that, while the playstyles exist, we cannot control how the players will welcome and use them. They’re gonna find entirely new ways of playing Hive Scum, but the playstyles really help with getting the initial direction of the class.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">“Gunslinger”</div><p class="bb_paragraph">This was the first archetype to come into being, and it best encapsulates the initial idea for the Hive Scum. Found in the left branch of the talent tree, the focus of the Gunslinger is <b>overwhelming close ranged firepower </b>and <b>nimble dodging</b>, a true Run and Gun playstyle.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The default Coherency Aura, Blitz and Combat Ability are all based on the ones that the Gunslinger improves.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peek at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>In Your Face</b>: Increased Ranged damage at close range, which is further increased for a short while after reloading.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Like the Wind:</b> Dramatically increased Sprint Dodge Angle, and can Sprint Dodge even without Stamina.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Base Coherency Aura: Gunslinger</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">When an Ammo pickup is collected by you or your Allies in Coherency, everyone else in Coherency also replenishes a small amount of ammo.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Base Blitz: Blinder</p><p class="bb_paragraph">An extremely quick to throw blinding grenade, which staggers enemies. This enables the Hive Scum to close the gap and get into their preferred range with very little effort, regardless of what gunlines the heretics have aiming your way.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“You can throw this out <b>really</b> fast, you can even throw it mid-combo while swinging your melee weapon.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You can recover Blinder grenades by killing enemies.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Base Combat Ability: Desperado</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Immediately swap to and reload your ranged weapon, entering <i>Desperado</i> for a few seconds. During <i>Desperado</i>, the Hive Scum is <b>immune to Ranged Attacks,</b> <b>Sprinting costs no stamina</b>, and <b>reloading does not reduce your Ammo Reserve</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Close Ranged Kills extends the duration</b> of <i>Desperado</i>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Keystone: Vulture’s Mark</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Killing Specials or Elites with a Ranged weapon gives you stacks of <i>Vulture’s Mark</i>, which improves Ranged Damage, Ranged Critical Strike Chance, and Movement Speed. At max stacks, ranged Special and Elite kills restore Toughness for you and Allies in Coherency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">“Ruffian”</div><p class="bb_paragraph">For those who want to lean a bit away from the ranged focus and enjoy feeling more like the guy who the Cartel sends to “convince” those who don’t cooperate, we have the Ruffian! Found in the middle branch of the talent tree, this is a <b>melee-focused</b> archetype that goes <b>all in on aggression</b>, still relying heavily on <b>mobility and dodging</b> to survive. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Duck, weave and shank them in the back, or bash their skulls in with relentless pressure!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peek at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Nimble:</b> Dodges move farther and last longer.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Hyper-Violence:</b> Upon Melee kill, gain bonus Melee Damage based on amount of overkill damage.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Coherency Aura: Ruffian</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased Melee damage for you and Allies in Coherency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Blitz: Boom Bringer</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A high powered missile launcher. What else is there to say? For when you really want something <b>dead</b>!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“That was so much fun. The idea came pretty early on because we were like ‘if we make a projectile weapon only exist as a Blitz, we can <b>really </b>crank the effect’. Because we can make sure that it doesn’t have too much ammo, or crazy numbers or doesn’t scale weird.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Combat Ability: Rampage!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“We wanted a ‘rage’ ability where you become unstoppable for a few seconds, as long as you play really aggressively and kill lots of things.” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Enter <i>Rampage!</i> for a few seconds, gaining vastly increased Melee Attack power, Attack Speed, Damage Reduction, and becoming immune to Stuns and Suppression. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Melee attacks extend the duration of <i>Rampage!</i>, although this effect is diminished after 30 seconds. Exiting <i>Rampage!</i> leaves you exhausted and vulnerable for a few seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Keystone: Adrenaline Frenzy</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A very aggressive keystone that encourages relentless brawling!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Melee hits grant stacks of <i>Adrenaline</i>, which are lost over time when not attacking. At max stacks, lose all stacks and gain <i>Adrenaline Frenzy</i>, increasing Attack Speed and Melee Damage for a few seconds.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">“Chemist”</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Found on the right branch of the Talent Tree, this archetype puts a bigger <b>focus on the unique Stimm and Toxin mechanics</b> of the Hive Scum, gaining bonuses related to using Stimms (whether it’s the Cartel Special from the Stimm Lab or normal Stimms found in missions) and applying Chem Toxin through various methods (including weapons! More on that in a future dev blog).</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Sneak peek at some of the talents:</i></p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Blessed Stimms:</b> While Stimmed, killing blows clear some Corruption.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Targeted Toxin:</b> Enemies infected with your Chem Toxin deal less damage. Increased effect on Monsters.</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Coherency Aura: Anarchist</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Increased Critical Chance for you and Allies in Coherency.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Blitz: Chem Grenade</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Throw a canister containing Chem Toxin, which breaks open and spills its contents across an area when it explodes. Any enemy that enters the lingering toxic cloud will be affected with stacks of Chem Toxin.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Combat Ability: Stimm Supply</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum has ‘repurposed’ military gadgets to come up with this customized Medical Crate that can be placed down on the ground. This is a supportive ability that grants nearby Allies the effects of the Hive Scum’s Cartel Special Stimm.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Keystone: Chemical Dependency</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While the Stimm Lab allows you to craft the perfect Stimm to suit your playstyle, the more potent Cartel Special Stimms have a longer cooldown. This Keystone is not so much about the perfect Stimm, but about taking as many Stimms as you can, as fast as you can!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">With this Keystone, using a Stimm (Cartel Special or otherwise) grants a stack of <i>Dependency</i> for a long duration. Each stack grants Ability Cooldown Reduction, up to a limit.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The gameplay I’d like to see there is players min-maxing the contents of their Stimms so that they can still get those Keystone bonuses while also balancing it with the contents themselves.” ~ Teodor</i></p><div class="bb_h1"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>Bonus: Most fun part of working with Hive Scum?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I had the most fun working with the Missile Launcher, for sure. Which is now called the Boom Bringer, which I think is great. \[...] That’s been really fun, and I really enjoyed that. And it’s got fun little things that I hope players find!” ~ Teodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>That’s all for today, but keep an eye out for our next Dev Blog, coming soon!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave and Tertium!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Hive Scum here:</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class/https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Class: Hive Scum coming December 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/627816814267597931</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Warband!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’re happy to finally reveal the newest class coming to Darktide: the <b>Hive Scum</b>, hardened criminals from the very streets of Tertium. No one else knows this Hive like they do, and they have the aggression and bravado to dig in and break as many bones as they have to to reclaim their home!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum class is coming on December 2, 2025, across all platforms.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://youtu.be/wZetaKE7KQo</p><div class="bb_h2">Cranked for mayhem</div><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum’s access to concoctions of a more dubious origin is shown in their signature customizable Stimm. Pick your own personal chemical mix, balancing bonuses to tear up enemies. Then break out your toxin kit: drench your saw in toxic coatings and control the streets with lingering Chem Bombs that set foes up for the kill.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Frenzied Gameplay &amp; Dual-Wielding</div><p class="bb_paragraph">These gunslingers and bladesmiths have a nifty trick up their sleeves. For the first time in Darktide, a class brings true dual‑wield expertise. Twin‑wield pistols to overwhelm enemies with firepower, and dual-wielding shivs to make you an efficient killer when the fighting gets close.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Hive Scum is an expert in makeshift weaponry: from crude shivs, brutal crowbars to cruel saws for bone‑shreddingly close work. Spray and pray from afar with your dual autopistols and stub pistols; pour lead, break ranks, don’t stick around.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">No matter your approach, you’ll have brutal abilities at your disposal: tear through enemies with your abilities, control the streets by disorienting your enemies with Blind Grenades, or drop elites and monsters in a single blast with a devastating missile launcher. </p><div class="bb_h2">Make them cower</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Tell your story through reimagined full‑body tattoos, new gritty hairstyles and vibrant hair colors, and the first-ever face paints and makeup. Choose from six distinct voice sets across three personalities so your Hive Scum doesn’t just look the part: they own it. Whether you’ll be in it for the money or the mayhem, make the streets of Atoma remember your name.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Players can wishlist the Hive Scum Class today and will be able to purchase it on all platforms on December 2 for the price of $11.99 / €11.99.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/c567d3f450b7860bf45bc537b27c9c2c661c20e0.jpg"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/562858fd624aa941385e168c53b1eca2febd3f27.jpg"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Dev blogs</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll be releasing<b> a series of dev blogs</b> to break down <b>the details of the Hive Scum class as well as the No Man’s Land operation</b>... Starting right now! If you're interested, check out the first dev blog, focused on the Class Design &amp; Talents.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Keep an eye on our newsfeed, and look forwards to more details coming soon! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for today! Thank you for reading, we hope you’re as excited to learn more about the new class soon!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>For the Conclave and Tertium!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Wishlist the Hive Scum here:</p><p class="bb_paragraph">https://store.steampowered.com/app/4013290/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Classhttps://store.steampowered.com/app/4013310/Warhammer_40000_Darktide__Hive_Scum_Class_Deluxe_Edition/</p><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">– The Darktide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tides of Torment: Meet Dechala</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510721067535302988</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/331366632abd3f583d5e2f5caf351e9c7b628f61.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Welcome, thralls! Today, we’re diving into the world of the merciless, many-armed champion of Slaanesh, Dechala the Denied One.<br/><br/>Daemonic in form, if not in essence, Dechala stalks the world, the living embodiment of the Prince of Pleasure’s aspects of decadence and cruelty. Head of the infamous Chaos Warband known as the Tormentors, she roams far and wide, mesmerising everyone she subjugates and rendering them into mindless Thralls to service her every whim. When their lives are all spent in her service, the warband moves on to the next ‘enthralling’ conquest.<br/><br/>In battle, Dechala is a blur of blades, moving and striking with grace, fury and frightening speed. She has her own unique skill-line which unlocks a series of abilities in combat, enhancing the capabilities of herself and her followers throughout battle. Her presence on the battlefield inspires her forces as they take the initiative and tear into enemy lines.<br/><br/>So, if you enjoy swift and punchy first-strike armies, and campaigns which alternate between fast-and-brutal land-grabs followed by periods of development, you’ll find much to love about Dechala!<br/><br/>👉 READ FULL BLOG HERE 👈<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team</p><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

</div><p class="bb_paragraph">SteamXFacebookInstagramDiscordBluesky</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return to the Reik Trailer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/624439114720084685</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" ktdlq1srveq?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes,</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Return to the Reik, the newest addition to Vermintide 2, is coming out on <b>November 20</b>! <i>In case you missed it, </i>check out our dev blog<i> on the level and sound design of it!</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This map is a re-imagining of the Vermintide 1 level <i>'The River Reik'</i>. Our Heroes must re-tread their steps as they return in search for one of Kruber's family heirlooms. But much has changed since the last time they were here, and now Ratmen aren't the only dangers lurking in the dark…</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/bf31079bf76b0e08b01cd7a36fe999201ce43142.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Embark on an exciting adventure, fending off hordes of enemies on both land and sea, and experience the River Reik like never before!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Blog - Return to the Reik</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/624438963127452274</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph"></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" ktdlq1srveq?fs='1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0"' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/" width="850"></iframe>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div><p class="bb_paragraph">We’ve interviewed <b>Lead Level Designer Rickard</b>, <b>Lead Sound Designer Anton</b>, and <b>Lead Gameplay Programmer Theodor</b> about their work on the upcoming free level for Warhammer: Vermintide 2, <b>Return to the Reik!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Level Design</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Rickard and I've been a Level Designer since the beginning of humankind, I think. \[Laughs] I started doing levels for my uncle when Doom came out, that’s almost 30 years ago now. Since then it’s been a hobby, but for the last 15, 20 years it’s been my profession. And it just keeps getting more fun.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>‘Return to the Reik’</b> is a re-imagining of one of Vermintide 1’s most popular levels, ‘The River Reik’, which is part of the Death on the Reik DLC. For those not familiar, this level has our Heroes crash into the river bank, fighting off hordes of Skaven as they follow the shore, trudge through caverns, and even sail a ship which gets boarded by the dastardly ratmen! In Vermintide 2, our Heroes are returning to these treacherous waters in search of a family heirloom, and they’ll find that much has changed in the seven years since their last visit!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/b88e3e4ac4c72849272ddbc75df50eba2283b14f.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“We started to think about what we should do for the 10 Years of Tide celebration. So, we looked at all of the old levels and we checked all our forums and what our fans wanted most and I think every query we made ended up with the River Reik level because it's such an epic, different level.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The first order of business was porting the original level into Vermintide 2, which took some work just to get running. After updating it and fixing all the errors, we ended up with a playable version of said level and began testing.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">However, we wanted to do more than just port the original level, we wanted to make a new experience as our Heroes return to this place, similar to how we re-imagined  other Vermintide 1 levels, like Drachenfels. <b>Players familiar with the original will recognize a lot of it</b>, but we also added more side paths, redid the terrain on various areas, added more encounters, and overall updated the level to represent the years that had passed since our last visit.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“We wanted to make something more. So every developer who played it had to give their input on what they wanted. And some were crazier than others, of course!” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">While the original map wasn’t necessarily short, <b>we still wanted to add even more stuff to it</b>, both for the sake of variety and just to make it a properly packed level worthy of celebrating 10 Years of Tide with! Skaven aren’t the only enemies lurking in these waters anymore! <b>Chaos encampments and even raiding ships</b> join the dangers of the River Reik, and we have caverns that act as both a shortcut, and lair of who knows what beastie…</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/7784c70750431acf94cad8f4dfe7cdd0eb521d47.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Like last time, you’ll have the chance to board and sail a ship along the river, only the ride will be even wilder this time! Luckily, the ship you’ll be boarding sports a <b>nifty set of cannons</b>, which will be quite useful to fend off the approaching Skaven and Rotblood vessels! <b>Mid-sail combat features more prominently in Return to the Reik</b>, and they not only last longer, but also feature more of them, with unique encounters and new challenges to deal with! Timing your cannon shots to sink the enemy ships circling your boat like sharks while fending off boarders is no easy feat, eh?</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s so fun to be able to use the cannons. That’s something that I’m kind of proud of, that I actually got it working, ‘cause it was such a struggle, haha.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/bf31079bf76b0e08b01cd7a36fe999201ce43142.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">There’s also plenty of new challenges and secrets to uncover, along the usual search for hidden Tomes and Grimoires. <b>Those of you with a passion for exploration will find many nooks and crannies to look into!</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I know some of our testers said it was almost too much to do, haha. \[...] The cool thing was, we said we wanted to convert some of the Vermintide 1 levels \[...] and someone said we’re not gonna be able to do River Reik, it’s too complicated, it was made so long ago and I just- I went ‘Okay, that’s a challenge, I will do it.’ \[...] It took me like two days just to understand how it was actually made. \[...] We had to update a lot of code to get everything working like it did in Vermintide 1.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Thankfully most of the assets in the level were already updated by the time we began work on it, but various of the models and texture that weren’t already used in Vermintide 2 definitely needed to be updated or even re-done. But it was the ship sailing mechanics that took the most effort, more on that later!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“There were so many things going on, but I think we got it to work, and it was worth it. Very worth it. \[...] It’s been an honour to be working with one of the coolest levels.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2">Programming challenges: Sailing and Elevators</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“I am Theodor, I’m the Lead Gameplay Programmer at Vermintide. \[...] I do racing on my free time, driving cars… I drive a Chevrolet Nova 1968!” ~ Theodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Elevators have never been a big part of Vermintide, and so while they function well enough for their usual purpose, a lot of work had to be done to improve them for Return to the Reik. That’s because the times where the ship our Heroes will be boarding is moving around, the game treats it as a giant elevator moving horizontally.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“When a game is so big, there’s so many layers that can go wrong when you want to move a lot of things along something else and have that look good and proper. It’s not as simple as just attaching a player to the elevator, because that would break so many other things.” ~ Theodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A lot of the jittering and sudden movements that players have while riding elevators, or the fact that blood splatters and items cannot follow along, are just a couple of things that are just fine in regular elevators but don’t quite cut it when you spend such a huge part of the level riding one.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Now if you die with a Tome on you or something, it won’t just detach on the elevator, it will actually be brought along <b>with</b> the elevator.” ~ Theodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Not only that, but all of the fighting done onboard the ship presented a lot of challenges getting the game to synchronize things well visually, as the boat has its own animation of swaying and rocking with the waters. These random movements are not synchronized between the players, and so figuring out how to make the movements of the players and items make sense according to what each client thinks the boat is doing was a huge headache.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">It was a struggle against both the game physics and networking to make this boat ride as smooth as possible, but the end result was worth it. And, while the improvements were mostly made for the sake of Return to the Reik, <b>these changes will also affect all elevators across Vermintide 2.</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/bf8a8042d61bf005ee82ebfc9fef2136c8ba55ee.png"/></p><div class="bb_h1">Sound Design</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My name is Anton, I’ve worked as a Sound Designer for around 10 years now, maybe a bit more. I started out in movies, commercials, trailers the first six years of my career. So I came from that part of sound designing, I worked almost exclusively with linear stuff. Then I transitioned more and more into gaming \[...] I’ve always had gaming as a hobby of mine, I’ve always been gaming, so that’s never been an issue. And I’ve always been interested in audio in games!” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">You might remember Anton from our previous Sound Design dev blog on A Parting of the Waves! This time around, one of the big challenges was updating the sound design from the original River Reik, figuring out what changes needed to be made and how to implement the sounds for the new additions.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“When we as a team decided we were remastering River Reik, I was really hyped because I like the idea. Like, boats! It’s different, it’s fun. But it’s also a bit scary to take on a challenge that’s already been designed, and it’s already been out there, in Vermintide 1. \[...] Like, how much can I change without players feeling that I took something away, or changed too much? It’s a tricky balance.” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Many things have changed since Vermintide 1, such as various constraints no longer being an issue, enemy density being much higher, overall sound quality improving, and so on. <b>This meant that every sound effect in River Reik had to be looked into</b>, to figure out what was acceptable, what needed to be replaced, and what could be improved.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“The mix in Vermintide 2 is completely changed so naturally I had to change a lot of stuff to make it work with our new gameplay. \[...] There were a lot of really nice assets from Vermintide 1. I reused almost all of the music we had in River Reik, because we felt like that’s a nice homage \[...] and it still sounds really good. We still have the original recordings from the music, so it was just for me to re-implement it.” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Even regular sounds like the chirping of birds, the creaking of the wooden hull, the sound of a cellar door, everything got a pass. But of course the most fun to be had was in implementing the sounds of cannons firing, boats ramming and explosions!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/fd88eb4d40075f93e40e2826e8d7e7b6d7923903.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">All of the new editions required new sound effects, the sea encounters in particular. The howling wind, the rushing waters, a moody ambiance for the short time of calmness our Heroes might enjoy before being attacked.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“There was a lot of work with the Chaos ships. Because those we haven’t done before, so I’ve added drums and chanting from the Chaos ships to make them more threatening, which was really fun.” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph">On top of that, the finale of the level has, to put it lightly, received some major modifications to make it more climactic and exciting, and the sound design had to be changed accordingly. A proper grand finale, with the booming toll of Skaven bells and so much more.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Despite how much work and attention to detail was put into these parts of the level, it was actually the Voice Over that presented the biggest challenge in sound design. Without spoiling too much, there’s a particular section where our Heroes are searching an area for something, and the dialogue system had to accommodate for tons of variables and dynamic situations. It might seem simple, but the logic of how to handle each Hero reporting each location, how to handle multiple of these events at once, or what to do when they finally found what they were looking for was a lot of manual work.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“Those small details are always, hilariously enough, the things that take the most time.” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">Bonus question: What was your favorite part of the level?</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“My favorite part is definitely the Chaos sea battle encounter, because it’s so fun to make use of something new. I mean we have been firing cannons, like for Brachsenbrücke, but not in this way, this way you actually have control over it.” ~ Rickard</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“What can beat the boat ride– I mean, plunder and adventure on the seas?” ~ Anton</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>“It’s so hard not to say ‘the boat part’... I really like the last stand, fighting the enemies back while you’re preparing to leave. \[...] And I love all the dynamic parts of how we implemented the boat into combat, and how we made it an actual interactive part of the level.” ~ Theodor</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h1">The future of Vermintide</div><p class="bb_paragraph">Return to the Reik features not just exciting adventures, but also more mysteries to solve, questions that won’t be answered in this level alone! While we can’t say anything more, suffice to say that <b>this won’t be the last map we make</b>, and that we’re already looking into what can come next in the adventures of the Ubersreik Five.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/dae7de9573ce480bc56532438913557891dba7d2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">That’s all for now! We hope you have a blast with Return to the Reik when it comes out!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">- The Vermintide Team</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
