<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>May Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500574015912412461</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines,</div><br/>Let’s review what happened in May, and what’s coming next!<br/>Shall we start off with what everyone’s waiting for?…<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SIEGE MODE TEASER TRAILER 🩸</div><br/>Revealed during the Skulls Festival of Video Games, the Siege Mode will arrive on June 26. This first teaser trailer gives you a first taste of the upcoming battle, watch it if you haven’t already!<br/><br/>Tear through unending waves of Tyranid and Chaos assaults and fight to survive as long as you can.<br/><br/><b>Give them no ground.</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NDScTIUHlnc?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h3">Let’s recap what we know about it already:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The action takes place on Kadaku.<br/></li><li> Up to 3 players (either with friends or with 2 bots, just like in regular PvE).<br/></li><li> You will get to fight waves of both Tyranids and Chaos.<br/></li><li> Difficulty will increase for each wave defeated.</li></ul>Your class, and weapon progressions are shared between Operations and Siege Mode<br/>The Siege Mode isn’t a DLC, it’s a <b>free update</b>!<br/><br/>Prepare to hold your ground and survive as long as you can against endless enemies, as <b>only in death does duty end</b>.<br/><br/>​Siege Mode will be playable on the Public Test Server (Steam) starting June 4.<br/>Here’s a tutorial on how to access it.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">How it will work ⚙️</div><br/>You will earn points for each completed wave. Points are distributed among each player (e.g. if the wave grants you 600 points, and there’s three of you: then, each person will get 200 points).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/55c25416184d4c71523316b925500b3312e4bfa0.png"/><br/>Spend your points at the Requisition Terminals to buy equipment or reinforcements such as Cadians and Marines (Each player can summon 1 AI Space Marine at a time. Choose their class without restrictions!). The strongest and most expensive being the Dreadnought, which joins the battlefield to help you for 3 minutes. Buy equipment and reinforcements to make the fight easier (or less unbearable 😁).<br/><br/>Every 5 waves, you’ll take the elevator to change sectors and therefore field of battle. Completing each Sector will grant your more rewards (requisition points, armoury data, etc.)<br/><br/>And most importantly, your mission is to ​<b>give them no ground</b>.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Are you ready? See you June 26! ⚔️</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a6e531e31a5a74b4a50ffd3fef3ebda28f84c081.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Patch 8.0 - SIEGE UPDATE</div><br/>You’ll be able to get a first taste of the new content, via the PTS, which will reopen on June 4. Apart from Siege Mode, other features, free and DLC Content are coming with Patch 8.0 in June. <br/><br/>Here’s a tutorial on how to access the PTS. Contrary to our first PTS: base Game owners can't equip the new customization packs on the PTS, but Season Pass holders can!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Let’s break it down together:</div><br/>Coming along with the Siege Mode : The White Scars and Blood Angels enter the fray.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">⚪ THE WHITE SCARS CHAPTER PACK</div><br/>The White Scars Chapter Pack will include a new Champion skin for the Assault class and three exclusive White Scars–inspired weapon skins for <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Occulus Bolt Carbine<br/></li><li> The Stalker Bolt Rifle<br/></li><li> The Combat Knife</li></ul><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c0fc4a0e132d08919324e6e27654fe15b3958f0a.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0254e5bfaa406e0d3d52e12db225d7cd3bd87237.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9f0a261a65d0e9e65f99d2e59ec33868f81f85c4.jpg"/></div></div></div>Also, a host of cosmetic options and heraldry markings for their Successor Chapters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b066256ea388e1db5bd6cd8e09d0c10107cd25eb.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b4c834898fa174b67debd3bf94cb8ed02cab7f98.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6db692fa5ef96c40a3454b8eafdfcf58f7d9b219.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b73fa5f9b8a36fa2e713d59c294a66e6f6151489.jpg"/></div></div></div>The White Scars Successor Chapters are the:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dark Hunters<br/></li><li> Solar Hawks<br/></li><li> Storm Reapers<br/></li><li> Mantis Warriors<br/></li><li> Destroyers<br/></li><li> Marauders<br/></li><li> Storm Lords<br/></li><li> Rampagers</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">🔴 THE BLOOD ANGELS COSMETIC PACK</div><br/>The Blood Angels Cosmetic Pack will provide a number of new armour pieces to be equipped on any of the game’s playable classes, in addition to heraldry markings celebrating eight of the Blood Angels’ Successor Chapters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e9b00e197758eebd0757f8b7881c56347bd9766e.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2fb39e0f5017cf83ce924c48783bd696c67ac436.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/46d0d37e4263b8b2ba15f7bd6d5127e61871dc7b.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6b8123edd3debacc0b18ab3e0d9d99dd7d4347a5.jpg"/></div></div></div>The Blood Angels Successor Chapters are the:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Atlantian Spears<br/></li><li> Blood Dragons<br/></li><li> Flesh Eaters<br/></li><li> Blood Scythes<br/></li><li> Lamenters<br/></li><li> Angels Penitent<br/></li><li> Angels Sanguine<br/></li><li> Flesh Tearers</li></ul>We can’t reveal more for the moment. 😉<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">SNEAK PEEK</div><br/>Many sneak peeks are coming with the June and July Community Updates. We’ll talk about the update that comes after 8.0, what we are planning to do after the one year anniversary, and more. 🤫<br/><br/>Stay tuned!!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FOCUS TOGETHER</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">🧑‍🎨 Fan Art Contest on Focus Together</div><br/>You, players, never miss an opportunity to impress us with your art skills. We keep seeing screenshots, painted mini and fan arts everywhere, to our great delight. This time we wanted to host a contest!<br/><br/>Our favorite fan art inspired by the campaign mode of Space Marine 2 will be granted with 2 keys of Space Marine 2 (any platform) to offer to fellow Astartes eager to join the fight.<br/><br/>Rules: Submit your creation in the #Fan-Creations channel of Focus Together to participate! The piece can be digital or traditional and must follow the said-theme! One entry per person.<br/><br/>The winner will be contacted via their DMs. The contest starts on May 30 and ends on June 25!<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">✏️ A word from Focus and Saber</div><br/>We wanted to acknowledge the fact that quality-of-life bugs matter too (such as typos, clipping props of the armour etc…), and we want to fix them. But right now, the major content updates promised in our roadmap are taking up a significant portion of our time. That means some of the smaller fixes will take longer to roll out.<br/><br/>Our current focus is on resolving high-impact issues like crashes and connectivity problems, which can significantly affect gameplay. Every patch aims to bring improvements on that front.<br/><br/>At the top of our priority list right now is improving the connectivity issues that arose after the 7.0 update: We’re mainly talking about infinite “Joining Server” loops and such issues preventing players from joining sessions. We made some improvements with the 7.1 and 7.2 hotfixes, but we’ll keep working on it for the 8.0 update.<br/><br/><b>Thank you</b> for your patience and understanding as we continue to improve the game. Your support and feedback help guide our work. 🖤<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH</div><br/>As usual, let’s keep in touch on Discord and Focus Together. You can also follow us on our socials: Instagram, X, Facebook, Threads and Bluesky.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield, Space Marines.<br/><br/><i>The Focus and Saber Teams. 🦾</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.6.2 - 28th of May</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546735912086668857</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<blockquote class="bb_blockquote"> <div class="bb_h2">	Hotfix 6.6.2 - 28th of May							</div> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Fixed players not being able to progress in Weaves.</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>(Versus) Fixed recent balance changes unintentionally removing certain passive buffs from various careers.</b> <br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash if a skeleton attacks an enemy that is exactly on top of the skeleton									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash if a skeleton's target enemy is despawned the same frame that it starts its attack.									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an issue where random poses wasn't used in the end screen when completing weaves									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where "reset" and "switch hero" descriptions switched places when crafting or salvaging items depending on if an item is selected or not.									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where Handmaiden's "Asrai Alacrity" talent didn't increase power level when not being the party leader.									<br/> </li><li>	(Versus) Fixed a crash when attempting to join someone from the main menu via Steam friends while they are hosting a Custom Game.									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where the player would end up in an infinite loading screen if they are in a friend's level, go to the Main Menu, and then join their friend via friend joining.									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed occasional enemy related crash when on very low framerate.									<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where the cursor got stuck on screen until shutdown if having viewed a cinematic in the main menu.									<br/> </li><li>	Weave Skins are now available for Weapon Poses.									<br/> </li><li>	(Chaos Wastes) Added the ability to scroll through the list of boons while in the Pilgrimage map.									<br/> </li><li>	Patched a bug in the 'Neuter Ult Effects' mod that was breaking the Huntsman's career skill invisibility.									<br/> </li><li>	(Chaos Wastes) Fixed the weekly expedition reward skin not displaying its name properly.																	<br/> </li><li> <b>The Well of Dreams fixes:</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>	Fixed a crash when a players character despawns while inside a spotlight in The Well of Dreams								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a client crash when walking into a spotlight area in The Well of Dreams just after losing connection to the host.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a spot where you could fall into a pit and get stuck.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where you could turn the pages on the event books after the event was over.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a bug where interacting with the pages too fast will make the symbols look funky.								<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash involving shaders in the map.</li></ul></li></ul></blockquote> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.3.2.29 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040876439</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hotfix 1.3.2.29 is live, fixing the problem with the new mirror in the Lord Captain's quarters that caused the character's model to become invisible.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #68 (1.7.6) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520840214227191257</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4d630310664380a40d3814f7acefe6c74ce1869d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heya Everyone,</div>Hotfix #68 (1.7.6) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Admonition Ascendant Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some instances where the top part of the nurgle totem would fall straight through the totem body.<br/></li><li> Fixed instances where some skulls on the totem would look low quality.<br/></li><li> Fixed instances where sound emitted from the nurgle totem would stop during high intensity moments.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where melee attacks failed to connect with destructible objects (e.g. Heretical Idols).<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring when dying in Vigil Station Oblivium.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring when tagging enemies as they were being killed.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring at the end of Rolling Steel.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Disrupt Destiny fails to show stacks in the HUD.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where The Theatre of Castigation did not randomize the wave compositions.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOIN/CREATE ISSUES FIXED</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689832129</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">WE'Z DUN FIXED IT LADZ!</div>We've tested this latest build thoroughly and it's zoggin' great 💪👍 <br/><br/>Please <b>restart Steam</b> to make sure Speed Freeks updates to latest<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Things FIXED:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Not being able to <b>join games</b> properly, whether through Quick Match, or the Game Browser 🎉,<br/></li><li>Not seeing all <b>regions</b> in the game browser 🎉<br/></li><li>Not being able to <b>create a game</b> 🎉<br/></li><li>Not being able to perform actions after a failed attempt at joining a game.  Now the game will tell you if it's still processing a previous request<br/></li><li>Servers now listed in order of lowest ping in the Game Browser</li></ul>Cheers for your patience with the game being pretty broken 🛠️ <br/>Obviously it was a pretty messy launch with these unforeseen connection issues popping up, but honestly we've had a really quick response to it thanks to our lead programmer (and only networking expert), the Wired QA testing team, and our community members for helping us test too.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Issues still happening:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Performance issues/stuttering when using Full Screen Windowed mode in the display settings. <br/>Workaround: Please instead use WINDOWED mode with your native resolution, or try FULLSCREEN mode instead,</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fatal error crashes.  We've done some work on this so hopefully it's better, but these are the types of deep crashes that are hard to reproduce and diagnose.  We'll continue to work on it<br/>Note: try to run as few things in the background when playing the game as possible</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Game browser can sometimes - but rarely - show nothing, or a loading icon<br/>Please just restart the game if this happens, and try not to refresh the game browser constantly or it will bug out</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There's an issue with servers using the same name and it confusing the game,</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/995ffe8e717de04ab7a9f557c54780e617c1da15.png"/><div class="bb_h3">What's coming soon❓</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improvements to team balancing and team switching,<br/></li><li>Improvements to hit reg 🙏<br/></li><li>Vehicle balance improvements<br/></li><li>General improvements and fixes<br/></li><li>Warbands, which are like a clan/club feature.  This was supposed to be in for launch but didn't make it in time.<br/></li><li> looking into reimplementing some kind of  **party system** (previous one died with the conversion of the multiplayer backend.  You can join games with friends through the game browser in the meantime though)<br/></li><li>Upcoming roadmap of potential features and content</li></ul>Thanks for sticking with the game everyone. Been chaos the past couple days but we've now nailed it we think.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Happy RACIN', STUNTIN' and KRUMPIN'!</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/129ec630ecc8eb6f0ee41d6e30a790c75eba5ae4.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 19:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
