<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Korean added to supported languages at launch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2532480/view/547864982714322547</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">We’re very pleased to announce that Team MoDakBul, who provided post-launch Korean localisation for the first game, will be providing their services once again for Mechanicus II.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Big thanks to both Team MoDakBul and our Korean-speaking players for your support. We’re excited to make Mechanicus II more accessible to even more of you on day one!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.4.0.200 is out</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762736041</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>A patch for Warhammer 40000: Rogue Trader has arrived for PC. We’ve addressed the blocking issue that might occur in Act IV for some players with the Arbites origin.<br/><br/><u>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</u><br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After speaking with Proctor Adriana Yeager in Act IV, further plot progress could become blocked for the players with the Adeptus Arbites origin in some cases – fixed. If you experienced this bug, speak to Adriana Yeager and then to Clerk Tertius Quart to advance in the quest.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 08:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.4.0.199 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523095184762736018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Update 1.4.0.199 is live! The Heartless now becomes available instantly, multiple commonly reported bugs have been fixed, and inactive weapon sets no longer contribute to the character stats!<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Based on player feedback, the Heartless, new escort ship from Lex Imperialis, will now appear instantly rather than after finishing repairs in Act IV. Its stats will be a bit lower while in Act II, to represent its damaged state;<br/></li><li> It is no longer possible to land on Thassera without Solomorne under certain circumstances;<br/></li><li> Solomorne no longer inserts himself into some dialogues when he’s not in the party;<br/></li><li> Fixed cases of incorrect behavior of Precognition ability that would sometimes prevent the player from ending the turn;<br/></li><li> Fixed severe FPS drop caused by unexpected interaction between Relentless Blaze and Will to Live. Also fixed Relentless Blaze not counting Soul Burn as burning;<br/></li><li> Fixed desyncs caused by saving during the preparation round;<br/></li><li> Inactive weapon sets no longer provide the weapon bonuses to characters in addition to the active set bonuses.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes 8.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500577186633222898</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Hello Space Marines,</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The 8.1 Hotfix is now live on every platform. It fixes various crashes and connectivity issues, as well as a bug preventing the Helmet reward for Siege Mode to unlock.</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several crashes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed several issues causing disconnects</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Siege Mode rewards from wave 25+</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Lots of small fixes to Siege Mode map geometry</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed bug that was causing random enemies to get stronger much faster in infinite waves, causing one shot deaths randomly (Note: enemies are still going to get stronger but it will be not random and more consistent)</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug in Siege Mode that occurred when a player would join a game in progress, the game would not apply difficulty modifiers correctly.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed a bug in UI that was causing inability to change colour presets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Minor localization fixes</p></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 09:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.6.4 - 30th of June</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546739082808526153</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">This hotfix includes the fixes missing from the Steam version.</p><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h2">Hotfix 6.6.4 - 30th of June</div><div class="bb_h3">Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Necromancer’s flames being orange in the Victory screen.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed an issue where poses wouldn’t work at the end screen after playing Weaves</p></li></ul></blockquote>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
