<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of the Machine God - OUT NOW - Pt. 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068466481708</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Devoted Rejects, </div><i>You are now reading pt. 2 of the patch notes for Secrets of the Machine Gods.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Additional Weapon Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Atrox Mk VII Tactical Axe</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased the range of the Light 2 and Light 3 attacks to be more in line with the Light 1 range, to avoid missing on the following attacks when chaining light attacks at the very edge of the weapon range.</li><li>Tweaked the hitbox of the Light 2 attack to be more aligned with the crosshair position.</li></ul><li><b>Duelling Sword Mk II</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned chain timing for the Heavy 2 attack to be equal when chained from every attack.</li></ul><li><b>Devil's Claw Mk IV </b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed the icon in the Inspect screen for the Light 3 attack to display the correct attack type (changed from Strikedown to Vanguard).</li></ul><li><b>Cadia Mk XIIIg Assault Chainsword</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed the Heavy 3 attack to chain into Light 3 instead of Light 1 to allow for a Vanguard attack loop.</li></ul><li><b>Deimos Mk IV Blaze Force Sword</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where an incorrect push direction was used if an enemy survived the Heavy 2 attack. It will now correctly push enemies away from you, instead of sending them to the right.</li></ul><li><b>Autoguns</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lowered the amount of hits that do increased damage on a critical hit string:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Columbus Mk V Autoguns from 4 to 3</li><li>Braced Autoguns from 3 to 2.</li></ul></ul><li><b>Locke Mk IIb Spearhead Boltgun</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increased ammo reserve from 80 to 100.</li></ul><li><b>Obscurus Mk II Blaze Force Sword</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added a new Heavy Strikedown damage profile for the Heavy 1 attack that suits the actual attack better, including slightly better Weakspot / Critical Hit values.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>First Target:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage increased from 100-200 to 150-350</li><li>Stagger increased from 4-8 to 7-15.</li></ul><li>Second Target:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Damage reduced from 80-160 to 60-130.</li></ul></ul></ul><li><b>Maccabian Mk II Duelling Sword</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a bug where the Heavy 1 attack dealt less damage than it was supposed to do.</li></ul><li>Fixed an issue causing melee weapons to get blood spatters when hitting inanimate damageable objects such as explosive barrels.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Talent and Blessing Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>'Brutal Momentum' weapon blessing: Removed Ogryns as possible enemies whose Hit Mass can be ignored. </li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>The 'Brutal Momentum' blessing paired with powerful Strikedown attacks (like the special activated attack on Ogryn folding shovels) led to possible one-hit kills on multiple stacked Ogryn-type enemies, like Crushers. This expanded too much out of the single target nature of those Strikedown attacks, and also made Strikedown weapons which did not have access to the blessing to feel comparatively less useful in situations where they should have excelled.</i><br/><b>Dev Note: </b><i>This is part of ongoing prep work we are carrying out for itemization. We are curious to collect player thoughts and feedback as we continue optimizing.  </i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘Run 'n' Gun’ </li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Close Damage while sprinting: 10% -&gt; 12%.</li></ul><li>'Perfect Strike'</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 7.5% Crit Chance.</li></ul><li>'Surge'</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 5% Crit Chance.</li></ul><li>‘Focused Channelling’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also removes 30% of Charging Movement Speed Penalties.</li></ul><li>'Blazing Spirit'</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tier 3: </li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stacks Per Crit: 2 -&gt; 3</li><li>Max Stacks: 10 -&gt; 9.</li></ul></ul><li>‘Sunder’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 20% Heavy Melee Damage.</li></ul><li>‘Man-Stopper’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 15% Bonus Impact.</li></ul><li>‘Adhesive Charge’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Now also grants 15% Damage vs Ogryns and Monstrosities.</li></ul><li>‘Infernus’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tier 3:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stacks per crit: 4 -&gt; 3</li><li>Max Stacks: 10 -&gt; 9.</li></ul></ul><li>‘Ceaseless Barrage’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Suppression Bonus: 20% -&gt; 10%</li><li>Damage vs Suppressed: 6% -&gt; 4%.</li></ul><li>‘Blaze Away’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Power Level: 8% -&gt; 7%.</li></ul></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>'Point Blank' weapon blessing: Fixed an issue where the blessing failed to trigger from kills with the primary weapon.</li><li>'Take a Swing' weapon blessing: Fixed an issue where the bonus weakspot damage failed to be added upon triggering the blessing.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Psyker</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed 'Perfect Timing' to trigger once per hit, instead of once per attack.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Ogryn</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the talent 'Bullet Bravado' failed to replenish toughness when shooting projectile-type weapons (e.g. Rumbler, Grenadier Gauntlet).</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Close Range Damage bonus from the Ogryn 'Thick of the Fray' talent was applied also to damage from the primary melee weapon.</li><li>Fixed an issue where stacks of the keystone talent 'Feel No Pain' would be removed incorrectly also when successfully blocking an attack, or when hit by friendly fire.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the talent 'Pacemaker' could fail to be triggered.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the talent 'Crunch' failed to be triggered if the talent 'No Pushover' was also selected.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Blitzes 'Big Box of Hurt'/'Bombs Away' and 'Big Friendly Rock' would fail to instakill Poxbursters and special Mutants spawned from the related Maelstrom mutator.</li><li>Increased the interval in between explosions of 'Big Box of Hurt' from (0.3 - 0.5) To (0.4 - 0.8). </li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b><i> This will reduce the overlap of the staggers, to allow for a slightly longer total Stagger Duration for those hit by the explosions.</i><br/><div class="bb_h3">Zealot</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘Punishment’ </li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Impact per Stack: 30% -&gt; 5%. The ‘Uninterruptible’ bonus still remains the same.</li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>A total of 150% Stagger left very little room for other bonuses such as ‘Hammer of Faith’ and various Weapon Blessings.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘Chastise the Wicked’ and ‘Fury of the Faithful’</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>100% Rending -&gt; 100% Melee Rending</li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This talent was always intended to emphasize the melee prowess of Zealots allowing them to charge up to enemies and devastating them with their melee attacks. This change is made to bring this talent back to its intended purpose.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Combat</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Bolt-type Explosions</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Bolt-type explosions are now always the same size, no matter if they hit or kill.</li><li>Added additional damage to the explosion when killing an enemy.</li><li>Removed the VFX explosion effect on close range hits where the bolt does not have time to prime the explosive package.</li></ul><li>Fixed an issue where the visual targeting effect of the secondary attack of Trauma Force Staves was mismatched to the actual explosion radius.</li><li>Fixed an issue where it was not possible to cancel into a block while starting an heavy attack with Force Swords.</li><li>Updated reflector pattern and colour of weapon flashlights. There are now specific styles of flashlights used for Infantry Lasguns, Recon Lasguns, Infantry Autoguns, and the Shredder Autopistol, instead of all sharing the same.</li><li>Fixed issue that could cause some players to be left behind when hogtied players were moved further ahead.</li><li>Made improvements to placement of rescued hang ledged players to avoid them being placed on the wrong floor.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players grabbed by a disabler enemy could fall through elevator floors once released.</li><li>Fixed a multitude of hang ledges issues.</li><li>Changed so that all player shots ignore body mass from other players.</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>Before, only attacks from specific weapons were able to go through players, but now shots from every weapon should be able to.</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">Enemies</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a crash that could occur when dodging into enemies while performing a chain-weapon sawing attack.</li><li>Fixed a case where enemies could appear burned also from non-burning effects.</li><li>Fixed a case where the Pox Hound leap could fail if staggered during approach.</li><li>Fixed Martyr's skull doors being already opened by enemies.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Missions</div><b>Smelter Complex HL17-36: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In the mid event enemies can now path to the platform above the elevator and can shoot from there.</li><li>The end event now has a new stage where players turn valves to restart the smelter.</li><li>Minor tweaks and adjustments to the end event area, added guardrails and covers for enemies.</li><li>Tweaked the difficulty of the event spawning to provide a better challenge.</li><li>Reduced camping scenarios by the extract door at the end event.</li><li>Fixed enemies that could spawn inside the Martyr's skull room.</li><li>Re-worked the area after the airlock in The 'Fab to have a more organic game flow and in-world purpose.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>With this change we wanted to show a bit more of the ongoing battle for Tertium and how it's affecting pre-existing areas and structures.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All corruptors in The Foundry will now be active from the start, allowing players to choose their approach. Additionally, we've made some performance improvements and art updates to the area.</li></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>We wanted to try adding some more agency to events, please let us know what you think of this more open approach.</i><br/><b>Enclavum Baross:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The mid event now has more spawn locations for enemies.</li><li>The mid event now has power core spawners more spread out.</li><li>The end event now has the lower part of the landing pad as an enterable area.</li><li>The location for the batteries in the "Lower the Skylink" event section have been moved around, and additional variety to the enemy spawn locations has been added to the side spaces next to the control room.</li></ul><b>Mercantile HL-70-04:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaks and adjustments to the end event layout.</li><li>Added a drop leading into the end event area.</li></ul><b>Dev note: </b><i>The corridor leading to the end event funnelled enemies into a too easily defended chokepoint, and therefore was the de facto best area for players to fight in, ultimately turning most of the huge play space to be unused. This change will force players to enter the arena proper and engage straight on with enemies.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where enemies could spawn inside an unintended area of the penance puzzle.</li><li>Fixed indestructible heretical icon.</li><li>Fixed issues with the pickup spawning.</li></ul><b>Consignment Yard HL17-36:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added more spawn locations and teleporters for enemies.</li><li>Removed a hacking point on the balcony in the mid event and expanded the open space to add another hacking point there. Increased the amount of enemies spawned on the balcony and intensified the event. </li><li>Increased the number of AA-guns that are needed to be destroyed in the end event and decreased the fortification time afterwards to compensate. Increased the overall intensity of the event. </li></ul><b>Magistrati Oubliette TM8-707: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added more covers to allow more ranged combat to happen over the chasm before the mid event. </li><li>Added more spawners and teleporters for enemies.</li><li>Made it possible for enemies to shoot from above in mid event and increased the amount of places where they could drop down to make it harder for players to camp the spawns. Increased overall intensity of the event. </li><li>Increased the amount of spawners and intensity of the end event.</li><li>Added a lever in the Martyr's skull puzzle area to prevent players to get softlocked.</li></ul><b>Silo Cluster 18-66/a:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added more enemy spawners.</li><li>Changed spawners and enemy pathing in the end event.</li><li>Tweaks and adjustments to the geometry in the end event.</li><li>Minor general tweaks to covers and hang ledges.</li></ul><b>Ascension Riser 31: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minor tweaks to event enemy spawning and smoother level collisions to provide better player navigation.</li><li>Fixed location where enemies could spawn and clip through a wall.</li><li>Fixed an issue where players could land on top of an elevator and get stuck.</li></ul><b>Excise Vault Spireside-13:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minor art and layout changes.</li><li>Added an additional decode location in the mid event.</li></ul>Chasm Logistratum:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Moved the end event respawn beacon location.</li><li>Tweaked geometry and covers, especially in the broken tunnel section for smoother player navigation.</li><li>Removed a ladder at the end event and replaced it with crates.</li></ul><b>Chasm Station HL-16-11: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The end event traitor captain now spawns inside one of the two trains.</li></ul><b>Power Matrix HL-17-36:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minor layout changes.</li><li>Added a side walkway above the steel conveyors in The 'Fab to broaden the traversal options.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This area would often become a very tight and unforgiving corridor, the new side path connects it up in a way that should alleviate it and give a new one-way backtracking drop.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a spot where players could end up floating mid air.</li></ul><b>Refinery Delta-17: </b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed players not respawning at the mid event respawn beacon before its activation and completion.</li></ul><b>Hab Dreyko: </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minor tweaks and adjustments to level for smoother collisions and layout.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Ogryn characters could pick up the Martyr skull without solving the puzzle.</li></ul><b>Comms-Plex 154/2f:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tweaked the difficulty of the event spawning to provide a better challenge.</li></ul>Vigil Station Oblivium: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added line of sight blockers to prevent snipers from shooting through walls in a specific location.</li><li>Added more spawners and variety of enemy compositions in mid event.</li><li>Reworked parts of the end event to make the gameplay space less filled with chokepoints. Increased the overall intensity.</li></ul><b>Warren 6-19:</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where enemies could potentially open the gate to the penance puzzle.</li></ul><b>Relay Station TRS-150:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed places where players could find a way to get out of gameplay space.</li></ul><b>Archivum Sycorax:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed walls that would not break when monstrosities broke through it.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">VO and Audio </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue that caused "out of ammo" sounds to play every frame when trying to shoot automatic fire weapons without any ammo in reserve nor magazine.</li><li>Added custom VO lines for Zealot Chorus of Spiritual Fortitude.</li><li>Added more banter responses for female Veteran Cutthroat.</li><li>Hestia may now be a mission handler for Enclavum Baross.</li><li>Implemented male Zealot Fanatic killstreak responses.</li><li>Added some new Mourningstar announcement VO.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">HUD/UI</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Using the Tactical Overlay now blocks interactions in the Mourningstar.</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>This was done to avoid triggering other actions in the Mourningstar while browsing the tactical overlay.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The Change Tactical Overlay Tab key can now be rebound.</li><li>Fixed issues where the auspex would not aim directly towards some scan targets.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the "Title Colour in The Mourningstar" and "Title Colour in Missions" options didn't reset when selecting "Reset to default settings".</li><li>The locked emotes now show on all emote slots when looking at equipping them in the inventory.</li><li>Fixed an issue where a player could sell the wrong weapon because a new weapon got selected after the confirmation timer started.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetics</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Voice modulation effects granted from a large amount of cosmetic headgears are now more noticeable than before.</li><li>Added opacity dithering to hair, which will improve the overall quality of hair rendering. </li><li>Fixed an issue where boots could clip with pants on multiple Zealot lower body cosmetics rewarded from Penances.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Veteran “Veteran’s Sentry Uniform” cosmetic upper body right hand was clipping through the glove.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the arms would clip with the vest on the sides of the Ogryn “Hired Muscle Leathers (Sub-level 101)” upper body cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed the Psyker “Scryer's Mantle With Psykhana Collar” headgear cosmetic removing hair completely.</li><li>Fixed an issue where ponytails would clip on the Psyker “Witchshroud” headgear cosmetic reward.</li><li>Fixed the Veteran “Arges Pattern Augmetic” headgear cosmetic incorrectly removing eyebrows.</li><li>Fixed instances of the “Mortis Rag Mask” headgear cosmetic clipping with the ears.</li><li>Fixed clipping issues on the Zealot “Cowl of the Avenger” headgear cosmetic reward.</li><li>Fixed some minor visual issues on the Veteran "Atoman Pattern Combat Helm with Rebreather" headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Zealot “Krieg Greatcoat (Marked by Faith)” upper body cosmetic’s shoulder candle light did not show up as intended. </li><li>Fix for an issue related to clipping on the Zealot “Ecclesiarchy-Approved Diadem (Words Of Faith Pattern)” headgear cosmetic while viewing it in your loadout. </li><li>Fixed an issue where the Zealot “Phaeton Pattern Rebreather” cosmetic headgear failed to modify the operative’s voice.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Miscellaneous</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where button mapping could be reset or incorrect on controllers when booting up the game if a non-default layout was selected.</li><li>Fixed a text issue in the descriptions of the Veteran Executioner’s Stance talent and other talents referencing it.</li><li>"Completed" in the penance menu is now translated into other languages.</li><li>Addressed a uniform infringement on an NPC Guard stationed by the Psykhanium on the Mourningstar.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of the Machine God - OUT NOW! - Pt. 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4207006068466422880</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6b698eb0c51ff1190a5715d18b8a87bcbbeb011e.jpg"/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zk9U-4jU93w?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Devoted Rejects,</div> <br/><br/>Here are the patch notes for our latest update, Secrets of the Machine God, which just went live on Steam and it will shortly be available on our other platforms.<br/><br/><i>NOTE: Because the patch notes are so long, we are posting in two parts.</i><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Mission: Clandestium Gloriana</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/0e1f02809ff44a4ae7f2f15f75481e9679d8017d.jpg"/><br/>The new mission, Clandestium Gloriana (previously mentioned as Atelium Foundryplex Omega V), sees our brave strike teams venture deep into the forgotten heart of Tertium for a rendezvous with a mysterious new character. The players are tasked with reawakening a long-dormant Adeptus Mechanicus Foundryplex, one of the fabled, lost Machinaria Gloriana. This level presents a new, frozen environment, sees a mission-giver accompany the strike team within the gameplay space and supports greater replayability with a new, variable end event. We're delighted with how it's turned out and we hope you'll enjoy playing it as much as we did making it!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7b510dfafd541ef80db3dd8fd4f1d12d94059b8b.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New In-Game Event: Test Your Metal</div><br/>Clandestium Gloriana’s awakening brings greater resources to the war effort. New weapons have been added to the armoury. Take up these arms and smite the enemies of the Imperium.<br/><br/>Use the Bolt Pistol, Double-Barrelled Shotgun, Shock Maul or Pickaxe to kill Elite and Specialist enemies. Qualifying kills from all party members count.<br/><br/>This event will start on Thursday, 27 June. The rewards will be Ordo Dockets, Plasteel and Diamantine. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/2b2c805cdf83cd7a6aaa86be6e795533313af8f1.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">New Weapons</div><i>Message from Hadron:</i> <br/>Listen up, Varlets. The awakening of the Clandestium Gloriana has opened new supply lines, increasing the arsenal available to the Rejects. All praise the Omnissiah. With these sacred tools, available to requisition from Brunt’s Armoury, the Heretics will find no respite from our blessed fury. Take up these arms and deliver unto our foe a fate deserving of such base treachery.<br/><br/><i>Availability </i><br/>The Pickaxes will be available for Ogryns, while the Shock Mauls, the Double Barreled Shotgun and the Bolt Pistol will be available for the Veteran, Zealot and Psyker classes.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Pickaxes</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/8cbf546ff3d4e346f111a4c17ead90911ce0f469.jpg"/><br/>Ogryns’ first two-handed weapon! Taking brutality and force to a new level.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Branx Pickaxe - Heavy</b></li><li><b>Borovian Pickaxe - Medium</b></li><li><b>Karsolas Pickaxe - Light</b></li></ul>For these weapons, we really wanted to lean into the differences in the Heavy, Medium and Light between marks in terms of speed, handling and purpose.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Heavy </b>is Strikedown focus, using the pickaxe as it was meant to be used on heretics skulls and with a powerful bash attack as weapon special.</li><li><b>Medium </b>is somewhere in between both in terms of handling and damage, with a mix of Strikedown and vanguard attacks and a hook pull as a weapon special that sets up enemies for big damage. </li><li><b>Light</b> is horde control focus with wide sweeps and more cleave, and a pull weapon special like the medium pickaxe. </li></ul>These weapons have big damage and impact.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Shock Mauls</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/bc59c3ad98328d59a27938a0f3b58da677f37237.jpg"/><br/>The perfect Warhammer 40,000 riot gear, an electric weapon that stuns and adds a shocked status to enemies.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Agni Mk Ia Shock Maul</b></li><li><b>Indignatus Mk III Shock Maul</b></li></ul>Two words: stun and impact. They are versatile weapons with rich movesets; the mark difference relates to the moveset variance, with the Agni MK la having more immediate access to Strikedown attacks and the Indignatus Mk III having delayed access to a looping heavy Strikedown chain.<br/><br/>The weapon special is a “cattle prod poke” that adds damage over time and keeps enemies stunned.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Double Barreled Shotgun</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/445299ec438b48a95de870187b4890c0b001d8f9.jpg"/><br/>A very close range and nervous shotgun that inflicts brutal damage and impact.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Ironhelm "Hacker" Mk IV Assault Shotgun</b></li></ul>With fast handling and movement speed, this shotgun supports Assault-style game play.<br/>Access the bracing stance with the secondary action to shoot both barrels at the same time (for maximum carnage). The weapon special is a weapon bash combo. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bolt Pistol</div><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7985048f4df79a3093dfd19b4e1e4d25b735fa2a.jpg"/><br/>An iconic Warhammer 40,000 weapon, mobile and perfect to lead an assault.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Godwyn-Branx Pattern Bolt Pistol</b></li></ul>Better handling and faster reload, but more difficult to control than the Boltgun version. The weapon special is a bash, which can be combo’ed into a hipfire shot. <br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Features and QoL</div><div class="bb_h2">Mission Updates from Community Feedback</div>We’ve made a number of changes to existing missions in this update based on player feedback. The detailed changes are listed further down.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Updated Crosshairs</div>Crosshairs have had a two-fold issue:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>They were in general larger than what the spread system (which handles how much a shot will deviate from where the barrel is pointing) was using.</li><li>They were affected by the Field of View and HUD Scale user settings.</li></ul>The combined effect of this was that at default settings shots would hit approximately within the centre 50-75% areas of the extents of any given crosshair, meaning that the crosshair itself was not a reliable way to gauge the extent of the weapon spread.<br/><br/>Additionally, increasing the Field of View would make the crosshair appear larger, while decreasing the FoV, especially when combined with lowering the HUD Scale, would make the crosshair appear smaller.<br/><br/>Fixing the first issue meant that several crosshairs now started to overlap with hit markers, which led to redesigning most of the crosshairs, as well as the hit markers themselves.<br/><br/>Hit markers are now slightly smaller and have an outline to be easier to see against light backgrounds. The major changes are that we now use a different hit marker for weakspot hits, to differentiate them from critical strike hits. <br/><br/>Weakspot hit markers are now doubled up, and like non-weakspot hits colour coded according to the type of hit (white = standard, blue = no or reduced damage, orange = critical strike, red = kill). <br/><b>Dev Note: </b><i>Previously both weakspot hits and critical strike hits were coloured orange.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/6043ab482b4b4c2e3f33189f4eab106c54d99c0d.png"/><br/><i>Standard Kill</i><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/dad0a7eceebcbbdda09ebd344f8b92e187d0f693.png"/><br/><i>Weakspot Kill </i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/fa37f9527f19caf6fa3d1f860104802cb1d41d66.png"/><br/><i>Standard No Damage </i><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/bba5676ce79c92e5415037072fd5f9f17e25e0f4.png"/><br/><i>Weakspot No Damage </i><br/>The major reason for this change is primarily due to several Blessings and Talents being triggered by either weakspot hits or critical strikes, and this change should hopefully make it easier to understand which hits should (or shouldn't) trigger a specific bonus. Plus it's satisfying knowing that the heretic killed died from a masterful blow to the head.<br/><br/><b>Crosshairs </b>have been categorised in several categories, each with their own style of crosshair that always leaves an empty space for hit markers no matter how high or low the weapon’s spread is.<br/><br/>All weapons have been categorised into one of these categories and by extension hit markers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>"Rapid Fire" for accurate single-shot or burst weapons, such as Infantry Lasguns or Headhunter Autoguns.</li><li>"Assault" for mid-range high rate of fire weapons, such as Infantry Autoguns or Shredder Autopistols.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>"Heavy" for slow-firing high-damage weapons, such as Quickdraw Stubrevolvers or Plasma Guns.</li><li>"Spreadshot" for pellet weapons, such as Combat Shotguns or Ripper Guns.</li><li>"Torrent" for inaccurate high-volume fire weapons, such as Twin-Linked Heavy Stubbers or alternate fire for Braced Autoguns.</li><li>"Flamer" for, well, Flamers.</li><li>"Dot" for melee weapons and Force Staves.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/1a8b02d13a70c0f4608833d78cd6d941d5f986c0.png"/><i>Old Assault Crosshair</i><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/5dff1e384e18e3306c7568942f6fda268b79bf74.png"/><i>New Assault Crosshair</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/2a45cef10921032561419c49908cdd26baed5736.png"/><i>Old Heavy Crosshair</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9d022196ec3101297321ad424775aa5328feb32a.png"/><i>New Heavy Crosshair </i><br/><br/>In addition, there are a few new user settings to tweak and change the look and behaviour of crosshairs and hit markers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Turn on/off crosshairs, aim trajectories, and/or hit markers.</li><li>Increase the time for which hit markers are shown.</li><li>Override all crosshairs with a specific style.</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The “Flamer” type is not available for the override. </li></ul></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/7deb33b432bab67f37c5dff7933fafe67874d281.png"/><br/><br/><b>Known Issues for Crosshairs </b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>"Crosshair Type" user settings don't revert when using the "Reset to default settings" button.</li><li>Force Staves incorrectly have their crosshairs overridden when using anything but the "Weapon Specific" option of "Crosshair Type".</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Headgear Voice Preview Option</div>Players can now preview the voice of any headgear which their operative can equip, including ones that modulate their voice. This preview is currently available by going into the Inspect to Show on Operative menu.<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/11a576064fa0523f826b7690ab1f79f04c499beb.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Sound Changes to Footsteps for Prosthetic Leg Cosmetics</div>The footsteps of your character while wearing a lower body cosmetic item that has a prosthetic will now sound different, to better match the visual and be closer paired with your actual gait. These items have a small icon on the item preview tiles, as well as a clarifying text in the item details.<br/><br/><b>Dev note:</b> <i>This is more noticeable in active gameplay/first person view, while footsteps in general are more subdued in the Mourningstar/third person view. </i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Bug Fixes and Changes</div><div class="bb_h2">Weapon Changes</div><b>Recon Lasguns</b><br/><br/>The Recon Lasguns, while having a really iconic and fun playstyle, failed to perform adequately due to a mix of low punching power and struggling ammo economy, especially when rising up in difficulties.<br/><br/>We performed a balance pass on every mark, strengthening their identity as assault, almost recoilless full-auto rifles while also inserting some peculiarities on each mark, while keeping some of their weaknesses (such as difficulty to pierce Carapace armoured enemies).<br/><br/>The MkII version received a significant base power bump, remaining a good all-rounder for the category.<br/><br/>The MkVId mostly maintained its previous base power profile, but received hefty buffs in fire speed and magazine size to lay down suppressing fire and reward keeping the aim on the targets.<br/><br/>Finally, the MkVIIa place as the heavy variant was confirmed by a further increase in its base attack and impact power values. To help with its increased ammo consumption per shot compared to the other two marks, we significantly increased the total ammo in reserve.<br/><br/>We will monitor the performance of the weapons and your feedback after the changes to evaluate possible additional adjustments!<br/><br/><b>Detailed changes:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>All Marks</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slightly increased the hipfire spread.</li><li>Upgraded the Dodge, Sprint and Aimed Movement templates to the Assault and bespoke Recon Lasgun profiles.</li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This will make the weapons more suited for agile engagements compared to other rifles like the Infantry Lasguns.</i><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Accatran Mk II Recon Lasgun</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack power distribution {40,70} to {78,108}</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Maniac 0.75 to 0.8 (near), 0.65 to 0.7 (far)</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Infested and Unarmoured 1.25 to 1.0 (near)</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Flak down to 0.75 (near), 0.5 (far)</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Unyielding down to 0.75 (near)</li><li>Impact modifier against Unyielding upped to 1.0 (near), down to 0.5 (far).</li></ul><li><b>Accatran Mk VId Recon Lasgun</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Set bespoke power distribution values:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack = {40,70} (unchanged)</li><li>Impact = {1.0,2.0} (unchanged).</li></ul><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Unarmoured 0.9 to 1.0 (near).</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Maniac 0.6 to 0.8 (near).</li><li>Fire rate from 16.77 to 20.00.</li><li>Magazine size from 60-120 to 100-200.</li><li>Removed one magazine in reserve (60x5-120x6 to 100x4-200x5).</li><li>Reload and Wield speed time slowed by 20%.</li></ul><li><b>Accatran Mk VIIa Recon Lasgun</b></li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Set bespoke power distribution values:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack = {95,165} (around 33% buff)</li><li>Impact = {1.5,3.0} (around 10% buff).</li></ul><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Flak 1 to 0.75 (near).</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Unyielding from 1 to 0.75 (near).</li><li>Added two magazines in reserve (60x5-120x6 to 60x7-120x8).</li></ul></ul><br/><b>Achlys Mk I Power Maul</b><br/>The power budget of the Ogryn Power Maul (aka “Paul”) was very unbalanced towards its Special activated attacks, while the rest of the moveset remained anaemic. This made spamming Light activated attacks often the optimal attack rotation for the weapon, leading to a very monotonous (and still underwhelming) experience.<br/><br/>We rebalanced the whole moveset, significantly increasing the usability of both standard Light and Heavy attacks while leaving the stagger and power of activated attacks mostly unchanged.<br/><br/>We also added a new Vanguard Light attack performed during a Slide, and new attack chains which will reward mastering the weapon by performing the correct attack strings in different situations.<br/><br/>For example, players could lead with an activated Heavy 1 into a flurry of Light Strikedowns (Special activate &gt; H1 &gt; LFollow-up &gt; L1 &gt; L2 &gt; repeat) to quickly pile on damage on priority targets while keeping players safe due to the initial staggering explosion; or clear crowds by reaching the Light 3 &gt; Light 4 attack loop through Heavy attacks or the brand new Light slide attack (H1 &gt; H2 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; ... / LSlide &gt; L4 &gt; L3 &gt; L4 &gt; ...).<br/><br/>We will monitor the performance of the weapon and player feedback after the changes to evaluate possible additional adjustments!<br/><br/><b>Detailed changes:</b><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light follow-up attack from Heavy 1 changed from Vanguard to Strikedown damage profile</li><li>Heavy 2 now chains into Light 3 / Heavy 1 (instead of Light 1 / Heavy 1)</li><li>Added an attack start from Slide, chaining into Heavy 1 and a new Light slide attack with Vanguard profile (same as Light 3 / Light 4):</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The new Light slide attack chains into Light 4 / Heavy 2.</li></ul><li>Lowered the total action time of the Special activate action from 2.6 to 1.2 seconds.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>Activation time will remain unaffected at 0.8 seconds, but it will be easier to chain into the new Light slide attack.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aligned windup time for all Heavy attacks to 0.6 seconds</li></ul><b>Dev note:</b> <i>"Windup time" is the minimum amount of time an Heavy attack needs to be charged before being released</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 1 / Light 2 Strikedown profile:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Changed stagger duration from {0.1, 0.5} to {0.1, 2.5}</li><li>Changed inherent finesse boost multiplier from 0.25 to 1</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Maniac from 0.5 to 0.75</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Carapace armour from 0.25 to 0.5</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Flak armour from 1 to 0.9</li><li>Equalised finesse boost to 0.5 against all armour types.</li></ul><li>Light 3 / Light 4 Vanguard profile:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Flak from 0.75 to 0.9</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Unyielding from 0.75 to 0.8</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Maniac from 0.5 to 0.7</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Carapace from 0.25 to 0.65</li><li>Cleave from medium to big</li><li>Added a 4th target damage profile</li><li>Power distribution from 1st (target) {60,120} / 2nd {35,70} / 3rd {25,50} / 4th n/a / Default {10,20} to 1st {80,150} / 2nd {60,110} / 3rd {40,80} / 4th {25,60} / Default {10,30}.</li></ul></ul><b>Dev Note: </b><i>These changes will be also applied to the Ogryn Slab Shield L3 and L4 attacks.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Light 3 / Light 4 Vanguard Special activated profile:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Power distribution override from {90,165} to {120,200}.</li></ul><li>Heavy 1 / Heavy 2 Relentless profile:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Flak from 0.75 to 0.9</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Unyielding from 1 to 0.8</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Maniac from 0.5 to 0.8</li><li>Armor Damage Modifier against Carapace from 0.25 to 0.75</li><li>Power distribution from 1st (target) {120,220} / 2nd {80,110} / 3rd {20,30} / 4th {10,25} / Default {5,10} to 1st {175,350} / 2nd {80,160} / 3rd {60,120} / 4th {50,100} / Default {40,80}.</li></ul><li>Heavy 1 / Heavy 2 Relentless Special activated profile:</li><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Power distribution override from {220,440} to {250,475}.</li></ul></ul><br/><i>Please continue reading via pt. 2.</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 5.1 and Karanak OUT NOW!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/6018578477454128372</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/3d83578fbc5bc71a3446939d0a26a848d6b2556c.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings everyone!<br/><br/>Patch 5.1 is live and Karanak is ready to join you on the battlefield! ⚔️ (Just don't forget the pats and treats)<br/><br/>👀 Find out how to claim Karanak here: <br/><br/>How to claim Karanak FAQ<br/><br/>We've also made some amendments to yesterday's patch notes, with a couple of extra items and some tweaks to the abilities sections to make the changes clearer - for those who missed them yesterday, you can read the full list in our Patch Notes 5.1.0 blog post.<br/><br/>We'll be back soon with more news, so until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebalance in the Koronus Expanse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4185613970223713932</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c3be0fd9f2bee2f3b6a9e12110a198fc77d1c812.jpg"/><br/><br/>Greetings, Lord Captains! <br/><br/>Rogue Trader has already been out for some time, and our team has not been sitting idle. <br/><br/>While working on fixes and improvements for the game (a <b>massive</b> 2,500+ changes are coming very soon in patch 1.2), we’ve also accumulated a lot of important data concerning character progression and player’s reception of the game’s various systems thanks to both your feedback and extensive internal analysis.<br/><br/>Having already dealt with most of the critical bugs, we felt that the upcoming patch would be a great time to revisit game balance. With these balance changes, we are aiming to provide a better challenge, offer more interesting gameplay, and expand the variety of viable builds, especially on higher difficulties.<br/><br/>To do this, we identified the list of key problems that we felt had the biggest negative impact on player experience. These were split into four major categories:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Excess of additional turns<br/></li><li> Overscaling in the late game<br/></li><li> Sanctioned psykers and pyromancy<br/></li><li> Arch-militant overtuning</li></ul>Let’s talk about each of them in detail.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Excess of Additional Turns</div>While the original design felt engaging, it appears that, in the end, we went too far with the abundance of out-of-sequence turns and attacks. Stacking additional turns gives such a dominating advantage that players who utilize it can entirely trivialize combat, sometimes to the point where the enemy doesn’t even get to take a single turn!<br/><br/>Tuning things like this has to be done carefully and in batches in order to prevent overnerfing, so we began with tweaks to the Officer in patch 1.1. In 1.2, we’re going a step further and implementing major changes to a whole set of abilities that provide additional turns and AP. We want them to stay true to their spirit but do something entirely different than before.<br/><br/>For example, <b>Seize the Initiative</b> no longer provides an additional turn to the Officer, instead allowing the Officer and allies under the effect of the Officer's <b>Voice of Command</b> to deal additional damage to enemies that have not yet acted in combat.<br/><br/><b>In the Hero’s Footsteps</b> now provides a stacking +5 Fellowship bonus when an ally uses a Heroic act and a +5 Toughness bonus when using Desperate measures instead of providing an additional turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/aa2e889596e44a47bb64918f6c876e61bc7b700d.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Overscaling in the Late Game</div><br/>Our players are very quick at finding the most effective combinations, but let’s be honest, those single shots for 1.5 million damage that we’ve seen on some player videos were somewhat… beyond our expectations.<br/><br/>Some of these crazy numbers were indeed caused by bugs, but putting those aside, there were still a handful of items and abilities in the game with multiplicative scaling that did silly things when stacked. While seeing 8-digit damage values is fun to an extent, the sheer amount and availability of such options removed the element of challenge, which we believe is not healthy for the overall game experience.<br/><br/>To address this, we’ve updated a lot of abilities, items, and talents across the game that provided multiplicative bonuses (such as 3 x <b>Intelligence bonus</b>) to give flat bonuses instead (for example, 10 + <b>Intelligence bonus</b>), tweaked some percentage based bonuses to be stronger in the early game but less devastating in late game (such as the Operative’s <b>Offensive Pattern Prediction</b>, the Navigator’s <b>Reveal the Light</b> or the Exemplar’s <b>Deadeye Shot</b>), and fixed a handful of bugs with incorrect scaling such as <b>Confident Approach</b>.<br/><br/><b>Killing Edge </b>was also tuned down, being one of the main offenders that caused skyrocketing numbers.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/e00914b7e51e1b702d6ef37dd8901044f539d205.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Sanctioned Psykers and Pyromancy</div><br/>Looking at sanctioned psykers prior to this update, we felt that they were always at a significant disadvantage compared to Idira and her higher psy rating.<br/><br/>We have now made it so that sanctioned psykers can take psy rating-increasing talents earlier (at levels 4/14/24/34 instead of 10/20/30/40). This will not only reduce the eventual difference in psy rating when compared to unsanctioned psykers, but it will also allow sanctioned psykers to take advanced psychic powers earlier. <br/><br/>Unsanctioned psykers can now also take those talents a bit earlier (at levels 9/19/29/39), mostly so that different archetypes have similar access to advanced psychic powers.<br/><br/>With these changes, we hope to achieve a certain parity, where the sanctioned psykers will still have a somewhat lower psy rating but will be able to take higher-level psychic powers earlier in order to compensate. <br/><br/>This wasn't our only change to psykers. For a while, we were concerned that the pyromancer, who was always supposed to be a dedicated damage dealer among psykers, had a weaker damage potential than a telepath (and we received a lot of player feedback about it, as well). In this patch we’re significantly boosting damage numbers for most of the pyromancy psychic powers, starting with <b>Ignite</b> — it now deals vastly increased damage, and pyromancers no longer need to rely on conventional weapons for the first half of the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c4e987d48bea8a7f66b3c60ab329478e6b74d4e2.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Arch-Militant Overtuning</div><br/>According to our observations and community surveys, the Arch-Militant remains the most effective archetype, with a damage potential so high that skilled players could stack bonuses from versatility extremely quickly, gaining a significant advantage. We’ve slightly reduced versatility generation and scaling from it to put the Arch-Militant more in line with the rest of the archetypes. In particular, we’ve made changes to <b>Confident Approach</b>, <b>Reckless Rush</b>, and <b>Wildfire</b>. Note that we don’t intend to nerf the Arch-Militant into the ground — it will still be very effective, but the numbers will be a bit more reasonable.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/9ac1ef8e0c22acc6843ccc1324a6e85e5ad3e162.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Plans for the Future</div><br/>Our work on combat balance is far from over. However, after this batch of changes and considering the massive wave of bug fixes that are coming with 1.2, we would like to spend some time assessing the performance of the updated archetypes and analysing the feedback from our players. Although we understand that some of you may end up frustrated with losing your archetype power fantasy, many of these changes are necessary for the game to deliver the experience we envision. Let us know what you think — we need to be sure that we’re going in the right direction!<br/><br/>Later, we intend to go over all encounters that are either known to be difficulty spikes or feel too easy for their level and tune them accordingly.<br/><br/>Lastly, although a bit unrelated, you may have seen in our roadmap and known issues thread on Steam that we recognized the limited availability of conviction points. We’ve received a lot of feedback that their distribution is uneven and scarce, forcing players to make certain decisions in fear of being locked out of conviction levels. We’re working to address this, but unfortunately, we are not yet ready to ship it with 1.2. We expect it to come a bit later, in one of the following updates.<br/><br/>Thank you for taking the time to read this. See you very soon in 1.2, where you will be able to see all the changes yourself, and looking forward to hearing your feedback!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - 5.1.0 Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4208126895057497131</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/08deb2d7f95c4d664f3481b7022224525f6aac36.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks!<br/><br/>Patch 5.1 is finally upon us, arriving Tuesday 25th June, and with it comes the baddest good boy there ever was - Karanak, the three-headed Hound of Vengeance - as a FREE Legendendary Hero!<br/><br/>In anticipation of tomorrow's release, you can now check out the full list of changes coming in Patch 5.1.0 in our comprehensive Patch Notes.<br/><br/>Read Patch Notes 5.1.0<br/><br/>Following the release of Update 5.1 tomorrow (we're expecting to release this at 11AM BST, Tuesday 25th June), look forward to us returning to you this Wednesday with a look at What's Next in Total War: WARHAMMER III. We're excited to share with you all more news about our next Update, and to give some more detail around the additions we're making to Khorne, Ogres, and Greenskins.<br/><br/>Until then, we'll see you on the battlefield! (Karanak says woof woof woof)<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
