<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>💥 News - 2024 Wrap Up 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/524203331331031095</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/147b1768aae9ac663c50a5fec47f3ba790647d05.png"/><br/>Oi Speed Freeks,<br/><br/>Firstly, we want to give you our greenest thanks to you gits for playing Speed Freeks during its Early Access phase. Since the launch in August, da Mek Boyz have nabbed and utilized your feedback to make a ton of fixes and quality of life improvements, plus changes to game modes, maps and vehicles.  This has led to a really solid foundation for the game, and it’s been truly humbling to see all of your positive comments and hear about all the fun players are having.<br/><br/>This week Early Access Update #4 landed which continues to grow and evolve the game into something we hope you’ll enjoy coming back to for a long time. This patch greatly improves Deff Rally mode, adding more racing and dynamic combat encounters, plus adds alternate weapons/abilities for some vehicles as a limited time mode, creating armament variety for each class.  It also brings the usual improvements we’ve been doing since launch in terms of bug fixes and quality of life stuff for the game. If you’ve not grabbed it yet, get on it!<br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/302045a8e552b15b6f7bdba12f6cc56723b6a4b5.png"/><br/>We want your feedback!<br/><br/>Closing out the end of 2024 and looking to the future, we want to hear from our valued community as we continue to roar through the grimdark wasteland together. This new survey will help us better understand what is important to you gits, with the results directly influencing our ongoing development of the game. So please give it a shot below!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/dffc9865e78ec717e30a35320c40c6a47c727808.png"/><div class="bb_h2"><b>Click for Feedback Survey</b></div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/87acda9033493108f66ab7c96205a970c7120a29.png"/><br/>In terms of the next update, rest assured that we are hard at work developing new features and improvements, including a more traditional Combat Racing game mode prototype -  which we want to get into your hands to start playing as soon as possible. As usual, we’re going to develop this feature alongside your feedback, and especially in this case, where it will become a permanent mode for the game in the future.<br/><br/>Further on from that next patch, we’re speeding towards the full launch of this game out of early access and into version 1.0.  We’ve got some really exciting things coming with that version and will be sharing some info about it in the new year. We can’t say much yet, but there will be a lot to look forward to in 2025 and beyond, so keep yer enginez burnin’ n’ yer dakka ready! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/995ffe8e717de04ab7a9f557c54780e617c1da15.png"/><br/><br/>Our ultimate goal is to make Speed Freeks one of the greatest combat racing games of all time, and as we solidify the base game towards it’s full release, we’re confident it will be a rich and rewarding experience for Warhammer 40,000 Ork fans and general vehicular combat fans alike. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bff6e97958bf7cec3025c8f54db27b7e22dbc4ee.png"/><br/>Before we forget, here’s a bit of a sneak peek showing a new map coming your way next year called Da Dust Up! This map starts in an Ork fortress up on a big hill, then speeds down into the valley for some intense racin’ and fightin’.  We’ll drop more info about this map and others as we get closer to their release.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/45e28095664ec8f8352612f4ff3fe3b58e7e3b76.png"/><br/>Finally, a proppa big thanks again to all you’z gits for being a part of this important development period called Early Access. You’ve had, and will continue to have, a substantial impact on the game as a whole. As much as it can be difficult to have the game live during this time, we are truly thankful to have you on this journey with us and encourage you to keep helping us through this fun and experimental phase of game development. <br/><br/>It really motivates us to have such dedicated and crazed fans of the game already and also gives us confidence of where this game can go in the future.<br/><br/>As always, feel free to drop your feedback and suggestions in the comments or the usual social spaces linked below. If there’s anything you think really needs fixing or improving, or if you have a feature suggestion that you think will have a big impact on the game, we’re happy to hear about it. <br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks! <br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Ultima Founding out now</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/521951078763202513</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
The Primaris are ready to step in the battle for the God Emperor and the Holy Throne. Eight new units and unique gameplay mechanics will give you more options for the fight for Gladius Prime.<br/><br/>These new units are available now:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Primaris Aggressor: Close-quarters anti-infantry unit equipped with flamestorm gauntlets.<br/></li><li> Primaris Hellblaster: Heavy armour-piercing ranged infantry.<br/></li><li> Primaris Inceptor: Powerful short-range unit equipped with jump packs.<br/></li><li> Primaris Intercessor: Tough versatile infantry unit<br/></li><li> Primaris Invader ATV: Light vehicle equipped with Onslaught Gatling Cannon<br/></li><li> Primaris Repulsor Executioner: Heavy tank with transport capabilities and a significant payload of ranged weapons<br/></li><li> Redemptor Dreadnought: Powerful walker unit with a vast array of weapons.<br/></li><li> Storm Speeder Thunderstrike: Fast assault vehicle with powerful anti-armour armament.</li></ul><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3326080/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Ultima_Founding/]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 04 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4444585538764144704</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/>Oi Speed Freeks,<br/><br/>We’ve been tinkering and dabbling under the hood. This is update is sure to spice things up and adds new things for you to try.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a0f5bbf289d0dd18cbe098ba929ff44ddbe94f11.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7118acc31227965eca37f7c54b4f5ed63f117588.gif"/><br/>We've added a new racing objective to Deff Rally mode! Players can now earn points by fighting OR racing.<br/><br/>When a capture point is first reached, its checkpoint race will begin after a short delay. Players can earn 1 team point by touching each green checkpoint, and earn up to 50 points for 1st place when (if) they finish the race. But be careful, because along each racing route enemies will be waiting to krump you.<br/><br/>If you'd rather fight than race, press Q to toggle off all the racing information, and get to krumpin! You can either find a chokepoint to set up an ambush, or just sit on the capture point and let them come to you. Kills still earn 10 points each, and preventing the other team from racing effectively by disrupting/destroying them is a very potent strategy.<br/><br/>We decided to make changes to this mode to add more replayability and more ways of skill expression. Many players who tried Deff Rally for the first time asked us, ""Where's the Rally? This is all Deff!"". However, we did our best to keep combat a focus, in both the rules and route design. Controlling the area around the capture point is still important, because all races start and end there, and often pass through more than once.<br/><br/>So if you don't want to race, have fun playing goalie and ruining some poor git's racing line, or just shoot anything that moves. <br/><br/>But, if you do want to race, then <b>START YER ENGINEZ!</b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/aa07b5cf41d12453ee786ff687eda2c306019016.jpg"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bef6004999942c0170fe4225041c5798cfb7a890.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3798cc5ef3dc5b10ebb2cc46cb43fdf52ec8e7cd.png"/><br/>Some exciting new ALTERNATE WEAPONS will be coming for the Boomdakka Snazzwagon, Kustom Boosta-Blasta, Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy and Looted Wagon. These weapons will be enabled by default during this weekend, as well as some upcoming weekends (from Friday to Sunday).   An explainer pop up will show when entering the Play Game menu if the alternate weapons are active.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Looted Wagon Lobba:</b> The Lobba fires mortars with an arc. It has a faster fire rate and larger explosive radius, but takes kunnin' to use effectively. Try lobbing these bouncing mortars into a pack of enemies or a choke point<br/></li><li> <b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon's Mek Speshul Burst:</b> This modified Mek Speshul fires a burst of dakka instead of a steady stream. It's better option than the regular Mek Speshul for mid-range combat<br/></li><li> <b>Kustom Boosta Blasta's Kustom Rivet Kannon:</b> This modded Rivet Kannon shoots hotter, higher damage rivets that do proximity damage. The fire rate is slower, but it really packs a punch if you can lead your target<br/></li><li> <b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy's Bigga Grub Squig:</b> This larger grub squig heals more per shot, multiple teammates can be affected by the splash, and it has a longer potential range</li></ul>In a future update these ALTERNATE WEAPONS will become permanent items you'll be able to swap with the current weapons, with corresponding progression to unlock them. Balance work may still need to be done with these alternate weapons, so we're grateful for any feedback.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/531a67e7ce34d0f75ea417d53eae03c0f99601a1.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Additional Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Removed recoil from throwing the Burna Bottle when driving the Boomdakka Snazzwagon<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the Megatrakk Scrapjet crosshair would disappear<br/></li><li> Fixed some vehicle tire scale issues<br/></li><li> Fixed some vehicle accessories not keeping their colour assignments<br/></li><li> Some weapons now deal damage based on distance. Smaller hit-markers mean you're dealing less than full damage and you should get closer. Our intent is to limit the extreme range of some weapons, and make the effective threat range more clear.  More information is below:</li></ul>Damage falloff notation: [100, 1.0] describes the X, Y coordinates on a graph. X is the range in meters. Y is the damage multiplier, from x1.0 to x0.0. So [100, 1.0] &gt; [125, 0.5] means that the damage at 100m is x1.0, and at 125 meters it's x0.5. The multiplier before and after the stated points is equal to the closest point. So everything before 100m is x1.0 and everything after 125m is x0.5. Some weapons deal more damage in close range, most deal more damage at long range.<br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon</b><br/>The Looted Wagon recieved a buff to its dakka, and a loss of close range damage from its primary weapon. It also lost projectile speed, making long range shots require more skill to hit consistently.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dakkaguns spread decreased to 2 (from 5), damage falloff set to [125, 1] &gt; [150, 0.5], max range set to 150<br/></li><li> Kannon damage falloff set to [50, 0.75] &gt; [150, 1.0], projectile speed reduced to 400 (from 700) <br/></li><li> Grot Rigging now restores 40 health (from 50). Also resolves an error that made LW's Grot Rigging restore 58 health</li></ul><b>Kustom Boosta Blasta</b><br/>The KBB recieved a small nerf to its effective range (weapon accuracy was already doing most of the work here), and throwing Stikkbombs at point blank is slightly less effective due to reverse damage falloff.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rivet Kannon damage reduced to 8.5 (from 9.15), max distance reduced to 200 (from 250), damage falloff set to [100, 1.0] &gt; [125, 0.5] <br/></li><li> Stikkbomb damage falloff set to [10, 0.25] &gt; [25, 1]</li></ul><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b><br/>The SJD loses some max range on its Shokk Rifle, and recieved a small buff to its missiles to compensate.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shokk rifle damage falloff set to [125, 1.0] &gt; [175, 0.33], aim assist returns to address hit reg issues<br/></li><li> Homing missiles damage increased to 8 (from 6), removes target requirement to fire, removes targeting reticule</li></ul><b>Grot Mega Tank</b><br/>The GMT had too much health!<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Health reduced to 240 (from 250)<br/></li><li> Grot Rigging now restores 40 health (from 50).</li></ul><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b><br/>The Squigbuggy now has more incentive to lay mines as traps rather than using them in point blank due to reverse damage falloff.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Squig Mine damage falloff set to [0, 0.5] &gt; [7.5, 1]<br/></li><li> Bot accuracy reduced because some of those boom squig shots were insane</li></ul><b>Deffkilla Wartrike</b><br/>The Wartrike didn't change much, as it's effective range was already limited by weapon accuracy. This change helps communicate that range to players.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Boomstikks damage falloff set to [65, 1.0] &gt; [85, 0.5], max range reduced to 100 from 300</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cac0e8374b951c48475b16b8b33b1e6179a8b62d.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added explainer popups for both Kill Konvoy and Deff Rally game modes when clicking them<br/></li><li> Added onboarding tips for new players.  If you're not a new player please just skip through them.<br/></li><li> Tips now display on the matchmaking screen while queuing for a match</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b69c541c6ee1a753d5a418378c23a824911ce34a.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Party size now increased to a maximum of 8 players<br/></li><li> Party splitting now implemented.  Party splitting can be enabled by the host for parties of 4 or less, and is automatically enabled for parties of 5 or more.  Note that upon joining an ongoing match, a party with splitting disabled will be automatically split if necessary, but then put on the same team for the next map.<br/></li><li> Teams are now better balanced based on skill rating, and balancing when players join has been improved</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6b9299ae4cee7fcdd906955c74a2bd7b8303a8e1.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Leaderboards now showing proper stats accrued since last patch<br/></li><li> Fix for completing achievements if they haven't been already, despite the requirements being met<br/></li><li> Improvements to WAAAGH Path player data handling</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/752388e0fbb271cae44bf236a3c624c3ebd115ad.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Made the Deff Rally capture point totem collision more smooth to avoid getting caught on it<br/></li><li> Added more structures and details to the end section of Kill Konvoy - Erupta<br/></li><li> Updated the lighting and atmosphere for Erupta<br/></li><li> Added boost pads to Deff Rally maps. These glowing orange spots will refill 2/3s of your boost bar when driven over.  The visual look of these boost pads will improve for next update</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/564bde73f77d4a171d62f758cb64b5773f27de44.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/609999d7f6dee428b0edc205b7b2cc5bf9e755c0.png"/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hopefully fixed a type of Fatal Error D3D crash associated with the GPU<br/></li><li> Bots now use dash more for movement<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with the hover state UI of a selected vehicle would be duplicated for multiple vehicles<br/></li><li> Fix for a bug in the store where items were incorrectly showing as owned<br/></li><li> Fix for notifications showing in the wrong main menu tab</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e0db447dc486730af2bd5402e608ced9bea38b7e.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War: WARHAMMER III - Gorbad Gameplay Showcase</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4458096337647305594</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Cunning, Brutal, Unrelenting.<br/><br/>Outmanoeuvre your enemies with your brutally cunning plans and lead the ultimate WAAAGH! as Gorbad Ironclaw 🪓<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HMrBhXDjamE?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Obelisk Update is OUT! Watch the trailer now.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/520825178851115542</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3">Greetings Marines!</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">NEW OBELISK UPDATE IS OUT!🎉🎉</div><br/><b>Watch the Trailer now!</b><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gNMrZ7_l9NM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">DARK ANGELS COSMETICS 🪽</div><br/>The new Obelisk Update is <b>out now</b>, which means the very much awaited Dark Angels Chapter Pack is now yours! It comes with:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dark Angels cosmetics for your weapons: the Auto Bolt Rifle, the Plasma Pistol and the Power Sword<br/></li><li> The Dark Angels Champion<br/></li><li> A unique armour set and banner for the Bulwark Class. The Bulwark class will also get a unique Dark Angels Storm Shield.</li></ul><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/7c0e21f6cf3e628e51642d9b4dfd4d4ca4e5d904.jpg"/></div> <div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/24adf9938e02a0fa566f531759b291c317d83028.jpg"/></div> </div> </div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/39308af705c0b0ffd996813ea1e63517d7240aba.jpg"/><br/>The Dark Angels Chapter Pack includes the heraldry items of the Second Foundings and Successor Chapters of the Dark Angels: <ul class="bb_ul"><li> the Angels of Absolution<br/></li><li> the Angels of Redemption<br/></li><li> the Angels of Vengeance<br/></li><li> the Unnamed<br/></li><li> the Blades of Vengeance<br/></li><li> the Cowled Wardens<br/></li><li> the Bringers of Judgement<br/></li><li> the Angels of Defiance.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/3e1d5d216b97ac72447bef274374296646fddf2e.jpg"/><br/>New armour pieces will also be  added, including a fan-favourite helmet: the Mark VIII Ravenwing! All these items will be available to unlock as part of an heraldry cosmetic.<br/><br/>Last addition to the customisation menu, the colour lenses are finally here! Choose among 15 different colours to customise your Space Marine even more!<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/88753ecbf0f7c215104223a1c96567e5e4cf5ad6.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/d9630bdb7172f9efbf708bc1d3f9751275018435.gif"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h2">NEW PVE OPERATION: OBELISK ⚔️</div><br/>For this Operation, you’ll be sent to Demerium to rotate a replica of the obelisk to disrupt the flow of energy protecting the Aurora device. This operation takes place in parallel to the final events of the campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/9765b64d3d9421d4e7871a92849ee4c15f307825.jpg"/><br/>To reach the console control of the obelisk, you’ll have to make it through a tomb plunged into darkness. To make your progression even tougher, the Chaos forces see a new addition to their roster: the Tzaangor Enlightened, a new Majoris enemy! They will now appear in every PvE Operation with Chaos.<br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/54d42c55cd984923bc6546ad7cfe53b0d97476ed.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"> <br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e26ebc6aa4036d719ba22cc7accb1a4248b8666d.png"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h2">TECH UPDATE ⚙️</div>Finally, on tech side, 5.0 update will bring Frame generation support with the integration of DLSS 3 and FSR 3.1.<br/><br/>To read the full patch note of the update, please check it here.<br/><br/>For more details read our FAQ.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">ACKNOWLEDGMENTS 💬</div>We're endlessly grateful for the <i>Space Marine 2</i> community. You have been expressing your desires and hopes towards the game since the very beginning, which is a blessing to us. Thank you, again, for the love and support you're sending towards both the game and the teams. We cannot wait to <b>continue this journey in 2025</b> with even more content! 😉<br/><br/><i>The Focus and Saber Teams</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0987068ebeefc14bd9004c2edbde7945e0fcb9a9.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">The Emperor Protects</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
