<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>⚙️ Early Access Update 05 ⚙️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515203109058775130</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><br/>OI YOU'Z GITS!<br/><br/>Speeding onto your PCs is another Early Access update our grots have been <span class="bb_strike">slaving over</span> working on. This update addresses a bunch of feedback from the community but also pushes the game further towards our wider goals, with part of that being it needing to feel more race-y.  Game'z called SPEED FREEKS now, innit?<br/><br/>So, along with the plentiful fixes/changes, and alternative weapons we've added for this patch, your vehicles can now drift.  Now let's GIVE IT SUM WAZZA!!!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f369570c4b43a0c9a442ae6c392825a8e3c29900.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b983c20a75342c97f091da3f03b56a2aaffb42d2.gif"/><br/><br/>Alternate weapons are back! <br/><br/>Every vehicle now has alternate weapon that are switched on for select weekends. The first weekend starts today until Sunday night! <br/><br/>Again we're looking for feedback on these for feel free to let us know your thoughts in Discord or Steam.<br/><br/><b>Deffkilla Wartrike</b><br/>The Trike now has an alternate hook (Pulla Klaw) in addition to the default hook (Grapnel), which has also been modified. The Grapnel no longer pulls enemies, but gives the user a much greater speed boost, even able to pull you into the air. The Pulla Klaw doesn't increase your speed, but it yanks enemies towards you which creates proppa fun scenarios!<br/><br/><b>Megatrakk Scrapjet</b><br/>The Scrapjet has a new alternate secondary weapon: the Combat Rokkit. This switches the high-recoil, high-cooldown rokkit with a weapon that's more suited for combat. It can be fired much more frequently and has much higher DPS. However, it still requires great driving skill to use, as the weapon is mounted to the vehicle and shoots straight forwards.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Scrapjet drill speed down to 185 from 200, and we’ve adjusted the curve to add speed more slowly. This should help players catch the Scrapjet before it can escape or reach a ramp to go airborne with the bomb in Kill Konvoy, since it's been relatively easy to deliver this way - and although fun for the bomber, it can be frustrating for opponents.<br/></li><li> Scrapjet recoil rokkit damage down to 20 from 35 and the recoil force has been reduced to 210 from 240 as well as its cool down increased to 8 second from 6. <br/></li><li> We’ve also added a large knockback force to give it a real punch.</li></ul><b>Shokkjump Dragsta</b><br/>The Dragsta has a new alternate primary weapon: the Unstable Shokk Rifle. This switches the long-range primary weapon with a spammable short range version. Use the Dragsta's great manoeuvrability to get in close and shokk your enemies, then disappear with the Warp Tunnel. Careful though, you still have to mind the asymmetrical firing angle.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> The braking force at the end of the Dragsta’s Warp Tunnel has been removed and its cooldown increased to 10 seconds from 8.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where Dragsta could deal full damage with the Shokk Rifle at up to 270m instead of the intended 125m<br/></li><li> The Shokk rifle now deals full damage to targets within 150m, up from the intended 125m. </li></ul>The Dragsta's max range has been drawn back because of the potential for passive playstyles, especially with groups of them. We welcome feedback about this change and will continue tweaking until a good balance is found, as we know there are some passionate Dragsta mains out there<br/><br/><b>Grot Mega Tank</b><br/>The Mega Tank now has a new alternate tertiary weapon, the Kustom Mega Blasta. This is a powerful energy weapon that applies a large knockback force in the area it hits, sliding vehicles along the floor if they're grounded and pushing them away in the air.<br/><br/><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon</b><br/>The Snazzwagon default primary weapon recoil has been removed. This was slowing the vehicle to 65kph (from its base speed of 80kph) with no boost and 80kph while boosting(!) when firing forward. <ul class="bb_ul"><li> To compensate, the base speed has been reduced to 70 (from 80). This results in about the same average speed as before, but its now more consistent.<br/></li><li> Following feedback from the community, its primary weapon range has been increased by 25m. <br/></li><li> Snazzwagon Burst alternate primary damage increased to 2.2 (from 2), damage falloff set to [75, 1.0] &gt; [125, 0.5] (from [25, 1.0] &gt; [75, 0.5])</li></ul><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Squigbuggy alternate Big Grub Squig cooldown has been increased from 2.0 to  2.5 seconds</li></ul>Two of the alt weapons we've added are aimed at giving more defensive options to players trying to stop aerial bomb deliveries in Kill Konvoy. We love the high flying bomb runs, but we want to ensure there is adequate counter-play. The Trikes's Pulla Klaw and the Mega Tank's Kustom Mega-Blasta are both effective displacement tools that are quite effective on players flying through the air.<br/><br/>Many weapons have also been given a small downwards knockback force to help fight aerial bombers<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4a05f84d6bb0731e159b47913cd2360e4cdad526.png"/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/251f9129b0c42960bcef3f7303907892e7e8fb76.gif"/><br/>As mentioned, we added drifting to the driving model for all non-tank vehicles.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>TAP </b>handbrake to drift while turning<br/></li><li> <b>HOLD </b>handbrake to do a tight donut.</li></ul>Drifting will tighten the <b>turning radius</b> and also provide a <b>speed boost</b>, making it helpful for racing, and chasing enemies down. Be sure to drift if you want to pull off tight manoeuvres.<br/><br/>This is the first public iteration of drifting so we're happy to gather your feedback about it!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/752388e0fbb271cae44bf236a3c624c3ebd115ad.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/993ba6bc48808f6021ddbc68ce62c41786e13954.gif"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added acid rain weather version for Big Erupta (Kill Konvoy)<br/></li><li> Added Megabommer planes to Big Erupta (Kill Konvoy)<br/></li><li> Added a 2nd race version to each capture point for all Death Rally levels<br/></li><li> Many boost pads added to Deff Rally maps<br/></li><li> Improved slope visuals and clarity in most maps, as well as added small rocks.  Now the slopes leading up to rock obstacles can more easily be seen<br/></li><li> Collision on rocks in all maps has been vastly improved for smoother traversal.  Collision improvements pass done on some maps in general<br/></li><li> Various small gameplay improvements to levels, including making sure tanks don't get stuck in pipes in Ded 'Ard Desert (Kill Konvoy)<br/></li><li> Improved dust VFX that comes off the back of vehicles when driving on terrain<br/></li><li> Added sparks effect to big fan in Burna Valley to communicate lifting force<br/></li><li> Changed some level shadow settings to be more performant</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6b9299ae4cee7fcdd906955c74a2bd7b8303a8e1.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added Challenge progress pop-ups on the HUD. Now players can now see their progress in real-time<br/></li><li> Added lifetime Medals to the game, which track progress for various stats like kills/assists, bombs delivered/stopped, races won, etc. Players will now see popups on the HUD when a lifetime medal is achieved<br/></li><li> Added Kill Streak medal popups ingame for when players get more than one kill in a single life (ex. getting 3 kills before dying). Kill Streaks of up to 15 are supported, but there is an issue with audio playing loudly at 12+ kills. This will be fixed next update </li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/609999d7f6dee428b0edc205b7b2cc5bf9e755c0.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> HUD damage falloff crosshair scaling is much stronger, so the "full damage" area should be clearly defined<br/></li><li> Some weapon crosshairs now have indicators for cooldown status<br/></li><li> Added moar skulls to da skulls vehicle kits 💀 <br/></li><li> Added AZERTY keyboard support<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with the game window losing focus if running in lower resolution than desktop default<br/></li><li> Updated Easy Anti-Cheat module and made it more stable on Steam Deck<br/></li><li> Enabled localization in the game.  Players can now choose their language from the settings menu<br/></li><li> Improved various VFX in the game<br/></li><li> Fixed issue with end of match Orks looking upwards when graphics settings are low<br/></li><li> Updated Shokkjump Dragsta Warp Tunnel SFX to sound even more cool AF<br/></li><li> Vehicle engine SFX now has a tremolo effect when airborne<br/></li><li> Improved many explosion sounds to be higher quality and more explodey<br/></li><li> Fixed bug where bomb drop noise played on top of the bomb pickup noise when someone picked up a bomb<br/></li><li> Fixed bug where rain/snow sounds from a map would persist to main menu and any other match played in the same session<br/></li><li> Added Orks to the back of the-... ah, never mind.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4bb558eba870b2549d6a6626efaaa14b48f30be7.png"/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added explainers to the main menu for update news and all 8 alternate weapons<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with a "new" notification showing for items that were not new<br/></li><li> Added HUD effect for driving over a boost pad<br/></li><li> Improved presentation of Challenges screen<br/></li><li> Added ingame player reporting system reason and comment box<br/></li><li> Switched Deff Rally and Kill Konvoy game mode buttons in the UI. We want people to try Deff Rally again as we've improved it significantly!<br/></li><li> Improved render scene for inspecting items<br/></li><li> Various UI texture optimizations</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/898132a2f28cc2a190c9b6b590960eebaab672b4.png"/><br/>Right, dat's enuf talk - let's get krumpin'!<br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! <br/>Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/147b1768aae9ac663c50a5fec47f3ba790647d05.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 14:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermintide 2's 7th Anniversary is live now!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546728306451416068</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>Another year has passed and Vermintide 2 celebrates its 7th anniversary! It’s time to party and go out drinking with our heroes across the ruined streets of Helmgart looking for that one last casket of Bugman’s, and fight whatever nasty Skaven or Rotblood dares to interrupt!<br/><br/>The event will last <b>from today until March 16!</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">A Quiet Drink &amp; new Portrait Frame</div>As always, head over to the Weekly Event game mode in the Adventure mission selection menu to enter the event mission, ‘A Quiet Drink’. Completing the event with any difficulty will reward you with a brand-new anniversary portrait frame!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/fc80166e9946e8597ed40b088c8549931c5753cd.png"/><br/><br/>Make sure to check the Event tab in Okri’s Challenges!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Double XP</div>For the duration of the anniversary event, all XP gains will be doubled! Time to max out those Heroes, get extra levels, and grind Versus Ranks!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Versus Map - A Grudge Served Cold</div>As mentioned in our previous dev blog, we’ve turned another Adventure into a playable Versus Map: ‘A Grudge Served Cold’! Heroes and Pactsworns alike will get to duke it out in these snowy vistas and through the dwarfen corridors. As always, the Versus version of the map has seen some adjustments to make it fit Versus better, including new objectives and changes to sections of the level. This Versus level takes 3 rounds to complete!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/ca6d147d9a3289e530de19a112ea41c93dcb927c.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Regarding the loss of data issue</div>A portion of our player base suffered some serious loss of data &amp; progression on their accounts on the day of Versus’ launch. It took us a while, but by now the brunt of those issues has been solved and reverted. As an apology for the inconvenience, we’ve added a new portrait frame to the game as compensation, the <i>‘Abasement’</i> frame!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/30503110/0ee6003f2b08016898827dcba683f83aed429f80.png"/><br/><br/>This portrait frame will be awarded to all of those who suffered the aforementioned data loss issue. Expect the frame to arrive by Monday!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">About the upcoming Weapon Pack</div>If you've been following our dev blogs and announcements, you've likely seen that we've been working on a new weapon pack, and we've even teased a prototype.<br/><br/>While we initially hoped to release it this year, we regret to inform you that it won't be coming out this year. At this point, we don't have more details to share.<br/><br/>We understand this is disappointing, and trust us, we're just as frustrated about it as you are. We’re eager to get these weapons into your hands and will keep pushing to make that happen!<br/><br/><i>Without further ado...</i><br/> <div class="bb_h1">	Patch 6.4.0 patch notes							</div> <br/> <div class="bb_h3">	Features &amp; Tweaks							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Fixed and re-enabled Sanctioned Mods &amp; Versus Quickplay Dedicated Servers.</b> <br/></li><li> <b>Enabled the Anniversary Event,</b> including the 'A Quiet Drink' map, double XP, Lohner's time-limited event shop and new Event challenges at Okri's.											<br/> </li><li> <b>Added a new map to Versus: 'A Grudge Served Cold'</b> <br/> </li><li> <b>Weekly Event &amp; Weekly Expedition changes:</b> We've made adjustments to the various modifiers used in rotation in the Weekly Event and Weekly Expeditions.											<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <b>Unstable Breed:</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Bomb Carriers now explode a moment after being staggered or pushed. This should allow for a much better counter against them in melee.									<br/> </li><li>	Delay between Bomb Carriers waves has been doubled (for Twitch Mode, the delay is unchanged).</li></ul></li><li> <b>Ranald's Sparking Gift:</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	A player's own explosion now always sends them flying backwards, to alleviate a bit of the randomness.									<br/> </li><li>	Delay between Gifts has been doubled (for Twitch Mode, the delay is unchanged).									<br/> </li><li>	Ranald’s Sparking Gift no longer affects bots. They never acquire the affliction or take damage from it, but can be catapulted.									<br/> </li><li>	As only players can be targeted by the affliction now, the delay between Gifts extends by 5 seconds for every bot on the team.</li></ul></li><li> <b>Curse of Comradeship:</b> <br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Curse of Comradeship damage intervals (the time between damage instances) now scale depending on distance:									<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	Minimum distance: 4m, with a damage interval of 1s.								<br/> </li><li>	Maximum distance: 12m, with a damage interval of 0.15s.				</li></ul></li><li>	Knocked down players are no longer affected and no longer affect other players.									<br/> </li><li>	Curse of Comradeship will no longer appear in Chaos Wastes Weekly Expeditions.					</li></ul></li></ul></li><li>	Horn of Magnus - Removed the chance for Beastmen to spawn in.											<br/> </li><li>	Versus: Rat Ogre leap charge can no longer be interrupted by Necromancer skeleton attacks.									</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">	Fixes							</div> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>	A Quiet Drink - Fixed a spot players could get stuck on in the tavern.											<br/> </li><li>	A Grudge Served Cold - Fixed a respawn point that caused rescued players to fall through the ground.											<br/> </li><li>	A Grudge Served Cold - Added a killzone at the bottom of a pit. Which is another way to prevent players from getting stuck when going where they shouldn't, SIENNA.											<br/> </li><li>	A Grudge Served Cold - Fixed a wall that enemies could walk through.											<br/> </li><li>	Into the Nest - Fixeda rare bug where non-Skaven enemies could spawn in the level.											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the navigation buttons not showing up the movement tutorials of the Handbook.											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed a crash due to wrong resources being loaded when joining a lobby that just started transitioning from one level to another.											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed bug where Kruber would respond with a Sienna voice line when Sienna steps in gas.											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed the Okri's challenges "Wuthering Heights", "Tech, No Mage" and "Fundamental force". They are now functional again.											<br/> </li><li>	Versus: Fixed a bug where players sometimes fall through the ground when rescued from being hoisted by a Packmaster.											<br/> </li><li>	Fixed an error where difficulty selection for Veteran shows that 300 is the highest obtainable power level instead of 200.											<br/> </li><li>	Versus: Fixed a crash if a Packmaster leaves while the round is ending and they have an enemy who is hoisted by them.											<br/> </li><li>	Weaves: Fixed the Chaos Warrior with Shield not triggering Chamon's Aurification.											<br/> </li><li>	Khazukan Kazakit-Ha! - Fixed so that the pressure plate objective doesn't show until you repaired the pipe and started the burner on each side of the ridge.										</li></ul> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Nightmares &amp; Visions - Releasing March 25, 2025</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/512951942084821207</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>At the end of last year, we told players we’d be bringing out four main updates to Warhammer 40,000: Darktide in 2025. It’s time to announce our first release – <b>Nightmares &amp; Visions</b> – will be <b>released </b>across all our platforms on <b>March 25, 2025</b>!<br/><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ota9aM8ePr4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/><br/><b>What can players look forward to for Nightmares &amp; Visions?</b><br/>As part of expanding content in Darktide, we’re introducing a new activity for players prepared by the enigmatic Sefoni. Similar to Havoc, we’ve got a dev blog typed up to share with everyone.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>New game activity - Mortis Trials</b>: mash through waves of enemies in visions induced by the ship’s Psyker. Each time you venture into the Sefoni’s visions, you will be able to build new and exciting playstyles by selecting between abilities and buffs for the duration of the trial. By overcoming the Mortis Trials, players will unlock secret information on some characters present on the Mourningstar.</li></ul>For the last few updates, players might’ve noticed we always include an event to go out with a new Darktide update. For Nightmares &amp; Visions, we designed an event to celebrate Mortis Trials.<ul class="bb_ul"><li><b> Time-Limited Special Event</b>: following the release of Nightmares &amp; Visions, Darktide will be hosting a special event focusing on playing Mortis Trials.</li></ul>We mentioned we would be continuing to work on Havoc, and that’s part of the work we’ve included for this update. The process included going through a lot of player feedback. For this first update to Havoc, the difficulty for Havoc has been upped and we reassessed the ranking system. A dev blog to outline the changes is on the way!<ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>Havoc mode gets a refresh</b>: the end-game experience testing the resolve of the most seasoned operative reaches a new juncture with improvements and new daunting challenges in the form of four new mutators.</li></ul>Since the update at the end of last year, we’ve heard it from the fans of the Big Guy. We’ve reworked the Ogryn Talent Tree, in addition to tweaking a few of his weapons. A preview dev blog has been put together to share off the planned changes, like we did before the Unlocked &amp; Loaded update. Players can expect this preview dev blog to be shared at the end of this week!<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <b>And more!</b> The Ogryn class is getting his Talent Tree revamped, giving players more build opportunities. We will also be bringing a few balancing changes as well as general improvements made to the game.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/><br/><br/>To wrap up, Nightmares &amp; Visions is our next major update rolling out across our platforms on March 25, 2025.<br/><br/>We’ve got more information to come and dev blogs lined up! The Ogryn Talent Tree Rework blog is first (this week - we’re talking <b>37 pages of notes</b>), and we’ll follow up with more blogs talking about the upcoming changes to Havoc and a proper introduction to Mortis Trials, too. We’re also working on some dev streams!<br/><br/>We’ll see you on the Mourningstar.<br/><br/>– The Darktide Team]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 18:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.2 Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500566410271917830</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines,</div><br/>As announced in the February Community Update, hotfix 6.2 has been deployed on every platform. <br/>This is a small patch that mostly focuses on crash fixes and minor balancing tweaks in preparation of a major Patch 7 that would focus on weapon perks and weapon loadouts rebalance.<br/><br/>As usual, if you encounter issues with this update, let us know by making a bug report here.<br/><br/>You'll find the complete patch notes down below.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/0a6ea410f462d2a5b6950db04e11ef0cb86b247b.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">PATCH NOTES</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Datavault ordeal Shredding Shrapnel now requires to kill 2 enemies simultaneously with a single frag grenade instead of 3.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the AI Director that could sometimes spawn too many spore mines for a very long period.<br/></li><li> Fixed several issues that would cause Assault class to teleport back after using its Jump Pack ability.<br/></li><li> Minor localization fixes.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Perk PvE Updates</div><br/><i>Overall we are quite happy with 6.0 perks rebalance, we are seeing way more build variety for all classes across all difficulties and seeing people experimenting with their builds more. That being said, there are still some perks that will require more attention or even full rework. We will be monitoring the situation and will be making necessary tweaks.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c741d6ad228423769275bff7e195c4362308e0d3.png"/><br/><br/><b>Heightened Vigour: </b><br/>- Fixed not triggering by perfect Parry or Block in some cases.<br/><br/><b>Close Targeting: </b><br/>- Damage increased from 15% to 25%.<br/><br/><b>Concentrated Fire: </b><br/>- Bonus duration of the Auspex Scan zone increased from 40% to 60%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1abf8c6d07944560f7c6535488e606fe81f15ea4.png"/><br/><br/><b>Perseverance:</b><br/>- Damage reduction bonus increased from 15% to 25%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/49a8b1e1d75b916ba063b4bcda14fc04e773850c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Restless Fortitude:</b> <br/>- Damage reduction bonus increased from 20% to 40%.<br/><br/><b>Tactical Prowess:</b> <br/>- Minimum enemy HP for auto finisher increased from 25% to 33%.<br/><br/><b>Unmatched Zeal: </b><br/>- Health regen bonus increased from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/b008de073c9e7e17f7c5410a6ebec4145b7304ca.png"/><br/><br/><b>Block Break: </b><br/>- Damage increased from 25% to 50%.<br/><br/><b>Evasion: </b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct cooldown of 30 seconds instead of 15 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Efficient Readiness:</b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct 20% movement boost instead of 10%.<br/><br/><b>Pattern of Excellence: </b><br/>- Fixed typo in the description, now it shows correct cooldown of 30 seconds instead of 180 seconds.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This perk was buffed in the 6.0 patch, but localization was not updated and it was missing in patch notes.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6dc73b997ce968ed4d170cec92bf099029c43431.png"/><br/><br/><b>Chapter Banner (starting perk): </b><br/>- Bonus health increased from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><b>Emergency Countermeasure: </b><br/>- Cooldown reduced from 120 to 90 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Defensive Mastery: </b><br/>- Cooldown reduced from 120 to 90 seconds.<br/><br/><b>Glory's Shield:</b><br/>- Now the perk protects not only from Ranged Damage but from all incoming Damage.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This should improve support Bulwark build a lot, since this perk doesn't impact Banner cooldown</i><br/><br/><b>Invigorating Icon: </b><br/>- The ability regeneration slowdown has been fixed, but the regeneration penalty is now -50% instead of -100%.<br/><br/><i><u>Note</u>: This perk has been discussed a lot in previous patch notes and here are my honest thoughts on this.</i><br/><br/><i>We've made a mistake making this perk in the first place. It changes the class behavior too much from what was originally intended. Bulwark is supposed to tank enemies and support his team mates, he isn't a dedicated healer. But players are now used to this playstyle a lot and now absolutely any change to this perk will cause negativity from the community. <br/><br/>The perk itself is so powerful that it is simply mandatory, plus it also changes how the ability is used. Unlike other classes where abilities are used whenever the player wants, it turns the banner into an ability that the player saves for the very last moment.<br/><br/>In our game it is absolutely fine, if you want to use it that way, but the problem is that with certain other perks you can bring its cooldown to ~20 seconds. This means that not picking this perk will be detrimental to your squad. No matter what the numbers on the neighboring perks, players will always stick to the ability to fully heal when needed.<br/><br/>We want to come back and rework this perk or, rather, perk column in later patches, but this requires some time of experimenting and testing. For now we are tweaking numbers to make a compromise between previous patch and community feedback.</i><br/><br/>- Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8884de443755dac7bb5665350a070df9cb37914c.png"/><br/><br/><b>Fortitude: </b><br/>- Health increases from 20% to 30%.<br/><br/><b>Conversion Field: </b><br/>- Radius increased from 10 to 20 meters.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Weapons Balancing</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Power Sword</div><i>We are very happy with the current melee balance. All melee options are now viable and getting picked by players across all difficulties. However, we see that Power Sword isn't strong enough, compared to much easier to wield Chainsword. It takes more skill to use the Power Sword properly, but the benefit wasn't that great. We want to adjust this a little.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Overall base damage increased by 5% <br/></li><li> Power Stance combo damage additionally increased:<br/></li><li> Attack 1 +10%<br/></li><li> Attack 2 +20%<br/></li><li> Attack 3 +30%"</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Tech</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Crash fixes and general stability improvements.<br/></li><li> General connectivity improvements.</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC Hotfix 6.3.4 - Easy Anti-Cheat update + Hotfix 6.3.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/552500/view/546728306451416317</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Heroes!</div>We’ve just pushed a patch that swaps our old version of Easy Anti-Cheat for the newest version. The previous version is scheduled to shut down on March 4, which would’ve meant no protection to the game from cheats or tampering unless we did this upgrade.<br/><br/>A couple of things to note about this change:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> For normal gameplay, <b>there should be no notable difference.</b> The game will continue to run normally in both Official and Modded realms, and no extra actions need to be taken from you as players to continue playing.<br/></li><li> Operating Systems that had incompatibility issues with our EAC may find those issues gone with this update. We still can only officially support Windows 10 &amp; 11, but nonetheless there might be one barrier less in that aspect.<br/><span class="bb_strike"></span></li><li> The system necessary to support Sanctioned Mods is changing. This means that <b>until sanctioned mods are updated by their authors, they might not work in the official realm.</b></li></ul>[/strike]<ul class="bb_ul"><li><span class="bb_strike">We are currently in communication with mod authors to find the swiftest solution to this issue for all sanctioned mods.</span><br/></li><li>Sanctioned Mods are now fixed as of Patch 6.4.0 without needing to update the original mods!</li></ul><li> Connecting to other lobbies might take longer than usual at first. Will go back to normal after some time.<br/></li><li> <b>Versus Quickplay will be temporarily disabled</b> as we update the servers.</li>[/list]<br/>We're working to fix the issues with Sanctioned Mods and Versus Quickplay Dedicated Servers as soon as possible, we'll keep you updated.<br/><br/><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.3.4 patch notes - 3rd of March</div><div class="bb_h2">Features &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Replaced the Kamu Easy Anti-Cheat for Epic Online Service<br/></li><li> Improved error messaging for banned players to show reason &amp; duration.<br/></li><li> Temporarily disabled Versus Quickplay / Dedicated Servers.</li></ul></blockquote><blockquote class="bb_blockquote"><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.3.5 patch notes - 4th of March</div><div class="bb_h2">Fixs</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where re-installing the game would not re-install EasyAntiCheat correctly.</li></ul></blockquote>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
