<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>September Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696782040340188230</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines</div><br/>Congratulations, after more than a decade of waiting, you’ve finally pursued Lieutenant Titus’ journey and you’re now honoring your pledge to the Emperor!<br/>We have some news to share in this Community Update, make sure you read it carefully!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">First of all, thank you… 💙</div><br/>On September 9, we released a long-time project - Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2, and your feedback has overflown us with pride and joy. We saw you smile, laugh, purge xenos and demonstrate undeniable loyalty to the Imperium.<br/><br/>The amount of players kept increasing over the month, rallying more Space Marines to the cause, which is amazing. We want to let you know that we love the game as much as you do, and we’ll take good care of it, offering new content and listening to the community in the upcoming months.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a98158606c540cd7d874f94c1c764dfce8617dbc.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Upcoming content 💫</div>A hotfix will arrive very soon! It mostly intends to fix crashes and improve stability.<br/>In the future, expect quality of life improvements, additional customization features (such as new colors for the lenses), and more. For PC players: a 4K Texture Pack will be downloadable! It will be entirely free.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">YOUR FUTURE BRIEF</div>The new map for Operations mode, located on Planet Kadaku, will arrive in October. Here’s your brief:<br/><br/><i>The Tyranid invasion of Kadaku is ending. The planet’s organic material is being transformed into biomass, and Tyranid Capillary Towers stretch high into the skies above, where the Hive Ships wait to taste their victory.<br/>The Cadian forces have made a valiant attempt to push back against the Tyranids. A team of Space Marines arrives on Kadaku with a simple mission: help the Cadians destroy the towers. The Tyranids may win the planet, but the Imperium will make it as painful as possible for them.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ea8e4d47f0ca45ce397a78fe792d6c22b51cb365.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Bug Patches and Questions 👾</div><br/><b>Therefore, our duty is not done here.</b><br/><br/>We’ve seen that many of you were experiencing server issues and other bugs. We’re taking your feedback into account for our future updates. An important patch was deployed here. It corrected a few bugs and added features such as:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Private mode for Operations<br/></li><li> The Hub Sparring Arena<br/></li><li> Ultrawide support (for PC)<br/></li><li> Improved spawns in multiplayer<br/></li><li> Rebalancing of various enemies you encounter in Campaign and Operations mode<br/></li><li> Correction of bugs that prevented players from progressing through certain levels</li></ul>Nevertheless, we’re still working on the remaining bugs.<br/><br/>We’ve also brought answers to many questions raised by you, on different platforms (mostly Focus Together, Discord and Steam). Many of these questions were answered in our Message to Community, which you may find here.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f60c85e6b08d5337a57570cc7deb6bbd6c203400.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Be loyal to the cause, be respectful 🙏</div>It has been reported that some players were displaying hurtful behaviors or comments in-game. We do not tolerate that and will take action to prevent it. <br/><br/>First and foremost, we kindly ask you to remain respectful, mature and mannerly with your fellow Space Marines. You can never know how old the other players may be, how their day is going, how sensitive they may be… overall, you never know who your brothers and sisters are… It could even be Henry Cavill 😏 … you don’t want to insult Henry Cavill, brother, no you don’t.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/fba66fe0818eada0763654837c9744c502e5f492.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">See you next month, for your next brief. 🫡</div>That’s it for September! These community updates will take place at the very end of every month. The goal is to keep players updated on upcoming content, updates, patches and news! So stay tuned and sign in to Focus Together to make sure you don’t miss a piece of it.<br/><br/>If you want to join the community and easily find mates to play with, you should join the official Space Marine 2 Discord Server! <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Check the roadmap below!</b></div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a18468b9407c3de92af500bac7e0f07bdc13140d.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For the Emperor.</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titus Talks: Episode 3 is here... and it's about Space Marine 2!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4696781406112877915</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings Space Marines!!</div><br/>The grimdark universe of Warhammer 40,000 can be daunting to dive into! This is why we're are thrilled to introduce the second episode of the “Titus Talks” a 3-part video series presented by Lieutenant Titus himself, Clive Standen, and dedicated to welcoming newcomers to the rich expanse that is the 41st millennium. ✨<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Watch Episode 3: What is <i>Space Marine 2</i>?</div><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8uRz5UBuZaQ?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><div class="bb_h2">This episode focuses on introducing players to game itself.</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> What is the backstory of Titus from <i>Space Marine 1</i>? <br/></li><li> What is Space Marine 2's gameplay like? <br/></li><li> Once I'm done with the campaign, what are mulitplayer modes like? </li></ul>Presented by Clive Standen, who voices Lieutenant Titus in the game, today’s video lecture is the conclusion to a three part series you can find on the Focus Entertainment YouTube channel.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/95c6c33219c5664bd4a2cc2f61e9ba8fb83754bb.png"/><br/><br/><i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is available now on PC. Get the Gold or Ultra Editions to secure your Season Pass!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2183900/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>To get the latest info about <i>Space Marine 2</i>, follow our socials and:<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's dedicated on Focus Together<br/>- Join Space Marine 2's Discord server]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4653997209662413241</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/f10181aa79fa2bdf71a6979ab8aee441f9ed739d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div>Hotfix #49 (1.5.2) is now live on Steam and it will shortly be live on our other platforms.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Changes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Added Penances for completing the Rolling Steel mission and for completing Operations missions.</li><li>Added a shortcut to the Party Finder menu from the mission board.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Bug Fixes &amp; Tweaks</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed an issue where the game could fail to retrieve the latest Mastery data from the backend when opening the Loadout screens.</li><li>Removed the “Stand By For Action” and “Rapid Response” penances, which were incorrectly added with the 1.5.0 release.</li><li>Fixed an issue where both marks of the Assault Chainsword family could be purchased from Brunt’s Armoury when playing as Veteran.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “new” marker could be displayed incorrectly in the Masteries menu.</li><li>Fixed an issue where Blessings could still be purchased while hidden when the focus was on the lower rewards track.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Power Rating value for Curios could be incorrectly displayed in the Emperor’s Gift tile after completing a mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the “Sort by Name” feature was not correctly sorting items.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the selection focus could be missing when performing operations in the Discard and Sacrifice screens while playing on controller.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the weapon name could overlap with other text and UI elements in the Sacrifice screen.</li><li>Tweaked the icon for the selected weapon in the Sacrifice screen to be slightly smaller.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the tooltip for the Frame Generation could display undefined text.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the coat of the Darinda Dukane NPC could clip with the legs.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the weapon cosmetic obtained from the Power Sword Mastery penance was missing the rarity and “obtained from” information.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Rolling Steel Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed a rare server and client crash which could happen in the Rolling Steel mission when a player joined the mission while no other players were alive.</li><li>Fixed a crash which could happen when pressing the “-” key in specific moments during the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Tweaked the matchmaking values to avoid players joining too close to the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li></ul><b>Dev Note:</b> <i>This is to limit the chance of joining an already ongoing mission, without the ability to affect the success of it due to the timer already being close to expiring.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed so that in the Rolling Steel mission no success audio effects are triggered when destroying the cogitators in the last carriage after the mission timer had expired.</li><li>Tweaked the spawn locations of the batteries in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where parts of the geometry would still shake after the train was stopped.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where players could clip through closed doors before completing the related minigame.</li><li>Fixed instances where pickups could be clipping with the geometry in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an instance of missing hang ledges in the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where rain could fall inside the locomotive at the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Tweaked geometry on a ramp in the Rolling Steel mission to make it easier to navigate.</li><li>Fixed an issue where bots could fail to properly board the extraction Valkyrie at the end of the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the thruster VFX from the enemy Valkyrie could remain visible even after it went away.</li><li>Tweaked the fade to the Valkyrie cutscene after winning the Rolling Steel mission.</li><li>Fixed an issue in the Rolling Steel mission where multiple characters could share the same seat in the Valkyrie cutscene after winning the mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Cosmetic Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fixed some mask clipping issues on the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burnt Sulphur” and “Illius Noctis Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetics</li><li>Fixed some issues where the tubes from the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic would clip with high-collared upper bodies .</li><li>Fixed an issue where some beards would clip through the Psyker “Illius Pattern Battleshroud with Psykana Collar (Burn Sulphur)” headgear cosmetic.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the Ogryn “Militarum Tox-Field Siege Jacket (XXXXL)” upper body cosmetic would clip with lower bodies while in the operative screen.</li><li>Fixed an issue where the shoulder area of the “Kinetic Witch’s Redemption Raiment” upper body cosmetic could look deformed on female characters.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">Known Issues</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>The Game Can Crash When Switching Between Fullscreen and Windowed Mode with FSR 3.1 Frame Generation Turned On</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>FSR 3.1 Frame generation is unstable when used in combination with exclusive Fullscreen Screen. Specifically switching between screen modes is prone to crashing.</li><li>We recommend using Borderless Fullscreen.</li></ul></li><li><b>Penances Shown As Not Completed</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>While migrating to the new Itemization system, there is a chance for a visual bug to occur where players with a lot of progression on their weapons might not see their Penances displayed as complete. This is only a visual issue which might occur when opening the Penances menu for the first time. Closing and opening the UI again will update it properly.</li></ul></li><li><b>Misaligned Weapon Skins in the Penance Preview Squares</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are some weapon skin rewards in the penance previews that are misaligned or don’t fit in the square.</li></ul></li><li><b>Mastery Level Value is Missing in The Marks Swap Screen</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>When in the Marks swap screen, the Mastery level value required to obtain locked Marks may fail to be correctly displayed.</li><li>The issue is only visual, and the locked Marks will be correctly available upon reaching the required Mastery level in the weapon family.</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Information in the Sacrifice Weapon Screen Tooltip</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The tooltip in Sacrifice Weapon screen incorrectly states that only Anointed (blue) rarity weapons (or higher) are able to be sacrificed.</li><li>The issue is only in the tooltip text, as the minimum rarity level required for the Sacrifice procedure is Redeemed (green).</li></ul></li><li><b>Incorrect Rounding of Weapon Stats</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On uncommon occasions when looking at a weapon card, the total value of the potential stats distribution shown might add up to 1% higher or lower than the maximum (380).</li><li>This is a rounding issue, however the actual stats total will always effectively be 380 for all weapons.</li></ul></li><li><b>Auspex Tooltip in Rolling Steel Localization Issue</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The “Move” text in the HUD tooltip when using an Auspex for the new hacking minigame in the Rolling Steel will appear localised in English but is missing in other languages.</li></ul></li><li><b>Zealots are Unable to Purchase Recon Lasgun from Brunt’s Armoury</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Zealots are currently unable to purchase Recon Lasguns from Brunt’s Armoury.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>Warp Unbound Having Inconsistent Activations (Added after original post)</b>:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>The "Warp Unbound" Psyker talent is not working correctly when using the Electokinetic and Inferno staves, as a Perils of the Warp explosion may still be atriggered while the talent is active.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><b>"Kinetic Flayer" Psyker Talent (Added after original post)</b><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The "Kinetic Flayer" Psyker talent is not working correctly as it can still be triggered by enemies that are not Specialist, Elites or Monstrosities."</li></ul></li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.2.1.12 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805561491109</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! A new hotfix is deployed, to deal with some more of the reported issues.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/>Consoles will receive the same update within ~24 hours.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Sometimes the Rogue Trader's voidship could lose the capability to move and use weapons or could use movement and weapons indefinitely, instead - fixed;<br/></li><li> Characters could become stuck after using the Veil of Blades ability - fixed;<br/></li><li> Under certain circumstances, an existing saved game could be converted into Grim Darkness mode, which shouldn't have been possible - fixed;<br/></li><li> Death from Above ability sometimes failed to deal damage - fixed;<br/></li><li> Wildfire sometimes didn't reduce the AP cost of attacks as intended - fixed;</li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4703536805557883738</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>We’re proud to inform all of you that we’re participating in <b>Steam Turn-Based RPG Fest</b> which has already begun! Be sure not to miss this entertaining event, as well as pleasant discounts on our titles - <b>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</b> and <b>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous</b>!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43222021/c5109ca10883ecfe4e76748b32c1258dc786545c.jpg"/><br/>There’s no time to waste, explore the event right now. Note that the Fest will be held till October 7th!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>The grim and dark universe of Warhammer has never been so close. Don’t miss your chance to grab the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game with <b>40% off</b>! It’s time to guide your people through the challenges of the Koronus Expanse!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Get the Season Pass and try the just-released first DLC for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader – Void Shadows! Explore the sinister secrets of your voidship with a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock access to the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>Get Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>40% discount</b> and unlock unique in-game items, digital add-ons, and the legendary voidship model!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>A journey full of danger, new friends, and foes lies ahead! Feel the true RPG experience and embark on a mission to save the world from a great peril in Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous with a <b>70% discount</b>. Choose your path in the story and explore where it leads you!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Unlock the ultimate experience of three DLCs full of new content by getting Season Pass 1 at a <b>70% discount</b>. Make your Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous unforgettable.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>The more DLCs, the merrier! Another three DLCs can be obtained as a part of the Season Pass 2 with <b>50% off</b>! Continue your journey as the Knight Commander, meet new companions, and explore new archetypes!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Please note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
