<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sale 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523078230806102208</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We wish you the most enjoyable time during the winter season! And discounts on Owlcat Games games will make your festivities even better. No more thinking about gifts for your family and friends - discuss at the parties which mythical path is cooler and brag about your success in exploring the Koronus Expanse. <br/><br/>Get Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader at 45% off and Pathfinder: Enhanced Edition at 70% off! <br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>However, the adventure doesn't end there! Pour a new mug of hot beverage and continue your heroic (or villainous) deeds in the DLCs for our games. The dangers of the forty-first millennium await you...<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/>...as well as epic accomplishments on Golarion! Purchase the DLCs individually or as part of the Season Pass.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497182532936138941</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/1b7e1f2b75505d5fac1fab6e42aab8bef98257c5.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>We’ve just rolled out Hotfix 6.0.2 for Total War: WARHAMMER III to all players, bringing with it a number of adjustments following on from last week's Update 6.0, including fixes to Ogre Camp and Vampire Counts stances, some improvements to one of Golgfag’s victory conditions and much more, as well as fixes for those known issues originally detailed in our message last week.<br/><br/>Note: If you previously opted in to the Beta version of this hotfix on Steam, your game will automatically switch to the full release version. You do not need to take any action. Players who were previously playing in the Beta will note that we have added two additional changes since we launched the Beta, which are <i>marked in italics</i> in the main post below. We want to thank everyone who downloaded this Beta and checked it out this week!<br/><br/>On top of the changes detailed in the release notes published earlier this week, we've also added Squig Herds and Black Orc Big Boss units to the core Orc &amp; Goblins roster in all of our products which share this faction as a part of this Hotfix.<br/><br/>These units will be added free of charge to anyone who didn't already have them as part of that change, ensuring that you can use Gorbad's tactics 'Light 'Em Up!', 'Erd Mentality', and 'Lead da Charge!' for players running his Campaign.<br/><br/>Our design intent was always to allow for Gorbad to have lots of variety in the units at his disposal to make best use of his tactics. On being made aware of this oversight, we've taken action to put things right. <br/><br/>We will be reviewing the rest of the feature, and will be back again with further changes as part of us better testing our content for the future.<br/><br/>Please accept our apologies for only now spotting this issue!<br/><br/>With all that said, let's dive into the full list of what's included in this Hotfix.<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.0.2 Release Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">HIGHLIGHTS</div>​<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where, if the Ogre Camp ranks up, its stance reverts to Raiding stance.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where, if an Ogre Camp recruits units from within itself, it drops out of Encamp stance and switches to Raiding stance.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Vampire Counts were missing the ambush stance.<br/></li><li> Added Lightning Strike to Skarsnik's 'Ready &amp; Waitin'' skill.<br/></li><li> Slightly adjusted Golgfag's victory conditions – gifts to clients now count as occupied settlements (see the dev note in the Victory Conditions section below).</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a soft lock that occurred after Valkia retreated from the Spear of Slaupnir battle mission.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Sneaky Rogues can now be used with any large monster, not just Rogue Idols</i><br/></li><li> <i>Sneaky Rogues mission now requires 25 monsters to be recruited</i><br/></li><li> Added a camp limit check for Ogre camps.<br/></li><li> Decreased the amount of Treasury and Meat gained from Golgfag's Contracts to align with the intended design.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Arbaal could receive the defeat dilemma after losing a Lightning Strike battle as a reinforcing army (i.e., not actively participating in the battle).<br/></li><li> Increased the amount of Planz gained from battles as Gorbad (1 → 2).<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Arbaal could sometimes receive more than eight Challenges of Khorne simultaneously.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where advice about a Chaos God becoming ascendant in the Great Game would play for factions without Unholy Manifestations.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Blood Host armies that were reinforcing would not have their attrition immunity timers updated after winning a battle.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where the 'Travel to Client' teleport for Golgfag was unavailable when any lord or settlement from the player faction was involved in a siege (either on attack or defence).</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">STANCES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the High Elves' Alith Anar's Stalking stance did not display the correct icon.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Vampire Coast Lords were unable to enter Dig stance to uncover treasure.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Vampire Counts were missing the ambush stance.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where, if the Ogre Camp ranks up, its stance reverts to Raiding stance.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where, if an Ogre Camp recruits units from within itself, it drops out of Encamp stance and switches to Raiding stance.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where loaned armies had no available stances.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TECHNOLOGY TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where the Khorne technology 'Giant Slayer' was not applying to Khorngor units.<br/></li><li> Fixed the Khorne technology 'Rage Within' – it no longer incorrectly targets non-infantry units.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">ABILITIES/ATTRIBUTES/TRAITS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed several issues where abilities and attributes were not functioning for the following Golgfag banners: Bomb Lobber, Bone Muncha, Feral, and Slayer.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Scyla Anfingrimm would not have his innate trait when playing as Daemons of Chaos.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SKILL TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added Lightning Strike to Skarsnik's 'Ready &amp; Waitin'' skill.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">RECRUITMENT</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Slaughtermasters and Butchers were not receiving Skrag's recruit rank bonus when recruited from Camps.<br/></li><li> Reduced Mangler Squig recruitment time from 2 turns to 1.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">VICTORY CONDITIONS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Slightly adjusted Golgfag's victory conditions – gifts to clients now count as occupied settlements.<br/><br/>​<i>Dev Note: Golgfag relies on gifting settlements rather than occupying, sacking, or razing, so we now count gifted settlements towards that total.</i></li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where the Ogre Camps scripted tour text said 'sent' instead of 'send'.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where fighting in the new regions added to southern Cathay could result in a blank battle map.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue preventing the Pit of Shades from targeting the ground correctly.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where certain units, including Oxyotl and Gyrobombers, could turn and fire multiple volleys at once.<br/></li><li> The Unstoppable Choppas ability now does +50% weapon strength up from 25%.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">MODELS/ANIMATIONS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a bug where Arbaal on Fleshound bent too far forward during a rider defend animation.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in Skulltaker's quest battle where the enemy Dwarf Runelord's model appeared corrupted.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue with the artillery manual aiming mode using ALT + Right-click.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">POST-BATTLE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased the Meat cap from post-battle captives from 62 to 250.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where, at times, the number of Mangler Squigs that survived a battle differed from the number of units alive in the post-battle.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/>Thanks once again for your ongoing feedback. As always, if you run into any issues after updating to Hotfix 6.0.2, please let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vote for Warhammer 40, 000: Space Marine 2 for the "Better with friends" Award!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/641297020996289818</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Greetings Astartes,</div> <br/>The final voting stage for the 2024 Steam Awards is now underway, and <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is nominated in the <b>"Better with Friends”</b> category! Show your unrelenting support for the Emperor of Mankind by casting your vote before December 31st and help us take the trophy back to Holy Terra! After you've voted, gather your fellow <i>Space Marines</i> over vox and let them know they can cast their vote as well!<br/> <br/><b>The Imperium is counting on you.</b><br/> <br/><i>- The Space Marine 2 Team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vote for Warhammer 40, 000: Space Marine 2 for the "Game of the Year" Award!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/498307633472602144</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Greetings Astartes,</div> <br/>The final voting stage for the 2024 Steam Awards is now underway, and <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> is nominated in the <b>"Game of the Year"</b> category! Show your unrelenting support for the Emperor of Mankind by casting your vote before December 31st and help us take the trophy back to Holy Terra! After you've voted, gather your fellow <i>Space Marines</i> over vox and let them know they can cast their vote as well!<br/> <br/><b>The Imperium is counting on you.</b><br/> <br/><i>- The Space Marine 2 Team</i>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam Winter Sale Now On!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497182374087360792</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/82ca5b9e88b010484cdec5035d9619581e228e53.png"/><br/><br/>The Steam Winter Sale is now on until 2nd Jan. Grab up to 90% off Total War titles and DLCs. Go on, treat yourself, you deserve it! 🎁<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/594570/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/364360/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends Thursday 2nd January @ 11AM PT/6PM GMT</div></div><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

— The <i>Total War</i> Team

<div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
