<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.4.1.229 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523098989784989850</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains, today we are releasing another post-release update that improves your experience with the Lex Imperialis expansion, adds some new dialogue options, a hefty chunk of new mechanical content for the Overseer and fixes a number of bugs and problems.<br/><br/>As usual, consoles will receive this update with a possible delay up to 24-48 hours.<br/><br/><i>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Highlights:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added 20 (!) new talents and features for the Overseer to boost its synergy with origins and first tier archetypes;<br/></li><li> Added some new reactivity bits and dialogue options;<br/></li><li> Operative’s Exploits are no longer consumed by dodged, parried and blocked attacks;<br/></li><li> Fixed the bug with Yrliet’s romance sending the player to Quetza Temer;<br/></li><li> Fixed the issue with inability to select the last two party members during the preparation phase on console and controller UI;<br/></li><li> And more!</li></ul><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes:</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">System and stability</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> An incorrect autosave at the Palace of Justice could cause the game to softlock when loaded - fixed;<br/></li><li> Removed the invisible unit that prevented the combat from continuing at the Lower Tunnels;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Narrative</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a widely reported bug with Yrliet’s romance where instead of her inner world, you would get teleported to Quetza Temer;<br/></li><li> Added new reactivity bits to the player’s origin at Leethus, Thassera and the Heartless;<br/></li><li> Added another, more neutral dialogue option to continue the romance with Solomorne that does not involve ordering him to continue the affair;<br/></li><li> Added two new dialogue options to personally execute the governor at Thassera, one of them Heretical;<br/></li><li> Solomorne’s nightmare cutscene has received minor improvements;<br/></li><li> Some descriptions no longer forget which of Solomorne’s hands is augmented;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case of missing speaker at Rykad Philia in the dialogue with Winterscale;<br/></li><li> Minor adjustments to the dialogue with the Servo-skull Swarm;<br/></li><li> Fixed narrative inconsistencies in the epilogues for Solomorne and the Arbites;<br/></li><li> Glaito will no longer occupy the bath forever after inviting Solomorne there once;<br/></li><li> The Heartless mission retained the old difficulty after being moved to the beginning of Act II - this was fixed and the enemy stats will be now more appropriate;<br/></li><li> Reinforcements in the final battle in the Lex Imperialis DLC will now always correctly reflect the player’s narrative decisions;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case where it was possible to get the dialogue about the fate of the Heartless twice;<br/></li><li> Fixed a case of incorrect speaker in a dialogue with Chorda on Footfall;<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug that caused the hearing in Abelard’s second quest to never begin;<br/></li><li> You can now choose to delay the conversation with the Adeptus Arbites, rather than instantly being forced into it after arriving to Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Maive has received multiple additional versions of her portraits to reflect the player’s decisions about her and the consequences of the events at Thassera;<br/></li><li> If you decide not to deal with Solomorne’s problems on the voidship right away, Ravor and Vigdis will now properly offer new dialogue options to come back to this discussion;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mechanics</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Exploit stacks are no longer used up if the hit was dodged/parried/blocked;<br/></li><li> Exploits now only provide bonus damage to attacks and not other damage sources;<br/></li><li> Degraded Defence had its description clarified that the number of stacks increases the damage done by a %, not a flat amount;<br/></li><li> The Cyber-Mastiff's claws now should correctly be present and equipped even in the rarest cases for people that still had them missing after the last update;<br/></li><li> Arbitrator’s Public Sentencing talent will no longer proc during the preparation round;<br/></li><li> Debuff from Falconry now correctly applies until the end of the round;<br/></li><li> The Cyber-Eagle now goes Soaring even at the end of the extra turn given to its Overseer;<br/></li><li> Psyber-Raven’s Purification Discharge is now complemented by a new feature that also connects the enemies it damaged to each other for 1 round: any damage dealt to one is also partially transferred to others;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Servo-skull Swarm): enemies in the Expanded area now receive Exploits automatically;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Servo-skull Swarm): extra turns granted in the Expanded area let you spend AP more effectively;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Servo-skull Swarm): extra turns granted in the Expanded area also strengthen the Overseer;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Cyber-Eagle): the familiar's attacks while using Obstruct Vision now also apply Exploits;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Cyber-Eagle): upon giving an extra turn to an ally, the Overseer also shares a bit of their familiar's key stats with them;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Cyber-Eagle): while Soaring, it applies Exploits to all enemies on the battlefield;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Servoskull Swarm): Exploits expended in the Expanded area now also make the familiar tougher;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): stay in cover to make your familiar tougher! Also, it interacts with Exploits now;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Operative Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): your familiar no longer expends Exploits while still receiving bonus damage from them;<br/></li><li> A new feature added exclusively for the Servo-skull Swarm familiar if Pasqal picks it: his Machine Spirit Communion is now also duplicated, centered on the Servo-skull Swarm whenever this ability is used;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Warrior Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): each time they are attacked, their familiar grows in power;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Warrior Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): convert your temporary wounds into pure power!<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): each time an extra turn is received around the familiar, it attacks an enemy nearby;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): using Voice of Command on an ally also applies it to the familiar;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Soldier Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): it works around applying and interacting with Prone more effectively;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Soldier Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): it decreases the Reload cost of all allies around it;<br/></li><li> A new feature was added exclusively for the Bladedancer Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): the familiar can now Blade Dance, too!.. in a way;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Bladedancer Overseer (Cyber-Mastiff): the Cyber-Mastiff gains in power depending on how many Wounds its Overseer lost;<br/></li><li> A new talent was added exclusively for the Officer Overseer (Cyber-Eagle): eliminating enemies that were Obstructed now restores AP and increases Resolve;<br/></li><li> Volatile Servitors now correctly die after using Volatile Self-Destruct. You could say they've become more... self-destructive;<br/></li><li> All features of Cinder are now consistently visible in the UI;<br/></li><li> Anver Specialist now correctly uses the Stun Grenade and drops it on death;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Added a unique Theodora’s cloak to the orbital station in the Lex Imperialis expansion;<br/></li><li> The effect of High Spinner Armour will no longer proc during the preparation round;<br/></li><li> Kinetic Module's damage bonus was not scaling with ranks - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Locations</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Some traps were impossible to disarm with the assistance of a Psyber-Raven at Kiava Gamma - fixed;<br/></li><li> Ulfar will now always be able to properly enter the combat with the Ambull;<br/></li><li> Chairs at Thassera are no longer illusionary and now have collision enabled;<br/></li><li> In rare cases, Solomorne could end up at the wrong side of the wall of fire during the boarding action - fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of objects lacking textures at the Palace of Justice on PS5;<br/></li><li> Fixed clipping in the cutscene of the first arrival to Footfall;<br/></li><li> Loading a save on Leethus no longer sometimes sends the party under the floor;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Space</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Clarified that Fury interceptors require a torpedo launcher to be installed;<br/></li><li> Colony decisions proposed by Solomorne will now be correctly reflected in the colony chronicles;<br/></li><li> One of the rumours related to the familiars didn’t appear correctly - fixed, it will now be available;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Co-op</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> It is no longer possible to select and control a pet owned by another player, which caused the UI to lock in weird ways;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">UI</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After one of the recent updates, when playing on console or with a controller, the last two members of the party could become impossible to move during the preparation round - fixed;<br/></li><li> UI notifications during the combat with Sargona covered the Start Battle button;<br/></li><li> On console and when playing with a controller, it is now possible to trigger the dialogue with the familiars at the captain’s quarters without activating the mouse cursor;<br/></li><li> Added an icon for upgrading the service station for familiars;<br/></li><li> Talents picked by the Overseer are now always displayed in their familiar's feature screen, too;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Miscellaneous</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Replaced incorrect legacy wording for Bring It Down! in the tutorial for Cassia’s abilities with the new version;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hear the advance of the Adeptus Arbites with the Lex Imperialis soundtrack!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523098355357712758</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>Any journey in the void of the Koronus Expanse must be accompanied by a fitting atmosphere, be that the sounds of indomitable advance of the Adeptus Arbites or the gloomy tunes of a feudal world. <br/><br/>Enjoy the full soundtrack for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader – Lex Imperialis DLC:<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pzGKjn0Chx4?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>The Emperor protects!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500580357225054283</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h3"><b>Hello Space Marines,</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Since it’s summer and everyone deserves a break, please expect fewer updates in August. This Community Update will be shorter than usual, but we promise it’s filled with good news!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/SM2_Separateur_1920.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>A WHOLE NEW YEAR OF FREE CONTENT </b></div><div class="bb_h2"><b>IS COMING 🎁</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">As announced last month, a second year of content is in the making, with both free and DLC content. This second year means a new Season Pass too! This new Season Pass will grant players access to the new DLC content. Overall, it will work the same way as Year 1 did. Let’s see what’s going to be free:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW PVP MAP 🗺️</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Let’s begin with the <b>new PvP map</b>. Set on Avarax, it is a mix of close quarters and long hallways. This fifth map will be available for <b>every PvP game mode</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">​</p><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcYlHu6RTxkUdk0oHW1ERWVbKEkeMly4w5o5uASzRnhqUxtrulybkltzyBhZcx29S3JXB0r8UJleJiQzG9CwgxnE0Q9Oy8uUR_SzW9UHzsJcMsc9roSfZeeHgSpaRX_17QD1xnAIg?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p></div><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdPBpfGDSgK5xXRvUJ7edPGV02SHuqnBMFBOuaIoQTIAHk0gbvUEBvrCMlKU-0CB_85gdrs7LBCZsOANpCMwB_4LjNMhD8NW6qM4FbgN0VcNAZMpt2r6T8gJWflD_s9VzA9Z4iFLA?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>Development still ongoing, final version subject to change.</i></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW GAME MODE: HELBRUTE ONSLAUGHT 🩸</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This new map will be introduced with Patch 10.0, and will coincide with the release of the new PvP game mode <b>​​“Helbrute Onslaught”</b>. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">Two teams of Chaos Marines will fight to control strategic areas, but also to take control of the Helbrute. The first team to take control of an objective gets to control the Helbrute, until the opposite team takes it down. One player gets to control the Helbrute at a time, and this player will be picked randomly among players who participated in securing the control point. To have the Helbrute on their side, the team that failed to secure the first control point will need to slay the Helbrute before securing a new designated control point. Controlling the Helbrute grants the team a strong advantage, but killing it will also reward points to the opposite team. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">The Helbrute uses a Helbrute Thunder Hammer in melee, and a Plasma Cannon in range. </p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW WEAPONS: PYRECANNON 🔥🔥🔥</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">New weapons will also be added! Last month, we revealed the Power Axe, this month we’re happy to show you the <b>Pyrecannon</b>! This weapon is ideal to dispatch the hordes.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">​</p><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf-ar9q2JtQntkCJVuMeFJ0joFnNTvMyIivdHoDp1EX-cVT-N-uj9kCo1bs5SUChfUr0FxpE9GJxILcuBm39QuUZO2P9lcXJaeDw9OgE-Xn0-52NNbxKf6emgek8VUS7Ai3aO8I-g?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p></div><div class="bb_table_td"><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcLJmuc-GHEgFXp4AGyZk-x9Wo_A2JUBYIbmiiES_iHEV-99XHaOHesccHw25TCzitdAHvLUHcQtsnet9KW-lgyud_ARW6fJMike6irYzF74VzgshK8-7M_5tkjwjABuCPBCk6v?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p></div></div></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW MAJORIS ENEMY: CHAOS SPAWN 😈</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">A new Majoris enemy will also reinforce the Chaos forces: the Chaos Spawn. This abomination has 3 different variations, each with their own moveset and abilities. Take a look at one of them:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/chaos_spanw,_cropped.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>NEW GAME MODE AND MODIFIERS 🔁</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Finally, a new variation will be added to PvE to bring replayability to the game. Some of you might remember when the 4.0 update brought a modifier that forced team members to stay close to each other to get their shield back. Following your feedback, we decided to remove this feature to rework it and bring it back later, integrated in a new game mode, along with new gameplay modifiers each week. </p><p class="bb_paragraph">This new game mode will come with Patch 10.0 (the specific modifier mentioned above will be implemented later, though). New free cosmetics and exotic weapons will also be granted for the completion of this new challenge. Stay tuned, we’ll reveal more on that later. </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/SM2_Separateur_1920-1.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>THE YEAR 2 SEASON PASS IS ON ITS WAY 🎫2️⃣</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Without spoiling too much, we can already tease you about a few things:</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">First of all, the <b>Black Templar Champion will be the first Champion of the Year 2 Season Pass</b> (coming with Patch 10.0). It will be associated with the Bulwark class. </p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There will be <b>brand new Chapters</b>, as well as <b>returning Chapters</b>.</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">And last but not least: this second Season Pass is coming with Patch 10.0 and will be available for purchase in September! 🗓️ </p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/SM2_Separateur_1920-2.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>JULY COMMUNITY EVENT</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Experience rewards for Siege are currently increased by 50% from July 29 to August 5. 🩸</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfwaXkVPdd-FBQ19iLACI2hKzigal7qQZvKepTbDh3hRSbT_NogrEfLqAynVs4GBuQaCtp5aUMx9hhJYV6r5LsxlpZRMfoVDgX_MIw3yCJ1Nr01Dnvh3ctv4Cst8fhQez7psR1p3g?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/SM2_Separateur_1920-3.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>HOTFIX 8.1</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Following the release of the 8.0 Siege Update, some of you reported connection instability, and crashes. The 8.1 Hotfix aimed to fix these issues. You can check out <u>the full changelog here</u> ⚙️ </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>PATCH 9.0</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph">Patch 9.0 was rolled out a few days ago. You can read <u>the patch notes here</u>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We saw your feedback on blocking weapons being too slow now. The goal of the patch was to establish an even field for all of the weapon variants and simplify weapon progression rules with almost 100 different weapon variants saw changes. We will continue to work with your feedback and make necessary adjustments.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfdQeJsbkdZDnuSouMABNyDo9-E8cylu_skhVnaDwKtQantdfpvih7gTeV1AMhNxpH_v7LIJ4jhnuriGD3EcQlOIzEjASfXhZrscYjMA8EsWl2iQrFthNhWZl8YiUXRwGCteiNf?key=BoPYub_ZPXTGzX9cL1X1EA"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Also, we wish to acknowledge the persistent connectivity issues. While this patch won’t fully solve them, please know that we’re actively investigating the root causes and continuing to work toward a long-term solution.  </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://medias.community.focus-entmt.com/forums/hylia/SM2_Separateur_1920-4.png"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h2"><b>THAT’S IT FOR THIS MONTH</b></div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We wanted to wish you all a good summer time and relaxing holidays if you’re lucky enough to have some! If not… don’t forget you have duty elsewhere, Space Marine 🫡</p><p class="bb_paragraph">As per usual, follow us on our socials to be updated with the latest news, and join the official Discord server along with the 70,000 other Space Marines already there!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Thank you for your unwavering support</b>.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><i>- Focus and Saber</i></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Version 1.16.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/511838722562467154</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">Hi everyone,</p><p class="bb_paragraph">we've just released a small update:</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>CHANGELOG</b></p><p class="bb_paragraph">General</p><p class="bb_paragraph">⦁ Updated Spanish translation.</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">Bug Fixes</p><p class="bb_paragraph">⦁ Fixed a Vulkan swapchain recreation issue.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">⦁ Fixed hints sometimes appearing blank.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XP Boost in Siege Mode - Community Event</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500579723494040975</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hi Space Marines,</div><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">This month’s Community Event <b>starts now</b>!</p><p class="bb_paragraph">Experience rewards for Siege are currently increased by 50% from July 29 to August 5. 🩸</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/49c5a0f27736f1fcbaf536e15c33a50f8983a255.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>Purge. them. all.</b></div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
