<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.3.2.29 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040876439</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Hotfix 1.3.2.29 is live, fixing the problem with the new mirror in the Lord Captain's quarters that caused the character's model to become invisible.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #68 (1.7.6) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/520840214227191257</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/4d630310664380a40d3814f7acefe6c74ce1869d.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heya Everyone,</div>Hotfix #68 (1.7.6) is currently rolling out across our platforms. In the meantime, you can read the notes below!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Admonition Ascendant Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some instances where the top part of the nurgle totem would fall straight through the totem body.<br/></li><li> Fixed instances where some skulls on the totem would look low quality.<br/></li><li> Fixed instances where sound emitted from the nurgle totem would stop during high intensity moments.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">General Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where melee attacks failed to connect with destructible objects (e.g. Heretical Idols).<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring when dying in Vigil Station Oblivium.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring when tagging enemies as they were being killed.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash occurring at the end of Rolling Steel.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Disrupt Destiny fails to show stacks in the HUD.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where The Theatre of Castigation did not randomize the wave compositions.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOIN/CREATE ISSUES FIXED</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/515210714689832129</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">WE'Z DUN FIXED IT LADZ!</div>We've tested this latest build thoroughly and it's zoggin' great 💪👍 <br/><br/>Please <b>restart Steam</b> to make sure Speed Freeks updates to latest<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Things FIXED:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Not being able to <b>join games</b> properly, whether through Quick Match, or the Game Browser 🎉,<br/></li><li>Not seeing all <b>regions</b> in the game browser 🎉<br/></li><li>Not being able to <b>create a game</b> 🎉<br/></li><li>Not being able to perform actions after a failed attempt at joining a game.  Now the game will tell you if it's still processing a previous request<br/></li><li>Servers now listed in order of lowest ping in the Game Browser</li></ul>Cheers for your patience with the game being pretty broken 🛠️ <br/>Obviously it was a pretty messy launch with these unforeseen connection issues popping up, but honestly we've had a really quick response to it thanks to our lead programmer (and only networking expert), the Wired QA testing team, and our community members for helping us test too.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4781ddc91481ba36d458573c5494dcd7dffc2910.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Issues still happening:</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Performance issues/stuttering when using Full Screen Windowed mode in the display settings. <br/>Workaround: Please instead use WINDOWED mode with your native resolution, or try FULLSCREEN mode instead,</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fatal error crashes.  We've done some work on this so hopefully it's better, but these are the types of deep crashes that are hard to reproduce and diagnose.  We'll continue to work on it<br/>Note: try to run as few things in the background when playing the game as possible</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Game browser can sometimes - but rarely - show nothing, or a loading icon<br/>Please just restart the game if this happens, and try not to refresh the game browser constantly or it will bug out</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There's an issue with servers using the same name and it confusing the game,</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/995ffe8e717de04ab7a9f557c54780e617c1da15.png"/><div class="bb_h3">What's coming soon❓</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improvements to team balancing and team switching,<br/></li><li>Improvements to hit reg 🙏<br/></li><li>Vehicle balance improvements<br/></li><li>General improvements and fixes<br/></li><li>Warbands, which are like a clan/club feature.  This was supposed to be in for launch but didn't make it in time.<br/></li><li> looking into reimplementing some kind of  **party system** (previous one died with the conversion of the multiplayer backend.  You can join games with friends through the game browser in the meantime though)<br/></li><li>Upcoming roadmap of potential features and content</li></ul>Thanks for sticking with the game everyone. Been chaos the past couple days but we've now nailed it we think.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Happy RACIN', STUNTIN' and KRUMPIN'!</div><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/129ec630ecc8eb6f0ee41d6e30a790c75eba5ae4.gif"/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/98bc62a0a96ba422c4e7d22cdb2b4f90f0b6fdab.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 19:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Metal Rogue Trader Song is released by Jonathan Young &amp; RichaadEB!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523092014040876103</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Today we proudly present you a heavy metal surprise by Jonathan Young and RichaadEB, made in collaboration with Owlcat Games — the epic Rogue Trader song! <br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/69iLUVInUuM?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Enough said: LET'S GO!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Chat on Norsca and Tides of Torment Design - What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497196316182447143</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/d47668c82cf861f59900db54b8540ae93b417bce.png"/><br/><br/>What’s Next is back, revealing the next faction for our upcoming DLC, Total War: WARHAMMER III – Tides of Torment, releasing later this Summer. This episode gives full focus to our next faction, Norsca, and its newest Legendary Lord: Sayl The Faithless.<br/><br/>Creative Director Todor Nikolov, Lead Designer Vasil Nikolov, and Art Director Stoyan Stoyanov sit down with myself, subbing in for KingGobbo who recently welcomed two baby Mangler Squigs to his family and will be spending some well-earned time off whilst we keep the wheels turning. Congratulations to the Colemans from all of us across Total War!<br/><br/>Watch this full episode of What’s Next right here on the Total War YouTube Channel 👇👀<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-wN0zM9gp-s?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>We were thrilled to reveal Sayl alongside our friends across gaming at yesterday's Skulls Showcase, which if you missed you can check it out here.<br/><br/>Unlike past Skulls events, this year we haven’t released a free legendary lord as we’ve shifted our priorities over the past year to introduce more free content through our game updates, but we didn’t want you to think we’d forgotten about you all the same. 6.2 is not too far beyond the horizon, bringing with it some new units:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Blood Knights (Sword &amp; Shield)<br/></li><li> Hobgoblin Bolt Throwa</li></ul>You’ll find an early preview of additional content coming to 6.2 in this episode of What’s Next, and we’ll be back in the next few weeks with more information about our next title update.<br/><br/>And What’s Next will return at the end of June with a look at our third and final faction for Tides of Torment. We’ll have more behind the scenes looks to show and share with you in the mean-time, and until then, let us know what you’ve loved hearing about today, we always enjoy reading through your feedback!<br/><br/>See you on the battlefields,<br/><br/>— Freeman // Head of Community<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
