<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>🛠️ Disconnect Fix 🛠️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740797808413685</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We have been investigating the disconnect issues that players have been facing and we believe that we have a solution to keep players from being kicked from the game. <br/><br/>Over the next hour, we will be terminating in-progress matches to roll out updated servers. You may be dropped back to the main menu while this fix rolls out. If this happens please restart the game and re-queue. <br/><br/>We apologize for any inconvenience this has caused and thank you for your continued patience and support.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT FIX is now live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162780890578</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
OI YOU'Z GITZ!<br/><br/>We've fixed a couple critical issues that plagued the release of the game:<br/><br/>- <b>Paid items</b> on the store were <b>disappearing </b>into smokey air, but this has now been fixed.  Rest assured that any items you've purchased are still yours and will show up with no problems now<br/><br/>- <b>Teef packages</b> are now properly represented on Steam, so feel free to grab some Teef if ya like<br/><br/>- <b>Localization of languages</b> has been disabled for now since it's not quite ready for use yet (will be in an update)<br/><br/>Thanks for your patience on this, and if you still experience issues with Teef or paid items (or anything else) please let us know here or the Steam discussions, or the Discord<br/><br/>Happy krumpin!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💥 Release News - WAAAGH! NOW!! 💥</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338740162758806914</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><b>‘Ere we go ‘n’ ‘itz Free!</b><br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4U8TvW76JU?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><b>Oi! Speed Freeks!  </b><br/>It is time to unleash the Speed WAAAGH! and get krumping! <br/> <br/>We’ve now entered Early Access! This is a huge dream come true for everyone on the Speed Freeks team. Our years-long need for speed is finally being fulfilled.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0bcc5ff3e06978328e4a8e099dbab67aa2308021.png"/><br/><br/><b>No messing about, here is what Early Access Speed Freeks offers you at release.</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Eight vehicles:  </div>Find your new best battle buddy and playstyle, or master them all <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Deff Rally:  </div>Race across four battle scorched maps while you secure points in this manic game mode <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Kill Konvoy:  </div>Defend your racing Stompa, while trying to deliver bombs to slow the enemies, on two maps in this dynamic game mode  <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Extensive customization options:  </div>Get snazzy and express your inner WAAAGH! with over 150 colors, vehicle kits and cosmetic items <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">WAAAGH! PATH:  </div>Progression system for unlocking cosmetics by simply playing, can be upgraded with the purchase of the Loot Pass which will unlock the opportunity to earn extra cosmetics and Scrap Boosts  <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">In-game cosmetic shop:  </div>For those who wish to buy specific none pay-to-win cosmetics <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Party System:  </div>Mob up with your mates and dive right into battle <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Daily challenges and rewards:  </div>Earn rewards by completing daily tasks <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Vehicle challenges and rewards:  </div>Earn specific vehicle rewards.  <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Languages:  </div>Currently only English is supported, but we will have many more language options at full release <br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Dat’s ‘enuff talk, get stuck in ‘n give it a go! </div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/89aaa76523fcedcde35508c65cef24a876de9a35.png"/><br/><br/>Much of the game so far has been refined using players feedback and we’ve no intention of stopping this. You can easily add your voice to the games development by using our feedback and bug reporting system here: https://speedfreeks40k.featureupvote.com/<br/><br/><br/>We’ve much planned during Early Access. After monitoring the first fully public forays into Speed Freeks, we will finalize and and share our Roadmap with you.  <br/><br/>We hope you will come along and enjoy the ride with us. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/7a2d5deb45f38fff9959e0e8f132fc4362b507e7.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/f0468d2c6e34fa040bb1a0643136d23ab628e3d2.png"/><br/><br/><b>Why do we have to sign up for an account?</b><br/><br/>Two things, mainly.  We would like to gather telemetry to improve the game, plus contact the community via email through our newsletter. Sharing telemetry data and signing up for the newsletter are both optional, but we need the Speed Freeks account system to ask people if they want to opt in.  <br/><br/>The <b>optional telemetry </b> is getting anonymous user data that helps us diagnose bugs and other issues, as well as gameplay info that will help us balance and improve the game overall.  Having this data also allows us to show you more detailed stats for things like vehicle ability usage, which will be shown in your Speed Freeks account.  <br/><br/>The <b>optional newsletter </b> is valuable for pinging players about new stuff added to the game.  As a free to play live service title, it’s important to be able to inform active and inactive players about updates and new content.  For example, there were thousands of players that accessed the Alpha test last year that we couldn't directly invite back to the Beta because the Speed Freeks account wasn’t implemented at that time.  The newsletter can also send the more dedicated players guides, community content, stats overviews and other info that would interest them.  Again, this is optional.  <br/><br/>We understand that some gamers are tired of making accounts, we get it.  But collecting anonymous user data allows us to improve the game, and the ability to get in touch with players directly impacts the number of users that will be playing it.  Free to play games have always survived with the assistance of user accounts, and we're asking you to make one so that it helps create a better, free experience that you guys can possibly enjoy for years.  <br/><br/>The Speed Freeks account takes a few minutes to create, but we hope that you’ll take that time to quickly sign up and try our game.   <br/><br/>Click here to read the Terms of Service and Use. <br/> <br/>Click here to find Privacy Policy and Data Collection details.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/9b066a8320e3935e8dffce91368395c1e90945ca.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9c04148e5c2b05df99b1ea46c5b553e77574520.png"/><br/><br/><b>The game is in Early Access and the current launch version has the following known issues:</b><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">CRITICAL</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> When respawning in a match, <b>you may lose your vehicle kit customization</b>, with the game reverting to the default kit.  We're working quickly to fix this issue</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL</div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The PLAY GAME button in the main menu may be greyed out for a short amount of time while the game connects to the backend. If it does not become available, restart the game <br/></li><li> The left mouse button can sometimes stop working and the player is unable to shoot for a brief time.  This happens rarely, and only to some users. <br/></li><li> Sometimes explosion VFX and burnt chassis will not spawn when a vehicle explodes, but this happens infrequently <br/></li><li> If you are experiencing very high mouse sensitivity issues, please go to the settings and set sensitivity to the lowest value. <br/></li><li> After getting destroyed, the player may not be able to click anything in the respawn screen and will need to quit to the menu. But this issue is rare. <br/></li><li> If joining a game as a party, you may occasionally get put onto opposing teams <br/></li><li> There is an issue with some vehicle textures looking messed up using certain kits <br/></li><li> In Kill Konvoy the Stompas may desync somewhat, so you may see them teleport back and forth, but this is rare <br/></li><li> Ork animations in the MVP/Player Recap screens might appear broken, but rarely <br/></li><li> AFK kicking engages at 1 minute and does not warn the player before throwing them back to the main menu <br/></li><li> If you are having issues successfully shooting other players, check your ping on the scoreboard.  If it is over 100, then you are likely playing on a server outside of your region <br/></li><li> Gamepad auto aim assist is not implemented yet, so we recommend using mouse and keyboard. There is very little aim assist for gamepad aiming  <br/></li><li> There is no form of team balancing yet, but the teams are shuffled after every match <br/></li><li> Players may spawn with “stuck” inputs for driving or firing a weapon. Just press these inputs again to fix it <br/></li><li> Unlocking vehicles mid-game can cause them to be not usable until next match. Instead the player will get the next vehicle in the grid if selecting the newly unlocked vehicle <br/></li><li> If you are kicked back to the menu from a loading screen, please click PLAY GAME -&gt; FIND GAME again <br/></li><li> The low health screen effect may persist even when the player’s health is replenished. This should fix itself after next death</li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">GRAPHICS </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> There is currently no automatic graphic settings based on hardware. There are no presets for LOW/MED/HIGH/EPIC yet either <br/></li><li> Sometimes textures may not load fully, causing them to look blurry. They should fix themselves after a while but if they do not, please go into the settings menu and set texture quality to a lower value <br/></li><li> When setting Anti-Aliasing to none, this can also negatively affect how the krumped kam and end of match sequence looks <br/></li><li> Resolutions under 1280x720 are not fully supported </li></ul><div class="bb_h3">VEHICLES </div><div class="bb_h3">Boomdakka Snazzwagon </div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The smoke left over from Billowing Smoke may disappear and reappear again if the user gets killed </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">Deffkilla Wartrike </div> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Wartrike’s grapple line can sometimes clip through world geometry after attaching to a victim. This is unavoidable for the time being <br/></li><li> The Wartrike can sometimes spin when driving diagonally on certain slopes </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">Grot Mega Tank </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The crosshair is sometimes transparent when it shouldn’t be. Transparent crosshair indicates that the current aiming direction is outside of range </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">Looted Wagon </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Grot Bomm sometimes may not appear to do damage, but this is a rare occurrence. This could be attributed to latency issues between players, but is potentially a bug where damage does not get applied </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">Shokkjump Dragsta </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Dragsta can sometimes spin when driving diagonally on certain slopes </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">NETWORKING </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Depending on ping, hit detection on a player’s machine may be different than that seen on the server <br/></li><li> On rare occasion, a match may not be full, with one team missing a player <br/></li><li> If matchmaking doesn’t work, please try again a few minutes later </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">CUSTOMIZATION </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> When respawning in a match, <b>you may lose your vehicle kit customization</b>, with the game reverting to the default kit.  We're working quickly to fix this issue<br/></li><li> The Presets system is still WIP, but should work most of the time <br/></li><li> Customizations for vehicles may sometimes be reverted to defaults while playing ingame, but then look properly assigned when returning to the main menu <br/></li><li> Some colour swatch slots at the top of the paints grid may not be assigned to anything, or look empty at first <br/></li><li> Some vehicles such as the Squigbuggy, do not have enough colour customization slots and therefore a small section of them may not be customizable<br/></li><li> Item rewards from the Open Beta currently may not show up in game, despite the player having achieved them.  We are working on this and will make sure all Beta rewards are assigned to players who earned them.</li></ul> <br/><div class="bb_h3">PARTY SYSTEM </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Leaving a game while in a party will force you to leave that party <br/></li><li> Players need to leave their current party before accepting an invite to a new one <br/></li><li> If a party host has already entered a match with their limited party before someone has accepted a party invite, that person accepting the party invite will not join the match the party is already in. The host must quit to the menu and start the party operation from there </li></ul> <div class="bb_h3">CRASHES </div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> There may be a crash that takes out the server instance and all players playing in it, but this is very rare </li></ul><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1.3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/3990819972762046425</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/1bda548badba2d50e8d2166b7e288684c0db4145.png"/><br/><br/>Greetings folks,<br/><br/>We've just rolled out Hotfix 5.1.3, bringing with it a pretty hefty range of bug fixes and tweaks.<br/><br/>Read on for the full rundown of what's included:<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Gameplay:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue in some Dwarf siege maps (Custom Battle and Campaign) where attacking units would end up floating in the air in their deployment zone<br/></li><li> Warlock Engineers now have the passive ability "Musk of Fear" in their skill tree<br/></li><li> The "Draftmaster" skill used by Nakai's secondary Lords now increases the global recruitment capacity<br/></li><li> Fixed some inconsistencies with Khorne unit recruitment costs<br/></li><li> Fixed the Exalted Keeper of Secrets gaining the passive ability "Feasting on Fear" twice from their skill tree<br/></li><li> Fixed Oxyotl's Silent Sanctum army abilities not always being enabled in adjacent regions<br/></li><li> The Axe of Khorne and Armour of Khorne magic items can now be equipped by Warriors of Chaos, Daemons of Chaos and Khorne factions<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some Legendary Heroes had upkeep costs<br/></li><li> Playing as Warriors of Chaos, upgrading a Chaos Trolls unit to Bile Trolls now requires the Rusted Branding Iron technology<br/></li><li> Fixed the major Nurgle settlement level 3 building costing 3 population surplus rather than 2<br/></li><li> Aligned the global recruitment durations for secondary Lords under Nakai (when their buildings are maxed out) with the local recruitment durations for Nakai himself<br/></li><li> Yuan Bo now starts the campaign with the technology "Seasoned Trackers" unlocked, as with other Cathayan factions<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where some Regiment of Renown units could gain experience during battles and rank up<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of effects not applying to Carnosaur units<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where checks for bankruptcy were being calculated in the wrong way<br/></li><li> Additional adjustments to how attrition is calculated at end of turn<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where bankruptcy prediction for attrition was not considering raid income<br/></li><li> Fixed the Legendary Red Crested Skink Chief Lord not having the Immortality skill<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the mission "A Hero Becomes a Legend" would sometimes update with the wrong number of battles won by Heroes<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in domination mode battles where AI units continued to be issued orders after being ordered to unsummon, overriding that order and preventing the units from successfully being unsummoned<br/></li><li> Fixed issue when playing as Empire, Kislev city walls were not displaying wall improvement effects<br/></li><li> Fixed Autoresolver inaccuracies with how single entities units (Land Ship, Steam Tanks etc.) behave when damaged in the context of the Autoresolver<br/></li><li> Fixed the Empire Captain skill 'Admired Infantryman' applying to Free Company Militia units<br/></li><li> Daemon Prince Lords can now be saved in Campaign in order to be loaded in Skirmish battles<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Malakai Makaisson's long victory condition would not trigger due to a Legendary Battle not being counted towards the total count of battles completed<br/></li><li> The player can no longer lose the Nemesis Crown to rebel armies, losing the crown altogether<br/></li><li> The Nemesis Crown can no longer be picked up by a character leading an army that has been loaned to the player<br/></li><li> Fixed the Infernal Castellan Chieftain missing the Increase Mobility skill<br/></li><li> Fixed Tamurkhan's Long victory condition stating it requires 3 chieftain devoted battles, when it actually requires 6<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Karl Franz was unable to confederate Balthasar Gelt's faction<br/></li><li> Added Siege Attacker to Ice Witches mounted on Frost Wyrms<br/></li><li> The Gunnery School building now unlocks one tier of Acclaim earlier when playing as Markus Wulfhart<br/></li><li> Multiplayer battle lobbies now auto-add the correct number of player slots for the battle type selected, and auto-adding Ais in Skirmish vs. AI<br/></li><li> Fixed the weapon profiles for the mount versions of Scourgerunner Chariots<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where when fighting Thorgrim Grudgebearer's quest battle "The Axe of Grimnir" in the Realm of Chaos campaign would result in the wrong battle type<br/></li><li> The Khorne Unholy Manifestation "Call of Battle" can now be used on armies that are at sea<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where completing a long campaign victory and gaining an effect that increases Lord recruit rank, would not apply when replacing a Lord<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Wood Elf skills intended to give bonuses to Spellsingers mounted on eagles were applying to Spellsingers mounted on unicorns<br/></li><li> The Electoral Machination "Requisition" now fully replenishes the state troop units rather than adding 1 unit, as the pool size can be increased by Karl Franz's unique skill<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue in Chokepoint Battle - High Peak Pass - Bretonnian Hills where defending players could deploy vanguard units in the attacker's deployment zone but could not place the same unit in their own<br/><i>To solve this issue the position of the attacker's guerilla deployment exclusion zone had to be inverted. Now both sides can correctly deploy their vanguard units within their respective deployment zones.</i><br/></li><li> Fixed missing hard collision in a Bretonnia river crossing battle map<br/></li><li> Fixed some Ethereal units not being set to the Ethereal ground type<br/></li><li> Fixed Marauder recruitment cost reduction from Norscan Iron resources not applying properly<br/></li><li> Improved the hard collision around the rocks in the Black Ark map (used in quest battles and domination battles)<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where barricades would give units a 10% ammunition replenish each time the unit docked to them<br/></li><li> Fixed Ripperdactyl mount animation and hitbox being misaligned whilst flying</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issues within the Warriors of Chaos red line skills that apply to rank 7 and above units where some Regiment of Renown units were affected twice<br/></li><li> Fixed a number of effects that weren't applying to Giant Slayers<br/></li><li> Fixed various issues with the Steam Tank portholes<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where some UI elements could be dragged outside their intended position<br/></li><li> Fixed the toggle overcast spells button displaying over the channel Winds of Magic UI<br/></li><li> Fixed missing example Lord and Hero portraits in Overlay UI in battle<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where clicking Esc when the Replace Lord menu was open would deselect the character, leaving the window open and making some features of the panel not work<br/></li><li> Fixed hidden missions showing on army banners if the missions target was that character<br/></li><li> Added the correct image to Conquest battle mode under options menu<br/></li><li> Fixed error where Wood Elves 'Recruit Wild Spirits' marker on settlements opened tooltip about Raise the Dead instead<br/></li><li> Fixed quest battle pins showing on top of characters if the character was in the same region as the quest pin<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the Forge button would not always unlock for all Dwarf players in a multiplayer campaign<br/></li><li> Fixed travel button for Oxyotl being active when he was recruiting even though he couldn't actually teleport<br/></li><li> Fixed some effects not showing when hovering over the resource bar effect bundle tooltip<br/></li><li> When playing as the Changeling, an icon now shows when an army is visible to enemy armies<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the help pages panel would open behind the Elector Counts panel<br/></li><li> Fixed some characters displaying with unit tiers<br/></li><li> Fixed the help page for Tribal Confederation (Norsca) displaying the same paragraph twice<br/></li><li> The help page button in the Recruit Wild Spirits panel (as Drycha) now correctly opens the Wild Spirits page<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the help pages panel would open behind the Forge of Daith panel<br/></li><li> Added the missing scripted objective in Rakarth's quest battle "Whip of Agony"<br/></li><li> Fixed UI issue where resources required would overlap with building chain name<br/></li><li> Fix auto unlocked skills not using the greyed out text when in the locked state<br/></li><li> Fixed the enemy lord in Kayzk's Chieftain battle not displaying the correct portrait</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Graphics/Animation:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed issue where Chaos Lord is holding his axes with open hands while mounted on the Chaos Steed<br/></li><li> Fixing a bug where Chaos Lord of Khorne would rotate 90 degrees while on his Chaos Steed during certain attack animations<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where Thorek and Thorgrim, on the Anvil of Doom mount, would stand up in a sitting position when selected on the Campaign map<br/></li><li> Fixing bug where Herald of Nurgle on Palanquin mount has several missing animations<br/></li><li> Fixed several missing animations in Campaign<br/></li><li> Fixed bugs where Waywatchers &amp; Hawkeyes of Drakira (Waywatchers) do not hold swords in their left hand during idle animations<br/></li><li> Fixing a bug where the walk animations of the Forsaken of Tzeentch are not restarting seamlessly<br/></li><li> Fixed various units not displaying stumps when dismembered:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Nasty Skulkers<br/></li><li> Reaper Bolt Thrower<br/></li><li> Amethyst Wizard<br/></li><li> Festering Stooges (Exalted Plaguebearers) RoR<br/></li><li> Chaos/Norsca Charioteers<br/></li><li> Hellforged Host (Exalted Bloodletters) RoR<br/></li><li> Spellweaver<br/></li><li> Night Goblin Warboss</li></ul></li><li> Fixed bug where the Herald of Slaanesh's leg rotates strangely during an idle animation when on a steed<br/></li><li> Fixed some Be'lakor animations where he is holding a whip when he shouldn't<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the two-handed hammer used by the Bretonnia Peasant Mob unit was not fully textured<br/></li><li> Fixed combat ready animation issues on High Elves Spearman<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with jumping attack animations for Goblin variants<br/></li><li> Resolved rendering issues with Sons of Ghorros (Centigor - Great Weapons) unit which would result in different model parts not being visible<br/></li><li> Addressed some skin issues on LODs to ensure proper rendering<br/><i>LOD means "level of detail", and refers to the models and textures used for units depending on their distance from the camera. For example, units in the far distance will use less-defined models than units that are closer to the camera.</i><br/></li><li> Fixed bug where Daemon Prince attack visual effects are played a few meters in front of him<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug with Chaos Lord of Nurgle's sword, which had the wrong orientation<br/></li><li> Empire Outriders are no longer missing their rifles on their back in idle and running animations<br/></li><li> Added several missing Plagueridden on Palanquin mount animations<br/></li><li> Fixed bug where Repanse on Suleman was not playing original WH2 idle animations<br/></li><li> Fixed various animation issues with the Ripperdactyl mount<br/></li><li> Morathi's animations on the campaign map now match her unique battle animations, and she now holds her sword when mounted on the campaign map</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Audio:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cathay War Drums will once again be audible on executing their abilities</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Performance/Stability:</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash that could occur when cancelling unit recruitment in Campaign</li></ul><hr/><br/>As always, we'd like to say a big thank you to everyone who submitted bug reports over in the CA Community. These reports go a long way in helping us shorten the gap between identifying an issue and resolving it, so if you run into any issues after updating to 5.1.3, please be sure to let us know in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>If you caught our "What's Next?" video back in June you'll remember we mentioned smaller pieces of new content coming alongside our regular patching, and we're excited to announce that patch 5.2, which is currently targeting a late August release, will be the first to include some extra bits and pieces. We'll be sharing a blog in the coming weeks from Design Director Mitchell Heastie, who's been heading up this project, to tell you more about what you can expect.<br/><br/>Until then, we'll see you on the battlefield!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - 1.14.1 - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/489630/view/4368013560353831248</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
We're releasing a new update for Gladius. As per usual, please let us know what you think of the list of changes. Your feedback is essential to keep improving the game.<br/><br/>The team is currently hard at work. We'll have news about new content soon.<br/><br/><i>Changes since 1.13.03</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Version 1.14.1 </div><br/><div class="bb_h3">General</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Technologies are now displayed in multiple columns when there are more than 6 technologies in a tier.<br/></li><li> Join Discord pop-up now appears once on game start.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Balance</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Increased Maleceptor hitpoints from 30 to 36.<br/></li><li> Added Witchfire, Psychic Lash and Ignores Cover to Maleceptor's Psychic Overload ability.<br/></li><li> Added Gift of Mutation to Warp Talons.<br/></li><li> Added Adrenal Glands and Regeneration to Maleceptor and Tyrannocyte.<br/></li><li> Spiritseer's Spirit Mark ability now affects Wraithlords.<br/></li><li> Skitarii Marshal's Agression Override and Control Edict abilities cannot affect fortifications anymore.<br/></li><li> Canoness Lead The Righteous ability cannot affect fortifications anymore.<br/></li><li> Removed Wraithlord' Smash trait.<br/></li><li> Added Chaos Lord, Master of Possession and Warpsmith to the list of Chaos Space Marines units benefiting from Gift of Mutation.<br/></li><li> Removed the action consumption for Weirdboy's Warpath ability.<br/></li><li> Replaced Canoness' Combi-bolter by Boltgun.<br/></li><li> Increased the Wraithlord's Ghostglaive damage from 6.5 to 8.<br/></li><li> Increased the Sydonian Dragoon's Taser Lance damage from 4 to 6.<br/></li><li> Added Acid Blood to Maleceptor and Tyrannocyte.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">Bug Fixes</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed Teleport Homer description not mentioning that Assault Terminators and Chaplains can benefit from the trait.<br/></li><li> Fixed Pulse Accelerator not affecting Breacher Fire Warriors' Pulse Blasters.<br/></li><li> Fixed Chaos Terminators' power sword not being affected by Conjoined Weaponry research.<br/></li><li> Fixed XV107 RVarna's Electromagnetic Shockwave dealing 10% damage to all adjacent units instead of itself only.<br/></li><li> Fixed Wraithlord research not unlocking the Hammer of Wrath research.<br/></li><li> Maleceptor now has hammer of Wrath instead of Living Battering Ram and is affected by Hammer of Wrath research.<br/></li><li> Minor language fixes.<br/></li><li> Tweaked death sound delays.<br/></li><li> Fixed Cryptek's Mindshackle Scarabs ability that should not target units with Synapse Link and Khaine Awakened.<br/></li><li> Fixed Warpsmith' Mechatendrils not being affected by Forbidden Energies research.<br/></li><li> Fixed Librarian's Shockwave ability not applying Pinned.<br/></li><li> Fixed Cryptek's Minshackle Scarabs description.<br/></li><li> Fixed researched technologies tier setting unlocking disabled DLC units.</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
