<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 11 - Deff Rally 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/4338739528778408393</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/3eb6793ca760a94568f7db337ba3cc589f4f3d7d.png"/><br/><br/>Oi, not long now till you all get racing again.<br/>So, let’s discuss this capture-the-flag inspired game mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/041d5eb1b04863a112682c7d2717f99247f56f9c.gif"/><br/><br/>Deff Rally is the other game mode, alongside KILL KONVOY, launching with Early Access on August 6th. It pits two teams of eight against each other in a race to capture points. The first one there, scores big for their team.  <br/><br/>Getting there first is, on paper, the easy part. You and your team then must hold the capture point as the enemy arrives, and the frenzy of bullets unfurls. Holding the point increases how many points you earn. Control is easy to lose, so keeping the capture point is crucial for victory. <br/><br/>Eventually, the point is secured, and a mad dash to reach and dominate the next point begins.  <br/> <br/>When all Capture points have been fought over, a final high Orktane race to the finish line beings to see who’s the ultimate speedy Ork. Your placement in the final race will decide how many points you earn, so it’s all about getting there faster than your opponents. Death, naturally, will slow you down.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/612062d68d7a35884219a907993bdfcb1b59ba2c.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Each vehicle has unique roles and abilities that come to life in Deff Rally. We can’t wait to see how you play it and evolve the game-mode. Here’s some examples of how vehicles can be played in Deff Rally. <br/><br/><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon –</b> With the Snazzagon being better in mid-close ranges, it excels when on the offense taking back the point or getting into the heart of the enemy team. <br/><br/><b>Defkilla Wartrike –</b> Because the Deffkilla Wartrike will struggle if it sits still on a capture point, you will often see it drive around taking down key enemy targets, such as Rukkatrukk Squigbuggies or long ranged vehicles. <br/><br/><b>Shokkjump Dragsta –</b> The Shokkjump Dragsta is fast, so getting to the next objective first, or winning the race is where the Shokkjump Dragsta really shines. <br/><br/><b>Kustom Boosta Blasta –</b> With some of the best mid to long ranges, chipping away at enemies while they’re approaching the capture point is a specialty of this vehicle. Soften them up for your team. <br/><br/><b>Looted Wagon –</b> With heavy damage at long range, one well-placed shot from the Looted Wagon can decide if a push onto the point will succeed or not. <br/><br/><b>Grot Mega Tank –</b> As the heaviest of the bunch, dislodging a Grot Mega Tank from the point after they’ve gotten settled is a struggle. Hold the point while your team is focused on stopping the enemy attack is where the Grot Mega Tank excels. <br/><br/><b>Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy –</b> Don't underestimate the Rukkatrukk Squigbuggy because they can quickly get their team back to full health and ready for the next enemy push onto the point. Recovering your teams' health stops them from being krumped and ultimately delayed while respawning. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c603ec0a4576ad8b56527c5b6ea0076f2baf2ddb.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>Your feedback this past year has helped us balance and shape Deff Rally into what you will see with August 6th release. <br/><br/>This game mode will continue to evolve with your feedback so don’t hesitate to leave your thoughts over on our feedback and bug reporting board: https://speedfreeks40k.featureupvote.com/ <br/><br/>With four maps available on early access release, and changes to the ones you know we’re excited to get you back in as fast as possible! <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/cf69ebec1314f26aef699ada21bfa45f7a8651c2.png"/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!  <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4326354629820779098</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines!</div><br/>We’re only 41 days away from the release of <i>Space Marine 2</i>; it’s the perfect time for our monthly Community Update!<i> (got it? 41 days? 41st Millenium?😉😉)</i> We can sense the excitement growing as the release gets closer, and even more, since we announced that <br/><br/><b><div class="bb_h1"><i>SPACE MARINE 2</i> IS OFFICIALLY GOLD </div></b><br/>For those unfamiliar with the gaming industry, this means that the game has been approved by Microsoft and Sony and that we’ve been given the green light for the production of our retail boxes. Though we’ll continue to work on polish until the release, this essentially means that the game is ready.<br/><br/>This is a huge milestone for the teams and another major step towards the game’s full release on <b>September 9</b>, so we’re very proud to share the good news with you all.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f2446b3f3ca06c5cdc594355c9f372f2319148cd.gif"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>Frequently Asked Questions</b></div><br/>Over the past months, we’ve seen many questions about the precise features of the game. We’ll try to tackle a few here:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Do I need to have played <i>Space Marine 1</i> to go into <i>Space Marine 2</i>? <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Not at all! While there are returning characters, it's a fresh story that can be understood as its own without having played the first game.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Will the game be available on GeForce Now? <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Yes.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Will it be possible to pre-download the game before the release?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> No.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Is there couch co-op?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> No, co-op features will only be available online.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Does the game require to be “always online” to play?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Offline mode is available for the campaign <br/></li><li> PVE can be played offline, but you won't have access to progression if you do not connect to the servers.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> How long does it take to complete the campaign?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> On average, the campaign should take between 10 to 12 hours to complete. This can vary depending on the difficulty and your player profile.</li></ul></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> What are the PC specs?<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> At this moment, we are conducting the final PC specs tests. We’re very aware that it’s one of the most awaited information on the game, and we will come back to you within the next couple of weeks with the recommended and minimum specs.</li></ul></li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>What’s next in August?</b></div><br/>We know you’re super thirsty for more content so be assured that you do not need to worry, you can expect more videos to pop up on our YouTube and social media channels (Discord, Twitter, Facebook). <br/>Talking about videos, we’re currently publishing on our secondary channel a series of short videos detailing some aspects of the game: weapons, enemies, environments… <br/><br/>You'll find the complete playlist <b>here</b>.<br/><br/>Amongst the upcoming short videos, there will be more weapons, a rundown of the different PvE classes, and more!<br/><br/>On top of that, you can expect co-op previews to start dropping during August, with content creators starting publishing videos on their side as well. <br/><br/>Next, we’ll detail the post-launch content of Space Marine 2 in a blog article that should be published around mid-August.<br/><br/>Finally, we’re reaching the final stages of our North America Tour, with Chicago (August 16-18) and Toronto (August 22-25) being the final places where you’ll be able to put your hands on Space Marine 2’s demo before the release. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1775b7d9acd2d9d530728b5ab5361daa9a3ab05f.jpg"/><br/><br/>Aaand that’s it for this month! We hope you’re as excited as we are! <br/>We’re really in the final weeks before the launch of Space Marine 2, it truly feels unreal and we can’t wait to see you play the game! <br/><br/>See you next month!<br/><b>The Emperor protects</b><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔧 Dev Blog 10 - Kustom Boosta-Blasta 🔧</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/7024009805570491473</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450<br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/868f9df0e78cfff3c67fd4690fa9a05682c0976e.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/68e9361c2399949b913369b407490b4a82f51df6.png"/><br/><br/>The Kustom Boosta-Blasta, is a roaring engine of destruction in the hands of the Orks. A mid-ranged vehicle who lays down Dakka upon the battlefield from afar and uses their utility to stay at a distance. <br/><br/>In Speed Freeks this versatile vehicle allows for a lot of different playstyles to suit the scenarios you find yourself in. Whether it’s using your mobility to help out with objectives, laying down fire on the battlefield, helping to pick off key targets or putting pressure on the enemy tanks.<br/><br/>The base speed of this vehicle is average, tied with the Boomdakka Snazzwagon. However, the Burna Exhaust ability is a strong movement tool that opens a lot of possibilities, such as jumping onto a roof to escape enemies, getting extra airtime to recharge your boost bar, or using Dash right as you land to convert vertical speed into horizontal speed. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/b09f0fbdabff31ddd0d90ffe6e1290afadc13069.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Abilities</div><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/c92d9b0654284f8bf398169b2199225006cf54ac.png"/><br/><b>Rivet Kannon </b><br/>This fearsome tool-turned-weapon fires a thunderous hail of heated rivets. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/0e303f935d8c5c8569613e8ff6105caf47c9ce3f.png"/><br/><b>Stikkbomb </b><br/>Hurl a Stikkbomb ​to damage and disrupt enemy vehicles. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/d1486798446edb272631dbef4ef558bc29c0b991.png"/><br/><b>Burna Exhaust </b><br/>An explosion of flame​ from the exhausts​ lifts the Kustom Boosta-Blasta off the ground. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4346af90da9a6945385d1ba4948228ea4512fdb0.png"/><br/><b>Dash </b><br/>The vehicle lunges violently forward and smashes enemies. The direction you are aiming determines where the vehicle will go. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/e57a81468738a0f5e750742154d74a58cc20f19f.png"/><br/><br/>Managing your range is key to playing the Kustom Boosta-Blasta. Never get too close to close ranged opponents, and never be too far away from long ranged opponents. As the Kustom Boosta-Blasta you are useful at many different ranges, use it to your advantage and be at the range your opponents are weak at. <br/><br/>Use your utility to keep opponents at the distance you want them at. Throw the grenade to throw them off their track or jump up to high ground where they can’t reach you. You decide where you want to fight. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/ec50a319871e11ed3ff2f181a3e6a940b3281d1f.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Team-Ups</div><b>The Snazzwagon</b> and Boosta-Blasta are a potent combo, with both vehicles having escape and/or disorientation abilities in Billowing Smoke and the Stikkbomb. This duo can be frustrating for the opposition – and fun for those driving them.   <br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Good Against </div><b>Looted Wagon –</b> Using walls and terrain you can stay out of enemy fire, while putting pressure on the Looted Wagon. If they don’t expect, you can easily end up scoring easy kills on it. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/67287117c1d91613deb37fd7faf437bacc5b7c13.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/20bbe82d5d4c77022c497e2ca3327c054e1a8a41.gif"/><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/6a7aba8acaa8b3f4d93db8dc8e970a806779b1b2.png"/><br/><br/>On behalf of Caged Element and PLAION, we’z shoutin’ a big WAAAGH! Thanks for joinin’ da Kult of Speed in Warhammer 40,000: Speed Freeks!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/819aea0a53b2c46043e4b92571963cfeb3b348a5.png"/><br/><br/><b>Join our community-focused game development discussions on your favorite platform:</b><br/><br/>Steam Discussions<br/>Discord<br/>r/SpeedFreeks<br/>Suggest Features &amp; Report Bugs<br/>Technical Support<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078450]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac hotfix 1.2.0.31</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4372516525983699422</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>We're deploying a small update 1.2.0.31 for Mac, which will resolve an annoying issue with colors suddenly becoming inverted. This issue is Mac-specific, and this update will not affect any other platforms.<br/><br/>For the Emperor!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 5.1.2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/4371390165253895429</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/07ce6276bc797229a0fa853f9c48102c239cf622.jpg"/><br/><br/>Greetings all!<br/><br/>We've just rolled out Hotfix 5.1.2, addressing a number of issues identified in the wake of Patch 5.1.0 and Hotfix 5.1.1.<br/><br/>Here's what we've got today:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where vassal income would significantly reduce after loading a save following the removal of a vassal due to endgame objectives. This was caused by the game subtracting the previous tribute from the income without resetting the tribute value, leading to repeated incorrect deductions. We missed this specific issue initially, but we believe this updated solution resolves all related problems.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue with the 'Continue Campaign' button in Launcher not continuing the campaign, and instead redirecting to the main game screen.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when players overcast a spell while commanding a unit with multiple shot types in battle. This issue was identified and resolved thanks to detailed reports from our community forums!<br/></li><li> Fixed the following abilities not affecting units that were not nearby when the battle began:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rune of Stoicism<br/></li><li> Ancestor Rune<br/></li><li> Rune of Courage<br/></li><li> Spirit Conduit (Hierotitan)</li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue when the general was removed from the military force, the unit would become a colonel and be treated by the UI like a hero rather than a normal unit.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where river crossing battle maps would not trigger when fighting on river crossings or alongside rivers on the Immortal Empires campaign map.<br/></li><li> Fixed rendering issues with Pistoliers unit which would result the rider model not being visible.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where playing custom battles as Daemons of Chaos, using the Shadow Legion colour scheme, the army abilities would be missing.<br/></li><li> Fixed plate armor opacity issues with several Empire units.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug when moving Thorek on Anvil mount in campaign, which would lead to his model tilting backwards during the move animation.<br/></li><li> Explosive ammunition for Hochland Long Rifles no longer reduces penetration value from 1 to 0.<br/></li><li> Tempest from the Lore of High Magic now matches its visual duration at 17 seconds for both regular and overcast.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Dark Elf buildings that reduce slave count only functioned correctly when constructed by the player. Captured settlements with pre-existing economic buildings did not reduce slave count until these buildings were upgraded or replaced. This fix ensures that the slave count reduction feature works as intended immediately upon acquiring such buildings.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash in multiplayer campaign games where completing the Changeling Cult building "Ravaging Host" in another player's settlement would cause the game to crash. This was due to a Lua error in the script that was meant to trigger a dilemma for the player upon discovering the cult.<br/></li><li> Fixed some instances of skills that penalise enemy hero success chance instead being granted to the enemy, making them penalise your success chance.<br/></li><li> Fixed issue where a placeholder icon would show on some Shadowy Dealing actions.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where a military force with plague was able to get infected and lost its ability to use the switching plagues mechanic.<br/></li><li> Fixing an audio issue with the Mechanical Steed mount which was not triggering surface appropriate footsteps.<br/></li><li> After a long tug-of-war with his rot beast, Kayzk has finally recovered his blade, which he now wields in all its disgusting glory.<br/></li><li> One player watching the Immortal Empires flyby will no longer block the other players' actions, sometimes causing desync.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the chance of a magic item dropping or being stolen was not being correctly modified by effects on Heroes embedded in the army.<br/></li><li> The Black Staff item's bound power of darkness now matches regular power of darkness.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> +0.3 winds per second.<br/></li><li> +does equivalent self damage.</li></ul></li><li> Added missing page-turning sound effects for Blue Scribes.<br/></li><li> Fixed a bug where armies would get replenished to 100% after being defeated and sacked. Now they will be replenished only by the desired amount of 25%.<br/></li><li> Added missing lava and portal sound effects to Bleeding Spire map.</li></ul><br/>Thanks for all of your bug reports and feedback, all of which have been extremely valuable in helping our teams investigate and resolve issues as quickly as possible! If you run into any issues after updating to 5.1.2, please be sure to report them in our dedicated bug reporting sub-forum.<br/><br/>See you on the battlefield!<br/><br/><b>—The <i>Total War</i> Team</b><br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">⚠ IMPORTANT</div><hr/><hr/><br/>If you experience any issues after downloading the update, please take a moment to <b>Verify the integrity of the game files</b> first to ensure there were no issues when downloading. A step-by-step guide can be found in this article.<br/><br/>If the issues persist, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><hr/><hr/><div class="bb_h1">🧱 MOD WARNING</div><hr/><hr/><br/>Please note that user-generated mods may have compatibility issues with new game updates. If you are encountering performance or stability issues following a release, is recommended that you disable any mods you're running. If you continue to experience issues, please visit our support site for additional troubleshooting steps and assistance.<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, drop by our official social channels.

Steam Discussions X Facebook Instagram Discord</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 09:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
