<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Plenty O' Fixes &amp; Improvements</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2078450/view/657092583901627781</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<p class="bb_paragraph">As we wind down 2025, we as a team have got to say that we're pretty proud of what we've done with <b>Speed Freeks</b> this year.</p><p class="bb_paragraph">The game launched into 1.0, we added a wild new vehicle, a level editor with workshop, and a new mode for playing custom maps - along with a ton of bug fixes and improvements overall that brought the game up to to a higher level of quality. We're really happy with the current state of the game itself, and hope you gits are too. Just need more players now! </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3">Thanks to all the gits who stuck with us and continue to do so, we've used your positive feedback, crazy gameplay videos and awesome custom maps as fuel to keep us going. You da best Orks around 💪</div><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/4bbf5c7b41218bfeadb372e928347b716aa19df2.gif"/></p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/a9ddc031a54d7d0169b5555691b580f941f20bd9.png"/></p><div class="bb_h3">DA UPDATE</div><p class="bb_paragraph">As for our final update of the year, it's got plenty of changes, so have a look below 👀 </p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>VEHICLES ➤</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Boomdakka Snazzwagon</b>Burst Speshul weapon damage reduced by 15%, removed weapon rotation clamp</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Deffkopta</b>Knockback from enemy weapons increased<br/>Brief timeout on accel/reverse inputs added when hit by a weapon with knockback</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph"><b>Looted Wagon</b>Fixed issue with Grot Bomm yeeting players randomly</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with <b>Deffkilla Wartrike </b>and <b>Grot Mega Tank</b> not taking damage from the front. Whoops</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>TEAM BALANCE ⚖️</b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added team balancing pass right before the 3,2,1 countdown, to account for any payers that have left during warm-up</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Made changes to player skill rating calculation to be more accurate. This should result in more balanced matches</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Maximum difference in player count between teams due to balancing reduced to 2</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>CREATION MODE </b>🛠️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Free Cam can now clip through geometry for easier movement</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Mouse wheel now increases free cam flying speed</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added death volume assets for placing in maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added spotlight assets</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Set rotation to snap to 5 degrees</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fix for AZERTY keyboard issues</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with host not showing up as a player in Game Browser player count</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Stopped Creation Mode from sending host back to main menu if a network error occurs</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved thumbnails for some interactive assets</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MEK WORKSHOP </b>⚙️</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added functionality for easily playing a map from anywhere in the Workshop. Now players can click on a map then go to Play ːsteamthumbsupː</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added a search bar to easier find maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added sorting by author</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Name of the base level used now shown for custom maps</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with maps getting duplicated as well as other submission issues</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed Workshop map reporting issue</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Improved handling of map IDs to avoid issues with overwriting or deleting maps</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>KUSTOM RALLY 🏁 </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Added "GO TO NEXT MAP" vote in ESC menu</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">An automatic vote prompt will pop up every 5 minutes in case players are stuck</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">End of race timer increased to 60 seconds from 30</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with players not being able to respawn during end of race timer</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">End of match timer is now cancelled when the last player finishes</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Removed start and end timers in solo matches</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MISC </b>🎲</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Bots now have <b>a lot</b> more fun while waiting for the match to start</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Reduced the amount of Stompa defense bots to 1, so most of them enter the fight</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Teammate bots now don't block players as much, having better avoidance code</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Enabled Dakka Frenzy in Kill Konvoy mode</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><div class="bb_h3"><b>MENU / UI 📜 </b></div><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">There's now a warning on the HUD for all players when the host's PC or network performance is poor</p><ul class="bb_ul"><li><p class="bb_paragraph">This will make it more clear as to why there are sync issues in the match, if the host PC is struggling</p></li></ul></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Switch teams prompt now showing on the HUD again</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with painting vehicle accessories</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed issue with painting Ork Lootas</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Fixed "Distance Travelled" calculation for popup medal</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Changed eligibility text on Leaderboard screen to be more accurate</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Refactored player report/vote kick into a single screen in ESC menu called PLAYER LIST</p></li><li><p class="bb_paragraph">Optimized colour swatches UI in KUSTOMIZE screen, so now all colours have proper image associated</p></li></ul><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">If you celebrate anything this time of year, we hope you have a great time with whoever's in yer mob (if it's a solo mob, too - dey still be krumpin' 'ard)</p><p class="bb_paragraph"></p><p class="bb_paragraph">We'll be jumpin' in fer sum krumpin' over da holidays, so we'z see you'z on da battlefield n' racetracks. YA GITS!</p><p class="bb_paragraph"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/44159197/bff6e97958bf7cec3025c8f54db27b7e22dbc4ee.png"/></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/594570/view/527614642864784439</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b6a4bf31711b2ae8081e2155f7472fbd8a8ed3bc.jpg"/><br/><br/>It is a snowstorm of discounts as the Winter Sale is now on! Grab up to 75% off Total War titles and DLCs, and treat yourself or your loved ones to the gift of strategy this holiday season! 🎁<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 05/01/26  @ 10AM PST/6PM GMT</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510726144262144995</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b6a4bf31711b2ae8081e2155f7472fbd8a8ed3bc.jpg"/><br/><br/>It is a snowstorm of discounts as the Winter Sale is now on! Grab up to 75% off Total War titles and DLCs, and treat yourself or your loved ones to the gift of strategy this holiday season! 🎁<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 05/01/26  @ 10AM PST/6PM GMT</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sale NOW ON!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/364360/view/494963545565299645</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b6a4bf31711b2ae8081e2155f7472fbd8a8ed3bc.jpg"/><br/><br/>It is a snowstorm of discounts as the Winter Sale is now on! Grab up to 75% off Total War titles and DLCs, and treat yourself or your loved ones to the gift of strategy this holiday season! 🎁<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/1142710/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/779340/Total_War_THREE_KINGDOMS/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1937780/Total_War_PHARAOH/<br/><br/>👉 Check out all the deals here 👈<br/><br/><div class="bb_code"><div class="bb_h3">🕙 Sale ends 05/01/26  @ 10AM PST/6PM GMT</div></div><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War - Thank You For Your Support In 2025</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/510726144262144981</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/b906761437e681c4f98c1053557cdd674b82466b.png"/><br/><br/>​Hello friends,<br/><br/>Here we are again; the end of another year and a moment to reflect.<br/><br/>Several letters ago I committed myself and the franchise to being more open and transparent (mixed success based on some feedback I see), and this is a chance for me to talk about both our successes, and failures.<br/><br/>Thank you so much for your support over the years be it through praise or criticism. We do read the feedback, take it to heart, sometimes beat ourselves up about how dumb we did a thing, and then plan how we make things better.<br/><br/>2025 has been a landmark year for the Total War franchise. We celebrated 25 incredible years of the franchise and marked the occasion by announcing three new projects I’ve been excited about since I came to CA. We also shared a first look at Warcore, the brand-new Total War game engine (to be fair it’s built on top of the last one so a little Ship of Theseus here), and spoke about bringing our new games to console (I'll talk more about that later).<br/><br/>We revealed the worlds’ worst kept secret, we’re making a game in one of my favorite universes, Warhammer 40,000. At the same time, we look to our past, both Total War’s and humanity’s, to set our sights on the Middle Ages with MEDIEVAL III (now? Soon?). I’ll write more on why we made the call to announce it. And finally, we are not finished with Total War Warhammer III as we revealed Lords of the End Times. It’s my hope that we talked about at least one setting that you're excited for.<br/><br/>Our Anniversary Showcase was the first event like this we’ve ever done; and a longstanding ambition for us.<br/><br/>We know we didn’t get everything perfect in this plan, but aligning three projects at very different stages in their development cycle is challenging. There’s plenty of feedback we’ll take on board for next time, and that’s exactly how it should be. In retrospect, I wish we’d also spent time celebrating our players and the mods across all our games – but that’s something we’ll explore in the future.<br/><br/>For a first attempt, I couldn’t be happier for the teams who pulled this off and gave you a genuine glimpse into the projects we’ve eagerly been building. I’m proud of what we did and happy for what we learned. Those in front of the camera are lifelong Total War fans, and while exciting, it’s also incredibly nerve wracking talking publicly about the things you’re working on – I'm hugely proud of them all. It was an enormously complex orchestration of presenting the showcase internationally, launching a DLC, and releasing Immortal Empires to WH1 and 2 players.<br/><br/>Over half a million people tuned in, and seeing that mix of familiar faces, players coming back after years away, and people discovering Total War for the very first time was awesome. It meant a lot to the team, and moments like that remind us why we choose to do this for a living.<br/><br/>In the future, we want to deliver more of these moments. Could a Total War-con work? Would you come? Regardless, future events might not all look the same, but each will show what Total War is up to across its many projects and where it’s going.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 CONTINUE READING 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
