<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #46 (1.4.12) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4613462277069020606</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/b5e2e36c1c1da35979e69db60e03486121cc24c9.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Everyone, </div><br/>Our latest hotfix (1.4.12) is out now on Steam and the rest of our platforms will follow. You’ll find the patch notes below!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where ammo crates would still spawn in Maelstrom Mission C-I-VI.<br/></li><li> The tooltip for the Stopping Power stat has been updated to reflect that it affects damage as well.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue that caused the canteen on Psyker “Shroudwrap Carapace” cosmetic upperbody to be warped.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Unlocked and Loaded - Update (September 26, 2024)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/4265558571909993932</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/9d07b750bf96cc23c008306a28c74295d3554eb3.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Heyo Devoted Rejects, </div><br/>We’re excited to announce the next free update coming to Darktide - Unlocked and Loaded - <b>will be releasing on September 26, 2024. </b><br/><br/>https://youtu.be/69zI8J5nnZU <br/><br/>Unlocked and Loaded will include the overhaul to itemization, a new mission with a new objective, and improvements to social features.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Itemization Overhaul: </div>Unlock Your Potential: With the itemization overhaul, players will master their weapons over time, unlock blessings, weapon marks, and perks, and tinker with their gear to increase its Power. This overhaul will help players carve a clear path to get the weapons and gameplay they want.<i> (More dev blogs on this soon and the next Q&amp;A blog will be released this week!)</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Mission:</div>Time’s running out! Players will race against time and repel heretics in this shorter high-octane mission in which players’ strike teams are the only thing standing between a barreling freight train and Tertium. (Did you see the end of the teaser trailer?) <i>(We’re also working on a dev blog for this mission, too!)</i><br/><div class="bb_h2">New Social Feature:</div>Team-up against Chaos: As Darktide is made to be enjoyed with others, our new Group Finder features will make teaming up with like-minded players easier. Before embarking on a mission, players will be able to form groups and band together to wreak havoc among the ranks of the heretics. You can form groups based on language, difficulty, mission focus, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Marine 2 - Roadmap and upcoming content</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4238536974144553830</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Greetings, Space Marines.</div><br/>Today we’re diving into the content we’re planning to add to <i>Space Marine 2</i> after release and what’s included in the Season Pass. Let’s get into it!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1cb696ec0f06e27ac2b0951cc64b04cfdf16b264.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">September</div><br/>First things first, the launch of the game! If you have pre-ordered the game, you will receive the Macragge’s Chosen DLC, which includes unique appearances for the Chainsword and Bolt Rifle, as well as a unique right Pauldron. You will unlock this cosmetic item after completing the campaign mission “Skyfire”.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/114b3b1552c2e165fe38be3bf8e4879ab3b0635c.jpg"/><br/>By pre-ordering the Gold or Ultra Editions, you’ll have access to the Season Pass, which has a series of cosmetic items based on specific chapters. More info about the first season can be found later in this blog.<br/><br/>The Season Pass has been envisioned as a way to enhance your customisation for your character. All the gameplay additions listed here in the roadmap (including weapons, game modes, and maps) are intended to arrive in *free game patches* and will be <b>accessible to everyone</b>.<br/><br/>Finally, Ultra Edition owners will receive the Ultramarines Champions Pack. It’s a unique, richly detailed full armour set for the Heavy class that comes with its unique Heavy Bolter.<br/><i>Note that this pack is and will only be available to Ultra Edition owners and won’t be sold separately.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/4f2914fbc240f087398326bb648624a519d387b0.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h2">First weeks after release</div><br/>The launch of <i>Space Marine 2</i> is only the start of our journey together withe the Season 1! In the first weeks after launch, we’ll focus on collecting your feedback across all community channels to bring some quick adjustments and improvements through quick patches. Then we will start our season 2.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Season 2</div><br/>Season 2 content will be released between October and the end of the year.<br/> <br/>Amongst the free content, you can expect a new Operations map, a new enemy, a harder difficulty level, a new weapon, and various other improvements.<br/><br/>Season Pass owners will be able to unlock new cosmetics based on the Dark Angels chapter: colour schemes, heraldry, a weapon skin, and a Champion skin: a unique full armour set for the Bulwark class.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">And after?</div><br/>Much more content will be added throughout 2025! New Operations, PvP maps, game modes like Horde mode, and more will all expand on the content of <i>Space Marine 2</i> for free! <br/><br/>On top of that, more cosmetic items based on iconic chapters will be added to customise your characters.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ea8e4d47f0ca45ce397a78fe792d6c22b51cb365.jpg"/> <i>Under development, subject to change</i><br/><br/><b>Today also marks the launch of a new community hub: Focus Together</b>. All players will be able to use this new platform to chat with our team, share feedback or even suggest new ideas for <i>Space Marine 2</i>. Make sure to create an account there ahead of launch!<br/><br/><i>Space Marine 2</i> has never been closer, and we’re blown away by your excitement. Thank you so much for the enthusiasm you have shared with us on all platforms! We truly can’t wait to read and watch your feedback next week about the fruit of years of work from all of us. <br/><br/>As you’ve seen above, the launch is the start of a new chapter for all of us and we’ll continue to share regular community updates about the wealth of content that will be  coming to the game through the rest of this year, and beyond!<br/><br/>Thank you,<br/><i>The Space Marine 2 team</i><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Custom Sale 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/4284698870322092511</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>The <b>Isometric Custom Sale 2024</b> on Steam has begun. Let’s take a look at the good deals it offers the players!<br/><br/>Please, note that the sale will take place <b>till August 30</b>, so don’t miss the discount!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</div><br/>Get the Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader game at a <b>35% discount</b> and dive into adventures of the Koronus Expanse. Claim your Warrant of Trade and become a legendary Rogue Trader!<br/><br/>
<iframe frameborder="0" height="200" src="https://store.steampowered.com/widget/2186680/" width="850"></iframe>
<br/><br/>Boost your gaming experience by getting unique in-game items and models, as well as digital add-ons available in Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Voidfarer Pack and Deluxe Pack at a <b>35% discount</b>!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682670/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Voidfarer_Pack/<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/<br/><br/>Get the Season Pass at a <b>35% discount</b> and unlock access to the first Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader DLC – Void Shadows alongside the upcoming Lex Imperialis DLC!<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/<br/><div class="bb_h2">Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous </div><br/>Dive into the adventures in the lands of the World Wound and lead the great Crusade! Get the Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous game at a <b>70% discount</b>. Hurry, Drezen City needs its hero.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1184370/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Enhanced_Edition/<br/><br/>Your journey doesn't end here. Three DLCs are waiting for you in the Season Pass 1, which you can get with <b>70% off</b>.<br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1694801/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass/<br/><br/>And that’s not all either. Another three wonderful plot DLCs can be obtained as a part of the Season Pass 2! A ton of fun and content awaits you at a pleasant <b>50% discount</b>! <br/><br/>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145870/Pathfinder_Wrath_of_the_Righteous__Season_Pass_2/<br/><br/>Note that the discount will be lower if you buy the DLCs separately.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about the customisation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/4238536974129469039</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Greetings, Space Marines!</div><br/>Today, we’re going to examine customisation in <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i> more closely. We’ve received many questions about this topic, and we hope to answer most of them here!<br/><br/>Customisation <b>starts in the Armouring Hall</b>, where you can select your class, your equipment, perks, and, today’s main topic, customise your Space Marine’s armour.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1257ec2f0e113c1f4ff55c25d5d5ced5dff82a73.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/798202ee80c44d5c8f17b16a4958f7159019bb7e.jpg"/><br/>Each class comes with a selection of pre-made armour sets that you’ll have to unlock in PvE or PvP game modes. You can also decide to <b>create your own custom armour set</b>. This is where your creativity shines! Various designs of helm, pauldrons, breastplate, wargear, gauntlets and greaves <b>can be unlocked by playing in multiplayer modes</b>. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/16eefc0a5c7e68f5cd292cc26d344ffaca2dbc5a.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e5692144b24dd5b8cbdef99cf27800bbeec94509.jpg"/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/40344855832f07abc6aea8018e1c89f04243d8e6.jpg"/><br/>Customisation gets especially interesting when checking out the second tab of the customisation menu, <b>“Astartes Chapters”</b>. Here, <b>you can access presets </b>representing many <b>legendary Space Marine Chapters. </b><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e56be28792ee543448d97d9f775c28c9232b573c.jpg"/><br/>Once again, you’ll be able to customise your armour set, <b>personalising each part with different paints, emblems, and colour patterns. </b>You’ll unlock these elements in the Heraldry menu to faithfully recreate the colour scheme of your favourite Chapter, or create your own custom design.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/988e7534ef1715482fee6197d0eaaa1e64228530.jpg"/><i>Before…</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/db3ed76c63323aafb2189e548198b285e5c8d901.jpg"/><i>And after! (don’t even say he’s ugly)</i><br/><br/><b>Heretic Astartes</b> characters can also be customised for your PvP matches! Each class corresponds to a <b>specific Traitor Legion </b>(for example, Assault will always be represented by a Night Lords Raptor), but you can change the colours and apply different emblems.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/80832908b59bf5d89b5a43f66414e062a44879cb.jpg"/><br/>Finally, there’s the <b>Astartes Heraldry menu</b>, where <b>you’ll acquire each Chapter’s unique customisation elements. </b>Emblems, colours and armour parts from Adeptus Astartes, Heretic Astartes, Unknown Foundings, First Founding, Second Founding and Successor Chapters! <br/><br/>On launch, <b>over 30 different Chapters have their colours and heraldry available to unlock. </b>Whilst some of them are exclusive to the Season Pass, the majority of them are available to unlock through game progression.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/ad19c4af6cf6be107625b23638690b288db8e4ea.jpg"/><br/>And that’s it for the customisation! Don’t hesitate to let us know if you still have questions regarding this feature. We know how important customisation is for any Warhammer fan! We hope you’ll like it and spend hours in these menus to create YOUR very own Space Marine.<br/><br/>See you very soon on the battlefield!<br/><br/><b>The Emperor protects.</b><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
