<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>February Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500566410271917053</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h2">Hello Space Marines 🫡</div><br/>Let’s recap what occurred in February on Space Marine 2 a bit and then we’ll tackle future topics! We know you're eager for Patch 7 to drop! There's still a bit of a wait, but in the meantime, we'll be sure to tease you a little.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">FEBRUARY RECAP</div><br/>This month we released the 6.0 Datavault Update, containing new free and Season Pass content. You may check the entire changelog here! 📖<br/><br/>Mostly, the biggest features that were added to the game are:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Datavault, with new cosmetic rewards<br/></li><li> The Biovore<br/></li><li> New PvP Map “Tomb”<br/></li><li> Salamanders Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Raven Guard Cosmetic Pack including its Successor Chapters<br/></li><li> FOV Slider<br/></li><li> Perks rework</li></ul>Following that, we released the 6.1 Hotfix to help with a few remaining bugs and connectivity issues, mostly. Again, you can read the patch notes here.<br/>We are aware that with these two updates, a few issues remain, such as: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> FPS drops<br/></li><li> Too many spore mines spawning at the same time</li></ul>We’re actively working on it.<br/>Hotfix 6.2 will arrive next week. It shall fix the spore mines issue and bring some balancing tweaks.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">IMPERIAL VIGIL COMMUNITY EVENT</div><br/>We heard about your desire to have an emblem-less Mk VIII Errant Helmet, so here’s your chance! ✨ This cosmetic is entirely free, the only requirement is to link your PROS account to Space Marine 2.<br/>Here’s your brief: “Achieve a victory with each of 6 classes in Operations Mode to win the emblem-less Mark VIII Errant Helmet”<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/876731048e75bea664881bc7949c13b396be58a9.png"/><br/><br/>The event lasts until March 3rd.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">NOTE ABOUT COMMUNITY EVENTS</div><br/>We have noted that the Community Events have received cold feedback since we introduced them as an additional way to unlock cosmetic items. We saw that many of you mentioned FOMO generated by the events. Rest assured, we are not looking to transform Space Marine 2 into a full live service game. The items available through events WILL be available later, for everyone. We want Community Events to be a way to unlock the items in advance, for the most dedicated players, and not to be a source of frustration and stress for everyone.<br/><br/>However, that means we must provide a smooth experience in unlocking said items, which has not been the case so far. We deeply apologize for the trouble, and are currently working on a simplified process to unlock the items, to make the experience less constraining.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WHAT’S COMING…</div><br/>The 7.0 Update is in the making! ✨ We’re working on it and we’ll give you a more precise date once we get one. 🙌<br/><br/>This update will bring several awaited features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> One Chapter Pack<br/></li><li> One Champion Pack<br/></li><li> Private PvP lobbies<br/></li><li> A new weapon (only in PvE for now)<br/></li><li> New Operation<br/></li><li> Weapon perks rebalance<br/></li><li> Class weapon loadouts rework<br/></li><li> PvE Prestige Rank: once you reach level 25 on a class, you can buy a Prestige Level that will unlock a unique Prestige Perk. Choose them wisely, because you won’t be able to change your selected Prestige Perks before unlocking the 4 Prestige Levels. On top of that power boost, each class will have a unique cosmetic reward that emphasizes the class’ iconic armour part. <br/></li><li> and more!</li></ul>Stay tuned, we’ll soon come with more info.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">HORDE MODE</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/6f4bd2012c6235fab5e95505ccc44b45a4d0c5db.png"/><br/><br/>…..So apparently you’re waiting for the Horde Mode.<br/><br/>You’re very eager to get more info on the Horde Mode, it’s one of our top priorities right now. <br/>One thing we can say is that it will be very different from the Space Marine 1 Horde Mode, and that there are surprises we can’t wait for you to find out about. 😉<br/><br/>Once we get really interesting things to show you about it, we will do it!<br/><br/>Bear with us 🙏<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">PUBLIC TEST SERVER</div><br/>We’re also excited to share our goal to launch our Public Test Servers  in just a few weeks! 🙌 Expect it to take place in March and before Patch 7.<br/>Once we get a specific date, we’ll make an official statement on our socials and Discord!<br/><br/>This will give you early access to upcoming features and the opportunity to share your feedback, helping us refine the content before its official release.<br/><br/>It will exclusively happen on Steam, neither on EGS nor consoles. It will be very easy to install because it will act as a separate game.<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">COMMUNITY FEEDBACK ON THE NEW ABSOLUTE DIFFICULTY - A word from our Game Director</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">We would like to hear your opinion regarding Absolute difficulty.</div><br/>Overall, we are quite happy with how intense the difficulty itself is. We see that it requires a lot of concentration and we feel like it’s fun in terms of how many enemies you have to face, how hard they hit you etc. <br/><br/>At the same time, we see some comments that it’s a bit easy. Yet on the other hand we don’t want to mess it up and would like to hear the voice of the community first.<br/>Here is some data and context.<br/><br/>According to our stats, the average win rate on Absolute difficulty is ~60% (significantly higher than Lethal difficulty that sits at 50%), which seems a bit higher than we expected.<br/>At the same time such high win rate is explained by three facts:<br/><ol><li> Absolute difficulty is locked for new users<br/></li><li> Only ~12% of daily play time is spent on Absolute difficulty.<br/></li><li> Only ~15% of weekly active players play at least 1 match on Absolute difficulty</li></ol><br/>This means that only a small portion of very hardcore and well-prepared players are playing the Absolute difficulty, and we must find a proper balance between wishes of the hardcore players and more casual players that simply want to have fun.<br/><br/>I will be completely honest; I think we are almost at our limit in terms of how we can make the game harder without making it unfair and not fun. We can’t significantly increase the number of enemies for performance and memory reasons. Greatly increasing enemy damage and hp will make it so players will die randomly and will make enemies bullet sponges, which will not be fun.<br/><br/>We do not want to implement a new difficulty, because that would split the matchmaking pool even more. We have to stick to the existing 6 difficulties.<br/><br/>The proper way of doing this would be implementing a set of gameplay modifiers (i.e. tight formation gameplay modifiers that we’ve tried to release earlier), combination of which would make each challenge unique. And I’m happy to announce that we are already working on the system, however this will take some time.”<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">For now, we can tweak some parameters and we would like to hear your opinion on specific items:</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 1:</div>Would you like to see Dual Terminus enemies and more Terminus enemies in general on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/><i>We can make it so there will be way more Terminus enemies on a level, potentially 2 at the same time. Plus we can lift restriction that prevents Terminus enemies from spawning on levels that have final bosses (i.e Hive Tyrant)</i><br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 2:</div>Shall we slightly increase enemy health and damage on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/><i>Some of the builds can break health thresholds and start one-shotting enemies. We are only talking about small health and damage tweaks that should not cause enemies to become bullet sponges.</i><br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 3:</div>Would it be better to have more limited ammo refills on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/>Vote here<br/> <br/><div class="bb_h3">❔ Poll 4:</div>Do you want even more aggressive enemies on Absolute difficulty?<br/><br/>Vote here<br/><br/>We will try to implement the adjustments as soon as we can.<br/><br/><i>- Dmitriy Grigorenko, Game Director.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3"><b>​Please do not take into account the total number of points spent on an answer. We will only consider the number of entries each answer has received for equity reasons.</b></div><br/><div class="bb_h1">EXCLUSIVE WALLPAPERS ON FOCUS TOGETHER</div><br/>Twelve new exclusive Space Marine 2 wallpapers have dropped on our community platform Focus Together. Make sure to create an account here and get them for free!<br/>Here’s a sneak peak of some of them:<br/><br/>Once you’ve created your account, you can directly link your Steam account to it. By doing so, you will earn different badges, avatars and titles to pimp your profile, so sign in now!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/754f328ed8ab7dcb2a920fded4233f6bd2b39c9a.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">EMOTES WERE WORTH A SHOT!</div><br/>Since the release of the Datavault Update, you’ve shared countless screenshots showing the different emotes, and we love it!!<br/><br/>Here’s a little compendium but if you want to see more, you should definitely check the wall of screenshots on our Discord! <br/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/dedee6d1073f6bf364bfbceb55b4862f8322365f.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/114535732445bbf52b3eb20b419716d9059a2b9e.jpg"/></div></div><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/1f4071e296ec74e487dc8c298c927f7812d21f36.png"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/09beb4a8dab61169c4a755a187f26de9223c1438.jpg"/></div></div></div>Props to adomic. , husky_jb, sisokalis and marcel_nemet for the shots!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">That’s it for this month!</div>Don’t hesitate to provide feedback on the upcoming content in the comments below, and in the ideas section of Focus Together.<br/>We’ll see you next month for another Community Update.<br/><br/><i>With love &amp; respect,<br/>From Saber and Focus.</i><br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">The Emperor Protects! 🙏</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.1 Dev Blog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497188710547194704</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/5cc792a3f0c79370a2d0787ae9f9a9550cc6cd7d.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>The time has come for us to talk more about what’s coming to Total War: WARHAMMER III in Patch 6.1, and today we have one of our talented Designers here to shed some light on the changes and additions you can expect to see when it arrives in mid March.<br/><br/>Before we hand over the mic, we’d like to say a huge thank you to everyone who has opted in to our Campaign AI Beta on Steam over the past few weeks. We’ve had some great feedback that we’re already hard at work parsing through, and will be closing this current round of Beta testing this Friday 28th February at 11:00 GMT. The Beta feedback survey will remain open until Sunday 2nd March at 21:00 GMT, so if you haven’t already, please do take a few minutes to share your thoughts with us and have your voice heard to help shape the future of Campaign AI. We’ll be in touch in the near future with an update on our next steps, and hopefully set a date for the next Beta round.<br/><br/>With that said, it’s time to hand over to Will to talk more about what’s coming with 6.1 in mid March.<br/><br/>Enjoy!<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">👉 PATCH 6.1 DEV BLOG 👈</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive Unreleased Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/502817574909644223</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains!<br/><br/>For those willing to infuse themselves with the epic Warhammer atmosphere, we present the exclusive music from Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader that was not included in the official game's OST. Let's praise the Emperor and listen to this epic soundtrack!<br/><br/>
<iframe allowfullscreen="1" frameborder="0" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOPz4SnSi8A?fs=1&amp;modestbranding=1&amp;rel=0" width="850"></iframe>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix #62 (1.6.9) - Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1361210/view/499439875179679150</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/824ddc640957bcbcbcf3714772bf42d9ef0d3ce4.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hey Everyone,</div><br/>We’ve got another quick one this week to smooth out a few bugs. The hotfix is currently rolling out across our platforms and it’ll be available today.<ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a crash which could happen when moving the analog stick on controller during certain transitions in the Havoc menu.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the coloration of a few cosmetic items had accidentally been swapped from a forest/military green to teal   <br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where the description of the Ogryn “Payback Time” Talent appeared as undefined text.</li></ul><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/38365286/a65c70af1027202631df9d22270d8a366b72f32d.png"/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 1.3.2.13 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/502817574909644214</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains! <br/><br/>After the launch of the game on Xbox Game Pass, some game settings could function incorrectly. We are publishing a minor hotfix 1.3.2.13 to address that issue.<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
