<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>December Community Update</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2183900/view/500560232665055477</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<div class="bb_h1">Dear Space Marines,</div><br/>The year is coming to an end, and we first and foremost want to assure you that 2025 will be just as epic as 2024. ⭐<br/><br/>You’ve been following our development very closely before and after the release of <i>Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine 2</i>, and we’ve loved collaborating with the players to improve the game.<br/>But before we dive into what’s coming to the game next year, let’s look back together, shall we?<br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WARPING BACK TO SEPTEMBER!</div>We launched <i>Space Marine 2</i> on September 9 and it was a success! We’ve been working on it for years and it has been a work of passion and dedication. Witnessing the warm welcome the players reserved for the game was the greatest reward and the best achievement to unlock after all these relentless years.<br/><br/>The enthusiasm motivated us to keep up the good work and make sure the game would remain up to the players’ expectations. Then, we released 2 big updates and several hotfixes.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Update 4.0 - Termination 🩸</div>Introduced a new PvE mission with a dreadful foe to annihilate: the Hierophant Bio-Titan. This update also introduced the much-awaited photomode in Operations mode, which you loved! Balancing tweaks were made too…<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8ffc8ad485fe9383da0969a10dcf5260f6f622f5.png"/><br/>This update received mixed reviews because it increased the difficulty in an unpleasant way. Our mistake! We closely listened to your feedback and released Patch 4.1 a few days later to revert the unwanted effects.<br/>Paying attention to your feedback has been incredibly helpful to us, and it's something we want to continue doing next year.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Update 5.0 - Obelisk 🪽</div>We knew the Warhammer 40k fans were waiting for this one, for it introduced the Dark Angels Cosmetic pack, with the Dark Angels Champion, new weapons skins and more. <br/><br/>This update brought a new PvE map, and also introduced a new enemy: the Tzaangor Enlightened. Along with that, a few feature additions such as the new lens colors (which you’ve also been waiting for) and the Neo-Volkite pistol, available in PvP, were also implemented.<br/>Finally, Space Marine 2 has been upgraded to 4K/60 FPS for PS5 Pro and now supports DLSS3 and FSR3.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">More and more Space Marines joining the ranks</div>In the span of 3 months, <i>Space Marine 2</i> reached the remarkable milestone of 5 million players, to our great delight. We want to sincerely thank all 5 million of you for this. 🥹🎉<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/f7338178ead67bcd2ed86a236881ada717efb85b.jpg"/><br/><div class="bb_h3">Fan creations 📷</div>Thousands of screenshots from the game were shared on social media (including some striking Titus selfies)<br/>Keep it coming, we love to see it! 📷<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2baaf315acfaa5d66cbac17d79deea9529f4c07b.png"/><br/><div class="bb_table"><div class="bb_table_tr"><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/da2f78e94b293059aa20b7578400d143a5c0451e.jpg"/></div><div class="bb_table_td"><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e328028882602a780c59f43f70d12185922736e6.jpg"/></div></div></div><div class="bb_h1">COMMUNITY EVENTS</div>There will continue to be in-game events in 2025. Currently, the ongoing Decimation Event invites you to win 10 times in Operations in order to unlock an exclusive skin: the Mark XI Hell’s Teeth Pattern Chainsword. You don’t want to skip this one, Space Marine, so gear up and head back to the battlefield already! ⚔️<br/><br/>The event starts on December 27 and ends on January 20<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8e374bcd4fd45a25f15bc4bc19b617f9e2b36c6f.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WHAT’S NEXT FOR 2025?</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">Fresh content for PVP</div>PVP Players - We have heard you, and we know you feel left out. We will have your back in 2025 with brand new and exciting content for the PvP. First thing we can tease you with is the new PvP map (it will be set in a closed environment with many narrow passages pushing you to engage more in Closed Quartered Battles).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/8bba97254756cf8618f983fe15a3c9bae1237453.png"/><br/><br/>Custom PvP lobbies will also be implemented in Patch 7.0: You will be able to play with modifiers and change the amount of players, up to 6v6 / You can change the timer limit for each match, the maximum limit score / you can have more than two players for each class (and have 6 snipers on your team if you want, even if it’s a questionable strategy!)<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">New PvE content</div>The hotly anticipated Horde Mode will arrive later in 2025. We’ll keep you updated once we get closer to it!<br/>Prestige Rank will be introduced during season 3, allowing you to upgrade your classes even further.<br/>On top of that, new Operations and new Enemies will come to expand the content of <i>Space Marine 2</i>. To spice things up, a new difficulty level with new rewards will also be added.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">And our next Champion will be… 🥁 </div>The Salamander Champion!! 🦎 And he will be a sniper, available in PvE and PvP. Let’s explain our choice a bit:<br/><ol><li> His cape is very cool (super important).<br/></li><li> An obvious choice for the Sniper Champion would have been to be a Raven Guard, but we have different plans for them.<br/></li><li> Everyone loves Salamanders, us included, and we really wanted to give them a Champion. Heavy and Tactical would have been good candidates, but Heavy was already taken, and we have a different idea for Tactical.</li></ol>Here’s a sneak peek: look at those flames. <br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/a62bc19a1e9e19f11e45fce9f8375b8a7e275d7f.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Customisation</div>We’ll keep adding customisation elements (such as the Mark VI Corvus 😉) throughout the year to represent more iconic Chapters of the Warhammer 40k universe.<br/>Battle Barge Expansion<br/><br/>The Datavault will make its entry on the Battle Barge next year. It will consist of a new area with unlockable information on most elements enemies from the game. Unlock them with a special currency earned through in-game achievements. We’ll get back to you quickly in the beginning of 2025.<br/><br/>Take a first look at it 📚<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/c13c735ecee476e9e720dfdfe05672063e031e89.png"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h1">WE’LL SEE YOU SOON, SPACE MARINES</div>2025 is near, whether or not you’re celebrating Christmas, we wish you a good end of 2024. Remember celebrating is cool, but protecting the Imperium is better. Don’t lose focus!<br/>Happy new year gamers. 🥂🎆🎊<br/><br/>Cheers,<br/><i>Focus &amp; Saber</i><br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/e4ba024509c3934efbed4a0ff5e8207f507f25d0.jpg"/><br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">For the Emperor</div><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/43315296/2e279301e7245e4d4f4991c30208b3664bf66546.gif"/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1.3.1.6 is live!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/2186680/view/523078230806103513</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
Lord Captains, update 1.3.1.6 is live!<br/><br/>It fixes an annoying loading bar bug that used to occur after Eurac-V for Mac, and addresses a number of issues with quests, abilities, items and more.<br/><br/>Please be aware of the plot spoilers below!<br/><br/>Note that https://steamcommunity.com/app/2186680/discussions/0/4027970580228219058/ always contains up-to-date information on known issues and the roadmap of upcoming patches.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h2">Patch Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">System and stability</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Loading bar will no longer get stuck after completing Eurac V on MacOS;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Narrative</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A Lucrative Opportunity quest will now correctly fail upon entering <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Commorragh</span></span>;<br/></li><li> Fixed a problem with the Request and Response quest in Act 1, which could cause the quest to be locked;<br/></li><li> Sometimes during the Echo of the Past quest, Idira didn't regain her consciousness, causing the quest to be locked - fixed;<br/></li><li> The quest "Compiler out of Order" couldn't be completed if you interacted with the problem nodes before speaking with the Astropath - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Mechanics</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bounty Hunter's Wild Hunt ability (and its Desperate Measures version) will now have a separate ability for the second weapon (similar to Operative's Dismantling Attack);<br/></li><li> Bounty Hunter's Withdraw talent no longer provides infinite dodge against all types of attacks;<br/></li><li> Daemons summoned by Perils of the Warp will no longer spawn in inaccessible areas, preventing random space encounters from ending;<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Kibellah could participate in combat with Chtonos from her cage in the <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Haemonculus Lab</span></span>;<br/></li><li> Fixed some malfunctioning traps across the game that didn't deal damage even when triggered;<br/></li><li> Some Heroic Acts didn't work if certain types of Heroic Acts or Desperate Measures were used before them - fixed;<br/></li><li> <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Uralon</span></span> in some cases could enter an infinite cycle of attacks - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Items</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Many items had descriptions for damage over time effects missing or displaying incorrect numbers - fixed;<br/></li><li> A couple of items from the Void Shadows DLC were incorrectly awarded to the players without the DLC in colony projects - fixed;<br/></li><li> Ancient Force Sword damage reduction was applying to all damage types instead of the specific types only - fixed;<br/></li><li> The Bead of Concentration worked incorrectly. The additional AP was not properly lost or gained in some situations - fixed;<br/></li><li> Bonuses from Prey Scanner are now correctly calculated when used by Bounty Hunters;<br/></li><li> Damage bonus of The Distortion and Awakened Nightmare is now correctly only applied to area attacks;<br/></li><li> Dark Providence and Incinerator no longer require purchasing the DLC to become available from vendors;<br/></li><li> Familial Power Armour can now be received from the "Call to Arms" level 4 project at Dargonus;<br/></li><li> Renunciation of Weakness now correctly triggers only on critical hits;<br/></li><li> Veilrender's damage bonus now correctly applies only to the attacks made with the weapon;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Locations</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed some camera issues at <span class="bb_spoiler"><span>Commorragh Arena</span></span>;<br/></li><li> It was sometimes possible to get stuck without the button to leave the location at Vheabos-6 - fixed;<br/></li><li> It's no longer possible to enter a version of the Temple of the Bloodspun Web fully devoid of people, making it impossible to complete the quests inside. If you experienced this before the update, leave the location and come back to refresh its state;<br/></li><li> The cutscene at the Wasteland Wayfarer no longer sometimes plays twice;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Visual</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> After breaking up with Cassia, the visual effects of her mood remained on the screen - while somewhat expected from a sad and angry Navigator, it was a bug and was fixed;<br/></li><li> Fixed minor texture issues with the Leman Russ tanks;<br/></li><li> Khorne Bloodletters sometimes had missing textures - fixed;<br/></li><li> The veil now restores correctly after the battle in the Astropathic Chapel;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">UI</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Torpedo overtips now have less overlap with the torpedoes themselves;<br/></li><li> Added images to the weapon equipping tutorial;<br/></li><li> Continue Game button in the main menu didn't work for Grim Darkness saves - fixed;<br/></li><li> Weapon sets will now switch correctly when on the Voidship Bridge;<br/></li><li> When playing with a controller or on console, scrolling between torpedoes and fighters caused their cooldown to refresh - fixed, no more endless torpedoes;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Audio</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Made flute sound louder at the Freight Line;<br/></li><li> One of the Idira's lines during her recruitment in the prologue that was voiced before 1.3, stopped playing after the 1.3 patch - fixed;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Space</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Minor UI and rewards fixes for some colony events;<br/></li><li> Torpedoes now have mini-portraits in the initiative tracker;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Co-op</div><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A player can no longer edit the other player's ability bar during their turn in co-op, which could cause desyncs;</li></ul><br/><div class="bb_h3">Localization</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed inconsistent Russian translation of force and power weapons - each type now correctly uses its own separate term;<br/></li><li> Fixed incorrect formatting for Turkish localization;<br/></li><li> Fixed some untranslated lines for Turkish localization;<br/></li><li> Message of the Day has received a Turkish translation;<br/></li><li> Russian translation of Scorpion Chainsword was corrected;<br/></li><li> Immolate The Soul had incorrect description in Chinese - fixed;</li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 11:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/657059620262511765</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/7ef363463dbf3bc7660f69f8dccc06f28865d253.png"/><br/><br/>Happy holidays from all of us in the Total War team! May 2025 bring many Decisive Victories! 💪<br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total War - Thank you for your support in 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497182532936139135</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/eb62cc6d8f1911b150370f903751419f2c81efec.png"/><br/><br/>Hey folks,<br/><br/>Before we say our goodbyes to 2024, we just want to say one more thing - <b>Thank You</b> ❤️<br/> <br/>Here's a letter from the VP of Total War, and a look at your year across our games.<br/><br/><div class="bb_h3">🎄 Read the blog here 🎄</div><br/><br/>— The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotfix 6.0.3 available as opt-in Beta</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/1142710/view/497182532936138992</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
<style>
        [data-focus-scheme="dark"] {
            color-scheme: none;
        }
    </style>
<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/4467df634c9fb3482140b6d254f0bb5925a2a84f.png"/><br/><br/>Hey everyone,<br/><br/>We’ve been continuing to listen to your feedback since the release of Update 6.0 and its subsequent hotfixes, and have been working on a number of adjustments for Skulltaker to address some of your concerns.<br/><br/>Our aim is to release these as part of our first hotfix in the new year, currently scheduled for late January, but we wanted to give you the chance to get an early look at some of these changes so have added a new opt-in Beta for Steam users, allowing you to try them out over the Holidays along with some other fixes and adjustments that have already made it in.<br/><br/>Once we’re back in the new year we’ll be cracking on with our work on this hotfix, getting some more fixes added in and completing our testing to ensure everything is working as intended.<br/><br/>For now, let’s take a look at what’s included in this Beta release.<br/><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h1">Hotfix 6.0.3 BETA Release Notes</div><br/><div class="bb_h2">SKULLTAKER UPDATES AND FIXES</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Adjusted Blood Hosts and Disciple forces so they no longer benefit from the Daemonic Reforging chance.<br/></li><li> Adjusted the effects of the Cloak of Skulls so that they now only apply when Skulltaker himself defeats a Lord.<br/></li><li> When playing as Skulltaker, the Legendary Lord 2x bonus for Champion’s Essence will now only be applied once. After defeating a Champion in battle, the bonus will no longer stack.<br/></li><li> Blood Hosts now increase the cost of the ‘Blood for the Blood God’ occupation option while they are on the map. This means that the more active Blood Hosts there are, the more costly it becomes to create new Blood Hosts. This change addresses the over-reliance of Khorne factions on excessive Blood Host forces.<br/></li><li> Reduced the XP gain bonus from the Cloak of Skulls on the ‘Dubois the Prescient’ skull, from 25/50 to 20/40.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Bloodspeakers lacked mounts when playing as Valkia.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Heralds of Khorne and Bloodreapers on Blood Throne mounts were missing Siege Attacker.<br/></li><li> Fixed the 2D porthole for The Slaughtergard (Chosen of Khorne - Halberds) using the wrong image.<br/></li><li> Fixed a text inconsistency in the description of the Daemons Reforged effect for the Skulltakers faction.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">PERFORMANCE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resolved a rare crash that could occur during VFX rendering.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when loading saved Savage Orc Great Shaman lords.<br/></li><li> Fixed a potential crash when loading a battle in certain cases.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when loading the Black Orc Big Boss character.<br/></li><li> Fixed a crash that occurred when teleporting to the Great Drill of Hashut quest battle.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">CAMPAIGN</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">GENERAL/GAMEPLAY</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Erd Mentality Rebalance:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Melee Defence: 40 &gt; 20<br/></li><li> Ward Save: 40 &gt; 20<br/></li><li> Number of Squig Herds in range for maximum value: 10 &gt; 5</li></ul></li><li> Fixed an issue where Da Acid Burpa (Colossal Squig RoR) was not counting towards the unit requirements for the ‘Splode Da Big One Tactik’ in Da Plan.<br/></li><li> Ogre Camps now take only 3 turns to be redeployed, instead of 5.<br/></li><li> Removed Destroy ‘Kraka Drak’ from Throgg and Astragoth’s victory conditions and replaced it with Malakai’s faction<br/></li><li> Nasty Skulkers, Rogue Idol, River Trolls, and Snotling Pump Wagon (base unit) have been added to Gorbad - Omens of Destruction DLC for use in his Da Plan feature.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">TECHNOLOGY TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The Hammer of Gork’s Blinded contact effect is no longer replaced by Dazed from the Orcs &amp; Goblins’ Avalanche Smash technology.<br/></li><li> Eshin Maneater’s Weeping Blade effect is no longer replaced by Armour Sundering from the Ogres’ Betta Plunda technology.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">SKILL TREE</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Snagla's ‘Beneath the Gloomy Canopy’ skill would lose its Stalk effect when upgraded.<br/></li><li> Removed the ‘Immune to Contact Effects’ from the Slaughtermaster's Poisonmaster skill, as they possess that attribute innately.<br/></li><li> Removed the Thundertusk and Stonehorn from the Hunter skill effects that provided Vanguard, Frenzy, and Stalk Hunter skills.<br/></li><li> Fixed the missing Idol of Gork Scrap upgrade for Savage Orc units.<br/></li><li> Fixed the Divinatory Authority skill incorrectly reducing cooldowns for Cold-Blooded instead of Focus Instincts.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Markus Wulfhart’s Imperial Regiments of Greatswords had a different tier to regular Greatswords.</li></ul><div class="bb_h3">UI/UX</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed a UI issue with the Ogre’s army ability ‘Meat Feast’, which incorrectly stated it affected multiple units when it only affects a single unit.</li></ul><div class="bb_h2">BATTLE</div><br/><div class="bb_h3">UNITS</div><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fixed an issue where Colossal Squigs were missing Siege Attacker.<br/></li><li> Added missing MP unit caps to the following: Colossal Squig, Da Acif Burpa, Snagla Deff Throwa, Piggyback Knights, Slaughterbrute, Eshin Maneater, Skullcannon, Hellforged Bellowers, and Arachnarok Flinger.<br/></li><li> Fixed an issue where Khorngors were still available for Warriors of Chaos when unit caps were active.<br/></li><li> Fixed the abilities ‘Bathed in Blood’ and ‘Blinding Radiance’ being incorrectly labelled as active abilities.</li></ul><br/><hr/><br/><div class="bb_h1">How to download the Beta branch</div><br/>If you would like to opt-in to this Beta branch and try these changes today, here's how you can do it:<br/><ol><li> Open your Steam client and go to your Library.<br/></li><li> Right-click on Total War: WARHAMMER III and select 'Properties'.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/98c24b13abbd656733e2aa2e0dfbae3479d675f8.png"/><br/></li><li> Navigate to the 'Betas' tab.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/39760201/29ca007f553c5434793d87997a06d529703fcf7c.png"/><br/></li><li> In the drop-down menu, select the option ‘<b>beta_hotfix_603 – BETA Hotfix 6.0.3</b>'.<br/></li><li> Steam will then download the necessary files and begin the patching process to install the Hotfix.</li></ol>The download is relatively small, but Steam will need to patch around 25GB of game data in order to install the Hotfix. This can take some time depending on your hard drive speeds.<br/><br/>The full release of Hotfix 6.0.3 is currently aiming for this Friday, and when this happens your game will automatically switch to the main release.<br/><br/><b>Please note:</b> If you update to 6.0.3 early, you will only be able to play multiplayer with other players who are also opted in to the 6.0.3 Beta until the update rolls out to all players. You can switch back to 6.0.2 at any time by selecting ‘None’ in the Betas dropdown menu.<br/><br/><hr/><br/>​Thanks to everyone who’s shared their feedback with us since the launch of Omens of Destruction and Update 6.0. This will be our last game update before we power down for a couple of weeks to rest, recuperate and eat our body weight in mince pies. We’ll be back in 2025, ready and raring to kick back into gear.<br/><br/>Happy Holidays!<br/><br/>—The <i>Total War</i> Team<br/><br/><br/><div class="bb_code">For the latest news and announcements, don't forget to visit our official social channels.

Steam X Facebook Instagram Discord [url=https://bsky.app/profile/totalwar.bsky.social 
 style=button]Bluesky[/url]</div>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
